1
00:00:08,295 --> 00:00:10,396
{\an8}圣城家园SCG字幕组

2
00:00:14,295 --> 00:00:16,096
{\an8}http://hd.cnscg.com/

3
00:00:18,595 --> 00:00:20,596
{\an8}仅供翻译交流使用

4
00:00:23,395 --> 00:00:25,196
{\an8}禁止用于商业用途

5
00:00:27,495 --> 00:00:29,596
{\an8}协调: 影子

6
00:00:29,945 --> 00:00:31,796
{\an8}翻译: 酱油影

7
00:00:32,095 --> 00:00:34,396
{\an8}翻译: 飘飘行天下

8
00:00:34,945 --> 00:00:36,946
{\an8}翻译: 肉肉君

9
00:00:38,695 --> 00:00:40,846
{\an8}翻译: 小黄不小黄

10
00:00:43,395 --> 00:00:45,096
{\an8}翻译: 夏至未寒

11
00:00:47,495 --> 00:00:49,596
{\an8}翻译: yjk8654

12
00:00:56,295 --> 00:00:58,296
{\an8}翻译: 鸟生鱼汤

13
00:01:06,895 --> 00:01:08,496
{\an8}校对: 假探UU

14
00:00:05,144 --> 00:00:07,144
# 输了战争 #
# The war was lost #

15
00:00:07,180 --> 00:00:09,430
# 签了条约 #
# The treaty signed #

16
00:00:09,465 --> 00:00:11,599
# 犯了禁忌 #
# I was not caught #

17
00:00:11,634 --> 00:00:13,884
# 却未被抓 #
# I crossed the line #

18
00:00:13,886 --> 00:00:15,886
# 纵然前赴后继 #
# I was not caught #

19
00:00:15,938 --> 00:00:18,222
# 依旧未果 #
# Though many tried #

20
00:00:18,224 --> 00:00:20,558
# 我巧妙伪装 #
# I live among you #

21
00:00:20,610 --> 00:00:22,726
# 混迹其中 #
# Well disguised #

22
00:00:22,728 --> 00:00:25,029
# 我得放弃 #
# I had to leave #

23
00:00:25,064 --> 00:00:27,148
# 旧的生活 #
# My life behind #

24
00:00:27,200 --> 00:00:29,450
# 你找不到 #
# I dug some graves #

25
00:00:29,485 --> 00:00:31,569
# 我挖的墓穴 #
# You'll never find #

26
00:00:31,621 --> 00:00:33,788
# 故事流传 #
# The story's told #

27
00:00:33,823 --> 00:00:36,073
# 真假掺半 #
# With facts and lies #

28
00:00:36,125 --> 00:00:38,325
# 我有名字 #
# I have a name #

29
00:00:38,377 --> 00:00:40,544
# 但无所谓 #
# But never mind #

30
00:00:40,580 --> 00:00:42,830
# 无所谓 #
# Never mind #

31
00:00:42,882 --> 00:00:44,632
# 无所谓 #
# Never mind #

32
00:00:44,667 --> 00:00:48,836
# 我得放弃 旧的生活 #
# I had to leave my life behind #

33
00:00:48,888 --> 00:00:51,138
# 故事流传 #
# The story's told #

34
00:00:51,174 --> 00:00:53,674
# 真假掺半 #
# With facts and lies #

35
00:00:53,726 --> 00:00:58,095
# 世界是你的 所以无所谓 #
# You own the world, so never mind #

36
00:00:58,097 --> 00:01:01,816
# 这曾是你心 满心肮脏 #
# This was your heart, this swarm of flies #

37
00:01:01,851 --> 00:01:07,071
# 这曾是你口 满嘴谎言 #
# This was once your mouth, this bowl of lies #

38
00:01:07,106 --> 00:01:11,525
# 恶人满意而归 我不意外 #
# You serve them well, I'm not surprised #

39
00:01:11,577 --> 00:01:15,663
# 你本就与恶同根 与恶同源 #
# You're of their kin, you're of their kind #

40
00:01:15,698 --> 00:01:18,249
# 输了战争 #
# The war was lost #

41
00:01:18,284 --> 00:01:20,701
# 签了条约 #
# The treaty signed #

42
00:01:20,753 --> 00:01:22,453
# 犯了禁忌 #
# I was not caught #

43
00:01:22,505 --> 00:01:24,872
# 却未被抓 #
# I crossed the line #

44
00:01:24,924 --> 00:01:27,124
# 纵然前赴后继 #
# I was not caught #

45
00:01:27,126 --> 00:01:29,293
# 依旧未果 #
# Though many tried #

46
00:01:29,345 --> 00:01:31,712
# 我巧妙伪装 #
# I live among you #

47
00:01:31,764 --> 00:01:34,048
# 混迹其中 #
# Well disguised #

48
00:01:25,798 --> 00:01:28,683
{\an8}真探 第二季第3集

49
00:01:45,611 --> 00:01:47,811
# 有人说 #
# Some say love #

50
00:01:49,982 --> 00:01:52,116
# 爱如河流 #
# It is a river #

51
00:01:54,353 --> 00:01:58,322
# 会淹没柔嫩的芦苇 #
# And that it drowns the tender reed #

52
00:02:01,210 --> 00:02:03,816
# 有人说 #
# And some say love #

53
00:02:05,251 --> 00:02:07,794
# 爱如刀刃 #
# It's like a razor #

54
00:02:09,752 --> 00:02:14,338
# 会让灵魂血流不止 #
# And that it leaves your soul to bleed #

55
00:02:14,340 --> 00:02:17,725
# 有人说 #
# Some say love #

56
00:02:17,760 --> 00:02:22,763
# 爱如饥饿 #
# It is a hunger #

57
00:02:22,815 --> 00:02:27,484
# 是种无休止境的渴求... #
# An endless, aching need... #

58
00:02:27,520 --> 00:02:30,070
你的手和你父亲一样
You got your father's hands.

59
00:02:30,106 --> 00:02:33,941
# 要我说 #
# I say love #

60
00:02:33,993 --> 00:02:37,328
# 爱如花朵... #
# It is a flower... #

61
00:02:37,363 --> 00:02:40,030
我爸爸让我很紧张
My father made me nervous.

62
00:02:40,032 --> 00:02:42,917
也许你原本就很紧张
Maybe you were already nervous.

63
00:02:44,203 --> 00:02:46,670
也许你缺乏勇气
Maybe you lacked grit.

64
00:02:49,926 --> 00:02:53,043
# 那是唯恐... #
# It's the heart... #

65
00:02:53,095 --> 00:02:55,045
我看到你...
I see you...

66
00:02:56,849 --> 00:02:59,883
在树林里奔跑
running through the trees.

67
00:02:59,885 --> 00:03:03,103
你很小
You're small.

68
00:03:03,139 --> 00:03:06,440
那些树就像是巨人
The trees are like giants.

69
00:03:07,643 --> 00:03:10,611
有人在追你
Men are chasing you.

70
00:03:10,646 --> 00:03:12,947
我就在这里
I'm right here.

71
00:03:12,982 --> 00:03:16,033
你跑出树林
You step out of the trees.

72
00:03:16,068 --> 00:03:19,069
但没那么快
You ain't that fast.

73
00:03:19,071 --> 00:03:21,038
儿子...
Oh, son...

74
00:03:22,992 --> 00:03:24,541
他们杀了你
they kill you.

75
00:03:26,912 --> 00:03:28,545
他们把你打成了筛子
They shoot you to pieces.

76
00:03:28,581 --> 00:03:35,836
# 似乎无法给予 #
# Who cannot seem to give #

77
00:03:35,888 --> 00:03:38,339
# 而灵魂... #
# And the soul... #

78
00:03:38,391 --> 00:03:41,392
这是哪?
Where is this?

79
00:03:41,427 --> 00:03:44,395
我不知道
I don't know.

80
00:03:46,766 --> 00:03:48,849
是你先到这里的
You were here first.

81
00:03:54,940 --> 00:03:58,075
# 当此夜 #
# When the night #

82
00:03:58,110 --> 00:04:02,579
# 太过寂寞 #
# Has been too lonely #

83
00:04:02,615 --> 00:04:05,616
# 而路途 #
# And the road #

84
00:04:05,618 --> 00:04:09,787
# 太过漫长#
# Has been too long #

85
00:04:09,789 --> 00:04:13,173
# 你觉得 #
# And you think #

86
00:04:13,209 --> 00:04:17,344
# 爱只光顾 #
# That love is only #

87
00:04:17,380 --> 00:04:20,881
# 幸运之人 #
# For the lucky #

88
00:04:20,933 --> 00:04:24,601
# 坚强之人 #
# And the strong #

89
00:04:24,637 --> 00:04:28,439
# 要谨记 #
# Just remember #

90
00:04:28,474 --> 00:04:32,276
# 在冬季 #
# In the winter #

91
00:04:32,311 --> 00:04:35,612
# 深藏于 #
# Far beneath #

92
00:04:35,648 --> 00:04:39,900
# 冰雪之下 #
# The bitter snow #

93
00:04:39,952 --> 00:04:43,203
# 种子萌芽 #
# Lies the seed #

94
00:04:43,239 --> 00:04:47,658
# 有了太阳的呵护 #
# That with the sun's love #

95
00:04:47,660 --> 00:04:50,911
# 在春季 #
# In the spring #

96
00:04:50,963 --> 00:04:54,665
# 玫瑰将盛放 #
# Becomes the rose #

97
00:05:01,924 --> 00:05:04,925
"怪兽麦克的晨间串烧"节目继续
"Monstrous Mike's Morning Mash-Up" moves on

98
00:05:04,977 --> 00:05:09,346
以泽方的歌曲 开始一天的生活
with a little Zevon to get you all the way up.

99
00:05:04,977 --> 00:05:09,346
{\an8}沃伦·泽方 美国摇滚歌手

100
00:05:14,820 --> 00:05:17,104
我尿裤子了
Pissed myself.

101
00:05:26,899 --> 00:05:29,733
怎么回事?
What the fuck, man?

102
00:05:29,735 --> 00:05:32,369
我是这次调查的负责警探
I'm commanding officer of this detail.

103
00:05:32,404 --> 00:05:34,288
你打电话告诉我有线索
You call me you got something.

104
00:05:34,323 --> 00:05:37,240
我中枪了 这就是线索
Well, I got shot. That's something.

105
00:05:37,293 --> 00:05:40,077
我还找到了谋杀现场 也是线索
I found our murder scene. That's something else.

106
00:05:40,079 --> 00:05:42,879
你不能不带搭档... 也就是我 擅自进犯罪现场调查
You don't enter a scene without your partner... me.

107
00:05:42,915 --> 00:05:44,414
我当时不知道这是犯罪现场
I didn't know it was a scene.

108
00:05:44,466 --> 00:05:48,218
我进去 接着就有人用散弹猎枪朝我开了一枪
I walk in, next thing somebody shotgunned me.

109
00:05:48,253 --> 00:05:49,886
- 两枪  - 那你怎么还...
- Twice.  - Then how are you still...

110
00:05:49,922 --> 00:05:52,422
只是橡皮子弹 冲击比较严重
Rubber buckshot. It's just impact.

111
00:05:52,424 --> 00:05:54,091
镇压暴乱子弹
Riot shells.

112
00:05:54,143 --> 00:05:57,761
你懂的... 就警察用的那种
You know, like... like cops use.

113
00:06:01,433 --> 00:06:02,599
你没事吧?
You all right?

114
00:06:02,651 --> 00:06:04,735
几根肋骨骨裂了
Couple of cracked ribs.

115
00:06:04,770 --> 00:06:07,604
胸骨中了一弹 所以我心脏疼
Took one in the sternum, so my heart aches.

116
00:06:07,606 --> 00:06:09,690
你怎么找到这地方的?
And how did you find this place?

117
00:06:09,742 --> 00:06:12,075
一个妓女线人提供的线索
Prost tip through a CI.

118
00:06:12,111 --> 00:06:14,244
说Caspere带她来过这里一次
Said Caspere took her here once.

119
00:06:15,781 --> 00:06:19,249
好吧 让医生帮你检查一下
All right. Well, get cleared by a doctor.

120
00:06:19,284 --> 00:06:21,284
然后看能不能带那妓女来问话
See if you can bring in the hooker.

121
00:06:21,286 --> 00:06:22,502
该死 怎么一股尿味
Fuck, it smells like piss.

122
00:06:22,538 --> 00:06:25,005
Burris已经在里面了
Burris is already inside.

123
00:06:26,925 --> 00:06:30,043
我是不是可以去休假一天了 老大?
So I'll go ahead and take the day, Xena?

124
00:06:36,101 --> 00:06:39,519
所有线索都要报告给Vinci警局谋杀案特别小组
Everything goes through Vinci PD Special Homicide Task Force.

125
00:06:39,555 --> 00:06:41,555
你来我负责的犯罪现场干什么 副队?
What are you doing with my scene, Lieutenant?

126
00:06:41,607 --> 00:06:44,358
保护现场
Securing it.

127
00:06:44,393 --> 00:06:48,228
我的手下中枪了 我当然要到现场来
One of my men gets shot, you better believe I'm on site.

128
00:06:55,320 --> 00:06:56,620
交给你了
It's all yours.

129
00:07:06,582 --> 00:07:09,082
隔音板
Soundproofing.

130
00:07:09,134 --> 00:07:12,335
天啊
Christ.

131
00:07:43,702 --> 00:07:46,536
根本没用
It ain't working.

132
00:07:46,588 --> 00:07:50,257
听着 这...
Look, this...

133
00:07:50,292 --> 00:07:52,459
该死
God damn it.

134
00:07:55,931 --> 00:07:58,381
是因为地方不好吗?
Is it the place?

135
00:07:58,383 --> 00:08:01,384
我这辈子都没不举过 偏偏这时候
This never happened to me in my fucking life.

136
00:08:06,442 --> 00:08:10,277
也许我们应该在附近开个房
Maybe we could get a room nearby.

137
00:08:10,312 --> 00:08:11,978
慢慢来
Take our time.

138
00:08:12,030 --> 00:08:14,698
我可没有时间
I ain't got the time.

139
00:08:14,733 --> 00:08:17,234
这很重要 Frank
This is important, Frank.

140
00:08:17,236 --> 00:08:20,203
废话 你以为我不知道吗?
No shit. You don't think I know that?

141
00:08:20,239 --> 00:08:23,707
我的人生都充满了事关生死的烦恼
There is no part of my life not overwrought with live-or-die importance.

142
00:08:23,742 --> 00:08:25,459
我去个厕所 都有人拿枪指着我的头
I take a shit, there's a gun to my head

143
00:08:25,494 --> 00:08:27,994
说"好好拉 别搞砸了"
saying, "Make it a good one. Don't fuck up."

144
00:08:28,046 --> 00:08:30,997
亲爱的 放轻松
Baby, just relax.

145
00:08:31,049 --> 00:08:33,083
整个就不正常
This whole thing is unnatural.

146
00:08:33,135 --> 00:08:35,802
一点都不对
Don't feel right.

147
00:08:35,838 --> 00:08:37,838
我们谈过的
We talked about this.

148
00:08:37,890 --> 00:08:39,306
很多次
A lot.

149
00:08:39,341 --> 00:08:40,841
这不正常
It's unnatural.

150
00:08:40,893 --> 00:08:43,009
他们说了我没问题
They already said I'm fine.

151
00:08:44,813 --> 00:08:45,929
你什么意思?
What does that mean?

152
00:08:45,981 --> 00:08:47,931
就这个意思
What I said.

153
00:08:47,983 --> 00:08:50,817
这个 还有这个
This. This.

154
00:08:50,853 --> 00:08:53,854
有十足的活力 医生这么说的
Phenomenal motility, the doc said.

155
00:08:55,607 --> 00:08:58,358
还真是不好意思啊
God forgive me for misreading what subtle clues

156
00:08:58,410 --> 00:09:00,527
我没能读懂你屌语的潜台词
you embed for me in your limp dick,

157
00:09:00,579 --> 00:09:04,364
它就跟你的情绪一样 变得比天还快
which is as wishy-washy as your fucking mood.

158
00:09:04,416 --> 00:09:07,167
就算是比较困难又怎样?
So what if it's hard for us?

159
00:09:07,202 --> 00:09:09,452
好像我就是给你生孩子的一样
Like I'm your fucking incubator.

160
00:09:11,957 --> 00:09:14,591
自己舔去吧
Suck your own dick.

161
00:09:24,469 --> 00:09:27,604
这平房是通过Catalast集团租的商务用房
Bungalow was a business lease through the Catalast Group.

162
00:09:27,639 --> 00:09:29,439
他的车也是通过那租的
Same place leased his car.

163
00:09:29,474 --> 00:09:31,308
水电费是Porpoise有限公司缴的
Utilities paid by Porpoise LLC,

164
00:09:31,360 --> 00:09:33,026
那是Caspere的公司
which was Caspere's company.

165
00:09:33,061 --> 00:09:35,612
他在这还装了固定电话
And he had a landline here, too.

166
00:09:35,647 --> 00:09:38,064
我打印了通话详单
Printed out the phone record.

167
00:09:39,067 --> 00:09:40,650
要是今天没收获
If we don't get anything today,

168
00:09:40,652 --> 00:09:42,652
我想让你去调查妓女
I want you on working girls.

169
00:09:42,704 --> 00:09:45,405
别浪费了你的好皮囊
Put those looks to use.

170
00:09:47,209 --> 00:09:48,825
没问题
Sure.

171
00:09:50,329 --> 00:09:54,130
本来不该提这个的 不过你是个成年人
So I could not mention it, but you're an adult.

172
00:09:56,051 --> 00:09:57,217
所以呢
All right.

173
00:09:57,252 --> 00:10:00,170
所以 那个女演员...
All right. That actress...

174
00:10:00,172 --> 00:10:03,473
要是你是想问我是不是真的做了她说的事情
If you're asking me if I did what she said,

175
00:10:03,508 --> 00:10:05,842
那我他妈立马下车
then I'm gonna get out of the fucking car.

176
00:10:07,229 --> 00:10:10,013
呃 我是想问你觉得报纸的曝光
Well, I was gonna ask if you thought the exposure

177
00:10:10,065 --> 00:10:12,482
会不会影响你做实地工作
would interfere with doing fieldwork.

178
00:10:19,524 --> 00:10:22,275
肯定不会
I seriously doubt it.

179
00:10:23,495 --> 00:10:26,663
这件事结束后你应该去控告她
You should sue her when it's over.

180
00:10:26,698 --> 00:10:28,248
那妞儿磕了药
Chick's loaded.

181
00:10:33,372 --> 00:10:35,872
那他妈是个电子烟吗?
Is that a fucking e-cigarette?

182
00:10:59,731 --> 00:11:02,065
有什么事不能在电话上说?
You can't talk on the phone?

183
00:11:02,067 --> 00:11:04,401
我尽量不用电话
I'm trying to stay off the phone.

184
00:11:04,403 --> 00:11:07,454
怎么了? 有什么进展?
What? What do you got?

185
00:11:07,489 --> 00:11:10,907
还有谁知道那个据点?
Who else knew about that spot?

186
00:11:10,959 --> 00:11:12,575
Caspere的房子?
Caspere's place?

187
00:11:15,130 --> 00:11:17,747
你把我套进去了 Frank
You walked me into something, Frank.

188
00:11:19,835 --> 00:11:21,468
你唠唠叨叨说什么呢?
What are you on about?

189
00:11:32,481 --> 00:11:35,649
操 你还真是走了狗屎运
That's some luck on you. Fuck.

190
00:11:35,684 --> 00:11:39,486
供出那地方的女孩在哪?
Where's the girl who gave up the place?

191
00:11:40,739 --> 00:11:42,022
Caspere招妓
Caspere bought whores.

192
00:11:42,074 --> 00:11:44,441
她是Danny Santos那的姑娘
She was one of Danny Santos.

193
00:11:44,443 --> 00:11:45,775
我手下可不拉皮条
My crew don't pimp.

194
00:11:45,861 --> 00:11:49,195
那也许她有个男朋友
Well, then maybe she had a boyfriend.

195
00:11:49,247 --> 00:11:50,864
你懂的 给Caspere设了个仙人跳
You know, set Caspere up for him.

196
00:11:50,916 --> 00:11:52,782
要么也许是Caspere肮脏事干太多
Or maybe Caspere was into so much dirt,

197
00:11:52,784 --> 00:11:54,918
都不知道暗箭从何而来
there's no telling which side the ax came from,

198
00:11:54,953 --> 00:11:57,537
我跟你说 还不是谋杀现场的时候
because let me tell you, there was some fucked-up psychology at work

199
00:11:57,589 --> 00:11:59,756
那地方就够诡异的了
in that place before it was a murder scene.

200
00:11:59,791 --> 00:12:04,878
现在 告诉我你到底和Caspere在搞什么
Now, are you gonna tell me what Caspere was doing with you

201
00:12:04,930 --> 00:12:07,130
还是非要等我下次再走进一间黑屋子
or do I wait to walk into another dark room,

202
00:12:07,215 --> 00:12:09,182
挨上真子弹了?
this time with real bullets?

203
00:12:09,217 --> 00:12:12,218
你语气不是很好啊
There's a certain stridency at work here.

204
00:12:12,270 --> 00:12:14,521
看在你挨枪子的份上我就放过你了
I'm gonna put it off to you getting blasted.

205
00:12:14,556 --> 00:12:18,274
哦 老实说我有点恼火了
Oh, frankly, I'm apoplectic.

206
00:12:18,310 --> 00:12:21,194
我才有点恼火了呢
I'm feeling a little apoplectic myself.

207
00:12:40,415 --> 00:12:42,165
你怎么改喝水了?
What's with the water?

208
00:12:42,217 --> 00:12:45,835
酒精会让人丧失敏锐 我想保持愤怒
Booze tends to take the edge off. I want to stay angry.

209
00:12:51,143 --> 00:12:54,511
Caspere在操作我的一大笔钱
Caspere had a lot of my money in play.

210
00:12:54,563 --> 00:12:56,262
投房地产
Real estate.

211
00:12:56,314 --> 00:12:58,565
铁路沿线的产业
Property adjacent to the rail line.

212
00:12:58,600 --> 00:13:01,818
你认识他多久了?
How long did you know him?

213
00:13:03,605 --> 00:13:06,022
过去几年里开始和他合作
Started working with him the last few years.

214
00:13:06,074 --> 00:13:08,525
我们搬出城的时候他就在这
He was here when we moved out of the city.

215
00:13:08,577 --> 00:13:11,494
他们把我击倒后
They stole a hidden camera

216
00:13:11,530 --> 00:13:13,830
偷走了一个隐藏摄像头
after they shot me.

217
00:13:13,865 --> 00:13:17,834
还有硬盘 搞不懂里面会有些什么
Hard drive. Boggles the mind what might be on it.

218
00:13:21,540 --> 00:13:26,092
我说过了 我这次忍忍你的态度
Like I said, I'm gonna put off the stridency.

219
00:13:27,629 --> 00:13:29,712
随你说吧 Frank
Well, you do that, Frank.

220
00:13:36,888 --> 00:13:39,722
Ray受伤了吗? 出什么事儿了?
Is Ray hurt? What happened?

221
00:13:41,026 --> 00:13:42,942
有人想杀他
Somebody murdered him.

222
00:13:47,899 --> 00:13:50,867
Vinci市市长住在贝沙湾?
The Mayor of Vinci lives in Bel-Air?

223
00:14:04,132 --> 00:14:06,299
你是Betty Chessani吗?
Are you Betty Chessani?

224
00:14:09,171 --> 00:14:11,471
我们是州警察 女士
We're state police, ma'am.

225
00:14:11,506 --> 00:14:13,506
我是Veronica Chessani
Veronica Chessani.

226
00:14:13,558 --> 00:14:16,309
Betty的继母
I'm Betty's stepmother.

227
00:14:16,344 --> 00:14:19,596
Chessani太太 你介意我问几个问题吗?
Mrs. Chessani, do you mind if we ask you a few questions?

228
00:14:19,598 --> 00:14:23,900
你了解Vinci市市政官Ben Caspere吗?
Did you know Ben Caspere, the Vinci City Manager?

229
00:14:23,935 --> 00:14:25,518
一点点
Only a little.

230
00:14:25,570 --> 00:14:28,238
我在晚宴上见过他一面
A dinner party I meet him once.

231
00:14:28,273 --> 00:14:29,823
你们昨晚办宴会了?
You guys have a party last night?

232
00:14:29,908 --> 00:14:31,608
没
No.

233
00:14:39,784 --> 00:14:42,535
这是治我眼睛的药
Is medicine for my eyes.

234
00:14:47,042 --> 00:14:48,958
你好呀
Hello.

235
00:14:53,882 --> 00:14:57,050
你见过Caspere先生和你丈夫
Do you remember Mr. Caspere and your husband

236
00:14:57,102 --> 00:14:58,718
在深夜里谈话吗?
ever talking late at night?

237
00:14:58,770 --> 00:15:01,437
没 没见过
No, I don't think.

238
00:15:01,473 --> 00:15:03,690
你们跟Austin谈过了?
Have you talked to Austin?

239
00:15:03,725 --> 00:15:05,942
他放你们进来?
He say okay for you coming here?

240
00:15:05,977 --> 00:15:07,977
- 当然  - 哦
- Sure.  - Oh.

241
00:15:08,029 --> 00:15:09,479
我们来调查是因为Caspere先生
We're checking because Mr. Caspere

242
00:15:09,481 --> 00:15:12,198
在城里有座公寓
kept an apartment in the city

243
00:15:12,284 --> 00:15:14,651
那的电话账单显示有许多电话
and his phone records show a lot of phone calls

244
00:15:14,703 --> 00:15:16,369
是打到这屋子来的
coming to this house.

245
00:15:16,404 --> 00:15:18,488
在凌晨1点 2点
1:00, 2:00 AM.

246
00:15:18,540 --> 00:15:21,374
我... 我不... 我不知道
I... I don't... I don't know.

247
00:15:21,459 --> 00:15:23,243
我没留意
I don't pay attention.

248
00:15:23,295 --> 00:15:26,162
是楼上的电话 谈公事的
Is upstairs line. Business.

249
00:15:31,169 --> 00:15:33,803
你和Chessani先生结婚多久了?
So how long have you been married to Mr. Chessani?

250
00:15:33,838 --> 00:15:35,555
是Chessani市长
Mayor Chessani.

251
00:15:35,590 --> 00:15:37,840
永远别叫先生
Never mister,

252
00:15:37,842 --> 00:15:39,842
他说的
he says.

253
00:15:39,844 --> 00:15:41,144
结了一年
For a year.

254
00:15:41,179 --> 00:15:43,930
你们是怎么认识的?
And how'd you guys meet?

255
00:15:46,651 --> 00:15:48,318
酒会上
A party.

256
00:16:31,396 --> 00:16:32,862
嘿
Hey.

257
00:16:32,897 --> 00:16:34,614
没事吧?
Everything all right?

258
00:16:44,409 --> 00:16:46,793
你就待在下面吧 傻婊子
And stay down there, you dumb bitch.

259
00:16:50,749 --> 00:16:53,216
告诉过你了别让这些婊子进我屋子
I tell you to keep these whores from my house.

260
00:16:59,174 --> 00:17:03,059
哟 Ronnie 这都是他妈的什么人?
Yo, Ronnie, who the fuck these people?

261
00:17:04,429 --> 00:17:07,146
州警察 把衣服穿起来
State police. Cover yourself.

262
00:17:08,099 --> 00:17:10,400
有搜查证吗?
Got a warrant?

263
00:17:17,609 --> 00:17:20,693
你为什么要这样伤害我?
Why you hurt me like this, huh?

264
00:17:20,745 --> 00:17:23,079
你怎么不去煮壶咖啡喝?
Yo, why don't you chug a pot of coffee?

265
00:17:23,114 --> 00:17:25,331
来片安定 镇静下来
Take a Xanax and chill your ass.

266
00:17:26,618 --> 00:17:29,952
Bodine会来的 我叫他了
Bodine on his way down. I called him.

267
00:17:30,005 --> 00:17:32,372
你们这这样大摇大摆闯别人家 人是不会开心的
People ain't happy with y'all goose-stepping up in here.

268
00:17:32,424 --> 00:17:34,290
你认识Ben Caspere吗?
You knew Ben Caspere?

269
00:17:34,292 --> 00:17:37,260
跟我老爹共事的一个老男人
Nah, some old guy who worked with my pops.

270
00:17:40,882 --> 00:17:42,799
不! 不! 不! 
No! No! No!

271
00:17:42,801 --> 00:17:45,435
谁没关门?
Who left door open?

272
00:17:47,138 --> 00:17:49,856
你从哪里学的口音?
Where'd you pick up that accent?

273
00:17:49,891 --> 00:17:51,357
口音?
Accent?

274
00:17:51,393 --> 00:17:54,360
你怎么这么种族歧视
You racist woman.

275
00:17:58,116 --> 00:18:01,234
我承认 这就是个骗局
I admit, it's a total put-on.

276
00:18:01,286 --> 00:18:03,569
不同的角色对应不同的职业
Different roles for different jobs.

277
00:18:03,621 --> 00:18:05,238
我有许多朋友
I have a lot of friends.

278
00:18:05,323 --> 00:18:06,956
那你是做什么的?
And what is it you do?

279
00:18:06,991 --> 00:18:08,991
特殊活动
Specialty events.

280
00:18:08,993 --> 00:18:11,044
我是一个组织者
I am an organizer.

281
00:18:11,079 --> 00:18:12,829
什么样的活动?
What kind of events?

282
00:18:12,881 --> 00:18:15,498
各种各样的
All kinds.

283
00:18:15,500 --> 00:18:17,583
如果你不介意的话...
Now, if you'll excuse me...

284
00:18:17,669 --> 00:18:20,086
你们最好在Bodine带律师来
y'all best to get stepping 'fore my man Bodine

285
00:18:20,138 --> 00:18:23,056
把你们生吞活剥之前 赶紧滚吧
come in here with a lawyer, chew your asses out.

286
00:18:23,091 --> 00:18:25,675
你们没有权利来这里
You ain't got no jurisdiction coming in here.

287
00:18:35,019 --> 00:18:37,770
毛细血管爆裂 胆固醇过高
Burst capillaries, cholesterol terrible,

288
00:18:37,822 --> 00:18:39,522
你的肝脏已经出问题了
your liver is redlining.

289
00:18:39,524 --> 00:18:42,692
我能问问你一星期平均喝多少酒吗?
Can I ask how much you drink in an average week?

290
00:18:42,744 --> 00:18:44,994
能喝多少喝多少
All I can.

291
00:18:45,029 --> 00:18:46,996
嗑药吗?
Drugs?

292
00:18:47,031 --> 00:18:48,498
一点
A few.

293
00:18:48,533 --> 00:18:50,416
那我就瞎猜一下
And I'll just go out on a limb here

294
00:18:50,452 --> 00:18:53,336
你饮食也不够健康吧?
and guess that your diet isn't particularly healthy?

295
00:18:53,371 --> 00:18:55,872
嗯 这个
Well, this,

296
00:18:55,924 --> 00:18:59,959
这件事让我想了很多...
you know, had me thinking about, uh...

297
00:19:00,011 --> 00:19:01,594
我想改变
changing some things.

298
00:19:01,629 --> 00:19:05,264
有不良的生活习惯当然可以活
Well, it's certainly possible to live with unhealthy habits,

299
00:19:05,300 --> 00:19:08,101
但最好是不要所有坏习惯都染上
but it helps if you don't have every one under the sun.

300
00:19:08,136 --> 00:19:10,603
我可以了吗?
Am I cleared?

301
00:19:10,638 --> 00:19:12,271
是我就再休息两天
I'd take a couple days,

302
00:19:12,307 --> 00:19:14,557
不过 嗯 你可以归队了
but, yeah, you're cleared.

303
00:19:14,559 --> 00:19:16,526
Burris说不管怎样都让你归队
Burris says to clear you at any rate.

304
00:19:16,561 --> 00:19:19,061
好 待会见
Great. All right, see you.

305
00:19:19,114 --> 00:19:22,064
Velcoro先生 我能问你一些事情吗?
Can I ask you something, Mr. Velcoro?

306
00:19:22,066 --> 00:19:24,450
你还想活着吗?
Do you want to live?

307
00:19:41,002 --> 00:19:42,585
你在这干什么?
What are you doing here?

308
00:19:42,587 --> 00:19:44,420
建购物商场
Vertical mall.

309
00:19:44,422 --> 00:19:45,755
你需要什么 Frank?
What do you need, Frank?

310
00:19:45,807 --> 00:19:48,591
首先 感激之情
Gratitude, for starters.

311
00:19:48,643 --> 00:19:51,594
Frank 你知道我充满感激之情
Frank, you know I'm grateful.

312
00:19:51,646 --> 00:19:52,812
我和你说过
I've told you.

313
00:19:52,847 --> 00:19:54,647
我要的是具体的
Gratitude you can count.

314
00:19:54,682 --> 00:19:59,519
我为了把你的股票赎回来花的钱
Frank, what I pulled together to take your shares back,

315
00:19:59,571 --> 00:20:02,155
没有人能比我出价更高
no one else would have paid what I did.

316
00:20:02,190 --> 00:20:04,574
而且我很感激
And I'm grateful

317
00:20:04,609 --> 00:20:06,526
铁路走廊那些东西
with the rail corridor stuff.

318
00:20:06,578 --> 00:20:08,027
它们很棒
It's great.

319
00:20:08,079 --> 00:20:09,579
谢谢
Thank you.

320
00:20:11,032 --> 00:20:13,833
同一件事情 你想让别人给你付多少次钱啊?
How many times do you expect to be paid for the same thing?

321
00:20:13,868 --> 00:20:15,868
每月一次
Every month.

322
00:20:15,954 --> 00:20:17,787
百分之二十五的纯利润
25% of your net.

323
00:20:17,789 --> 00:20:20,706
我... 我已经给你付钱了 别这样 哥们
I... I already paid you. Come on, man.

324
00:20:20,758 --> 00:20:22,341
你已经干开别的了
You moved on.

325
00:20:22,377 --> 00:20:25,294
世道变了
Things change.

326
00:20:25,296 --> 00:20:29,298
如果他们收我的钱 他们能也收你的钱
If they change for me, they can change for you.

327
00:20:31,302 --> 00:20:33,269
你这儿现在挺好
Things are good right now.

328
00:20:33,304 --> 00:20:35,438
不错
That's good.

329
00:20:35,473 --> 00:20:39,976
没准哪天 卡车司机或你的电工们
Maybe one day the Teamsters, your electrical workers,

330
00:20:39,978 --> 00:20:41,894
会找工地的麻烦
they get a problem with this site.

331
00:20:41,946 --> 00:20:44,730
给你贷款的公司
Probity Loan that loaned you that money

332
00:20:44,782 --> 00:20:47,316
让你买进这个天上掉下的大馅饼
that lets you buy into this gravy train,

333
00:20:47,318 --> 00:20:49,318
他们也许会收回这笔钱
they're gonna call back the note

334
00:20:49,320 --> 00:20:51,537
那时你就需要朋友了
and you'll need a friend,

335
00:20:51,623 --> 00:20:54,407
我那时也乐意帮你忙
which is what I'm offering you.

336
00:20:54,459 --> 00:20:56,742
Mary和孩子们怎么样?
How's Mary and the boys?

337
00:20:56,794 --> 00:20:58,377
她很支持你 对吧?
She stood by you, huh?

338
00:21:00,465 --> 00:21:02,665
你喜欢Tarzana的学校吗?
You like the schools in Tarzana?

339
00:21:09,340 --> 00:21:11,841
我想要周末送货
I want weekend deliveries.

340
00:21:11,843 --> 00:21:13,392
那些电工混蛋们
And those electrician fucks,

341
00:21:13,428 --> 00:21:16,062
三个人的工作他们要我付五个人的钱
they're charging me for five guys when three will do.

342
00:21:16,097 --> 00:21:17,763
这就对了
There you go.

343
00:21:17,815 --> 00:21:20,182
握手成交 互惠互利
One hand in the other.

344
00:21:20,235 --> 00:21:22,852
每月初 Bart
First of the month, Bart.

345
00:21:22,904 --> 00:21:25,187
我就坐等着
I'm not going anywhere.

346
00:21:42,206 --> 00:21:45,374
他在贝沙湾保险公司有一个保险箱
He had a safe-deposit box at a Bel-Air security firm.

347
00:21:47,428 --> 00:21:50,880
还有很多有限责任公司的合同
Articles of incorporation for a couple LLCs.

348
00:21:50,882 --> 00:21:53,883
他在去年组建的这些公司
These corporations he had formed within the last year.

349
00:21:53,935 --> 00:21:55,851
我们正在资产清单里找线索
We're looking into asset listings now.

350
00:21:55,887 --> 00:21:58,888
不错 他们可以根据这个来跟踪他的开支
Good. They can use that to follow his money.

351
00:21:58,940 --> 00:22:00,439
还没有找到嫌疑人?
No closer on a suspect?

352
00:22:00,475 --> 00:22:01,691
Velcoro没看到谁对他开的枪?
Velcoro didn't see who shot him? 

353
00:22:01,726 --> 00:22:02,692
他说他们戴了面罩
Said they were masked.

354
00:22:02,727 --> 00:22:05,027
你觉得可能是他装的吗?
You think he could have staged that?

355
00:22:05,063 --> 00:22:08,064
你看 最后他也就受了点小伤
I mean, at the end of the day, he just got banged up some.

356
00:22:11,402 --> 00:22:13,819
我想不出来他为什么要装
Can't imagine why he would.

357
00:22:16,124 --> 00:22:18,574
盒子里还有别的东西
There was something else in that box, too.

358
00:22:19,827 --> 00:22:22,078
蓝钻石
Blue diamonds.

359
00:22:22,080 --> 00:22:23,746
实验室检查那所公寓的同时
We'll follow up on the corporate holdings

360
00:22:23,748 --> 00:22:25,214
我们会查看公司的股份
and the prostitution connections

361
00:22:25,249 --> 00:22:27,383
还有和妓女的联系
while the lab processes the apartment.

362
00:22:27,418 --> 00:22:30,086
Caspere看来和Catalast集团有很深的勾结
Caspere seems deep with Catalast.

363
00:22:30,088 --> 00:22:33,222
没有公开的东西 买了许多土地
Nothing much public on them. Own a lot of land.

364
00:22:33,257 --> 00:22:35,558
更了解Velcoro了吗?
Gotten close to Velcoro?

365
00:22:35,593 --> 00:22:37,259
- 我的印象?  - 嗯
- My impression?  - Mm.

366
00:22:37,261 --> 00:22:38,811
- 坦白说?  - 嗯
- Straight up?  - Mm.

367
00:22:40,315 --> 00:22:41,897
他没救了
Guy's a burnout.

368
00:22:41,933 --> 00:22:46,018
没有搜查令 什么都没有 那群婊子就进了我家
Bitch comes into my house, no warrant, no nothing,

369
00:22:46,070 --> 00:22:50,356
骚扰了我妻子和孩子
harasses my wife, my children.

370
00:22:50,408 --> 00:22:53,075
市长很生气
The mayor is very upset.

371
00:22:53,111 --> 00:22:54,944
你发现什么了 Ray?
What did you find, Ray?

372
00:22:54,946 --> 00:22:58,080
西好莱坞的一个公寓里面发现了杀人现场
A murder scene in an apartment in West Hollywood.

373
00:22:58,116 --> 00:23:02,868
这个叫Catalast的私人集团把它租给了Caspere
This private development group Catalast rented it for Caspere.

374
00:23:02,920 --> 00:23:04,503
然后?
And?

375
00:23:04,589 --> 00:23:06,839
跟他大房子里一样的怪异的东西
Oh, same kinds of weirdness we found at his other place.
å

376
00:23:06,874 --> 00:23:08,290
那些他的性癖好
You know, his fetish shit.

377
00:23:08,343 --> 00:23:11,177
还有个角落里藏了摄像头和硬盘
And there was a spot where a camera and a hard drive had been,

378
00:23:11,212 --> 00:23:13,212
但是开枪打了我的人把它拿走了
but the guy that shot me took it.

379
00:23:13,264 --> 00:23:15,131
你都没有看清楚他的样子吗?
And you didn't get a look at him?

380
00:23:15,183 --> 00:23:19,051
没 我一转身就被打了
No. As soon as I turned, I just saw the blast.

381
00:23:19,103 --> 00:23:20,970
那个婊子呢?
What about the cunt?

382
00:23:21,022 --> 00:23:25,191
就是Bezzerides 她问起公寓的事了吗?
Bezzerides. She ask any questions about the department?

383
00:23:25,226 --> 00:23:27,476
没 没有
No, not really.

384
00:23:27,478 --> 00:23:31,280
Velcoro不干净 我要抓他
Velcoro's dirty. I want him.

385
00:23:31,315 --> 00:23:33,449
我以为我跟你说清了这一点
I thought I was clear on that.

386
00:23:33,484 --> 00:23:35,484
有个不干净的Vinci警察我们可以利用
We got a crooked Vinci cop we can leverage.

387
00:23:35,486 --> 00:23:37,570
多好的事
All the better.

388
00:23:37,622 --> 00:23:39,705
他可是个男人
He's a man, for Christ's sake.

389
00:23:39,741 --> 00:23:42,324
是 那又怎样?
Yeah, so what?

390
00:23:43,961 --> 00:23:47,163
我不是说操他 但让他觉得你想去操他也行啊
I'm not saying fuck him, but maybe let him think you might fuck him.

391
00:23:47,215 --> 00:23:50,166
Bezzerides警探既不是内务部的也不是情报处的
Detective Bezzerides isn't IA or UC.

392
00:23:50,168 --> 00:23:52,334
她是被安排去调查谋杀案
She's tasked with a murder.

393
00:23:52,387 --> 00:23:53,669
对 对
Sure. Sure.

394
00:23:53,721 --> 00:23:56,338
我就不把这件事强调太多
And I'm not putting this in a memo,

395
00:23:56,424 --> 00:23:59,258
但是Velcoro很有价值
but Velcoro is worth a bonus.

396
00:23:59,310 --> 00:24:02,011
我可以给你升职
I can see working a promotion for you.

397
00:24:03,231 --> 00:24:05,698
州律师传我们上交时间表
State attorney subpoenaed our time sheets.

398
00:24:05,733 --> 00:24:07,817
- 嗯  - 你下一步打算怎么对付Caspere?
- Hmm.  - What's your next move on Caspere?

399
00:24:07,869 --> 00:24:09,702
- 呃...  - 我要她的徽章
- Well...  - I want her badge.

400
00:24:09,737 --> 00:24:13,155
我要她的那张破烂的老大的徽章
I want her hick sheriff boss's badge.

401
00:24:13,208 --> 00:24:16,325
周内调查这事情马上就能结束了
This state thing is gonna get cleared up soon enough.

402
00:24:16,327 --> 00:24:18,828
他们会欠我一个人情...
They're gonna come out owing me and that...

403
00:24:18,830 --> 00:24:21,797
我不会给那个婊子好日子过的
that cunt is walking the plank.

404
00:24:21,833 --> 00:24:24,166
听着 那个照相机被拿走肯定是因为里面有东西
Look, the camera taken means there was something on it.

405
00:24:24,168 --> 00:24:26,168
可能是杀人的过程 可能是杀手的图像
Maybe the killing, maybe footage of the killer.

406
00:24:26,221 --> 00:24:29,255
但他在全州到处交易土地
But he was traveling up and down the state doing land deals.

407
00:24:29,307 --> 00:24:31,641
我们看得到烟但是找不到火
Well, that's smoke and no fire.

408
00:24:31,676 --> 00:24:34,393
去查土地交易查不出什么的
Land deals aren't gonna bring this in.

409
00:24:34,479 --> 00:24:37,179
还是要继续去查妓女 把案子结了
But keep working the hooker angle and get it wrapped

410
00:24:37,181 --> 00:24:39,849
别扯进州内调查
before state makes this part of their probe.

411
00:24:42,020 --> 00:24:43,319
清楚了吗?
Clear?

412
00:24:45,023 --> 00:24:47,189
Bezzerides在负责这个案子 长官
Bezzerides is running the case, sir.

413
00:24:47,242 --> 00:24:49,825
Bezzerides还是去负责卖酸奶吧
Bezzerides is gonna be running a yogurt stand.

414
00:24:49,861 --> 00:24:53,579
把她引导到一些实际的东西上去
So steer her to something concrete.

415
00:24:54,749 --> 00:24:56,165
比如找个皮条客
I like a pimp for this.

416
00:24:56,200 --> 00:24:58,034
听着 你想听实话吗?
Look, you want the truth?

417
00:24:58,036 --> 00:25:01,203
也许正好可以用这个借口把我撤下来
Maybe this is a good excuse to take me off.

418
00:25:01,256 --> 00:25:03,039
你懂吗?
You know?

419
00:25:03,091 --> 00:25:05,625
我就是想说 她不信任我
I mean, she don't trust me.

420
00:25:05,677 --> 00:25:07,793
{\an8}Columbo 神探可伦坡

421
00:25:05,677 --> 00:25:07,793
我也不是什么神探
And I ain't ever exactly been Columbo.

422
00:25:07,845 --> 00:25:10,129
这他妈什么意思?
What the fuck does that mean?

423
00:25:10,181 --> 00:25:12,632
这就是你最厉害的人?
This is your best man?

424
00:25:12,684 --> 00:25:14,550
你必须加入 Ray 就这样
You're on it, Ray, period.

425
00:25:14,552 --> 00:25:18,220
那个 呃 调查怎么样了?
How's the, uh, probe looking?

426
00:25:20,725 --> 00:25:23,559
我们会搞定的
We'll work it out.

427
00:25:23,561 --> 00:25:25,695
是啊
Yeah.

428
00:25:34,906 --> 00:25:36,238
他们对你还好吗?
They treating you all right?

429
00:25:36,291 --> 00:25:39,075
{\an8}就像钻井平台上的啦啦队长一样

430
00:25:36,291 --> 00:25:39,075
感觉下一秒就要被上了
Like a cheerleader on an oil rig.

431
00:25:40,545 --> 00:25:42,495
我靠
Oh, shit.

432
00:25:42,547 --> 00:25:44,997
嘿 我以为你手机坏掉了
Hey, thought your phone was busted.

433
00:25:45,049 --> 00:25:47,750
- 我听说你在这里 所以就过来看看  - 好的
- I heard you were up here. I thought I'd stop by.  - Okay, yeah.

434
00:25:47,752 --> 00:25:49,251
我刚刚... 我在南边工作呢
I've just... I've been working down south.

435
00:25:49,304 --> 00:25:50,636
是的 我知道 我知道
No, yeah, I know. I know.

436
00:25:50,672 --> 00:25:52,972
我只是想我们也许可以一起去吃点东西
I just thought maybe we could go grab a bite.

437
00:25:53,007 --> 00:25:55,508
嗯 我能去南边
Ahem. I can come down,

438
00:25:55,560 --> 00:25:57,760
因为你不接我电话
you know, since you're not answering my phone calls.

439
00:25:57,762 --> 00:26:00,813
Steve 听着 你是个好人 但是...
Yeah, Steve, look, you're a decent guy, but...

440
00:26:00,848 --> 00:26:03,316
- 等等 等等 等等 拜托  - 但这已经结束了
- Wait, wait, wait. Come on.  - This has run its course.

441
00:26:03,351 --> 00:26:04,850
好吗?
Okay?

442
00:26:04,936 --> 00:26:06,686
没什么的 你没做错什么
No big deal. You didn't do anything.

443
00:26:06,738 --> 00:26:10,189
但你和我之间已经没什么东西了
But you and I, there's just not much there.

444
00:26:10,241 --> 00:26:13,192
没什么东西了?
There's not much there?

445
00:26:13,244 --> 00:26:15,277
呃 你本可以骗骗我的
Well, you could have fooled me.

446
00:26:18,916 --> 00:26:20,366
他妈的明明是你主动的
You know, you fucking started this.

447
00:26:20,418 --> 00:26:22,618
别把事情搞得很难看
Don't push this somewhere ugly.

448
00:26:22,620 --> 00:26:25,454
稍微成熟点
Just be a little mature about it.

449
00:26:25,506 --> 00:26:27,957
- 给自己留点尊严  - 尊严?
- Have some dignity.  - Dignity?

450
00:26:31,295 --> 00:26:33,379
你真是那种玩好就丢的人啊?
You're a real suck 'em and leave 'em type, huh?

451
00:26:35,183 --> 00:26:36,966
你要是再跟我那么讲话
You talk to me like that again,

452
00:26:37,018 --> 00:26:40,302
你就得找个袋子装你自己的牙齿了
you're gonna need a little baggie to carry your teeth home.

453
00:26:50,815 --> 00:26:53,032
- 妈妈的好孩子  - 啥?
- Mama's boy.  - What?

454
00:26:53,067 --> 00:26:56,535
停 停 滚出我的办公室
Stop. Stop. Get the fuck out of my squad room.

455
00:27:00,825 --> 00:27:02,491
好的
All right.

456
00:27:03,828 --> 00:27:06,379
我跟你说 你有大毛病 探长
You know, you got serious problems, Detective.

457
00:27:06,414 --> 00:27:08,247
我正在一点一点改正呢
I'm whittling them down.

458
00:27:11,636 --> 00:27:13,135
- 哇  - 嗯?
- Wow.  - Yeah?

459
00:27:13,171 --> 00:27:14,670
- 真棒  - 你想说什么吗?
- Nice.  - You got something to say?

460
00:27:14,756 --> 00:27:17,006
什么都不想说
Nothing at all.

461
00:27:31,239 --> 00:27:34,023
你可以直接拿着瓶子喝的
You could just drink from the bottle.

462
00:27:34,075 --> 00:27:37,109
把这瓶都喝完 就有麻烦了
Drink out the bottle, you got a problem.

463
00:27:40,198 --> 00:27:43,082
你上次给我的那点东西让我一晚上没睡
You know that last shit you gave me kept me up all night.

464
00:27:43,117 --> 00:27:45,084
我以为我听到你妈妈讲话了
Thought I could hear your mother.

465
00:27:45,119 --> 00:27:47,086
啊 不是那种 是打骂
Well, not that. It's indica.

466
00:27:47,121 --> 00:27:50,039
这是肉烧起来的味道 你的肉
The smell of burning flesh. Your own.

467
00:27:50,091 --> 00:27:51,757
那就说话啊! 你用这东西干了什么?
Well, then talk! What did you do with the stuff?

468
00:27:51,793 --> 00:27:54,960
各位 等等 Louis没问题
Now wait a minute, fellas. Louis is okay.

469
00:27:55,012 --> 00:27:58,714
我做了一个梦
I had a dream

470
00:27:58,716 --> 00:28:00,216
关于你的
about you.

471
00:28:00,218 --> 00:28:03,018
我从来记不住我做的梦
I can't ever remember my dreams.

472
00:28:03,054 --> 00:28:04,804
我也没怎么睡
Barely sleep anyway.

473
00:28:12,613 --> 00:28:14,280
你的徽章呢?
Where's your badge?

474
00:28:15,233 --> 00:28:17,283
呃 它...
Well, it's...

475
00:28:28,796 --> 00:28:31,497
你不该这么做的
You shouldn't do that.

476
00:28:31,549 --> 00:28:33,833
万一你在新闻上看到什么或者谁让你生气
Whatever you saw on the news or whatever pissed you off,

477
00:28:33,885 --> 00:28:35,251
你会想念它的
you'll wake up one day and you'll miss it.

478
00:28:35,303 --> 00:28:37,553
我不会想它的
I won't miss it.

479
00:28:37,588 --> 00:28:40,089
已经没有警察局了
There ain't no PD anymore.

480
00:28:40,091 --> 00:28:42,558
好吧 如果你想把它处理掉的话 就给我吧
Well, if you're gonna throw it away, I'll take it.

481
00:28:42,593 --> 00:28:44,593
我把它拿给Chad
I'll give it to Chad.

482
00:28:48,182 --> 00:28:51,267
你有朋友会这样推你吗?
Pull. Have you got any friends with push like that?

483
00:28:51,269 --> 00:28:54,069
你吃过了吗?
You been eating?

484
00:28:54,105 --> 00:28:56,739
没 我不饿
Nah, I don't get hungry.

485
00:28:56,774 --> 00:28:59,241
呃 大麻能让你胃口好点
Well, that grass will give you an appetite.

486
00:28:59,277 --> 00:29:01,160
还能让你睡觉呢
Put you to sleep, too.

487
00:29:07,952 --> 00:29:09,368
你的儿子怎么样了?
How's your boy?

488
00:29:10,788 --> 00:29:12,421
他还好
He's all right.

489
00:29:12,456 --> 00:29:15,040
当一个小孩不容易
It's hard being a kid.

490
00:29:15,092 --> 00:29:17,843
我们不能想见面就见面
We don't see each other as much as we'd like.

491
00:29:20,765 --> 00:29:25,184
爸 Vinci那些人 你认识Kevin Burris吗
Pop, the guys in Vinci, you knew Kevin Burris a little.

492
00:29:25,219 --> 00:29:26,685
那个叫Holloway的长官?
Holloway the chief?

493
00:29:26,721 --> 00:29:29,104
Holloway是个好人
Holloway's a good man.

494
00:29:29,140 --> 00:29:31,557
一根筋
Hard charger.

495
00:29:31,609 --> 00:29:33,309
老古董
Old school.

496
00:29:33,361 --> 00:29:36,312
在Gates的带领下让他们高强度工作
Worked them tough beats under Gates.

497
00:29:37,698 --> 00:29:40,065
那个时候你还能真的干点警察的事
Back when you could actually do police work.

498
00:29:41,903 --> 00:29:44,954
是啊 Burris也是
Yeah, Burris, too.

499
00:29:44,989 --> 00:29:47,072
他为什么离开?
Why'd he leave?

500
00:29:47,158 --> 00:29:49,158
在Vinci开店?
Set up shop in Vinci?

501
00:29:49,210 --> 00:29:51,410
因为他太他妈聪明了
'Cause he's fucking smart.

502
00:29:53,047 --> 00:29:54,797
暴乱之后 又有辛普森案那档子事
Then after the riots and OJ,

503
00:29:54,832 --> 00:29:57,633
我们就是没法好好干活了
we just couldn't do the job right.

504
00:29:57,668 --> 00:30:00,169
所以他和那些傻逼拜拜了
So he said so long to those cunts

505
00:30:00,171 --> 00:30:02,338
然后 一溜烟...
and, phew...

506
00:30:02,340 --> 00:30:04,506
出城去
headed on out of town.

507
00:30:06,811 --> 00:30:08,727
我应该看远点的
I should have been looking ahead.

508
00:30:11,816 --> 00:30:13,933
这样也不会现在拿着一半的养老金了
Wouldn't have no half pension now.

509
00:30:16,654 --> 00:30:18,771
总之 好久不见了
Anyways, I hadn't seen you in a while.

510
00:30:18,823 --> 00:30:20,272
是啊
Yeah.

511
00:30:20,324 --> 00:30:21,690
我想你缺药了吧
I figured you needed your medicine.

512
00:30:21,692 --> 00:30:24,910
看看这东西
Look at that shit.

513
00:30:24,946 --> 00:30:26,996
Kirk Douglas这小子
Kirk Douglas.

514
00:30:30,618 --> 00:30:33,035
这地方不是给白人待的 小子
No country for white men, boy.

515
00:30:35,706 --> 00:30:37,873
那我就走吧
I guess I'll take off, then.

516
00:30:55,026 --> 00:30:56,442
我不懂
I don't get it.

517
00:30:56,477 --> 00:31:00,396
我们还要在拉斯维加斯待几天 我还有别的事要做
We'll be in Vegas for a few days. I have other business.

518
00:31:00,398 --> 00:31:03,532
我需要点时间和我的人商量
Gives me time to confer with my people.

519
00:31:03,567 --> 00:31:06,952
我们可以下个礼拜再谈
We can talk next week.

520
00:31:06,988 --> 00:31:09,538
一个月以前好像一切都安排好了
A month ago it sounded like we were a done deal.

521
00:31:09,573 --> 00:31:11,490
我们已经谈过了 Frank
We've been over this, Frank.

522
00:31:11,542 --> 00:31:14,410
我没法做决定
I don't make these decisions myself.

523
00:31:14,462 --> 00:31:16,629
那Caspere呢?
And Caspere?

524
00:31:16,664 --> 00:31:21,000
我觉得这跟你临阵畏缩有关系
My thinking is this is somehow connected to you getting cold feet.

525
00:31:21,085 --> 00:31:24,753
是啊 我们又不笨
Sure. We're not stupid.

526
00:31:24,805 --> 00:31:28,507
你干的活收尾没收好 Frank
What you had sewn up, the stitching's frayed, Frank.

527
00:31:31,228 --> 00:31:33,595
这件事太大了 你不能离开
This is too big to walk away from.

528
00:31:34,849 --> 00:31:36,849
我从不请求许可
I don't ask permission.

529
00:31:36,901 --> 00:31:39,435
我说的不是你
I wasn't talking about you.

530
00:31:39,487 --> 00:31:43,105
你要走了? 那你滚吧(法语)
You leaving? Bon fucking voyage.

531
00:31:45,276 --> 00:31:47,159
那好吧 Frank
All right, Frank.

532
00:31:58,039 --> 00:32:00,506
该死的犹太共产党
Fucking Commie Jew fuck.

533
00:32:05,596 --> 00:32:07,096
Blake在哪儿?
Where's Blake?

534
00:32:07,131 --> 00:32:08,681
我给他发过信息了
I messaged him.

535
00:32:19,477 --> 00:32:22,194
还有Stan... 他怎么没来?
And Stan... why isn't he here?

536
00:32:22,229 --> 00:32:24,980
一个懂道理的人不是应该
Shouldn't a reasonable man infer

537
00:32:24,982 --> 00:32:27,533
从Osip来和走的态度
from Osip's arrival and departure

538
00:32:27,568 --> 00:32:29,868
而且他们没答应我们的条件来推测出
and fucking failure to make good on our terms

539
00:32:29,904 --> 00:32:32,821
他不但和Caspere有联系
as being connected not just to Caspere,

540
00:32:32,873 --> 00:32:35,157
而且还预料到了这场谋杀?
but prefiguring Caspere?

541
00:32:35,209 --> 00:32:37,826
这之间肯定有因果联系
In a causal sense.

542
00:32:37,878 --> 00:32:39,995
我是说...
I'm saying...

543
00:32:39,997 --> 00:32:42,381
会不会是Osip干掉了Caspere?
do you think Osip could have done Caspere?

544
00:32:42,416 --> 00:32:44,466
这个不是我的职责
Not my department.

545
00:32:44,502 --> 00:32:50,005
但如果你问我他是不是那种人
But if you're asking me is he that kind of guy,

546
00:32:50,007 --> 00:32:54,893
看上去他黑白通吃
he looks half anaconda and half great white.

547
00:33:02,670 --> 00:33:04,503
我看见那张纸了 哥们儿
So I saw that paper, bro.

548
00:33:04,538 --> 00:33:06,839
我觉得应该和你证实一下
Thought I'd check up on you.

549
00:33:06,874 --> 00:33:08,707
真是不给你留活路啊?
Got you downrange, huh?

550
00:33:08,759 --> 00:33:11,293
全是狗屁
It's bullshit.

551
00:33:11,345 --> 00:33:14,213
给州内这事儿我已经做了一半了
I'm half working this thing for state.

552
00:33:14,265 --> 00:33:16,131
按说应该要完成了
Supposed to see me through.

553
00:33:16,183 --> 00:33:18,300
所以呢?
So?

554
00:33:18,302 --> 00:33:21,520
所以没有 我没做那种事
So fuck no, I didn't.

555
00:33:21,555 --> 00:33:23,972
是 我也不觉得你会做
Yeah, well, I didn't think you did.

556
00:33:25,809 --> 00:33:27,526
你还去参加那些交流会吗?
So you been going to meetings?

557
00:33:27,561 --> 00:33:30,479
我第一年去过
I went the first year.

558
00:33:30,481 --> 00:33:33,982
我是说 要是你想摆脱什么事
I mean, if you want to get over something,

559
00:33:33,984 --> 00:33:36,201
坐在那里然后仔细回忆
maybe sitting around and remembering it

560
00:33:36,237 --> 00:33:38,871
每个具体细节
in every detail

561
00:33:38,906 --> 00:33:40,906
也许不是个好方法
ain't the right way.

562
00:33:40,958 --> 00:33:43,408
对 呃 不过呢
Yeah, well, the thing of it is

563
00:33:43,460 --> 00:33:46,411
有些他们说的那些话很对
some of that knowledge they spill makes sense.

564
00:33:47,998 --> 00:33:50,382
一些过去的事
Stuff about the past,

565
00:33:50,417 --> 00:33:52,501
不要否认它...
not denying it...

566
00:33:53,554 --> 00:33:55,470
而要让它成为你的一部分
letting it be a part of you.

567
00:33:58,309 --> 00:34:00,008
对啊
Yeah.

568
00:34:01,345 --> 00:34:03,762
你在工作吗?
You working?

569
00:34:03,814 --> 00:34:06,982
是 就是做一些杂七杂八的事情
Yeah, just some things here and there.

570
00:34:08,686 --> 00:34:12,604
呃 我加上了电工工会
Mm, I got on with the electricians union.

571
00:34:12,656 --> 00:34:15,023
- 嗯 不错  - 算不上成功
- Mm, great.  - Still a low man.

572
00:34:17,077 --> 00:34:19,745
你怀念过吗?
You ever miss it?

573
00:34:19,780 --> 00:34:21,580
是
Yeah.

574
00:34:23,167 --> 00:34:26,868
你知道的 我一直在想关于那个村庄的事情
You know, I keep thinking about the village.

575
00:34:27,788 --> 00:34:29,955
在Al Awjar外面
Outside Al Awjar.

576
00:34:31,208 --> 00:34:33,592
那个山谷
The valley.

577
00:34:33,627 --> 00:34:36,378
和那些善良的人 兄弟
Nice people, man.

578
00:34:36,380 --> 00:34:38,297
还有山脉
Mountains.

579
00:34:38,349 --> 00:34:41,600
兄弟 我们再也不是士兵了 
We ain't soldiers anymore, man.

580
00:34:41,635 --> 00:34:44,386
当时我想
I remember thinking

581
00:34:44,438 --> 00:34:46,605
我可以留在那里
I could have just stayed there.

582
00:34:47,942 --> 00:34:50,559
忘掉找队伍的事情
Just forget finding the squad.

583
00:34:50,611 --> 00:34:54,396
我是说...
I mean...

584
00:34:54,398 --> 00:34:58,116
我觉得 呃 那就像是...
I think, like, that was like the...

585
00:35:00,204 --> 00:35:02,904
那对我来说就是最后一段美好时光了 兄弟
it was the last time shit felt right for me, bro.

586
00:35:02,957 --> 00:35:04,573
你说战争
You mean combat.

587
00:35:09,663 --> 00:35:11,630
你想回到那个时候吗?
Would you ever go back to it?

588
00:35:11,665 --> 00:35:13,715
我没那么想
I don't think so.

589
00:35:13,751 --> 00:35:15,717
我觉得应该待不了那么久了
Didn't think I'd stay on as long as I did.

590
00:35:15,753 --> 00:35:18,971
回家来又一堆破事 你懂吗?
And then it was hard to see coming home, you know?
574   

591
00:35:20,257 --> 00:35:22,507
我不是那个意思
That's not what I mean.

592
00:35:22,559 --> 00:35:24,309
你知道我在说什么
You know what I'm talking about.

593
00:35:24,345 --> 00:35:26,228
那三天
Them three days.

594
00:35:26,263 --> 00:35:29,398
- 我一直在想你 兄弟  - 别说了
- I think about you, man.  - Stop it.

595
00:35:29,433 --> 00:35:32,601
为什么? 要是我就不想忘记呢?
Why? What if I don't want to forget, huh?

596
00:35:34,772 --> 00:35:37,773
伙计 你还是走吧
Dude, you should go.

597
00:35:39,159 --> 00:35:41,276
- 我要走了  - 嘿 别走
- I'm out.  - Hey, look.

598
00:35:41,278 --> 00:35:43,528
别装了 好吗? 别...
Don't pretend, all right? Don't pre...

599
00:35:43,580 --> 00:35:45,364
嘿 嘿 嘿 你看见了吗?
Hey, hey, hey. You see that?

600
00:35:45,449 --> 00:35:47,366
去你妈的 混球
Fuck you, asshole.

601
00:35:47,418 --> 00:35:50,669
对不起 Woodrugh
Woodrugh, I'm sorry, man.

602
00:35:55,342 --> 00:35:57,376
我不是故意的
I didn't mean for that.

603
00:35:58,629 --> 00:36:00,796
对不起 兄弟 我喝多了
I'm sorry, man. I'm drunk.

604
00:36:00,848 --> 00:36:03,515
我喝多了 对不起
I am drunk. I'm sorry.

605
00:36:19,533 --> 00:36:22,117
交通录像传过来了
City traffic cams came back.

606
00:36:22,152 --> 00:36:24,786
在谋杀案那天的凌晨一点 Ventura城里拍到了这个
Ventura picked this one up 1:00 AM night of the murder.

607
00:36:24,822 --> 00:36:26,988
一辆凯迪拉克从33口驶入太平海岸高速
Caddy pulling onto PCH from the 33.

608
00:36:26,990 --> 00:36:29,958
这个车是注册在一个电影车队名下
Car's registered to a film transportation department.

609
00:36:29,993 --> 00:36:31,993
是他们在这拍的那片子?
That flick they're shooting here?

610
00:36:31,995 --> 00:36:33,412
第一次就猜对了
Got it in one.
594  

611
00:36:42,473 --> 00:36:44,673
你回来了
You're back.

612
00:36:44,808 --> 00:36:47,008
是的 大难不死
Yeah, not for lack of trying.

613
00:36:54,268 --> 00:36:56,818
Caspere给了我们的税务优惠
Caspere arranged our tax incentives.

614
00:36:56,854 --> 00:36:59,187
这是唯一能在加州拍电影的办法
Only way you can film anything in California now.

615
00:36:59,239 --> 00:37:01,026
给他在联合制作人里留了个名字
Threw him a coproducer credit.

616
00:37:01,027 --> 00:37:03,064
我们很抱歉听到那消息
We're real sorry to hear what happened.

617
00:37:03,065 --> 00:37:03,889
停!
Cut!

618
00:37:03,924 --> 00:37:05,699
- 他经常来这边吗?  - 不
- Was he around here much?  - No.

619
00:37:05,700 --> 00:37:06,955
他也来过...
I mean, he came by...

620
00:37:06,997 --> 00:37:10,365
我们当时正在筹备 帮着解决警局 分区的问题
we were in prep, helped out with PD, zoning.

621
00:37:10,367 --> 00:37:12,367
除了署名 还有钱吧?
That producer credit come with a paycheck?

622
00:37:12,419 --> 00:37:14,002
对 杀青之后
Back end, yeah.

623
00:37:14,037 --> 00:37:15,871
那辆车呢? 那辆凯迪拉克?
What about that car? The Caddy?

624
00:37:15,923 --> 00:37:17,589
上周早上丢了一辆
Went missing one morning last week.

625
00:37:17,624 --> 00:37:19,091
我们跟警长报了案
We filed it stolen with sheriff's.

626
00:37:19,126 --> 00:37:20,842
昨天提交了保险理赔文件
Put in the insurance papers yesterday.

627
00:37:20,878 --> 00:37:24,112
我带你们去见车队队长
I'll bring you to our transpo head.

628
00:37:24,148 --> 00:37:25,714
是的 周一早上就没了
Yeah, Monday morning it was gone.

629
00:37:25,766 --> 00:37:27,215
大门的锁被撬了
Lock on the gate was bolt cut.

630
00:37:27,267 --> 00:37:28,717
跟警长打了报告
Sheriff's took a report.

631
00:37:28,719 --> 00:37:30,185
有人失踪了吗?
Any personnel missing?

632
00:37:30,220 --> 00:37:32,971
没有 没什么特别的
No, nothing unusual.

633
00:37:33,023 --> 00:37:36,224
一周前 我们有一个司机因为家庭事务辞职了
We had a driver quit the week before due to family issues.

634
00:37:36,226 --> 00:37:38,860
我从没听说过Caspere这个人
I never knew the Caspere guy.

635
00:37:38,896 --> 00:37:42,114
我需要你们部门所有人的姓名和住址
I need names and addresses of everyone in your department.

636
00:37:43,233 --> 00:37:45,450
好的 可以
Sure. Yeah.

637
00:37:48,122 --> 00:37:50,489
停 操他妈的
Cut. Fuck it.

638
00:37:50,541 --> 00:37:53,074
去检查一下大门 我们走
Check the gate. Let's move.

639
00:37:56,880 --> 00:37:59,748
嘿 这是拍什么呢?
Hey, what's this thing about?

640
00:37:59,800 --> 00:38:01,716
两吨垃圾
About two tons of shit.

641
00:38:03,303 --> 00:38:07,973
文明毁灭后复仇的电影
Some collapse of civilization revenge flick.

642
00:38:08,008 --> 00:38:11,426
应该做成默片 那男的根本不会念台词
Ought to make it a silent picture the way the guy does his lines.

643
00:38:11,478 --> 00:38:14,596
- 这就是你的工作?  - 是的 场景摄影师
- That's your job?  - Yeah, set photographer.

644
00:38:18,352 --> 00:38:20,769
这是目前为止 我做的最有用的事
It's the best use of my time so far.

645
00:38:20,821 --> 00:38:22,771
你有没有...
You ever...

646
00:38:22,823 --> 00:38:25,357
你有没有在这附近见过这个人?
you ever seen this guy around?

647
00:38:26,243 --> 00:38:28,026
是 我见过他
Yeah, I've seen him.

648
00:38:28,078 --> 00:38:29,411
从城里来的人
Some city guy.

649
00:38:29,446 --> 00:38:32,330
想跟电影圈的人套近乎吧 我猜
Wants to brush shoulders with the industry, I guess.

650
00:38:32,366 --> 00:38:34,282
听说他和我们的导演开过几次趴
Heard he partied with our director once or twice.

651
00:38:34,334 --> 00:38:36,084
噢 是吗?
Oh, yeah?

652
00:38:36,119 --> 00:38:39,788
是的 Daisun不停说他们去的那个聚会
Yeah, Daisun was going on about some party they went to.

653
00:38:39,840 --> 00:38:42,958
他说 去的人很有料
Well-attended, he said.

654
00:38:43,010 --> 00:38:45,544
全是姑娘 满园春色
I mean pussy. Like, wall to wall.

655
00:38:45,596 --> 00:38:49,464
我猜场景摄影师不值得邀请吧
I guess being the set photographer don't rate an invite.

656
00:38:49,516 --> 00:38:52,884
是个晚宴 吃吃喝喝的
Yeah, it was just like a dinner, drinks thing.

657
00:38:52,936 --> 00:38:55,887
业内业外的人 有很多潜在的投资人
Lots of suits, potential investors.

658
00:38:55,939 --> 00:38:57,355
有姑娘吗?
What about girls?

659
00:38:57,391 --> 00:38:59,975
有不少
Yeah, girls were there.

660
00:39:00,027 --> 00:39:01,726
毕竟女人占了一半的人口
They are over half the population.

661
00:39:01,778 --> 00:39:03,728
有妓女吗?
Were there any hookers at this party?

662
00:39:03,780 --> 00:39:05,814
这我就不知道了 女士
I really wouldn't know that, ma'am.

663
00:39:05,816 --> 00:39:08,650
- 行吧  - 地方在哪?
- Hmm.  - Where was it?

664
00:39:08,702 --> 00:39:10,702
Ventura附近
Somewhere up above Ventura.

665
00:39:10,787 --> 00:39:12,654
实在不记得了
I really don't remember.

666
00:39:12,706 --> 00:39:15,907
说实话吧 我喝酒了
Tell you the truth, I drink.

667
00:39:15,959 --> 00:39:19,411
所以我的回忆不太靠谱
So it makes my recollection unreliable.

668
00:39:19,463 --> 00:39:21,963
Jack 让大家集合排练
Jack, get everyone up for a rehearsal.

669
00:39:21,999 --> 00:39:25,050
我马上来 工作不等人
I'll be there in a sec. Burning dollars.

670
00:39:25,085 --> 00:39:27,002
好
Yeah.

671
00:39:33,727 --> 00:39:35,894
我还在市政官办公室工作
I still work for the city manager's office.

672
00:39:35,929 --> 00:39:38,847
因为Caspere先生...
With Mr. Caspere...

673
00:39:38,849 --> 00:39:40,348
他去世了这件事
with what happened,

674
00:39:40,400 --> 00:39:43,318
他们让我来收集税收协定的复印件
they sent me down to collect copies of the tax agreements.

675
00:39:43,353 --> 00:39:45,437
为什么? 出什么问题了?
Why? Something wrong with them?

676
00:39:45,489 --> 00:39:47,522
我不觉得
I don't think so.

677
00:39:47,524 --> 00:39:50,659
他们只是把市里的文件整理好
They're just trying to get all the city's paperwork in order.

678
00:39:50,694 --> 00:39:52,694
方便州里审计
With the state's inquiry.

679
00:39:55,415 --> 00:39:57,282
好吧
All right.

680
00:39:57,334 --> 00:39:58,783
谢谢
Thank you.

681
00:40:05,509 --> 00:40:07,175
你他妈去哪了?
The fuck have you been?

682
00:40:07,210 --> 00:40:09,711
你现在翅膀硬了?
You take off on me now?

683
00:40:09,796 --> 00:40:12,380
和我媳妇在一起
Just with my lady.

684
00:40:12,432 --> 00:40:14,883
- 我... 我手机没电了  - 手机没电了?
- My... my phone died.  - Your fucking phone died?

685
00:40:14,885 --> 00:40:16,718
当我是十几岁的小姑娘?
Am I a goddamn teenage girl?

686
00:40:16,720 --> 00:40:19,554
Frank 是Stan
Frank, Stan.

687
00:40:19,556 --> 00:40:22,107
他怎么了?
What about him?

688
00:40:22,142 --> 00:40:24,025
他死了
He's dead.

689
00:40:27,898 --> 00:40:30,899
我们的几个墨西哥人发现了他 老大
Couple of our Mexicans found him, boss.

690
00:40:32,653 --> 00:40:34,202
什么情况?
What is this, huh?

691
00:40:36,239 --> 00:40:38,907
谁会和Stan有仇?
Who the fuck would have something against Stan?

692
00:40:41,411 --> 00:40:43,461
完全说不通
Don't make any fucking sense.

693
00:40:43,497 --> 00:40:46,131
杀了他有什么好处?
What is he to anybody?

694
00:40:46,166 --> 00:40:49,301
冲着Caspere来的人太多了
Too much coming right after Caspere.

695
00:40:51,672 --> 00:40:53,722
还用你说
No shit.

696
00:40:56,310 --> 00:40:57,926
那是谁?
Who, huh?

697
00:41:02,599 --> 00:41:04,566
谁给我使绊子?
Who the fuck's coming after me?

698
00:41:04,601 --> 00:41:07,102
是谁?
Huh? Who?

699
00:41:12,326 --> 00:41:15,110
去把Santos Fregredo Constantine
Get Santos, Fregredo, Constantine,

700
00:41:15,112 --> 00:41:16,778
和我们干过活的人
anybody that works on our property

701
00:41:16,780 --> 00:41:19,414
还有以前干过的人都找来 就今晚!
or what used to be our property now tonight!

702
00:41:19,449 --> 00:41:22,117
去Santos的地盘
Santos' place.

703
00:41:22,119 --> 00:41:23,618
你想怎么干?
What are you thinking?

704
00:41:23,670 --> 00:41:25,670
照我说的做
Just fucking do what I tell ya.

705
00:41:30,043 --> 00:41:31,960
把他安顿好
Pack him up.

706
00:41:33,347 --> 00:41:35,847
他不应该是这样的下场
He deserves better than this.

707
00:41:47,611 --> 00:41:49,644
你们好吗?
How you guys doing?

708
00:41:50,947 --> 00:41:54,899
在附近见过这个人吗?
You ever see this guy around?

709
00:41:56,703 --> 00:41:58,820
你见过这个人吗?
You ever see this guy?

710
00:42:10,884 --> 00:42:14,419
# 杀手 #
# oh, there are killers #

711
00:42:16,840 --> 00:42:21,760
# 就在城里 #
# oh, in this town #

712
00:42:24,347 --> 00:42:30,235
# 杀手 #
# oh, oh, killer, killers #

713
00:42:30,270 --> 00:42:36,107
# 计划天衣无缝 #
# with all their killer plans #

714
00:42:40,530 --> 00:42:43,865
# 一场战争 #
# a war is #

715
00:42:43,917 --> 00:42:48,953
# 即将来临 #
# on the horizon... #

716
00:42:52,959 --> 00:42:56,711
你们在附近见过这个人吗?
You guys ever see this guy around?

717
00:43:00,050 --> 00:43:01,766
我不是来查你们的
Look, I'm not vice.

718
00:43:01,802 --> 00:43:04,853
我不管谁上谁
I don't give a shit who fucks who here.

719
00:43:04,888 --> 00:43:07,555
没见过吗?
No?

720
00:43:07,607 --> 00:43:09,190
我见过他
I've seen him before.

721
00:43:10,560 --> 00:43:12,060
在哪?
Where?

722
00:43:13,447 --> 00:43:15,396
没和他约过
Never dated him, I mean,

723
00:43:15,449 --> 00:43:18,867
不过他来过这附近几次
but he'd been around a few times.

724
00:43:18,902 --> 00:43:20,368
当时我在工作
I was working.

725
00:43:20,403 --> 00:43:21,903
我记人很在行
Good with faces.

726
00:43:24,074 --> 00:43:26,040
在哪?
Where was this?

727
00:43:26,076 --> 00:43:29,994
几个街区那边的俱乐部 见过他好几次
Couple times, this club a couple blocks down.

728
00:43:30,046 --> 00:43:32,080
无尽的勒克斯
Lux Infinitum.

729
00:43:32,082 --> 00:43:33,748
你去过吗?
You been there?

730
00:43:33,750 --> 00:43:35,416
没有
No.

731
00:43:37,587 --> 00:43:39,471
有很多妓女吗?
Is it big with hookers?

732
00:43:39,506 --> 00:43:41,339
有很多各种各样的人
Big with all sorts.

733
00:43:41,391 --> 00:43:44,893
不过妓女确实爱去那儿
But, yeah, they got some prime time in there.

734
00:43:44,928 --> 00:43:47,428
就是那种夜店
It's one of them circuit clubs, you know?

735
00:43:47,481 --> 00:43:50,398
都是生意嘛
Trade runs through.

736
00:43:50,433 --> 00:43:52,600
一群欧洲人
Some European.

737
00:43:52,602 --> 00:43:54,936
那的姑娘可不便宜...
That pussy is expensive, so...

738
00:43:54,988 --> 00:43:57,188
也有找乐子的
yeah, you got party people,

739
00:43:57,274 --> 00:43:59,741
当然也有谈生意之类的
but also suits and whatnot.

740
00:44:02,612 --> 00:44:04,746
好
All right.

741
00:44:04,781 --> 00:44:06,498
谢了
Thanks.

742
00:44:09,786 --> 00:44:12,120
他们不会跟你说话的
They're not gonna talk to you.

743
00:44:14,958 --> 00:44:17,842
可能都不会让你进去
They probably wouldn't even let you in.

744
00:44:17,878 --> 00:44:21,713
就凭你演的忧郁警察这出
This angsty cop drama you're rolling.

745
00:44:37,531 --> 00:44:39,814
你喜欢模型啊?
You like models, I guess?

746
00:44:39,866 --> 00:44:44,202
是啊 开始和孩子一起拼
Yeah, started building them with my kid.

747
00:44:44,237 --> 00:44:46,654
后来我就自己玩了
Then I just started doing them without him.

748
00:44:46,656 --> 00:44:49,157
多谢
Thanks.

749
00:44:56,666 --> 00:44:58,049
靠
Shit.

750
00:45:00,420 --> 00:45:02,170
很快
Just a minute.

751
00:45:08,595 --> 00:45:09,978
嘿
Hey.

752
00:45:12,816 --> 00:45:16,651
Ray 我...
Look, Ray, I, uh...

753
00:45:16,686 --> 00:45:19,404
我只是想谈谈Chad的事
I just wanted to see about Chad.

754
00:45:19,439 --> 00:45:21,906
我不想再重复上次的对话
Yeah, I don't want to repeat that conversation.

755
00:45:21,942 --> 00:45:24,442
我也不愿意
I don't want to do that.

756
00:45:24,494 --> 00:45:27,528
我想你惹上更大的麻烦了
I think you've got worse trouble.

757
00:45:27,581 --> 00:45:29,914
州警今天来找我们
State police officers came to see us.

758
00:45:31,451 --> 00:45:34,535
两个人 调查员
Investigators, two of them.

759
00:45:37,340 --> 00:45:39,123
想知道你的情况
Wanted to know about you.

760
00:45:39,175 --> 00:45:41,092
想知道什么?
Wanted to know what?

761
00:45:41,127 --> 00:45:44,045
问我见没见过你不能审报的现金
If I ever saw extra cash you couldn't account for.

762
00:45:45,348 --> 00:45:48,049
问我知不知道你有暴力倾向
If I had ever known you to be violent.

763
00:45:48,051 --> 00:45:50,101
问我...
If I, uh...

764
00:45:52,154 --> 00:45:54,974
是否知道或者怀疑
ever knew or suspected

765
00:45:55,456 --> 00:45:57,992
你报复过那个攻击我的人
you took retribution on the man who attacked me.

766
00:46:03,450 --> 00:46:04,983
这是一万美元
It's 10,000.

767
00:46:06,703 --> 00:46:08,953
干什么?
For what?

768
00:46:08,989 --> 00:46:10,622
别跟我争抚养权
To not contest the custody.

769
00:46:14,494 --> 00:46:17,128
我们只是... 只是为了Chad好
We just... we just want to do what's best for Chad.

770
00:46:20,834 --> 00:46:23,751
你觉得你能花钱买我儿子?
You think you can buy my son?

771
00:46:23,753 --> 00:46:27,388
不 这只是...
No, it's for...

772
00:46:29,926 --> 00:46:31,926
只是让你走 Ray
it's to just go, Ray.

773
00:46:31,928 --> 00:46:33,928
这是种选择
It's an alternative.

774
00:46:34,014 --> 00:46:35,596
去别的地方
Go somewhere.

775
00:46:38,601 --> 00:46:40,768
趁事情还能挽回
Before we can't turn back.

776
00:46:41,988 --> 00:46:44,155
不管怎么样 那些问题
Whatever happens, those questions,

777
00:46:44,190 --> 00:46:46,441
争夺抚养权的官司
a custody battle,

778
00:46:46,493 --> 00:46:48,359
对Chad都不好
it's not gonna be easy for Chad.

779
00:46:48,411 --> 00:46:50,828
那你就别打
So don't start it.

780
00:46:50,864 --> 00:46:53,665
看那两个调查员的意思
The way those two investigators sounded,

781
00:46:53,700 --> 00:46:55,700
这只是时间问题 Ray
it's a matter of time, Ray.

782
00:47:02,258 --> 00:47:04,792
你把那个信封拿走
You put that envelope away.

783
00:47:04,794 --> 00:47:07,261
我会当做你从没想过我会收下
I'm gonna pretend like you never really thought I'd take it.

784
00:47:07,297 --> 00:47:09,630
我没有
I didn't.

785
00:47:09,632 --> 00:47:11,716
但我希望我是错的
But I hoped I might be wrong.

786
00:47:33,490 --> 00:47:35,540
- 你还好吗?  - 好啊
- You all right?  - Yeah.

787
00:47:37,877 --> 00:47:40,128
对了 我们该回去工作了
Yeah, we should get back to work.

788
00:48:21,704 --> 00:48:24,122
见过 他喜欢这里
Yeah, he liked it here.

789
00:48:24,174 --> 00:48:26,457
是其中一个老家伙 一直在吧台边
One of them older guys, never left the bar,

790
00:48:26,509 --> 00:48:28,176
等着妓女找他说话
just wait for the girl to walk up.

791
00:48:28,211 --> 00:48:29,761
谢谢
Thank you.

792
00:48:29,796 --> 00:48:32,430
知道他带谁回去过吗?
You know anyone he ever left with?

793
00:48:32,465 --> 00:48:34,799
呃 肯定有几个
Uh, a few of the girls here for sure,

794
00:48:34,851 --> 00:48:36,184
但我不会跟她们说话
but I wouldn't try talking to them.

795
00:48:36,219 --> 00:48:38,219
只会让她们惹上麻烦
You'd just get them into trouble.

796
00:48:42,025 --> 00:48:44,475
- 他喜欢男的吗?  - 更像是他喜欢看 
- He like boys?  - More like he likes to watch.

797
00:48:44,527 --> 00:48:47,695
让我和一个妞儿搞过一次 他就在角落里看
Had me and this girl go at it while he sat in the corner.

798
00:48:48,898 --> 00:48:50,698
你也上女人
You do girls.

799
00:48:50,733 --> 00:48:53,234
如果有需要的话 吸点儿粉
In a pinch. With the right medication.

800
00:49:00,577 --> 00:49:02,376
这个妞儿是谁?
Who's this girl?

801
00:49:05,715 --> 00:49:07,465
妈的
Fuck.

802
00:49:10,470 --> 00:49:11,803
她叫Tascha
Her name's Tascha.

803
00:49:11,838 --> 00:49:13,588
她是欧洲来的妞儿
She's one of them Euro tricks.

804
00:49:13,640 --> 00:49:16,007
最近没怎么出现
Hasn't been around lately.

805
00:49:16,059 --> 00:49:19,260
是那种高级妓女 参加私人派对的
One of those elite bitches, worked those private parties.

806
00:49:19,262 --> 00:49:21,179
什么样的派对?
What kind of parties?

807
00:49:21,231 --> 00:49:22,847
我也只是听说过
I just heard about them.

808
00:49:22,899 --> 00:49:25,600
豪华的 私密的 都是有钱人
Expensive, private, rich men.

809
00:49:26,853 --> 00:49:28,903
也许她找了个干爹
Maybe she found a sugar daddy.

810
00:49:34,828 --> 00:49:36,244
两倍量
Doubles.

811
00:49:42,168 --> 00:49:44,035
Frank 你看
You know, Frank,

812
00:49:44,087 --> 00:49:45,837
我不知道这是怎么回事
I don't know what this is,

813
00:49:45,872 --> 00:49:49,257
因为 这不是我的风格
but, look, I don't run things like that.

814
00:49:49,292 --> 00:49:50,625
我是说 谁还这么干?
I mean, shit, who does anymore?

815
00:49:50,627 --> 00:49:53,544
墨西哥人? 俄罗斯人?
Mexicans? Russians?

816
00:49:53,596 --> 00:49:56,180
是个好问题... 是谁?
That's a good question... who?

817
00:49:56,216 --> 00:49:58,549
这样整我对谁有好处?
Who has something to gain by trying to fuck with me?

818
00:49:58,635 --> 00:50:00,101
你觉得是我们中的一个?
You think it was someone here?

819
00:50:00,136 --> 00:50:02,220
对我们有什么好处?
What's in it?

820
00:50:02,272 --> 00:50:04,388
他的意思是
What he means is

821
00:50:04,440 --> 00:50:06,307
Frank 在你这儿还能得到什么好处呢?
what you got worth taking anymore, Frank?

822
00:50:06,359 --> 00:50:08,192
我的合伙人
My associate.

823
00:50:08,228 --> 00:50:09,944
名字是Ben Caspere
His name's Ben Caspere.

824
00:50:09,979 --> 00:50:12,446
他跟那个在你们的地盘上的
He was into that sweet Eastern Bloc pussy

825
00:50:12,482 --> 00:50:14,899
东欧的妓女有过来往
you all run between clubs.

826
00:50:14,951 --> 00:50:18,986
所以你们中的一些人也许认识他见过的女人
So some of you might have girls that know him.

827
00:50:18,988 --> 00:50:21,739
Daniel认识
Daniel here did.

828
00:50:21,791 --> 00:50:23,824
而我需要你们为我做的是
And what I need you to do now for me

829
00:50:23,910 --> 00:50:25,660
把话散出去
is put the word out.

830
00:50:25,662 --> 00:50:27,578
每个你们抢劫的嫖客
Any john you rob,

831
00:50:27,630 --> 00:50:30,498
每只跳蚤 每个在你的地毯上爬过的虱子
any flea, any tick crawls across your carpet,

832
00:50:30,500 --> 00:50:32,717
问问他们是否见过Ben Caspere
you ask them about Ben Caspere.

833
00:50:32,752 --> 00:50:34,752
找出谁在觊觎本来属于我的东西
You find out who wants what's mine.

834
00:50:35,889 --> 00:50:39,173
Frankie 我觉得你把我们
Frankie, I think you got us confused

835
00:50:39,175 --> 00:50:40,808
跟楼上那些贱人搞混了
with them bitches upstairs.

836
00:50:40,843 --> 00:50:43,427
感激你过去的帮忙
Appreciate our past dealings,

837
00:50:43,479 --> 00:50:45,563
不过是你自己放手不干的
but you're the one that left all that behind.

838
00:50:45,598 --> 00:50:48,316
这儿不再是你的地盘了
This ain't your club no more.

839
00:50:48,351 --> 00:50:50,234
那些日子已经过去了
Those days done been over.

840
00:50:50,270 --> 00:50:52,403
你很清楚的 对吗?
You're straight, right?

841
00:50:52,438 --> 00:50:54,772
怎么不去找警察呢?
Why don't you call a cop?

842
00:50:54,824 --> 00:50:57,325
给我站在原地
Stay where you fuckin' are.

843
00:50:59,078 --> 00:51:01,946
对了 我知道
Yeah, I know.

844
00:51:01,998 --> 00:51:04,532
你瞪着疯子一样的眼睛
You put them crazy eyes on

845
00:51:04,584 --> 00:51:07,368
以为会把人吓得尿裤子
and everybody's supposed to shit their pants.

846
00:51:07,420 --> 00:51:10,705
事实是 你不再是那样的人
Thing is, you ain't that thing no more

847
00:51:10,707 --> 00:51:13,257
再也不是了
what you used to was.

848
00:51:13,293 --> 00:51:15,009
他说的代表你们所有人吗?
He speak for all of you?

849
00:51:15,044 --> 00:51:17,295
我只代表我自己
I'm speaking for me.

850
00:51:17,347 --> 00:51:20,464
没错 你很高 但是真的不算什么
Yeah, you're tall, but you're really little,

851
00:51:20,516 --> 00:51:23,217
而且你老了
and you're old.

852
00:51:23,269 --> 00:51:26,854
喂 会议结束了
Yo, this meeting is over.

853
00:51:26,889 --> 00:51:28,889
你们这些混蛋可以滚出我的地盘了
Y'all motherfuckers get out of my place.

854
00:51:30,360 --> 00:51:32,059
等我把你的嘴唇撕掉
Will you talk this much

855
00:51:32,111 --> 00:51:35,479
看你还敢不敢这么多废话?
when I rip your fuckin' lip off?

856
00:51:38,067 --> 00:51:40,952
好吧 Frankie
All right, Frankie.

857
00:51:40,987 --> 00:51:42,570
想要练两下?
You wanna squab?

858
00:51:45,959 --> 00:51:48,242
你可以带着戒指
You can keep your rings on.

859
00:51:48,244 --> 00:51:49,744
对我来说都一样
Won't matter to me.

860
00:51:53,333 --> 00:51:54,415
好吧
All right.

861
00:52:19,942 --> 00:52:21,993
不!
No!

862
00:52:27,116 --> 00:52:29,617
我最讨厌的就是他妈的这种东西
I've always hated these fucking things.

863
00:52:29,619 --> 00:52:31,786
哪有这样跟世界打招呼的?
What kind of way is that to greet the world?

864
00:52:44,934 --> 00:52:47,768
我们听说你几周前辞掉了司机的工作
We heard you quit your job as a driver a couple weeks back.

865
00:52:47,804 --> 00:52:50,855
是的 他在照顾我 我病了
Yes, he took care of me. I was sick.

866
00:52:50,890 --> 00:52:53,808
他也不能整天坐在车里
And he couldn't take the sitting all day.

867
00:52:55,111 --> 00:52:57,228
是个好孩子
He's a good boy.

868
00:52:57,280 --> 00:52:58,646
你跟她一起住吗?
You live here with her?

869
00:52:58,648 --> 00:53:00,314
偶尔会来
Only sometimes.

870
00:53:00,316 --> 00:53:02,566
我跟几个朋友一起住
I got a place with friends.

871
00:53:02,652 --> 00:53:04,785
在你工作的地方有辆车被偷了
A car was stolen from where you work.

872
00:53:04,821 --> 00:53:06,454
他绝不会做那种事
He wouldn't do it.

873
00:53:06,489 --> 00:53:08,956
从小他就不是那种惹事的孩子
He ain't been in trouble since he was a little boy.

874
00:53:08,991 --> 00:53:11,992
喂 喂 我只是辞掉了工作
Yo, yo, all's I did was quit my job.

875
00:53:12,045 --> 00:53:14,328
腰椎有问题
Got a lumbar problem.

876
00:53:32,231 --> 00:53:34,014
是这辆车吗?
Is that the fucking car?

877
00:53:35,685 --> 00:53:38,018
嘿!
Hey!

878
00:53:38,104 --> 00:53:39,570
嘿 站住!
Hey, hold on!

879
00:53:39,605 --> 00:53:41,856
不许动! 警察!
Don't move! Police!

880
00:53:41,908 --> 00:53:43,858
妈的
Fuck.

881
00:54:06,048 --> 00:54:07,882
滚开!
Get outta here!

882
00:54:21,280 --> 00:54:22,897
停下 你个混蛋!
Stop, motherfucker!

883
00:54:24,901 --> 00:54:26,617
妈的!
Fuck!

884
00:54:26,652 --> 00:54:29,120
噢! 都烧起来了!
Oh! You're gonna burn it all!

885
00:54:35,711 --> 00:54:37,244
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.

886
00:54:53,229 --> 00:54:55,729
啊! 天啊!
Ah! God damn it!

887
00:54:55,765 --> 00:54:57,348
哦 糟了!
Oh, fuck!

888
00:54:57,400 --> 00:54:58,315
我的肋骨
My fucking ribs.

889
00:54:58,351 --> 00:55:01,185
就是他 绝对是他
That was him. That was fucking him.

890
00:55:01,237 --> 00:55:04,772
妈的
Fuck.

891
00:55:12,031 --> 00:55:14,331
谢谢你
Thank you.

892
00:55:14,367 --> 00:55:18,836
你想谢谢我 告诉我州里有我什么情报
You wanna thank me, tell me what state has on me.

893
00:55:26,629 --> 00:55:28,546
我不知道
I don't know.

894
00:55:51,454 --> 00:55:54,488
我在等你
I waited for you.

895
00:56:03,165 --> 00:56:04,498
发生了什么?
What happened?

896
00:56:32,578 --> 00:56:35,079
我们该和好了
We should make up.

897
00:56:36,666 --> 00:56:38,532
我觉得...
I thought...

898
00:56:40,536 --> 00:56:42,586
我一直没睡着
I stayed up.

899
00:56:51,514 --> 00:56:53,714
你想要聊聊吗?
Do you wanna talk?

900
00:57:07,313 --> 00:57:09,280
明天吧
Maybe tomorrow.

901
00:57:32,521 --> 00:57:37,891
# 迟早你都会找到释放的方式 #
# in time you find your way to release #

902
00:57:37,927 --> 00:57:43,631
# 然后它又消失不见 #
# and then it goes away again #

903
00:57:43,666 --> 00:57:49,637
# 你曾经最强大的敌人 #
# what had been the strongest force against you #

904
00:57:49,672 --> 00:57:55,709
# 变成你唯一的朋友 #
# becomes your only friend #

905
00:57:59,548 --> 00:58:02,716
# 你也只能一笑而过 #
# you can't help but laugh #

906
00:58:02,752 --> 00:58:05,152
# 我拥有了你的灵魂 #
# and I own your soul #

907
00:58:05,187 --> 00:58:10,958
# 一个被人唾弃的身影 #
# a shadow unwanted by any on earth #

908
00:58:10,993 --> 00:58:17,031
# 我们因你哭泣而欢喜 #
# most of us rejoice at your awful crying #

909
00:58:17,066 --> 00:58:23,037
# 我们的存在让你后悔来到这个世界 #
# we live to force you to regret your own birth #

910
00:58:25,675 --> 00:58:34,057
# 爱的天平已经失衡 #
# the balance of love is shifting #

