1
00:00:00,520 --> 00:00:01,880
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

2
00:00:00,620 --> 00:00:01,980
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

3
00:00:00,520 --> 00:00:01,780
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

4
00:00:00,660 --> 00:00:01,930
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

5
00:00:00,760 --> 00:00:02,030
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

6
00:00:00,560 --> 00:00:01,830
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

7
00:00:00,800 --> 00:00:01,980
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

8
00:00:00,900 --> 00:00:02,080
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

9
00:00:00,700 --> 00:00:01,880
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

10
00:00:00,950 --> 00:00:02,030
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

11
00:00:01,050 --> 00:00:02,130
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

12
00:00:00,850 --> 00:00:01,930
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

13
00:00:01,090 --> 00:00:02,080
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

14
00:00:01,190 --> 00:00:02,180
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

15
00:00:00,990 --> 00:00:01,980
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

16
00:00:01,230 --> 00:00:02,130
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

17
00:00:01,330 --> 00:00:02,230
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

18
00:00:01,130 --> 00:00:02,030
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

19
00:00:01,380 --> 00:00:02,180
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

20
00:00:01,480 --> 00:00:02,280
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

21
00:00:01,280 --> 00:00:02,080
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

22
00:00:00,520 --> 00:00:01,280
{\an5}{\pos(146,217)}0,0,0,fx,学习

23
00:00:01,280 --> 00:00:01,730
{\an5}{\pos(146,217)}0,0,0,fx,学习

24
00:00:01,730 --> 00:00:05,740
{\an5}{\pos(146,217)}0,0,0,fx,学习

25
00:00:01,530 --> 00:00:02,430
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

26
00:00:01,630 --> 00:00:02,530
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

27
00:00:01,430 --> 00:00:02,330
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

28
00:00:01,680 --> 00:00:02,580
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

29
00:00:01,780 --> 00:00:02,680
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

30
00:00:01,580 --> 00:00:02,480
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

31
00:00:01,830 --> 00:00:02,730
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

32
00:00:01,930 --> 00:00:02,830
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

33
00:00:01,730 --> 00:00:02,630
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

34
00:00:00,520 --> 00:00:01,730
{\an5}{\pos(192,217)}0,0,0,fx,分享

35
00:00:01,730 --> 00:00:02,180
{\an5}{\pos(192,217)}0,0,0,fx,分享

36
00:00:02,180 --> 00:00:06,010
{\an5}{\pos(192,217)}0,0,0,fx,分享

37
00:00:01,920 --> 00:00:02,820
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

38
00:00:02,020 --> 00:00:02,920
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

39
00:00:01,820 --> 00:00:02,720
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

40
00:00:02,010 --> 00:00:02,910
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

41
00:00:02,110 --> 00:00:03,010
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

42
00:00:01,910 --> 00:00:02,810
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

43
00:00:02,100 --> 00:00:03,000
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

44
00:00:02,200 --> 00:00:03,100
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

45
00:00:02,000 --> 00:00:02,900
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

46
00:00:02,190 --> 00:00:03,090
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

47
00:00:02,290 --> 00:00:03,190
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

48
00:00:02,090 --> 00:00:02,990
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

49
00:00:02,280 --> 00:00:03,180
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

50
00:00:02,380 --> 00:00:03,280
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

51
00:00:02,180 --> 00:00:03,080
{\an5}0,0,0,fx,m 5 0 b 2 0 0 2 0 5 b 0 8 2 10 5 10 b 8 10 10 8 10 5 b 10 2 8 0 5 0 m 5 2 b 6 0 9 2 8 4 b 7 6 4 4 5 2

52
00:00:00,520 --> 00:00:02,180
{\an5}{\pos(238,217)}0,0,0,fx,进步

53
00:00:02,180 --> 00:00:02,630
{\an5}{\pos(238,217)}0,0,0,fx,进步

54
00:00:02,630 --> 00:00:06,280
{\an5}{\pos(238,217)}0,0,0,fx,进步

55
00:00:06,290 --> 00:00:36,290
{\an7}{\pos(39.5,211)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14 

56
00:00:06,290 --> 00:00:36,290
{\pos(51.4,231.16)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 

57
00:00:06,290 --> 00:00:36,290
{\pos(27.7,188.26)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 

59
00:00:06,290 --> 00:00:11,290
{\an4}本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv

60
00:00:11,290 --> 00:00:16,290
{\an4}{\pos(57.12,210.56)}翻译   冰蓝     aaaBao

61
00:00:16,290 --> 00:00:21,290
{\an4}{\pos(57.12,210.56)}翻译  roaddog

62
00:00:21,290 --> 00:00:26,290
{\an4}{\pos(57.12,210.56)}校对  roaddog

63
00:00:26,290 --> 00:00:31,290
{\an4}时间轴 aaaBao

64
00:00:31,290 --> 00:00:36,290
{\an4}{\pos(57.12,210.56)}后期 斯人       总监 roaddog

65
00:00:36,290 --> 00:00:41,290
{\an4}{\pos(70,211.2)}打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息

66
00:00:36,290 --> 00:00:46,290
{\an7}{\pos(22.2,180.8)} m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340

67
00:00:04,930 --> 00:00:07,500
我看起来怎么样
So, how do I look?

68
00:00:07,690 --> 00:00:10,180
像是罗德里格斯特工
Like Special Agent Rodriguez.

69
00:00:11,490 --> 00:00:12,720
为什么穿西装啊
What's with the pantsuit?

70
00:00:13,150 --> 00:00:13,900
是不是因为今天是洗衣日
Is it laundry day 

71
00:00:13,910 --> 00:00:16,590
你的宽松运动裤都在洗衣机里
and all of your big sweatpants are in the wash?

72
00:00:16,660 --> 00:00:19,250
不  班吉随时都可能来
No. Benji's gonna get here any minute.

73
00:00:19,300 --> 00:00:20,780
难以置信你的小胖墩弟弟
I can't believe your chubby-wubby little brother

74
00:00:20,790 --> 00:00:23,290
要搬来旧金山为市长工作了
is moving to San Francisco to work for Mayor...

75
00:00:24,390 --> 00:00:26,520
约翰·比尔吗
John... Bill...

76
00:00:26,530 --> 00:00:27,630
艾德·李
Ed Lee. 

77
00:00:27,640 --> 00:00:29,470
艾德·李市长吗
Mayor Ed Lee?

78
00:00:30,550 --> 00:00:31,750
我想是吧
I suppose.

79
00:00:32,770 --> 00:00:34,130
总之  我穿成这样
Anyway, I'm dressed like this

80
00:00:34,140 --> 00:00:35,520
是因为我想让班吉知道
because I want Benji to know

81
00:00:35,520 --> 00:00:38,100
我在加伯  苏肯贝克和利兹公司工作
that I'm working at Garber, Stukenbaker and Rizz.

82
00:00:38,390 --> 00:00:39,390
你又复职了吗
You got your old job back?

83
00:00:39,390 --> 00:00:40,920
没有  但是那听起来可信吗
No. But did that sound believable?

84
00:00:40,930 --> 00:00:43,620
因为他不能知道我丢了工作  加比
Because he cannot know that I lost my job, Gabi, okay?

85
00:00:43,630 --> 00:00:46,850
我们是罗德里格斯家族  我们工作  成功
We're Rodriguezes. We work. We succeed.

86
00:00:46,860 --> 00:00:47,950
我们不会在大中午
We do not play "Candy Crush"

87
00:00:47,960 --> 00:00:49,240
一边昏昏欲睡地看《冰道卡车司机》
while falling asleep in the middle of the day

88
00:00:49,250 --> 00:00:50,750
一边玩《糖果粉碎》
watching Ice Road Truckers.

89
00:00:51,950 --> 00:00:54,180
你会帮我假装我还没丢工作吗
So, will you help me pretend like I still have my job?

90
00:00:54,840 --> 00:00:55,850
当然啦
Please...

91
00:00:55,860 --> 00:00:58,190
我可是假装小镇的镇长
I am the mayor of pretend town.

92
00:00:58,550 --> 00:01:00,550
你可以叫我艾德·李
The Ed Lee, if you will.

93
00:01:01,180 --> 00:01:03,030
天啊  我真是等不及我们三个
Oh, man. I can't wait till the three of us 

94
00:01:03,030 --> 00:01:04,310
团聚的时候了
are back together again.

95
00:01:04,320 --> 00:01:05,920
我给他做了他最爱的晚餐
Oh, and I made him his favorite dinner...

96
00:01:05,930 --> 00:01:08,100
做成小恐龙形状的鸡柳条
Chicken fingers shaped like little dinosaurs

97
00:01:08,110 --> 00:01:09,890
甜点是软糖蛋糕
and a fudgy cake for dessert.

98
00:01:09,900 --> 00:01:11,510
他不是十岁了  加比
You know, he's not 10 anymore, Gabi.

99
00:01:11,520 --> 00:01:12,620
我知道  但在我看来
Yeah, I know. But to me,

100
00:01:12,630 --> 00:01:15,380
他一直都是我的小胖墩班吉
he'll always be my little Benji, the Hut.

101
00:01:17,540 --> 00:01:18,820
他来了
That's him!

102
00:01:20,190 --> 00:01:21,560
班吉
Benji!

103
00:01:23,120 --> 00:01:24,310
班吉
Benji?

104
00:01:24,550 --> 00:01:25,710
你们好啊
Hey, guys!

105
00:01:26,120 --> 00:01:28,130
你问我为什么穿成这样吗
Why am I dressed like this you ask?

106
00:01:28,510 --> 00:01:29,670
因为我刚经历了
That's because I just returned

107
00:01:29,680 --> 00:01:32,060
严酷的一天  一直在进行股权交易
from a rigorous day of trading stock options

108
00:01:32,070 --> 00:01:34,110
对非常不称职的人大吼大叫
and yelling at woefully incompetent people.

109
00:01:34,830 --> 00:01:36,050
好吧
Okay then...

110
00:01:36,470 --> 00:01:37,930
你好啊  加比
Hey, Gabi!

111
00:01:40,110 --> 00:01:41,460
这是你为我做的吗
Aw, did you make that for me?

112
00:01:41,470 --> 00:01:43,750
是啊  我真想尝尝你
Yeah! Would I like a piece of that...

113
00:01:44,590 --> 00:01:47,440
我是说  你想尝尝我吗
I mean, would you like a piece of this?

114
00:01:47,850 --> 00:01:49,890
我的意思是  谁想尝一块...
What I'm saying is, who wants a piece...

115
00:01:50,750 --> 00:01:52,020
蛋糕
of cake?

116
00:02:11,130 --> 00:02:13,750
{\an8}饥饿的青春
第二季  第十四集

117
00:02:16,240 --> 00:02:17,460
早上好
Good morning.

118
00:02:18,520 --> 00:02:19,910
你在看着我睡觉吗
Were you watching me sleep?

119
00:02:20,630 --> 00:02:21,790
我吗
Me?

120
00:02:21,800 --> 00:02:24,330
不  我在忙着看...
No, no. I'm... I was too busy reading...

121
00:02:24,340 --> 00:02:25,830
对  跟我想的一样
Oh, yes. Just what I thought...

122
00:02:25,840 --> 00:02:28,110
二十一种必要的维生素和矿物质
21 essential vitamins and minerals.

123
00:02:29,970 --> 00:02:32,560
我吗  又升职了吗
Me? Another promotion?

124
00:02:32,570 --> 00:02:35,550
真是青云直上啊
Wow! This really is a meteoric rise!

125
00:02:37,330 --> 00:02:39,090
好  再见
Okay, okay. Bye.

126
00:02:39,780 --> 00:02:41,150
瞧瞧我姐姐
Look at my big sis...

127
00:02:41,160 --> 00:02:42,690
称霸商界
taking over the world!

128
00:02:42,930 --> 00:02:45,070
我的弟弟为市长工作呢
My little brother working for the Mayor!

129
00:02:45,080 --> 00:02:46,220
大名艾德·李
...Ed Lee.

130
00:02:47,500 --> 00:02:48,800
我知道很多事的
I know stuff.

131
00:02:50,170 --> 00:02:52,500
你知道怎么逃过顶头吗
Do you know how to get out of a noogie?

132
00:02:52,560 --> 00:02:55,070
不  班吉  不要
No, Benji! No!

133
00:02:56,800 --> 00:02:58,890
-我要去洗澡了  -我也是
- I'm gonna grab a shower. - Okay. Me, too.

134
00:02:59,440 --> 00:03:01,960
我是说等你洗完
I mean... you know, once you're out of it.

135
00:03:02,310 --> 00:03:04,550
除非...  我开玩笑啦
Unless, you know... I'm kidding!

136
00:03:05,910 --> 00:03:08,350
好  我要去...
Okay. Well, I am gonna go...

137
00:03:08,450 --> 00:03:11,020
街角的汽车店待一天了
hang out at the car dealership on the corner for the day.

138
00:03:11,180 --> 00:03:12,490
他们还有免费无线吗
They still have free wi-fi?

139
00:03:12,500 --> 00:03:14,720
还有甜甜圈呢  天啊
And donuts! Oh, my gosh! You know...

140
00:03:14,740 --> 00:03:16,920
说到美味的东西
Speaking of delicious things...

141
00:03:17,250 --> 00:03:19,970
你弟弟真是...
uh, your brother is really gotten all...

142
00:03:23,450 --> 00:03:24,640
懂吧
You know?

143
00:03:25,160 --> 00:03:26,210
不懂
No.

144
00:03:26,220 --> 00:03:29,340
我是说  我可以约他出去吗
What I'm saying is... what if I asked him out?

145
00:03:30,530 --> 00:03:31,840
你看上我弟弟了吗
Are you attracted to my brother?

146
00:03:31,850 --> 00:03:33,540
当然  你不是吗
Yeah! Aren't you?

147
00:03:35,540 --> 00:03:36,520
好吧
Okay.

148
00:03:36,530 --> 00:03:38,950
你最好是开玩笑  因为那太变态了
You better be kidding, because that would be sick.

149
00:03:38,960 --> 00:03:40,330
我们一起长大的
Okay? We grew up together.

150
00:03:40,340 --> 00:03:41,880
跟他约会就像是跟你自己的
Going out with him would be like going on a date 

151
00:03:41,890 --> 00:03:43,120
弟弟约会一样
with your own brother.

152
00:03:43,130 --> 00:03:45,610
不过我是在跟你弟弟约会
Uh, except I'd be dating your brother,

153
00:03:45,620 --> 00:03:47,980
我跟他没有任何亲戚关系
who I am not related to in any way.

154
00:03:48,940 --> 00:03:51,460
加比  你不能约我弟弟出去
Gabi, you cannot ask my brother out.

155
00:03:51,470 --> 00:03:53,680
我理解  为什么
I totally get it... Why?

156
00:03:53,690 --> 00:03:55,830
因为这很尴尬
Uh, well, because it's awkward,

157
00:03:55,840 --> 00:03:57,660
很奇怪  根本不可能
it's weird and it's just not going to happen.

158
00:03:57,670 --> 00:03:59,520
-所以...  -我们回头再聊
- So... - We'll talk about it later.

159
00:03:59,530 --> 00:04:00,630
拜拜
Bye!

160
00:04:04,090 --> 00:04:05,810
你还没走  真好
I'm glad I got you before you left.

161
00:04:05,860 --> 00:04:07,630
我刚收到市长办公室的邮件
I just got an e-mail from the mayor's office...

162
00:04:07,640 --> 00:04:09,960
他邀请员工今晚参加鸡尾酒派对
He invited his staff to a cocktail party tonight.

163
00:04:09,980 --> 00:04:11,180
想去吗
Wanna go?

164
00:04:14,020 --> 00:04:15,240
腹肌...
Abs...

165
00:04:15,250 --> 00:04:16,500
没问题
...solutely.

166
00:04:17,200 --> 00:04:19,060
我是说  不行  我是说...
I mean, no. I mean...

167
00:04:19,930 --> 00:04:22,510
等等  是你叫我跟你出去
Wait, you asked me to go with you.

168
00:04:22,520 --> 00:04:25,050
不是我叫你跟我出去
I didn't ask you to go with me.

169
00:04:25,840 --> 00:04:27,100
没错
That's right.

170
00:04:28,380 --> 00:04:30,360
那七点来接你好吗
So, pick you up at 7:00?

171
00:04:30,900 --> 00:04:32,340
你知道我家在哪...
You know where I live...

172
00:04:34,980 --> 00:04:36,350
目前为止
for now.

173
00:04:39,960 --> 00:04:41,910
我要在阳台上放个木制猫头鹰
I think I'm gonna get a wooden owl for the terrace...

174
00:04:42,070 --> 00:04:43,290
把这些鸟吓走
scare the birds away.

175
00:04:43,690 --> 00:04:44,870
我挺喜欢这些鸟
I like the birds.

176
00:04:44,880 --> 00:04:47,030
它们把残渣都吃了  我不用擦桌子
They clean up the crumbs so I don't have to.

177
00:04:47,960 --> 00:04:49,050
逮着你们了
Caught-cha!

178
00:04:49,060 --> 00:04:51,240
我知道你们在讨论什么
I know what you're talking about!

179
00:04:51,310 --> 00:04:53,060
我深表怀疑
I sincerely doubt that.

180
00:04:53,960 --> 00:04:56,590
你们在讨论我的单身派对
You're talking about my bachelor party.

181
00:04:57,380 --> 00:04:59,970
你们真够守口如瓶的
You guys are so secretive!

182
00:05:00,370 --> 00:05:03,680
要是几个月前我没告诉你们确切日期
If I didn't tell you months ago the exact date to throw it,

183
00:05:03,690 --> 00:05:05,840
我都不知道派对就要开了
I'd have no idea it was even happening.

184
00:05:07,610 --> 00:05:08,620
你的单身派对嘛
Is it happening!

185
00:05:08,620 --> 00:05:10,440
没错  就是这事
Yeah! It sure is!

186
00:05:10,750 --> 00:05:12,560
什么时候办来着
Um, when is it happening again?

187
00:05:13,390 --> 00:05:14,630
你们真逗
You guys are so funny.

188
00:05:14,640 --> 00:05:16,840
-明知道就是今晚  -今晚吗
- You know it's tonight. - Tonight?

189
00:05:17,560 --> 00:05:20,420
对  埃兰飞去拉斯维加斯参加他的单身派对了
Yeah, Alan just flew to Vegas for his bachelor party

190
00:05:20,430 --> 00:05:22,520
我也计划同时办我的
and I planned mine for the same time.

191
00:05:22,700 --> 00:05:25,290
{\an8}结合音乐  科技与戏剧的梦幻表演秀
在全美多个城市上演

192
00:05:22,700 --> 00:05:25,290
他们给埃兰买了蓝人秀的前排票
They got Alan front row tickets for Blue Man Group...

193
00:05:25,350 --> 00:05:27,410
真奇怪  因为他是色盲
Which is weird because he's colorblind.

194
00:05:29,120 --> 00:05:31,030
我已经跟埃兰说了
I already told Alan

195
00:05:31,040 --> 00:05:33,100
你们的点子会更棒
that yours will be way better!

196
00:05:33,330 --> 00:05:35,190
等不及看看是什么了  棒耶
I can't wait to see what it is! Yay!

197
00:05:37,570 --> 00:05:38,840
一定超赞的
It's gonna be so good!

198
00:05:39,630 --> 00:05:40,810
我们得快点想出点子来
We've got to come up with something fast

199
00:05:40,820 --> 00:05:41,870
不然他一定会勃然大怒
or he's gonna be devastated.

200
00:05:41,880 --> 00:05:42,990
还会怀恨在心
And vengeful.

201
00:05:43,000 --> 00:05:44,600
那次我忘了他的半岁生日
When I forgot his half birthday,

202
00:05:44,610 --> 00:05:45,800
他用钥匙刮了我的车
he keyed my car.

203
00:05:47,970 --> 00:05:49,530
我不知道要怎么办同志单身派对
I don't know how to throw a gay bachelor party.

204
00:05:49,530 --> 00:05:50,800
他们通常在派对上做什么
I mean, what do they even do there?

205
00:05:50,810 --> 00:05:52,450
我觉得我们可能需要很多闪粉
I'm guessing we're gonna need a lot of glitter.

206
00:05:52,560 --> 00:05:53,690
加比
Oh, Gabi... 

207
00:05:54,810 --> 00:05:55,760
我想问一下...
question...

208
00:05:55,770 --> 00:05:59,090
你能帮我做个男人屁股形状的蛋糕吗
Do you think you can bake me a cake that looks like a guy's butt?

209
00:06:00,410 --> 00:06:02,440
行啊  但你确定早餐要吃这个吗
Yeah, but are you sure that's what you want for breakfast?

210
00:06:03,500 --> 00:06:04,050
不是给我的
It's not for me.

211
00:06:04,060 --> 00:06:05,390
是给今晚艾略特单身派对用的
It's for Elliot's bachelor party tonight.

212
00:06:05,400 --> 00:06:06,910
好的  没问题
Yeah. You got it.

213
00:06:06,920 --> 00:06:09,140
尤兰达  有件事我能听听你的意见吗
Uh, Yolanda, can I get your advice on something?

214
00:06:10,160 --> 00:06:13,270
索菲亚要我别勾搭她无敌帅气的弟弟班吉...
Sofia asked me not to go out with her smoking-hot brother Benji...

215
00:06:13,280 --> 00:06:14,720
所以我答应了不会约他出去
So I said I wouldn't ask him out.

216
00:06:14,730 --> 00:06:16,680
但当她今天假装去上班后...
But then when she left to go to her fake job...

217
00:06:16,690 --> 00:06:18,940
他约我出去  这样的话...
He asked me out. So that's like...

218
00:06:19,070 --> 00:06:20,580
就能去了  对吗
totally cool, right?

219
00:06:21,360 --> 00:06:22,600
是的
Yeah!

220
00:06:22,610 --> 00:06:25,670
跟他只出去一次没关系
There's no harm with going out with him one time.

221
00:06:26,050 --> 00:06:28,200
买东西前不都得先试试嘛
You gotta try it before you buy it.

222
00:06:30,230 --> 00:06:32,070
我能试四次吗
Can I try it four times?

223
00:06:37,910 --> 00:06:39,850
好  我们搞定场地了
Yes! All right, we have a venue.

224
00:06:39,860 --> 00:06:41,600
我问了埃兰那家KTV的经理
I asked the manager of Alan's karaoke bar 

225
00:06:41,610 --> 00:06:43,060
她说我们今晚可以用那里
and she said we could use it for tonight.

226
00:06:43,070 --> 00:06:43,770
太棒了
That's great!

227
00:06:43,780 --> 00:06:45,140
我准备了许多小吃
And I made a ton of appetizers,

228
00:06:45,150 --> 00:06:46,210
都是从那超火的博客...
all from this cool blog...

229
00:06:46,220 --> 00:06:47,810
"娜塔莎的厨房"上学来的
natashaskitchen.com.

230
00:06:47,880 --> 00:06:49,380
你该付她工钱才对
You should be paying her.

231
00:06:49,690 --> 00:06:51,760
不  扯远了  还是付我工钱吧
Nope. Too far. Don't do that. Keeping paying me.

232
00:06:53,650 --> 00:06:58,080
你好  "就要改姓  也许不用改
Oh! Hi, Mister "about to change his last name, or maybe not,

233
00:06:58,090 --> 00:07:00,550
我也不知道同志怎么办"先生
I don't know how it works with the gays."

234
00:07:02,370 --> 00:07:05,470
你好  "每个情景都要想出一个昵称
Hey, Miss "Comes up with a nickname for every occasion,

235
00:07:05,480 --> 00:07:07,380
烦死人了"小姐
and it's really irritating."

236
00:07:09,290 --> 00:07:11,890
这铃声真萌  你从哪下的
Ooh, cute ring tone. How do I get that?

237
00:07:12,200 --> 00:07:15,720
同志会用一个叫"好基友"的同志约会应用
You be gay and you have "Yo Fellas," the gay dating app.

238
00:07:15,730 --> 00:07:17,580
如果周围有人看上你了  就会提示
It alerts you when there's a match nearby.

239
00:07:17,860 --> 00:07:19,200
等等  你怎么会用"好基友"
Wait, why do you have Yo Fellas?

240
00:07:19,210 --> 00:07:20,580
你还打算结婚的  对吗
You are still getting married, right?

241
00:07:20,590 --> 00:07:21,360
我和尤兰达
I mean, Yolanda and I 

242
00:07:21,370 --> 00:07:24,020
策划你的单身派对花了一...个月呢
have been planning your bachelor party all morn...th.

243
00:07:25,260 --> 00:07:27,330
是的  婚礼照常
Yes, the wedding's on.

244
00:07:27,340 --> 00:07:29,170
我只是还没把这个应用删掉
I just haven't deleted the app.

245
00:07:29,180 --> 00:07:32,330
不是为了猎艳  只是为知道我还有市场
It's not like I meet anyone. It's just nice to know I could.

246
00:07:32,390 --> 00:07:33,600
这就像汽车保险
It's like car insurance.

247
00:07:33,610 --> 00:07:35,800
你从来不会用  但它让你安心
You never use it, but it gives you peace of mind.

248
00:07:36,070 --> 00:07:39,140
可我没有汽车保险  依旧很安心啊
But I don't have car insurance and I still have peace of mind.

249
00:07:43,070 --> 00:07:44,530
是大楼的管道工
It's the building's plumber.

250
00:07:44,580 --> 00:07:46,570
他才别想碰我的管子[老二]
He ain't getting anywhere near my pipes.

251
00:07:53,050 --> 00:07:54,380
你好  我找加比
Hi. I'm here for Gabi.

252
00:07:55,350 --> 00:07:56,590
她死了
She died.

253
00:07:58,960 --> 00:08:00,250
我叫尤兰达
I'm Yolanda.

254
00:08:01,220 --> 00:08:04,220
-班吉  你好帅  -谢谢
- Hey, Benji. Wow, you look great. - Thanks.

255
00:08:04,230 --> 00:08:06,350
但你在我身边  没人会注意到我的
But nobody's gonna look at me when I'm walking with you.

256
00:08:07,490 --> 00:08:08,890
不如你先去等电梯
Why don't you go push the elevator button,

257
00:08:08,900 --> 00:08:10,290
我拿一下包
I'm gonna grab my purse.

258
00:08:13,010 --> 00:08:15,060
好吧  不用试我就想买他
Okay, I don't have to try him before I buy him.

259
00:08:15,070 --> 00:08:16,980
他太赞了  我要怎么办
He's amazing. What am I gonna do?

260
00:08:17,430 --> 00:08:19,310
找个新的闺蜜
Get yourself a new best friend.

261
00:08:20,930 --> 00:08:23,180
因为他好帅
'Cause he is fine!

262
00:08:32,990 --> 00:08:35,830
不得了  今晚"好基友"有得热闹了
Damn! Yo Fellas is blowing up tonight.

263
00:08:36,770 --> 00:08:38,390
搬来旧金山真让人高兴
So glad I moved to San Francisco.

264
00:08:42,240 --> 00:08:43,850
-这件衣服真性感  -谢谢
- Sexy outfit. - Oh, thanks. 

265
00:08:43,860 --> 00:08:46,120
我都忘记买过这衣服了  一直藏在柜子里
I forgot I had it. It was hiding in my closet.

266
00:08:57,990 --> 00:09:00,170
乔什  你确定要这样装饰吗
Josh, are you sure about this decor?

267
00:09:00,180 --> 00:09:02,620
对单身派对是不是太正式了
Don't you think it's too formal for a bachelor party?

268
00:09:02,630 --> 00:09:06,030
相信我  艾略特会喜欢"只戴黑领结"的
Uh, trust me. Elliot's gonna love "black tie only".

269
00:09:07,240 --> 00:09:11,680
只戴黑领结的是他们啊
Oh! They're the ones wearing the black tie!

270
00:09:12,660 --> 00:09:13,980
厉害[摸]
Nice touch!

271
00:09:14,360 --> 00:09:16,610
说到这  我能摸一把吗
Speaking of which... am I allowed to?

272
00:09:18,710 --> 00:09:20,540
-难以置信  -什么
- I don't believe this! - What?

273
00:09:20,980 --> 00:09:22,280
又有人说不能来
We got another "No."

274
00:09:22,490 --> 00:09:24,220
山姆"不能来"  布鲁斯"不能来"
Sam, no. Bruce, no.

275
00:09:24,270 --> 00:09:26,300
不能来  不能来
No. No. No.

276
00:09:26,590 --> 00:09:27,800
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?

277
00:09:28,140 --> 00:09:30,060
让艾略特变得不毒舌吗
Give Elliot a better personality?

278
00:09:30,220 --> 00:09:32,920
不  我们等到最后才通知  现在没人能来
No, we wait until the last minute and now no one can come.

279
00:09:33,450 --> 00:09:35,340
艾略特会知道是我们忘了办派对
Elliot's gonna know this was our fault that we forgot

280
00:09:35,350 --> 00:09:37,330
想哄好他可不止一座钱宁·塔图姆冰雕
and it's gonna take more than a Channing Tatum ice sculpture

281
00:09:37,340 --> 00:09:38,430
那么简单了
to cheer him up.

282
00:09:40,260 --> 00:09:42,230
我有主意了  手机给我
I got an idea. Give me your phone.

283
00:09:45,280 --> 00:09:48,270
恭喜  你注册"好基友"了
Congratulations, you're on Yo Fellas.

284
00:09:49,510 --> 00:09:50,360
什么
What?

285
00:09:50,370 --> 00:09:52,570
我用你的照片
I'm making a Yo Fellas profile

286
00:09:52,580 --> 00:09:56,290
建了"好基友"账号  提醒周围每个同志
with your photo and alerting every gay man on there,

287
00:09:56,300 --> 00:09:58,820
你要办派对  酒水免费
that you're throwing a party with free booze.

288
00:09:58,830 --> 00:10:01,140
不  不行
Uh, no. No, no, you're not.

289
00:10:01,630 --> 00:10:02,850
那你去告诉艾略特
Then you tell Elliot

290
00:10:02,860 --> 00:10:05,520
我们搞砸了  没人来他的派对
that we screwed up and no one's coming to his party.

291
00:10:07,530 --> 00:10:08,890
拍点我裸上身的
Get a couple of me shirtless.

292
00:10:09,180 --> 00:10:10,290
我想也是
I thought so.

293
00:10:19,150 --> 00:10:20,370
索菲亚
Sofia?

294
00:10:21,450 --> 00:10:22,690
在吗
Hello?

295
00:10:24,680 --> 00:10:27,210
她一定是还在上那重要的班
She must still be at her very important job.

296
00:10:27,650 --> 00:10:28,790
胡说
Rats!

297
00:10:28,800 --> 00:10:30,540
谢谢你今晚陪我去
Thank you so much for coming with me tonight.

298
00:10:30,550 --> 00:10:32,520
随时奉陪啦
Oh, for you anything.

299
00:10:32,820 --> 00:10:34,190
我渴了
I'm thirsty.

300
00:10:34,640 --> 00:10:35,870
你想喝水吗
You want a water?

301
00:10:36,270 --> 00:10:37,880
你确定不想喝些有劲的
You sure you don't want something stronger,

302
00:10:37,890 --> 00:10:39,700
好酩酊大醉  酒后失态
so you can get drunk and make bad decisions

303
00:10:39,710 --> 00:10:41,590
变成最棒的政客吗
and become the best politician ever?

304
00:10:43,030 --> 00:10:44,760
你还是那么幽默
You're still so funny!

305
00:10:46,460 --> 00:10:47,540
说实话
To be honest...

306
00:10:47,550 --> 00:10:49,420
你是我第一个动心的女生
you were the first girl I ever had a crush on.

307
00:10:49,430 --> 00:10:50,700
真的吗
Really?

308
00:10:50,820 --> 00:10:52,040
也是最后一个
And the last.

309
00:10:52,590 --> 00:10:54,600
因为...  加比
Because Gabi...

310
00:10:55,860 --> 00:10:57,320
我有话要跟你说
there's something I have to tell you.

311
00:10:57,330 --> 00:11:00,030
我也有话要跟你说
Oh, there's something I have to tell you, too!

312
00:11:01,500 --> 00:11:02,710
怎么回事
What the hell?

313
00:11:03,210 --> 00:11:06,200
我忙了一天合并收购回来
I come home from a day of mergers and acquisitions

314
00:11:06,210 --> 00:11:08,380
却发现你在跟我弟弟合体吗
to find you merging with my brother?

315
00:11:09,530 --> 00:11:12,420
我噎住了  班吉在给我人工呼吸
Well, I was choking and Benji was giving me mouth-to-mouth!

316
00:11:12,430 --> 00:11:13,690
噎住不是这么急救的
That's not what you do for choking!

317
00:11:13,700 --> 00:11:15,150
噎住不是这么急救的
That's not what you do for choking!

318
00:11:16,620 --> 00:11:17,720
难以置信  加比
I can't believe-- Gabi,

319
00:11:17,720 --> 00:11:19,690
我说了不要跟我弟弟出去
I told you not to go out with my brother...

320
00:11:19,690 --> 00:11:21,530
你还跟我对着干
and you do the exact opposite.

321
00:11:21,540 --> 00:11:23,770
实际上  你是说不要约他出去
Actually, you told me not to ask him out 

322
00:11:23,780 --> 00:11:25,230
是他约我出去的  所以...
and he asked me out, so--

323
00:11:25,240 --> 00:11:27,160
-都一样  -是吗
- So... it's the same thing! - Is it?

324
00:11:27,170 --> 00:11:28,500
当然
Uh, yes!

325
00:11:28,960 --> 00:11:30,490
你发现了漏洞
Just because you found this loophole,

326
00:11:30,500 --> 00:11:32,220
也不代表就能背着我
doesn't mean you can go behind my back

327
00:11:32,230 --> 00:11:34,130
和我弟弟约会  这样不对
and date my brother. It's not okay.

328
00:11:34,140 --> 00:11:35,520
说真的  索菲亚
Seriously, Sofia...

329
00:11:35,590 --> 00:11:37,970
-不是你想的那样  -好  那是什么样
- It's not what you think! - Okay, then what is it?

330
00:11:41,080 --> 00:11:42,320
知道吗
You know what?

331
00:11:42,330 --> 00:11:43,780
这让我好紧张
This is stressing me out.

332
00:11:45,010 --> 00:11:46,600
你们家周围有甜甜圈店吗
Is there a donut shop around here?

333
00:11:48,520 --> 00:11:49,900
难以置信
I can't believe you.

334
00:11:50,260 --> 00:11:52,240
说真的  索菲亚  我不知道你为什么生气
Seriously, Sofia, I don't understand what your problem is.

335
00:11:52,250 --> 00:11:53,600
如果班吉是我在酒吧遇见的
I mean, if I met Benji at a bar...

336
00:11:53,610 --> 00:11:55,250
你肯定鼓励我去追
you'd totally tell me to go for it.

337
00:11:55,260 --> 00:11:56,390
他那么性感
I mean, he's hot...

338
00:11:56,400 --> 00:11:58,860
闻起来香喷喷  我好想咬...
He smells good, and I want to bite his--

339
00:11:59,870 --> 00:12:01,450
你看吧  就是这样
See! See, it's happening already.

340
00:12:01,450 --> 00:12:04,100
我就不想听到这话  加比
This is exactly what I didn't want to hear, Gabi.

341
00:12:04,100 --> 00:12:05,020
我们分享一切秘密
We share everything 

342
00:12:05,020 --> 00:12:07,010
但我不想听到我弟弟的...
and I don't want to hear about my brother's...

343
00:12:07,010 --> 00:12:08,180
一切
everything.

344
00:12:08,520 --> 00:12:10,640
我不会说一切的
I'm not gonna tell you everything.

345
00:12:10,640 --> 00:12:13,340
我保证  除了我觉得他好性感
I promise, except I think he's so hot!

346
00:12:13,490 --> 00:12:15,920
加比  你看谁都是真命天子
God, Gabi, with you everybody's the one.

347
00:12:15,920 --> 00:12:17,520
乔什是  库珀是
Josh is the one, Cooper's the one.

348
00:12:17,520 --> 00:12:19,890
-现在班吉也是了吗  -你也觉得吗
- now Benji is the one? - So you see it, too?

349
00:12:20,790 --> 00:12:22,470
天啊
Oh, my god!

350
00:12:22,470 --> 00:12:24,320
否则都那么多年了  他怎么
Why else would he come back into my life

351
00:12:24,320 --> 00:12:25,720
又回到我人生里
after all of these years?

352
00:12:25,720 --> 00:12:27,400
他来看姐姐啊
To visit his sister!

353
00:12:27,810 --> 00:12:28,500
说真的  加比
Seriously, Gabi, 

354
00:12:28,500 --> 00:12:30,910
你毁了自己的一切感情
you screw up every single relationship you're in.

355
00:12:30,970 --> 00:12:32,210
还想毁了我们的吗
Are you willing to screw up ours?

356
00:12:32,210 --> 00:12:33,520
真的吗  我和你弟弟约会
Really? You think me dating your brother

357
00:12:33,520 --> 00:12:35,030
会毁了我们的友情吗
is gonna screw up our relationship?

358
00:12:35,030 --> 00:12:38,410
-没错  -那我们就来实践一下好了
- Yes! - Well, I think it's time we test that theory out!

359
00:12:50,090 --> 00:12:53,050
-这比我想得顺利多了  -没错
- This is going better than I expected! - Yeah!

360
00:12:53,700 --> 00:12:55,270
我还真能塞
I can really pack 'em in!

361
00:12:55,580 --> 00:12:57,310
这话可别大声说
Be careful how loud you say that.

362
00:13:00,550 --> 00:13:02,380
看看这些帅哥们
Check out all these hotties.

363
00:13:02,390 --> 00:13:05,340
这派对太棒了
This is the best party ever!

364
00:13:07,700 --> 00:13:08,860
不过好奇怪
But it's weird...

365
00:13:08,860 --> 00:13:10,830
都没看见我的朋友
I haven't seen any of my friends.

366
00:13:11,420 --> 00:13:13,950
他们在  就在这
No, they're here. They're around.

367
00:13:14,460 --> 00:13:16,730
没错  谁会错过
Yeah, no one wanted to miss the chance 

368
00:13:16,730 --> 00:13:19,930
和旧金山最帅单身汉派对的机会呢
to party with San Francisco's... sexiest bachelor.

369
00:13:20,140 --> 00:13:22,600
说太对了
No, they didn't.

370
00:13:22,770 --> 00:13:24,370
容我失陪一下
Now if you'll excuse me...

371
00:13:24,370 --> 00:13:27,760
老娘要来个壮汉下酒
mama needs a stiff one... and a drink!

372
00:13:30,390 --> 00:13:31,830
尤兰达
Oh! Yolanda...

373
00:13:31,910 --> 00:13:33,930
-你在这里  -加比  你怎么来了
- There you are! - Gabi, what are you doing here?

374
00:13:34,030 --> 00:13:36,060
我真的需要再听听你的建议
I really need to talk to you. I need your advice again.

375
00:13:36,060 --> 00:13:39,120
索菲亚和我为跟班吉约会大吵了一架
Sofia and I got in a huge fight about me going out with Benji,

376
00:13:39,120 --> 00:13:41,550
她觉得这会毁了我们的友情
because she thinks it's gonna ruin our friendship.

377
00:13:41,550 --> 00:13:42,530
我觉得这不公平
And I really don't think that's fair

378
00:13:42,530 --> 00:13:44,300
班吉或许就是我真命天子呢
because I think Benji could be the one!

379
00:13:44,640 --> 00:13:45,930
真可惜
That's a shame!

380
00:13:46,450 --> 00:13:47,570
为什么
Why?

381
00:14:01,830 --> 00:14:03,550
-班吉  -加比
- Benji. - Gabi?

382
00:14:09,200 --> 00:14:10,540
怎么回事
What's going on?

383
00:14:11,520 --> 00:14:13,220
-我是同志  -我猜到了
- I'm gay. - I gathered.

384
00:14:14,470 --> 00:14:16,360
之前我就想告诉你  但真的很难开口
I tried telling you earlier, but it was really hard

385
00:14:16,360 --> 00:14:18,300
我猜我误导你了
and somehow I guess I led you on.

386
00:14:18,670 --> 00:14:20,300
因为你跟我约会
By inviting me on a date!

387
00:14:20,300 --> 00:14:21,650
我没说过那是"约会"
I never called it a "date."

388
00:14:21,880 --> 00:14:23,570
只是说"你想跟我出去吗"
I called it a "wanna come with me?"

389
00:14:24,710 --> 00:14:26,850
是啊  真是一点也不会误会
Oh, yeah! I don't know how that could be confusing.

390
00:14:27,940 --> 00:14:30,250
那是我第一次工作聚会  我没有熟人
It was my first work party and I didn't know anyone.

391
00:14:30,350 --> 00:14:32,320
想跟能让我安心相处的人一起去
I wanted to go with someone I was comfortable with.

392
00:14:32,540 --> 00:14:34,000
你就像是我姐姐
You're like a big sister to me. 

393
00:14:34,000 --> 00:14:35,980
真是越来越棒了
Yeah. This just keeps getting better and better.

394
00:14:36,770 --> 00:14:37,750
加比
Gabi...

395
00:14:37,750 --> 00:14:39,400
抱歉我误导了你
I'm sorry I gave you the wrong impression.

396
00:14:39,540 --> 00:14:41,370
只是我还没跟任何人出柜
I'm just not out to anyone yet.

397
00:14:41,480 --> 00:14:44,550
这很难  我们家是虔诚的天主教徒
It's not easy. We were raised strict Catholics.

398
00:14:44,550 --> 00:14:45,880
索菲亚还是处女呢
Sofia's still a virgin.

399
00:14:48,240 --> 00:14:49,430
是啊
Yeah, well...

400
00:14:50,030 --> 00:14:52,160
你家真是太多秘密了
so many secrets in this family.

401
00:14:52,690 --> 00:14:54,200
知道吗  你说得对
You know what? You're right...

402
00:14:54,390 --> 00:14:55,570
我受够这些秘密了
and I'm sick of them!

403
00:14:55,600 --> 00:14:56,870
我今晚就跟索菲亚出柜
I'm telling Sofia tonight.

404
00:14:57,320 --> 00:14:58,840
是该这样
As-- as you should.

405
00:14:59,550 --> 00:15:00,740
不过等到我跟她说
But right after I tell her that

406
00:15:00,740 --> 00:15:03,500
我觉得不该重色轻友以后
my friendship with her is more important than you.

407
00:15:04,530 --> 00:15:06,550
行了  少来
Oh, come on. Don't be so hurt.

408
00:15:06,550 --> 00:15:08,560
你刚才还说把我当姐姐
Okay? You just called me your big sister when...

409
00:15:08,880 --> 00:15:10,340
姐的分明是你
you're the big sister.

410
00:15:10,510 --> 00:15:11,980
加比  为什么
Gabi, come on!

411
00:15:11,990 --> 00:15:13,880
我既然出了柜  肯定要让我姐姐知道
Now that it's out. I want my sister to know.

412
00:15:14,350 --> 00:15:15,930
我不想再等了
I mean, I can't wait any longer.

413
00:15:16,240 --> 00:15:17,070
是吗  班吉
Really, Benji?

414
00:15:17,070 --> 00:15:19,020
因为你要知道  到现在为止
Because you know, up until this very moment

415
00:15:19,020 --> 00:15:20,400
你在柜里藏了那么久
you were so far in the closet...

416
00:15:20,530 --> 00:15:22,090
都能拍《纳尼亚传奇》了
you were in Narnia.

417
00:15:35,350 --> 00:15:36,530
干什么
What happened?

418
00:15:36,870 --> 00:15:39,810
我跑了好多甜甜圈店
Well, I was running from donut shop to donut shop

419
00:15:39,810 --> 00:15:41,970
找班吉  然后突然想到
trying to find Benji, you know, when it hit me...

420
00:15:42,340 --> 00:15:44,300
他是不是真命天子才不重要
it doesn't matter if he's the one.

421
00:15:44,300 --> 00:15:45,400
谁在乎这个
Who cares about that?

422
00:15:45,400 --> 00:15:47,710
重要的是你  你才是那个人
You know what does matter? You. You're the one. 

423
00:15:49,390 --> 00:15:51,100
我现在没心情跟你抱
Yeah, I'm not really feeling the hug yet.

424
00:15:51,700 --> 00:15:53,460
是吗  我想抱呢
Aren't you? 'Cause I am. 

425
00:15:56,060 --> 00:15:57,330
怎么回事
What's going on?

426
00:15:57,330 --> 00:15:59,070
就是我爱你啊
What's going on is I love you.

427
00:15:59,070 --> 00:16:02,400
好吗  我不会让男人破坏我们友谊的
Okay? And I would never let a guy jeopardize our friendship.

428
00:16:02,400 --> 00:16:05,120
而且说实话  他肯定还会变胖
And let's face it, you know, he's gonna get fat again.

429
00:16:05,710 --> 00:16:07,010
加比
Gabi...

430
00:16:07,200 --> 00:16:08,560
你跟班吉说了吗
have you told Benji yet?

431
00:16:08,790 --> 00:16:10,860
说了  那真的是...
I have. Yeah. And it was seriously...

432
00:16:11,080 --> 00:16:12,970
我干过最艰难的事之一了
one of the hardest things I've ever had to do.

433
00:16:12,970 --> 00:16:14,620
但你明白  我得跟他直说
But, you know, I had to be straight with him.

434
00:16:14,620 --> 00:16:16,340
只是希望他也能变直...
I just wish he would've been straight for me--

435
00:16:16,340 --> 00:16:17,930
跟我直说  真艰难
with me. It was hard.

436
00:16:19,670 --> 00:16:22,340
谢谢你  你真的听进了我的话
Well, thank you. I really feel like you heard me 

437
00:16:22,340 --> 00:16:24,560
尊重了我  谢谢
and respected me and I appreciate that.

438
00:16:24,560 --> 00:16:26,600
-现在我想跟你抱抱了  -好棒
- I will now accept that hug. - Oh, yay.

439
00:16:26,980 --> 00:16:28,180
幸亏班吉人好
You know, it's a good thing that

440
00:16:28,180 --> 00:16:30,110
聪明  长得又帅
Benji is sweet and smart and good looking...

441
00:16:30,110 --> 00:16:32,180
-他会找到其他女生的  -他才不会...
- he'll find another girl. - Ah, he won't...

442
00:16:32,430 --> 00:16:34,640
单身很久呢
...be alone for long.

443
00:16:37,970 --> 00:16:39,220
你好  班吉
Oh, hey, Benji.

444
00:16:40,080 --> 00:16:43,560
你跟她说了你选的是她吗
So, did you tell you chose her over me?

445
00:16:43,560 --> 00:16:46,510
是的  才说完  你来太早了
I did. Barely. You're cutting it a little close.

446
00:16:47,480 --> 00:16:48,790
你还好吗
Are you okay?

447
00:16:49,270 --> 00:16:51,520
非常好
I'm surprisingly okay.

448
00:16:52,710 --> 00:16:54,180
不过我们还是坐下吧
But let's sit down.

449
00:16:54,670 --> 00:16:56,010
我有话跟你说
I have something to tell you.

450
00:16:56,010 --> 00:16:57,050
什么
What?

451
00:16:57,050 --> 00:16:58,650
天啊  是什么  你吓到我了
Oh, my god. What is it? You're scaring me.

452
00:16:58,650 --> 00:16:59,970
爸爸妈妈还好吗
Are mom and dad okay?

453
00:17:00,200 --> 00:17:01,420
暂时还好
For now.

454
00:17:03,630 --> 00:17:05,230
不过等我跟他们出柜以后吧
But wait until I tell them I'm gay.

455
00:17:06,000 --> 00:17:07,490
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?

456
00:17:08,920 --> 00:17:11,430
天啊  真是没想到
Oh, my god! I did not see that one coming!

457
00:17:11,430 --> 00:17:13,550
晴天霹了个雳啊
This is a shock-a-roon-ey.

458
00:17:15,470 --> 00:17:16,620
是吗  加比
Is it, Gabi?

459
00:17:16,620 --> 00:17:19,510
还是你发现他是同志  明白了跟他没结果
Or did you find out he was gay, realized he wasn't the one,

460
00:17:19,520 --> 00:17:21,180
才在他跟我出柜之前
rushed over here to tell me I'm the one

461
00:17:21,180 --> 00:17:22,260
跑过来哄我
before he came out to me, 

462
00:17:22,260 --> 00:17:24,140
好让自己看起来像是好朋友  不惹我生气
so you'd look like a good friend and I wouldn't get mad?

463
00:17:24,150 --> 00:17:25,400
什么呀
What?

464
00:17:27,110 --> 00:17:29,980
很显然  他的出柜新闻
Clearly, the shock of his brand-new gayness

465
00:17:29,980 --> 00:17:32,520
都让你怀疑我的真心了
has caused you to doubt my sincerity.

466
00:17:33,560 --> 00:17:35,050
但我知道这难以消化
But I see three's a lot going on here, okay?

467
00:17:35,060 --> 00:17:36,520
我给你们些时间
So I'm gonna give you two a moment.

468
00:17:38,440 --> 00:17:40,440
所以...你是同志吗
So... you're gay?

469
00:17:41,040 --> 00:17:42,330
是的
I am.

470
00:17:43,780 --> 00:17:45,360
什么时候...
When did-- when did--

471
00:17:47,920 --> 00:17:49,640
抱歉这事发生[出柜]的太快
I'm sorry it came out so fast...

472
00:17:50,210 --> 00:17:51,450
不像我
unlike me.

473
00:17:52,580 --> 00:17:55,550
我知道你很震惊  只是不知道该怎么说
Look, I know you're shocked. I just didn't know how to tell you.

474
00:17:55,720 --> 00:17:57,170
你知道什么才奇怪吗
You want to know something weird?

475
00:17:57,370 --> 00:17:58,810
我一点也不震惊
I'm not that shocked.

476
00:17:59,140 --> 00:18:01,020
现在一切都说得通了
You know, it's all sort of making sense now.

477
00:18:01,020 --> 00:18:02,600
怪不得当初爸爸不给你看
Like when you locked yourself in your room

478
00:18:02,600 --> 00:18:03,740
《天桥风云》的季终集
Because dad wouldn't let you watch

479
00:18:03,740 --> 00:18:05,740
你会把自己反锁在房间里
the season finale of Project Runway .

480
00:18:05,990 --> 00:18:08,460
你以为是谁给儿童保护机构打的电话
Who do you think called child protective services?

481
00:18:10,170 --> 00:18:12,830
我没告诉你  是不想让你排斥我
I just didn't tell you because I didn't want you to reject me.

482
00:18:12,830 --> 00:18:15,450
闭嘴  你是我弟弟啊  我爱你
Oh, shut up. You're my brother and I love you.

483
00:18:15,450 --> 00:18:17,890
你才闭嘴  我也爱你
You shut up! I love you, too.

484
00:18:20,610 --> 00:18:22,060
都没事了吗
So everything's good?

485
00:18:22,060 --> 00:18:23,790
你们都说通了吗
You guys talked about everything?

486
00:18:23,800 --> 00:18:26,060
-是的  -他也能接受你失业了吗
- We did. - So he's cool with you not having a job?

487
00:18:26,060 --> 00:18:27,220
-什么  -加比
- What? - Gabi!

488
00:18:28,000 --> 00:18:29,770
起码我没说你不是处女
At least I didn't tell him you're not a virgin.

489
00:18:29,770 --> 00:18:32,920
-什么  -好吧  再给你们些时间
- What? - Okay, I'm gonna give you a moment.

490
00:18:41,250 --> 00:18:42,870
是我喝醉了
Have I had a little bit too much to drink...

491
00:18:42,870 --> 00:18:44,740
还是我的朋友一个都没来
or are none of my friends here?

492
00:18:45,960 --> 00:18:48,180
来了  是你太矮看不见他们
They're here. You're just too short to see 'em.

493
00:18:49,320 --> 00:18:51,580
没错  可能是我看不见
You're right. Maybe I can't see them...

494
00:18:51,840 --> 00:18:53,400
但我看得见这个
but I can see this.

495
00:18:53,520 --> 00:18:54,410
没错
That's right.

496
00:18:54,410 --> 00:18:56,550
我收到"好基友"的派对提醒了
I got the Yo Fellas alert about the party.

497
00:18:56,550 --> 00:18:58,050
我的派对
My party!

498
00:18:58,270 --> 00:18:59,630
听我解释
I can explain...

499
00:19:00,070 --> 00:19:01,330
告诉他  乔什
tell him, Josh.

500
00:19:03,420 --> 00:19:04,640
艾略特
Elliot...

501
00:19:05,140 --> 00:19:06,570
你是个了不起的人
you're an amazing guy...

502
00:19:06,860 --> 00:19:09,800
和很棒的公关
and an unbelievable publicist,

503
00:19:09,800 --> 00:19:10,790
碰巧犯了错
who happened to drop the ball

504
00:19:10,790 --> 00:19:12,470
没提醒我要办你的单身派对
by not reminding me about his bachelor party.

505
00:19:13,180 --> 00:19:14,910
-你是在怪我吗  =我在尽力
- You're blaming me for this? - I was trying.

506
00:19:15,880 --> 00:19:18,530
所以你觉得仓促办个单身派对
So you thought throwing together a last-minute bachelor party

507
00:19:18,530 --> 00:19:19,930
弄一堆气球
with a ton of balloons,

508
00:19:19,930 --> 00:19:22,700
请一群半裸的醉汉帅哥打着领结
and a bunch of drunk, half-naked bow-tied strangers

509
00:19:22,710 --> 00:19:24,170
到处跳舞
dancing all over the place

510
00:19:24,170 --> 00:19:26,110
就能补偿你忘办派对这事吗
would make up for the fact that you forgot?

511
00:19:27,430 --> 00:19:29,830
你成功了
Well, it did!

512
00:19:30,140 --> 00:19:32,270
这是我人生中最棒的一晚
This is the best night of my life!

513
00:19:34,210 --> 00:19:35,620
真高兴你喜欢  伙计
I'm glad you enjoyed it, buddy.

514
00:19:35,620 --> 00:19:37,450
你配得上  对吗  尤兰达
You're worth it. Right, Yolanda?

515
00:19:38,950 --> 00:19:40,980
没错  生日快乐  亲爱的
Oh, yeah. Happy birthday, baby.

516
00:19:44,440 --> 00:19:45,620
静一静
Attention!

517
00:19:45,630 --> 00:19:47,270
请静一静
Attention beautiful strangers,

518
00:19:47,270 --> 00:19:50,040
平时绝不会鸟我的帅哥们
who normally would never give me the time of day.

519
00:19:50,490 --> 00:19:53,320
虽然"好基友"把我们聚在了一起
Even though Yo Fellas is what brought us all together...

520
00:19:53,320 --> 00:19:55,710
但今晚就是终点了
for me it ends tonight!

521
00:19:56,170 --> 00:19:58,010
我有两个好朋友
I have two great friends

522
00:19:58,390 --> 00:20:00,680
和一个棒极了的未婚夫
and an amazing fiance.

523
00:20:00,680 --> 00:20:02,830
我不需要保护伞了
I don't need a security blanket anymore.

524
00:20:02,900 --> 00:20:05,510
我决定做出终极牺牲
I've decided to make the ultimate sacrifice...

525
00:20:05,510 --> 00:20:07,240
删掉"好基友"
deleting Yo Fellas.

526
00:20:08,710 --> 00:20:11,640
艾略特·帕克从此名花有主
Elliot Park is officially off the market.

527
00:20:15,180 --> 00:20:18,180
艾略特  这是班吉  索菲亚的弟弟
Hey, Elliot, meet Benji, Sofia's brother.

528
00:20:18,270 --> 00:20:20,130
他刚刚出柜
He just came out of the closet.

529
00:20:20,260 --> 00:20:22,290
天啊  真对不起  这该你来说
Oh, my god, I'm so sorry. That's your news.

530
00:20:22,680 --> 00:20:24,140
我就是好骄傲
I'm just so proud.

531
00:20:24,310 --> 00:20:25,830
恭喜
Wow! Congrats.

532
00:20:26,170 --> 00:20:27,360
你听见我刚才的讲话了吗
Did you hear my speech?

533
00:20:27,360 --> 00:20:28,420
抱歉  没赶上
No, sorry. I missed it.

534
00:20:28,420 --> 00:20:30,300
太好了  我们来跳舞吧
Perfect. Let's dance.

535
00:20:33,750 --> 00:20:35,320
把衬衫脱了嘛
Take off your shirt!

536
00:20:37,660 --> 00:20:38,680
我觉得你们要跟
You know I think it's really great 

537
00:20:38,680 --> 00:20:41,110
父母说出人生真相  真的很棒
you guys are gonna tell your parents the truth about your lives.

538
00:20:41,200 --> 00:20:42,560
如果我说了我的事
What if I tell them about me

539
00:20:42,650 --> 00:20:44,100
他们不让我回家怎么办
and they never let me come home?

540
00:20:44,610 --> 00:20:47,060
如果我说了我的事  他们让我回家怎么办
What if I tell them about me and they want me to move home?

541
00:20:47,180 --> 00:20:49,390
你们都想错了
You guys, you're looking at this all wrong.

542
00:20:49,390 --> 00:20:51,400
当他们知道索菲亚没了工作
When they find out that Sofia's jobless...

543
00:20:51,400 --> 00:20:53,130
就不在乎你是同志了
they won't care that you're gay.

544
00:20:53,260 --> 00:20:54,560
当他们知道你是同志
You know, when they find out you're gay...

545
00:20:54,560 --> 00:20:56,520
就不会在乎索菲亚失业
they won't care that Sofia's unemployed.

546
00:20:56,520 --> 00:20:59,020
因为不管爸妈怎么看待我的事
Because no matter what mom and dad think of my news--

547
00:20:59,020 --> 00:21:00,210
或者我的事
Or my news--

548
00:21:00,230 --> 00:21:01,570
我们会共同面对
We're in this together.

549
00:21:02,940 --> 00:21:04,630
我也想要个好性感的同志弟弟
I want a super-hot gay brother.

550
00:21:06,860 --> 00:21:08,780
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Are you ready? - Ready.

551
00:21:12,520 --> 00:21:13,790
你好  妈妈
Hi, mom.

552
00:21:13,790 --> 00:21:15,010
你好  爸爸
Hi, dad.

553
00:21:17,340 --> 00:21:18,520
班吉是同志
Benji's gay!

554
00:21:19,660 --> 00:21:21,140
索菲亚失业了
Sofia's unemployed!

555
00:21:22,590 --> 00:21:24,390
我给你们些时间
I'm gonna give you two a moment.

