Previously on Z Nation.
We're gonna meet up with the team.
We're gonna get Murphy to that lab.
And then we are going to cure this virus.
It's a lie, and it's gonna get us both killed.
Well then I'd rather die believing in a lie
than live believing in nothing.
Addy! Addy! Addy!
Stay with me, Addy!
- What happened?  - I know what the flashbacks are.
I killed my mom.
We don't leave each other behind.
I came back for you. I'll always come back for you.
Are you sure Citizen Z said we should be down here?
Yeah, that's what he said.
Hear that?
What do you think, huh?
Dead? Alive? Human? Zombie?
Dead.
Here, here, here, here, here.
Bingo.
Cinderella dressed in yella.
Went upstairs to kiss a fella.
She took a pill.
Lost her frills.
How many zombies
does she kill?
One, two, three, four.
You couldn't just give them mercy?
What fun would that be?
What was that?
I don't know.
Come on.
Shhhh.
Hold it right there.
Oh, it's the damn wonder twins.
Guys.
What?
The wonder...
Hey!
Oh my!
Never, I mean never, ever, in a million years,
truly did I think I'd see you guys again.
Citizen Z send you guys?
Yeah. He told us there was food and
somebody named Chester who could help us out.
Yeah, he told us that too. We're starting to have our doubts.
Okay, well he should be, you know what, right down there.
Let's hit it.
What happened to her?
She got caught on a piece of barbed wire.
Now it's all infected.
Hello!
Well I guess we found Chester.
Hello, Chester.
Somebody got up on the wrong side of the apocalypse.
What happened to you guys out there?
She's working out some stuff.
You know how things can catch up with you.
Chester?
You got them yet? You got my team?
Hello? Anyone?
Warren?
Addy, it's...
Hey, hey, hey! Up here!
It's your old pal, Citizen Z.
Oh, it's everyone.
Hi, everyone. Hi!
Addy, looking gorgeous as always.
Oh, hey uh, you must be Mack.
Kinda thought you'd be taller.
I thought you'd be old enough to shave.
Hey, Murphy. Squeeze in so I can see you.
Yeah, lookin' good, sir.
So guess what? I've got good news.
California's back.
They're alive and online, well most of them.
But they're getting ready for you,
and the dream is alive.
The mission is a go, thanks to yours truly.
That's good news, right?
Good news would be a package of Oreos
and a couple gallons of milk.
Oh, oh yeah, right. Sorry.
Down the same hall, next door on your left.
Should be everything that you need.
I can't tell you how good it is to see you all again.
Good to see us too, kid.
Hey, what was this place anyway?
CIA black site.
Oh, like waterboarding, Zero Dark Thirty, black site?
Yeah, I kinda thought it would be obvious
from what Chester told me.
So where is the old crackpot anyway?
Oh man. Bummer.
Whoa, Warren. Slow up here, will ya?
It's just a kid.
That is not a kid. It's zombie road kill.
Ten o'clock.
Another kid.
Not anymore.
Stop.
Warren, stop. It's just a boy. Stop.
Don't! You're hurting me! Don't!
Addy!
What?!
Fine!
Heads up, we got a live one.
Another sad kid in a weird flowered shirt.
I got this one.
You okay?
A little thirsty is all.
Of course.
Hold on.
Water.
Thanks.
Here you go, champ.
Thanks, ma'am.
You can call me Roberta.
What's your name?
I'm Sam.
Sam.
Does your mom know you're out here all by yourself?
I'm going to Salt Lake City to see my dad.
That's not a good idea.
Yes, it is.
I'm old enough now. I finally get to meet my dad.
It's too far. It's not safe.
It's not too far.
Brennan and Dax are already there.
Sam.
Salt Lake City's been overrun by zombies.
Yeah, right.
Uh, wait, wait, Sam.
You're right.
You are old enough to go see your dad.
But here's the thing.
We've run out of food.
Can you help us?
My friend Helen could help you get some food.
Cool.
Will you show us where they live?
Tell you what.
You take us there,
we will drive you to Salt Lake City.
Okay.
Murphy, move.
Hey there.
Hey man, I'm Mack.
Just up there.
Anybody home?
Doesn't look like it.
Mack, you want to check it out?
Yeah.
Get back in the truck!
You're not welcome here!
Hold on, hold on!
It's okay.
We're friendly. We just...
Stop! Stop! It's fine! Just listen to me for a second!
We have...
I thought you said they were friendly, Sam.
Stop! Don't shoot! Please!
We have your boy!
We have Sam!
Hold your fire!
Open the gate.
Ms. Helen, it's okay. They just need food.
They're nice.
It's good to see you, Sam.
Why don't you go inside and find your mother?
I'm sure she's anxious to see you.
Thank you for bringing him back.
Sometimes our kids get cabin fever
and decide to go exploring.
What's wrong with you?
It's infected.
Oh, that could be dangerous.
Yeah, it could.
We can help you.
You've arrived at the Sisters of Mercy.
Anytime now!
You don't have to stay!
Yes, he does.
We're a team.
You are?
Yes.
Well, team or not,
if you want to stay here, you'll have to split up.
Women and children only here.
You can go inside with your friend.
But your men will have to stay outside the wall.
We'll give you 24 hours.
You can rest, get some food, and then you'll leave us.
That's very fair of you.
And you are?
Helen. And you?
Lieutenant Roberta Warren. Missouri National Guard.
Addy.
Don't worry.
I got her.
Yeah, this blows.
Can you help her?
She has an infected leg. Take her to the infirmary.
You're pretty.
Hi.
Want to see my carrots?
Sure.
I planted them myself.
Here?
Yep.
It's beautiful here.
Come on.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Now look at this one, and look at all the flowers in it.
Here we grow our own vegetables.
We have chickens and cows out back.
Cows? You get milk?
Milk, butter, yogurt.
Most importantly for you, penicillin.
Amy makes it herself. She used to be a chemist.
Lina's in the kitchen,
she'll show you where you can wash up.
And I hope you'll join us for our mid-day meal.
Thank you.
No. It's back, front, clap,
right, then left.
Sorry, I haven't done this in forever.
My mom taught me a really long time ago.
Is she nice?
Yeah, yeah, she is.
Let's try again.
Whoever built this place
must've seen the Apocalypse coming.
It's perfect.
That was my husband.
His philosophy was that we become
absolutely self-sufficient and off the grid.
Your husband?
He's gone.
Like the others.
All these women?
Well Zina and Emmeline were my sister wives.
And when Ammon went, we had each other and this place.
These other women weren't so lucky 'til we found them.
Now they're safe.
They're free.
More strawberries?
No. I...
I think I'm gonna go look in on Cassandra
and see how she's doing.
- Thank you.  - Of course.
So these are the carrots you grew? They're delicious.
Feeling better? Thank you.
Starting to.
Remember what Sam told us about where he was going?
Salt Lake City to see his dad.
Amy has a son a little older than Sam.
He's not here.
You know why?
Went to Salt Lake City to see his dad?
The girls stay here, but all the boys leave when they turn 13.
That's what she said.
They seem so happy.
Yeah, maybe a little too happy.
Nice people always scare me.
Let's get you well, and let's get out of here.
All these women give me the creeps.
That blonde one keeps looking at me.
Oh man, don't get down on yourself like that.
You are a perfect hunk of man meat,
and don't you ever forget it.
Ha, ha. Don't quit your day job.
Is there really all women in there?
Yeah. Enjoy your imagination, kid.
That's probably all you're gonna get.
You know what I don't understand, Doc?
What the hell happened to all their men?
Well maybe we can ask her.
Angels from heaven.
Is that pie?
Blueberry. Ummm, I, I, I made it by myself.
Do you guys know where the...
the other one is? The one with the with the a
the hair and those eyes? He...
10K, Hold my calls, wake me up after the apocalypse
I'm gonna go give him a piece of this.
What?
Pie?
Beat it, kid.
Beat it!
You like that?
It's okay. Somebody hurt you?
Yeah? I know. I know.
Daddy.
You need me to take care of you.
Part of me wants you to stop.
But part of me really needs the pie.
Cannibals?
I'm so sorry that happened to you.
And I wish I could say I was surprised.
Man.
He can't help himself.
The animal instinct takes over.
Kill,
destroy,
rape.
Now this disease, this virus.
Testosterone is the most toxic chemical on Earth.
And you survived through it all. Now you're here.
I was really lucky.
I met Mack on the first night.
I think he was the lucky one.
What about this?
This is special.
Yeah, yeah. How'd you know?
Tell me.
I can't.
It's too much for you.
I can see that.
You can tell me. Just tell me.
It was my mom.
And my brother.
And I had to...
both of them.
Oh, my sweet, sweet, sweet girl.
Let it go. Just let it all go.
Can I tell you something?
You don't ever have to go through that again.
This place, our sisters,
we're protected from that.
We could use a woman like you.
Smart, resourceful, caring.
You're not like the others. You're special.
I can see that.
Hmmm, looks like we have a new sister.
What's going on?
I'm not sure.
This is Tessa.
Tessa, welcome.
You're home now.
You're safe.
It's okay.
No one can hurt you here.
This is why we exist.
We provide a place that is safe
from the violent destructive world of men.
And we bring the perpetrators to justice.
That is our purpose.
Bring him.
What is your name?
Bite me, Bitch.
Hmmm, Bitch.
I like that. It suits you.
Well it's time that you learn about justice, Bitch.
Take him away.
You should see this.
What's gonna happen to him?
Justice.
You harm a woman, you die. That's our rule.
Tessa?
Now, Tessa.
No!
He was a bad man.
You all right?
Yeah.
Tessa said there are two sisters still out there.
We could use your help to free them.
Of course.
Addy.
You sure you're up to that?
Warren.
Any one of us could be those sisters.
I'm in.
Wonderful.
Yeah, you got me too.
You don't have to.
No, no, no.
I always got my sister's back.
We got to burn this joint, boys. Time to motor.
Whoa, Doc. Hold on, man. What Is it?
What'd you see?
Zombie.
Bear.
Someone's coming.
They wouldn't just leave us, would they?
No, Addy doesn't go anywhere without me.
Sorry, pal.
She just did.
Here they come.
You got a problem there, darlin'?
What do you think?
Kinda dangerous, ain't it?
Two pretty little gals like you,
travelin' all alone?
It's not safe out here.
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you tell me where you're headed,
and Sidecar here can have a look at that engine.
Hands up, gentlemen.
Your little game is over.
Wait, wait, wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm not really with them. They just...
- I was stranded, and they helped me out. - Shut up!
Drop your guns.
That ain't happening, sweetheart.
Hold your fire! Hold your fire.
You see, huh?
I'm a reasonable man.
I'm sure we can come to some kind of an arrangement.
Why don't you just tell me what you want?
Let me ask.
These girls with you voluntarily?
Didn't think so.
Ladies.
Hey, hey, listen to me.
That saddlebag, it's full of oxycontin.
You can take it.
Not interested.
What kind of a raging bitch doesn't want to make a deal?
This one.
Hey, Addy. We could use your help over here.
It's time for some justice.
Shoot one.
A mortal wound, anywhere but the head.
The rest will take care of themselves.
Oh, not this one.
The other one.
Addy, wait.
I swear. I...it wasn't me. I... please. Please. I wasn't...
Is this really necessary?
Addy, don't do this.
You don't want to get in my way, sister.
Please, I...I swear. I swear. I wasn't gonna do anything.
He's lying.
Remember the cannibal remember when he kidnapped.
Remember.
Remember Tobias.
Remember when he kidnapped.
Oh, God! No! No! No!
Good girl.
It's time to go.
We got to get out of here.
I know. I saw the bear.
That's not the problem.
If a zombie bear isn't the problem, what is?
I need to see her.
She's in a weird place.
I've been there.
It's not gonna be easy to get her back.
Well it's fine, but I'm not leaving here without her.
You guys just get ready.
I'll do my best to get her out.
But you may have a choice to make.
I know what you did seemed hard.
I felt the same way
when I freed myself from my husband.
He said he was innocent, too.
You know we were both raised to
believe all the rules, that
they were good and true and
from God.
And after I almost died after my fifth child,
I started not to believe.
I didn't want anymore children.
I didn't want him.
And that didn't square with the rules.
So he beat me.
He broke my nose and my arms, ribs.
But that's not even the worst story
that you'll hear from the women in here.
We got to go now.
You seen Addy?
No.
We will find her on the way out.
I'll be fine.
Hope so.
I will.
You've been out there.
You know what it's like.
I just... don't know
what I'm supposed to do anymore.
I can't un-see any of it.
The people,
even the zombies.
It's too much
for anyone.
You need rest.
Peace.
Stay here.
Be a part of our family.
I can't leave Mack.
I can't.
I love him.
I know you do, sweetheart.
So it'll hurt all that much more when you have to watch him die.
And one day he will die.
And it will be you
that has to give him mercy.
Yeah.
How do I tell him?
What do I say?
I'll tell you what to say.
Okay.
Addy
Hey, can we go talk somewhere real quick?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, of course.
So what's it like in there?
Sounds a little weird, I mean a zombie...
Uh, no, no, no, no, no. Mack, it is...
It's so beautiful.
I wish you could see it.
Yeah, I wish I could too.
It's so different from out here.
I feel safe.
I haven't felt that in such a long time.
Good. That's good.
I'm glad. It's...
I'm sure it's gonna be hard to leave.
That's what I wanted to talk to you about.
It's too much.
I can't do it anymore, Mack.
But Addy...
I can't stay with you here.
I need to rest.
I can't.
I can't do this without you.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Addy. Addy, come on. Come on.
I love you. I... I... Don't you...
Mack, I love you so much.
I cannot go back out there and watch you die.
I'm not gonna die.
Yes, you will.
We all will.
And this is how I want to remember you.
Mack, I cannot kill somebody I love ever again.
I'm not going back out there without you, Addy.
I'm not. I can't.
This is for the best.
Addy. Addy, wait. Wait a minute.
What about Murphy, huh?
And the mission?
You said, you said you would rather
die believing in something than live believing in nothing.
I have to go.
Look at me. Look at me.
I understand. I do. You're...
You're upset about your mom. Of course. Of course.
It's horrible. I mean it's, it's beyond horrible.
But you're gonna get through this.
That's not who you are.
You're a good person. You're, you're, you're strong.
You're strong. You don't need Helen
and some stupid cult.
I'm sorry.
Addy, Addy, Addy. You can't do this.
- Mack. - You can't leave me. This is crazy.
- Mack. - Addy, wait.
- Mack, let me go. - Addy, just listen to me.
Just listen to me, okay?
- Mack. - You're not thinking clearly.
You're hurting me!
Wait. Addy.
Addy!
Wait!
Hey. Addy!
Addy!
Please talk to us!
Come on, Addy!
Maybe I could help?
I think we've had enough of your help.
Addy?
It's me.
Open the door.
Addy?
Don't touch me.
Where's Murphy? We need the tent.
Uh, he's still in it with that girl.
She's still in there?
Party's over, everyone. Time to go.
Where'd you get a cigarette?
Whatever daddy needs,
daddy gets.
Yeah, well time to go now, sweetheart.
Come on. Up and at 'em.
Thanks, man.
Thought she'd never leave.
Surprise.
Go ahead. Tell them.
Tell them what you told me.
I've made up my mind.
I'm gonna stay here
with Helen.
No. Addy.
Trouble at the gate. We need you.
You stay here. You'll be safe.
Addy, I know this place feels safe.
It feels good.
Well that's how I felt when I met Tobias.
But it wasn't real.
You and me,
we've been through so much together.
Addison Carver.
Listen to me.
Enough now.
You got sucked into this thing,
and you did something.
And we all do things.
But it is time for us to go. Now.
All of us.
You don't have to worry.
I'm home now.
No.
How'd she get outside?
Where is she?!
The tall one?
Your leader?
I'm here! What do you want?
You, sweetheart.
I want you.
You open that gate
and you come out here.
And we'll have a nice little conversation.
All polite like.
Shoot him.
I'm a real quick trigger.
You shoot me,
she's dead before I hit the ground.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
She's coming, right?
Yes, she's coming.
It's all right, Addy.
Come here, please.
Addy.
Please?
I will always love you, Mack.
We don't do this.
We don't leave each other.
Goodbye, Mack.
No.
You shot him?!
It's a warning. Get him out of here now.
Before it gets worse.
Get his gun.
Come on.
Addy!
- Come on, buddy. - Addy!
- What about Addy? - Come on.
She's not coming!
Let's go, Doc! Now!
Stop the truck.
- No. - Stop the truck!
Keep driving!
Mack, Mack, Mack.
I can't.
Okay.
Get in!
Butterfly, butterfly, happy all day.
Butterfly, butterfly, fly fly away.
Three little butterflies looking at you.
One flew away and then there were two.
Two little butterflies soaking up the sun.
One flew away and then there was one.
One little butterfly stayed all along.
It flew away and then they were gone.
.