.
Previously on Z Nation.
Those are zombie bites.
Eight of them.
If we can get him to the lab in California,
they can use his blood and make more of the vaccine.
Shoot him!
You're that sharp shooter that saved my ass, aren't you?
So what's your name, kid?
Ten Thousand.
Does it mean anything?
How many zombies I'm going to kill.
One thousand fifty-nine.
One thousand sixty!
Nice shot, kid!
Amish zombies.
Really?
They tried to quarantine themselves
from the rest of society.
Keep the Zs from spreading the infection.
That was before we knew Romero had it right.
We were all carrying the virus.
Didn't matter who you were or how you died.
Night of the Living Dead. Great movie, sucky reality.
You know what I don't get, If the Zs didn't spread the virus,
how did we all get infected?
Best guess I heard, it was spread by birds.
Some kind of parasite piggybacked on the bird flu.
Stays dormant 'till you die.
You know
take it from somebody who knows first hand.
Other than the fact that they find brains delicious,
when it comes to zombies nobody knows nothin'.
My turn.
Have we just met?
Thank you.
Hey, hurry up.
I want to get past DC before dark.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm tellin' ya, there ain't nothin' there.
No thoughts, no memories.
No soul.
Nothin'.
Well they're not dead.
They want something.
Yeah. Brains.
You can't want something if you're not conscious,
if you don't have a soul.
When my pa was wounded,
he told me to tie him up before he turned.
Made me promise to show him mercy when he died.
Kill the brain, you know?
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't hurt my pa,
no matter what he'd become.
I stared into his eyes for the longest time, just
looking for some sign he was still in there.
Did you see anything?
What did you do?
I killed it.
Damn, kid.
You had to put down your own dad?
Didn't kill him.
Killed it.
But if it's not alive, how did you kill it?
Piked it.
Right here. My first kill.
I always wish he knew, you know,
somehow knew that I kept my promise.
Humans! Six o'clock!
I see them.
Is that more of your cannibal friends?
No. Something else.
Up ahead!
Where's he going?
Hey! Kid!
What do you think?
Plow right through?
No, I don't want to wreck the truck again.
Let's pike them and be on our way.
Oh what, are we having a little mercy party?
Hey, let's do this quietly.
There might be more of them nearby.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Something's wrong.
Yeah, she's right. Look at their feet.
Hold it right there!
All right, now drop your weapons
or die
right where you stand.
Put down the weapons
or eat brains.
God, I love that kid.
Now, we just want the vehicle.
All right?
So give us the truck
and we'll let you live to die another day.
Give them the truck!
Don't give them a goddamn thing!
Do the math Garnett.
We have other priorities.
Get them the damn truck.
Listen to your friend there.
Nobody wants to die.
But we're taking that truck.
Say the word, Garnett.
Let them have it.
The truck.
Let them have the truck.
Smart move.
All right guys, let's go!
And leave the junker!
They're not gonna get very far.
Murphy.
Beautiful.
Sergeant Raymond Valdez.
Delta Force. Deceased.
Lieutenant Mark Hammond.
Cause of death.
Unknown.
Alvin Bernard Murphy.
AKA Patient Zero.
Previously serving three years in federal prison
for postal fraud.
Compulsory volunteer, project Bite Mark.
Status.
Believed to be en route
to Mt. Wilson CDC lab, California.
Sergeant Charles Garnett, National Guard.
Believed to be in possession of Patient Zero.
Current location, somewhere south of Philadelphia,
accompanied by an unknown number of civilians.
Come in, Citizen Z.
Mayday. Mayday.
This is Addison Carver with Delta-Xray-Delta.
Trying to contact Citizen Z.
- Come in, Citizen Z. - Addy Carver.
- Mayday. - Doesn't sound military.
Slightly east coast accent.
I wonder.
Level nine top secret clearance only.
That would be me.
Facebook, Friendster, Twitter, Tinder.
A regular trip down memory lane.
Someday this will be all that's left of us.
Addison Carver, AKA Addy.
Age twenty-six. Student.
Believed to be accompanying Patient Zero to Mount Wilson
regarding operation Bite Mark.
Last contact seven days ago.
Status,
Single.
I mean, status unknown.
What a tomato.
What?
No offense babe, but you need a bath.
Do I?
Yeah.
Oh, okay. Yeah, when was the last time
you changed your underwear goat-boy?
What underwear?
Y'all see that?
That's them, all right.
Bastards.
Looks like they're trying to rob some poor family this time.
Not if I have anything to say about it. Come on.
Would it matter at all if I said don't do this?
Drop your weapons on the ground
or the first shot takes your head off.
You heard the man. Drop your weapons.
Now.
What's this?
A robbery.
Drop your weapons.
Now.
I don't want to have to kill you.
Never get out of the boat.
Yo, can't this thing go any faster?
I'm gonna die of old age before we get to California.
You can always get out and push.
No, not me, sister. I'm special.
Talking to you makes me wonder
about this whole saving humanity thing.
Stop the car!
Oh, it's the family.
We got to get off this road.
To update today's top storys:
absolutley nothing new is going on
in this decimated world of ours.
It's the same desperation, the same devastation
everywhere you look.
And who the hell keeps posting all these cat videos?
We should have known piano playing kittens
was a harbinger of the Apocalypse.
Quiet!
This is Sergeant Charles Garnett calling Northern Light.
Charles Garnett calling Northern Light.
Come in, Northern Light.
Can you read me? Citizen Z, are you there? Over.
Yes, this is Northern Light for Garnett.
Citizen Z hitting you back. Go for Garnett.
Thank God. We've been trying to make this work for hours.
What are you broadcasting on?
Uh, Clowny the french fry guy.
One of our team, Carver jerry-rigged a drive-thru camera
Addy Carver?
Yeah.
Is she there? I wanna say hi.
Oh, okay.
Hi, Addy.
Hey.
How's it going down there?
Ummm, it's pretty eff'd up actually.
How's it going wherever you are?
Aww you know, same ol' same ol'.
Busy keeping an eye on the world.
What can I do for you folks?
Can we get a chocolate shake and fries for ten thousand men?
Could we please get on with this before the Zs find us?
Wait. Is that Murphy?
Outstanding.
Glad to see you're still alive, sir.
Yeah but he won't be for long if we don't get off this highway.
We're in desperate need of alternate transpo.
We're looking for an airplane or a chopper or a hot air balloon.
Anything airborne.
There is one thing.
I've been monitoring some random transmissions
from what's left of the
Emergency Headquarters for Infection Control.
I can hear them, but they don't respond when I reply.
And it's pretty garbled.
General McCandles might still be holed up there.
You're in luck.
I have a visual confirmation on that chopper.
It looks like it's still there.
Where is it?
McLean, Virginia.
Twenty clicks due west of Washington DC.
Look for a high-rise with structural damage
and a chopper on the roof.
Now that's a hundred miles south from here.
We're going west, not south.
- West. - Do you want to get off the road or not?
Puppies and kittens!
We gotta go.
Bye, Addison.
Call me when you get there.
Not exactly what I was hoping for.
One of these days you're gonna learn to quit hoping for things.
You better hope not
cuz that's when we leave your ass at the side of the road.
Halt! Who goes there!
Sergeant Charles Garnett, National Guard.
This is Lieutenant Roberta Warren,
- State your business. - Also National Guard.
We're on a high priority mission
to get this man to a CDC lab in California.
We were sent here by an Intell Officer from the NSA
to see General McCandles.
We need his help finding transpo.
We were told he has a helicopter.
Yeah, he's got a chopper.
But General McCandles is a very busy man.
He's got the entire east coast under his command.
He can't worry about some raggedy ass group of civilians
on a suicide mission.
I suggest you move on before the infected find you.
Nothing raggedy ass about this group of civilians, sir.
And this man has important information
about a vaccine for the zombie virus.
He smells like a damn Z.
You don't smell so good yourself, septic tank.
You gonna help us or not?
You want to see the General?
You're going to have to pay a tribute.
Gesture of goodwill to show him you're serious.
What kind of tribute you have in mind?
Our medic has been MIA over a year.
We need painkillers. Antibiotics.
Anything you got.
I'll get my bag.
I got aspirin, tetracycline, cipro.
That should knock out most any infection.
And oxycontin.
The oxy. We need painkillers.
You want to see the General or not?
This is the last of our supply.
That'll do.
The General will see you now.
Why are you wasting my time?
General McCandles, sir.
We have a National Guard unit and several civilians
requesting permission to speak to you.
Is sweet Jesus with them?
No, sir.
- Then tell them to go to hell! - I don't believe so.
I've got a war to fight! Where's that close air support I ordered?
Tell the Admiral I need those subs in position by 0800.
Bravo Company, hold your position at all costs.
Repeat, all costs.
You heard the General.
General McCandles, sir.
We're on a mission of extreme importance
by direct order from the president.
It's imperative that we find air transport
-to Mt. Wilson CDC lab - Sorry, I'm busy.
in California.
Where are my reinforcements?
You heard the man. Time to go.
That's it?
I've a good mind to make you barf up my oxycontin.
Doc! Doc! Stand down!
Did you say Doc? As in doctor?
Yeah, our team includes a medical doctor.
Why didn't you say so? Send him up.
I have a wounded man in need of medical attention.
Just the doctor. The rest of you wait here.
I got this.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey. Talk to him about the chopper.
Son of a bitch.
I was saving that oxy
for a party when we got to Cali.
You the medic?
I am indeed.
You the General?
General Arthur C. McCandles.
Commander, Central Command,
Infection Response Forces.
Where's your wounded man?
Right here.
It's not a bite.
This looks bad.
Real bad.
It's just a scratch.
No, that's... that's more like gangrene.
Can you save the leg?
I'm afraid not, General.
It's already starting to spread.
Soon the Z virus will take over.
All I can do at this point is show you mercy
when the time comes.
You call that a diagnosis?
I call it the truth.
You're gonna die.
And soon.
That's what the last guy said.
Look who.
What do you think, pup?
Could we use another friend?
My thoughts exactly.
That was quick.
How are things at the North Pole?
Awesome. Beautiful Aurora today.
How's your day going?
Kinda lonely. Nice to have somebody to talk to.
I know the feeling. Gets lonely here too.
Keeping an eye on the planet keeps you busy though.
I feel safer just knowing you're there.
You seem so cool.
I wish I could meet you in person.
Super busy, but I'm sure that could be arranged.
What are you doing right now?
Aww you know.
Same ol', same ol'.
One thousand ninety.
One thousand ninety-one.
One thousand and ninety-two.
Okay, what's going on with Doc?
Guys, if we don't get out of here soon
this could get ugly.
Oh, you mean uglier.
Do you hear that?
Hear what?
I don't hear anything.
Sounds like Doc.
Make it stop!
That's Doc all right. But where the hell is he?
Somewhere up there.
We're going up after him.
No, you don't.
Let us up now.
Nobody goes upstairs without the General's orders.
We go up now
or I scramble your egg-brain inside the shell.
You'll be sorry.
So will you cuz you're coming up with us.
10K! Cover our flank.
Don't let man or zombie follow us up.
Yes, sir.
One thousand ninety-three.
No.
Ninety-four.
What floor is the General on?
Top floor.
He's the General, man.
What floor do you think he's on?
My world is but an illusion.
Oh God, why didn't I pay better attention
to that sweet little Buddhist chick I dated?
Stay calm.
I'm sure they're...
I'm sure they're watching you right now.
They're looking for you.
They're looking for you right now.
There's no way they'd just leave you here
trapped in the air shaft with an ugly-ass zombie
waiting to eat my face off!
Oh, wait.
Oh, that's more like it.
I was saving this for a special occasion.
Like now.
Come on, suck it up.
Come on. Come on.
That's good shit, man.
Chill!
Help!
Now what?
Be ready for anything.
Did I mention that
the one thing I have a phobia of aside
from zombies is elevators.
Shouldn't have messed with the General.
Is it getting hot in here?
Hey, come on. Open the damn door.
I got to get out of here.
Relax, Murphy.
No, no, I got to get out. There's not enough oxygen.
Chill out!
Mack!
I'm here, babe.
Hey, why aren't we moving?
It'll start in a second.
Thank you, son.
It's good.
Can I do anything for you?
Make sure those knots are tight.
It's not gonna be long now.
It's double-half-hitch. Just like you taught me.
Just be sure.
Promise me
you'll do what we talked about
when the time comes.
Promise me.
I promise.
Just like we talked about.
I swear.
Don't swear.
Your mother never liked that.
I promise.
Good.
I could always trust you to do the right thing.
You're a good boy.
Your mother,
she'd be proud of the man you're growing up to be.
Give me another puff.
Will ya?
Ya know, now don't take offense.
But the only thing worse than that mug of yours
is your breath.
Not my fingers, you animal!
I was offering you the last hit.
Well, fine. I'll bogart it myself then.
A thousand and one uses, I tell ya.
Well I'll be damned.
I think you're stoned.
Hell, we don't need a vaccine.
Just need a few billion tons of some primo Ganja,
and the world would be just fine.
Doctor Morgan Henley.
Does that name ring a bell
in any of those cannabinol soaked brain cells you have left?
I must be really stoned.
Obstetrics, huh?
I wonder what that must have been like.
Bringing all them beautiful little angels into the world.
I mean just to be present for so many miracles.
Yeah, it's a bummer all those babies grew up to be zombies.
You know,
I got a kid out there somewhere.
I never told anybody that before.
I had him when I was 19.
Too young.
Wasn't really around for him like I should've been.
Never really got to know him.
Kept telling myself maybe you know
someday I...I would just call him up.
Make up for lost time.
Lost time. Lost time.
And I don't even know if he's alive or dead.
Help!
Somebody!
Anybody!
Help!
Bravo Company must hold their positions
until the reinforcements arrive.
If their line is broken,
there's nothing to stop the infected
between here and the ocean.
You tell that wing commander
if he doesn't get those planes in the air right now
I'm gonna come down there personally
and tear his head off his shoulders
and beat the damn zombie horde to death with his bloody skull.
What do we have here?
Insubordinate curs can't take no for an answer?
We'll see about that, eh?
Why aren't we moving? What's going on?
All right, everyone needs to relax.
Don't mess with us.
I'm not messing with you, man.
Anything happens, you'll be the first to go.
I got to get out of here!
Murphy! No!
Don't fire!
I should have slapped that fool harder.
Murphy!
Murphy! Murphy!
All right Warren, you come with me.
You guys stay here in case he comes back.
Got it.
You okay?
Let's get out of here.
Dude,
you're really starting to marsh my mellow.
Well I coulda used you about an hour ago.
Look, man.
It's been fun,
but I think it's time you go home now.
You're starting to creep me out, man.
Let's just get this over with.
Doctor Morgan Henley.
I give you mercy.
Okay.
There.
Now how am I gonna get out of here?
Warren!
Help! Somebody!
Doc? Doc?
Anybody!
Doc, is that you?
Murphy?
Murphy, is that you?
Hang in there, Doc.
Someone will come help you.
Just not me.
I'm out of ammo.
Me too.
Well look who.
I think that's the last of them.
Is everybody okay?
Anybody seen Murphy?
Murphy! Murphy!
You don't have to shout. I'm right here.
You don't sneak up on people
in the zombie apocalypse, okay?
Sorry, sorry.
I know where Doc is.
Where?
Holy shit.
I'm out of ammo.
Me too.
I got this.
Garnett!
Take cover!
No!
Is everybody okay?
Yeah.
Murphy, where's Doc?
He was down that air shaft.
What?
Let's go find that helicopter
and get out of here.
Now.
No disrespect Madame President,
but you're not fit to lead a gang of kindergartners
in a dirt clod war.
Let alone this great nation in a moment of grave national peril
like we find ourselves in now.
I've been waiting for you.
Ah, crap.
Nothing works anymore.
Nothing.
What do you people want anyway?
We're on a mission that just might save the human race.
This man has antibodies in his blood
needed to make a zombie vaccine.
We've been tasked with getting him
to a CDC lab in California.
Alive.
We need your helicopter.
Well hell, why didn't you say so sooner?
I'll fly you there myself.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
What is this, some kind of joke?
Sure, she needs a little maintenance.
But,
with some TLC,
a little help scrounging a few spare parts,
I'll have you to California in no time.
Jackass!
A friend of mine died trying to get to that pile of junk.
You and Doc were friends?
We played cards...once.
This is war, son.
We've all lost friends.
Hell, everybody I ever knew is dead.
Why am I not surprised?
You know I don't like you.
Well get in line.
General McCandles.
Sir.
Thank you, but I think we'll find alternate transportation.
You think I'm insane, don't you?
Well maybe I am.
Too much death.
Too many good men sent to an early grave.
Too many zombies.
Stand down! I got this!
Come here you Godless brain eating scum!
I'll see you in Hell!
What happened to Doc?
He didn't make it.
Zombies.
Oh God, is that...
It's Doc.
Someone's gotta...
I'll do it.
Steven "Doc" Beck.
I give you mercy.
What the hell, Warren?
You trying to kill me?
You're alive?
Damn straight I'm alive.
We thought you were dead.
Well so did I.
Some numbskull threw a grenade
in the air shaft I was stuck in.
Well hurry up!
Here.
Come on.
Give me a kiss, baby.
Well I should let you go.
I'm sure you're busy with
keeping an eye on the world and all.
Yeah.
I got a hungry dog here I better go feed.
Nice talking to you.
I hope we get to meet someday.
I'd really like that.
Good night.
Sweet prince.
Good night, fair lady.
Here's a song for all the lonely people out there,
which is just about everybody that's left.
So if you've got somebody to go through the Apocalypse with,
you better watch their backs.
Cuz there ain't many of us left.
And oh yeah,
I'd like to dedicate this song to Addison Carver,
wherever you are.
I talked to the guy twice. Come on.
You know kid,
I've been thinking about what you told me about your dad
and how you wished he knew you did the right thing
giving him mercy like you promised.
Yeah?
Well I just want you to know
your dad knows what you did for him.
And he knows you did the right thing.
You kept your promise.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, papa.
I love you.