1
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:05,000
{\pos(70,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:05,000
{\pos(70,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:05,000
{\pos(60,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:05,000
{\pos(86,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:05,000
{\pos(100,254)}人人影视
YYeTs.com

6
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:05,000
{\pos(101,267)}原创翻译  双语字幕

8
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:05,000
{\pos(240,267)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

9
00:01:05,100 --> 00:01:10,000
{\pos(190,278)}翻译：小黎   glorydai   Ethan   绒布熊   圈圈   鱼小姐

11
00:01:10,100 --> 00:01:15,000
{\pos(190,278)}初校：DJ   Ethan   glorydai    苹果

13
00:01:15,100 --> 00:01:20,000
{\pos(190,278)}时间轴：仓鼠sama   搁浅   加森   后期：冰河   监制：苹果

15
00:06:23,210 --> 00:06:27,870
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)绿   箭

16
00:06:23,210 --> 00:06:27,870
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)第一季 第八集

17
00:00:01,570 --> 00:00:03,780
我是奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.

18
00:00:03,780 --> 00:00:07,460
五年里我被困孤岛  只有一个目标
For 5 years I was stranded on an island with only one goal--

19
00:00:08,720 --> 00:00:09,720
生存
to survive.

20
00:00:09,720 --> 00:00:11,720
奥利弗·奎恩还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.

21
00:00:11,720 --> 00:00:14,210
现在我要完成父亲的遗愿
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish--

22
00:00:14,210 --> 00:00:16,080
用他留给我的名单
to use the list of names he left me

23
00:00:16,080 --> 00:00:19,230
扳倒那些荼毒城市的人
and bring down those who are poisoning my city.

24
00:00:19,730 --> 00:00:22,450
要做这些  我只能伪装成另一个人
To do this, I must become someone else.

25
00:00:22,940 --> 00:00:26,180
成为另一个存在
I must become something else.

26
00:00:26,490 --> 00:00:27,640
《绿箭》前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...

27
00:00:27,640 --> 00:00:30,090
奎恩夫人投资的公司其实并不存在
The company Mrs. Queen invested in doesn't exist.

28
00:00:30,090 --> 00:00:32,560
暴风雨公司在星城买了一个仓库
Tempest purchased a warehouse in Starling City.

29
00:00:32,890 --> 00:00:34,900
奥利弗  这是我女儿海伦娜
Oliver, this is my daughter, Helena.

30
00:00:34,900 --> 00:00:36,240
星城的治安维持者
The Starling City vigilante

31
00:00:36,240 --> 00:00:38,550
总是来无影去无踪  对吗
comes and goes as he pleases, doesn't he?

32
00:00:38,680 --> 00:00:39,510
你怎么知道的
How did you know?

33
00:00:39,510 --> 00:00:41,020
我看见你打斗的样子
I saw you fight.

34
00:00:41,520 --> 00:00:42,810
还看到了你眼睛的深处
And I saw your eyes.

35
00:00:42,810 --> 00:00:44,150
迈克尔的死是你的错
It's your fault Michael's dead.

36
00:00:44,150 --> 00:00:45,490
不能怪你父亲下令杀死他
Not your father for ordering the hit

37
00:00:45,490 --> 00:00:47,040
亦或是怪我来执行
or me for carrying it out.

38
00:00:47,040 --> 00:00:50,040
那个岛  只有像我这样的人才能懂
That island only someone like me can understand.

39
00:00:50,040 --> 00:00:52,860
我知道你觉得自己在伸张正义  其实不然
I know it feels like justice, but it's not.

40
00:00:52,860 --> 00:00:55,190
复仇就是伸张正义
Revenge is justice.

41
00:00:55,550 --> 00:00:57,900
你和我的感觉是一样的  我懂
You feel the same as I do. I know it.

42
00:01:45,980 --> 00:01:47,070
{\pos(195,239)}这里安全了

43
00:02:13,800 --> 00:02:14,640
{\pos(195,239)}现在

44
00:02:14,670 --> 00:02:15,810
{\pos(191,239)}杀了她

45
00:02:30,000 --> 00:02:31,330
把你的手从我身上拿开
Take your hands off me!

46
00:02:31,330 --> 00:02:32,770
你知不知道自己在做什么
What the hell did you think you were doing?

47
00:02:32,770 --> 00:02:34,710
那人是三合会的首领
That man was the leader of the Triad.

48
00:02:34,710 --> 00:02:37,530
我父亲认为这些人前日袭击了他的手下
My father blames them for the recent hits against his men.

49
00:02:37,540 --> 00:02:39,160
这些是你杀了的人
These are men you killed.

50
00:02:39,160 --> 00:02:40,190
没错
That's right.

51
00:02:40,340 --> 00:02:43,130
我干掉了芝山和三合会暴徒
I take out Zhishan and the Triad retaliates.

52
00:02:43,130 --> 00:02:45,330
我已经削弱了我父亲组织的力量
I have weakened my father's organization to the point

53
00:02:45,340 --> 00:02:48,000
他不可能在他们的攻势下存活的
where there is no way that he can survive their onslaught.

54
00:02:48,010 --> 00:02:50,020
然后呢  你就能报仇了吗
What, and then you'll have your revenge?

55
00:02:50,890 --> 00:02:52,490
然后我就为他
Then I have justice,

56
00:02:52,560 --> 00:02:55,420
对迈克尔和我的所作所为伸张了正义
for what he did to Michael and me.

57
00:02:55,420 --> 00:02:56,950
这不是伸张正义
It's not justice.

58
00:02:58,220 --> 00:02:59,670
你做的事就是伸张正义吗
And what you do is?

59
00:02:59,670 --> 00:03:01,820
你能让我给你看吗
Would you let me show you?

60
00:03:08,450 --> 00:03:09,810
还需要别的吗
Get you anything else?

61
00:03:10,020 --> 00:03:11,240
不用了  谢谢  卡莉
No, thank you, Carly.

62
00:03:11,240 --> 00:03:12,690
我小叔子呢
Where's my brother-in-law?

63
00:03:12,920 --> 00:03:14,990
天色已晚  这又是贫民区
It's late and this is the glades.

64
00:03:14,990 --> 00:03:16,340
他不是应该保全你的安全吗
Shouldn't he be keeping you safe?

65
00:03:16,340 --> 00:03:18,310
她比外表要坚强
She is tougher than she looks.

66
00:03:23,460 --> 00:03:26,220
我好久都没和女孩第二次约会了
I haven't been on a second date in a while.

67
00:03:27,080 --> 00:03:28,540
目前为止感觉很不错
It feels good so far.

68
00:03:29,480 --> 00:03:32,040
听着  我们上了床
Look, um, we slept together,

69
00:03:32,040 --> 00:03:34,600
感觉很棒
and it was really nice.

70
00:03:34,610 --> 00:03:37,390
正是我需要的  但我并没在寻求什么
And I needed it. But I'm not looking for anything.

71
00:03:37,400 --> 00:03:39,360
是  因为你已经把所有事都想清楚了
Right. Because you have everything figured out.

72
00:03:39,360 --> 00:03:40,970
我觉得还轮不到你品头论足
I don't think you're one to judge.

73
00:03:40,970 --> 00:03:42,490
我看到你杀人了  记得吗
I saw you kill people, remember?

74
00:03:42,490 --> 00:03:43,940
我只在必要的时候
I only kill people

75
00:03:44,300 --> 00:03:46,130
才还会杀人
when it is absolutely necessary.

76
00:03:46,130 --> 00:03:47,550
这不是我的初衷
It's not my opening move.

77
00:03:47,550 --> 00:03:48,860
而你的那套做事方法
And the way that you're going,

78
00:03:48,860 --> 00:03:50,190
会伤及无辜的
you're gonna get somebody hurt,

79
00:03:50,190 --> 00:03:52,200
像我母亲  或是你自己
like my mother or yourself.

80
00:03:52,200 --> 00:03:53,930
对你母亲我深表抱歉
I'm sorry about your mother.

81
00:03:54,120 --> 00:03:55,120
那是个意外
That was an accident.

82
00:03:55,120 --> 00:03:56,670
在你成功报复你父亲之前
How many more accidents have to happen

83
00:03:56,670 --> 00:03:58,860
还要发生多少次意外
before you're done getting back at your father?

84
00:03:59,310 --> 00:04:01,090
最好一次都没有
Hopefully none.

85
00:04:01,500 --> 00:04:03,830
我没有在报复他
I am not getting back at him.

86
00:04:03,830 --> 00:04:07,120
我在夺走对他来说一切有意义的东西
I--I am stripping away everything that has meaning to him,

87
00:04:07,120 --> 00:04:09,360
正像他杀了迈克尔时对我做的一切
just like he did to me when he had Michael killed.

88
00:04:09,360 --> 00:04:10,920
我给你另指一条路怎么样
What if I could show you another way,

89
00:04:10,930 --> 00:04:13,410
一条既能搞垮你父亲的组织
a way you could take down your father's organization

90
00:04:13,410 --> 00:04:16,030
又不会危及无辜的方法
without putting innocent people at risk?

91
00:04:20,580 --> 00:04:21,540
谢谢你
Thank you

92
00:04:21,990 --> 00:04:23,700
的咖啡
for the coffee...

93
00:04:24,690 --> 00:04:25,960
还有床上功夫
and the sex.

94
00:04:26,250 --> 00:04:27,920
但是我并不感兴趣
But I'm not interested.

95
00:04:31,020 --> 00:04:32,950
奎恩工业股份有限公司
钢铁制造与焊接

96
00:04:34,530 --> 00:04:35,750
我不知道下次奥运会在哪开
I don't know where the next Olympics are at,

97
00:04:35,750 --> 00:04:38,490
但你可以报名参加一下
but you might want to think about signing yourself up.

98
00:04:40,160 --> 00:04:41,690
你想谈谈昨天晚上吗
So, you want to talk about last night?

99
00:04:43,410 --> 00:04:46,520
好吧  上次我们聊天时
Ok. Last time you and I spoke,

100
00:04:47,040 --> 00:04:48,600
你正要去阻止海伦娜·波提纳尔
you were on your way to stop Helena Bertinelli

101
00:04:48,600 --> 00:04:50,930
不让她女侠走单骑  独打黑手党
from her one-woman war against the mafia.

102
00:04:51,350 --> 00:04:52,750
那件事进展如何
How'd that work out for you?

103
00:04:52,760 --> 00:04:55,730
尼克·赛瓦缇  弗兰克·波提纳尔的得力助手
Nick Salvati, Frank Bertinelli's right hand,

104
00:04:55,730 --> 00:04:57,310
被人发现脖子被扭断
was found with his neck snapped

105
00:04:57,310 --> 00:04:58,950
边上还有几个歹徒的尸体
along with a few of his thugs.

106
00:04:59,510 --> 00:05:00,750
是她还是你干的
Was that her or you?

107
00:05:01,210 --> 00:05:03,450
有人袭击时  我和海伦娜在一起
I was with Helena when somebody jumped us.

108
00:05:03,810 --> 00:05:05,070
我们别无他选
We didn't have a choice.

109
00:05:05,930 --> 00:05:06,540
我们
We?

110
00:05:06,540 --> 00:05:08,280
她知道  狄格尔  关于我的事
She knows, Diggle, about me.

111
00:05:08,280 --> 00:05:09,640
不是我秘密揭露  就是她性命不保
It was my secret or her life.

112
00:05:09,640 --> 00:05:12,120
这不再只是你的秘密了  奥利弗
It's not just your secret anymore, Oliver.

113
00:05:12,330 --> 00:05:13,090
这女人是个杀人魔
This woman is a killer.

114
00:05:13,090 --> 00:05:14,990
这城市到处都是她杀的人的尸体
She's been dropping bodies all over the city.

115
00:05:14,990 --> 00:05:16,430
狄格尔  她并不像你想的那样
Diggle, she's not what you think she is.

116
00:05:16,430 --> 00:05:19,120
三年前  她正想把她父亲告发给FBI
3 years ago she was gonna turn her father in to the FBI.

117
00:05:19,120 --> 00:05:21,110
她把所有关于他的信息存在笔记本里
She put everything she had on him on a laptop.

118
00:05:21,110 --> 00:05:24,330
她父亲发现了  以为那是她未婚夫的
Her father found it, thought it belonged to her fiance,

119
00:05:24,330 --> 00:05:26,050
然后把他杀了
and had him murdered.

120
00:05:28,460 --> 00:05:30,820
听着  这事很沉重  老兄
All right, listen, that's a heavy thing, man.

121
00:05:30,820 --> 00:05:33,620
但这不能改变她很危险这一事实
But it doesn't change the fact that she is dangerous.

122
00:05:33,620 --> 00:05:35,750
而且如果波提纳尔反击三合会
And if Bertinelli retaliates against the Triad

123
00:05:35,750 --> 00:05:38,460
或察觉到什么  三合会会杀人不眨眼
or perceived to, the Triad is gonna rain down hell

124
00:05:38,460 --> 00:05:40,550
无辜之人必将被杀
and innocent people are gonna be killed.

125
00:05:42,210 --> 00:05:43,850
她很迷茫  狄格尔
She's lost, Diggle,

126
00:05:44,150 --> 00:05:46,620
而且无论她知情与否  我都能救她
and whether she knows it or not, I can save her,

127
00:05:47,100 --> 00:05:48,570
阻止她的鲁莽之举
stop her from doing anything reckless.

128
00:05:48,570 --> 00:05:50,570
问题正在于此  你救不了她  懂吗
That's just it. You can't save her, ok?

129
00:05:50,570 --> 00:05:52,080
有些人本性难移
Some people don't change.

130
00:05:52,080 --> 00:05:53,200
我就变了
I can.

131
00:05:53,620 --> 00:05:54,660
我也能帮助她
I can help her.

132
00:05:54,670 --> 00:05:55,560
好吧
All right.

133
00:05:56,850 --> 00:05:59,020
也许你认为你比实际更有说服力
Maybe you think you're more persuasive than you are,

134
00:05:59,890 --> 00:06:01,510
又或者她自认为像现在这样
or maybe she thinks she's fine the way she is

135
00:06:01,510 --> 00:06:03,040
变成正义使者是好的选择
on her mission of righteous fury.

136
00:06:03,040 --> 00:06:04,450
但不管是哪种
Whatever it is, either way,

137
00:06:04,450 --> 00:06:07,610
任何一种都没有好下场
all of this, it ends badly.

138
00:06:07,910 --> 00:06:08,940
不管怎样
Either way...

139
00:06:15,620 --> 00:06:16,820
我都得试一试
I got to try.

140
00:06:28,920 --> 00:06:31,550
你一大早要去哪儿啊  你才刚到家
Where are you off to so early? You just got home.

141
00:06:31,550 --> 00:06:33,330
几周海外旅行的后果是
The trouble with traveling overseas for a few weeks

142
00:06:33,340 --> 00:06:35,980
几周的文件都堆在办公桌上等我处理
is that a few weeks' worth of work is piling up on my desk.

143
00:06:35,980 --> 00:06:38,290
我只是想早点处理完好松口气
I just want to start digging my way out from underneath it.

144
00:06:38,290 --> 00:06:39,340
当然
Of course.

145
00:06:44,650 --> 00:06:45,610
这是什么
What is it?

146
00:06:49,210 --> 00:06:51,210
从你离开后我们就没交谈过
We haven't spoken since you left.

147
00:06:52,880 --> 00:06:54,080
真正的交谈
Really spoken.

148
00:06:55,190 --> 00:06:56,110
我知道
I know.

149
00:06:57,470 --> 00:06:59,180
我能理解当你得知
Well, I can imagine finding out

150
00:06:59,180 --> 00:07:00,930
我将罗伯特的游艇打捞上来
that I had Robert's yacht salvaged

151
00:07:00,930 --> 00:07:02,230
发现他是被谋杀的
and that he was murdered,

152
00:07:02,230 --> 00:07:04,170
你一下子无法承受
it was a lot for you to take in.

153
00:07:07,230 --> 00:07:08,430
是啊
Yes, it was.

154
00:07:09,960 --> 00:07:13,020
我只不想让你觉得我不再可信了
I just don't want you to feel that you can't trust me anymore.

155
00:07:14,000 --> 00:07:16,840
我撒谎  并不是想伤害你
I wasn't lying to-- to hurt you,

156
00:07:17,170 --> 00:07:18,670
而是保证你的安全
but to keep you safe.

157
00:07:20,040 --> 00:07:21,650
我并没有改变  沃尔特
I haven't changed, Walter.

158
00:07:22,600 --> 00:07:25,420
我还是那个你当初深爱并迎娶的女人
I'm still the woman you fell in love with and married.

159
00:07:26,870 --> 00:07:28,250
你明白吗
Do you see that?

160
00:07:29,080 --> 00:07:31,100
是的  我当然明白
Yeah. Of course I do.

161
00:07:34,700 --> 00:07:36,180
我只是希望我们
I just want us to agree

162
00:07:36,180 --> 00:07:38,250
能够坦诚相待  向前看
to be honest with one another, moving forward.

163
00:07:38,250 --> 00:07:39,680
当然
Ok. Yes, of course.

164
00:07:39,870 --> 00:07:40,820
沃尔特
Walter.

165
00:07:43,080 --> 00:07:44,820
你能送我去学校吗
Will you give me a lift to school?

166
00:07:45,110 --> 00:07:48,310
我有时喜欢搞点意外  准时到校
I like to mix it up sometimes and actually be on time.

167
00:07:48,320 --> 00:07:50,230
那是我为人父的荣幸
That would be my parental privilege.

168
00:07:52,060 --> 00:07:54,070
或者  你也可以给我买一辆敞篷车
Or, you know, you could just buy me a convertible

169
00:07:54,070 --> 00:07:55,150
以后就不麻烦你了
and then we could avoid this.

170
00:07:55,150 --> 00:07:56,390
那不就没有和你
What, and miss out on all those

171
00:07:56,390 --> 00:07:58,330
在车上交谈的美好时光了
wonderful conversations we have in the car?

172
00:07:59,060 --> 00:08:00,490
我可不想这样
I don't think so.

173
00:08:03,040 --> 00:08:04,610
我很抱歉  弗兰克
I'm so sorry, Frank.

174
00:08:04,610 --> 00:08:07,190
我真不该在你肩膀上哭了一夜
The last thing you need is me crying on your shoulder all night.

175
00:08:08,340 --> 00:08:10,180
我只是不敢相信尼克就这样走了
I just can't believe that Nick is gone.

176
00:08:10,190 --> 00:08:11,840
迪娜  你和小尼克
Dina, look, you and Nicky,

177
00:08:12,460 --> 00:08:13,720
你们就像我的家人一样
you're like family to me, ok?

178
00:08:13,720 --> 00:08:15,060
在我家里
And in my family,

179
00:08:15,080 --> 00:08:17,100
互相照顾是应该的
we take care of our own. Ok?

180
00:08:19,580 --> 00:08:21,060
请节哀顺变
I'm sorry for your loss.

181
00:08:21,850 --> 00:08:23,580
尼克就像我的哥哥一样
Nick was like a brother to me.

182
00:08:25,230 --> 00:08:26,590
好了  来
Hey now, come on.

183
00:08:29,360 --> 00:08:31,460
我们稍后聊
We'll talk to you soon. Ok.

184
00:08:35,640 --> 00:08:37,630
我一定要抓到杀害尼克的狗崽子
I'm gonna find the son of a bitch who did this.

185
00:08:38,530 --> 00:08:41,000
我以我的生命立誓  我要他血债血偿
And on my life, I'm gonna make him pay.

186
00:08:45,710 --> 00:08:47,700
她总是丢三落四的
You know, that girl's always forgetting something.

187
00:08:51,000 --> 00:08:51,950
弗兰克
Frank.

188
00:08:52,040 --> 00:08:53,400
抱歉突然拜访
Sorry to drop by unannounced.

189
00:08:53,400 --> 00:08:54,950
不不  进来  没关系
No, no, no, come on in. It's all right.

190
00:08:54,950 --> 00:08:56,780
快进来
Come on in. Um...

191
00:08:58,260 --> 00:09:01,360
我知道我们一直致力于那个建设项目
Look, I know, I know we've been working on that construction deal,

192
00:09:01,370 --> 00:09:03,450
很抱歉因为我而搁置了
and I'm sorry for my dropping the ball.

193
00:09:03,450 --> 00:09:04,650
家里最近有人去世了
We've had a death in the family.

194
00:09:04,650 --> 00:09:06,430
-我很遗憾听到这个消息  -谢谢
- I'm terribly sorry to hear that. - Thank you.

195
00:09:06,430 --> 00:09:10,550
其实我今天不是来讨论生意上的事的
Actually, though, I'm not here to discuss business.

196
00:09:13,640 --> 00:09:15,050
噢  好吧
Oh. Ok.

197
00:09:17,380 --> 00:09:18,660
这...
This is...

198
00:09:19,650 --> 00:09:22,110
我可不会阻碍你们两个谈恋爱
This is one merger I won't stand in the way of.

199
00:09:23,770 --> 00:09:24,930
我先离开了  亲爱的
Excuse me, sweetie.

200
00:09:25,010 --> 00:09:26,770
爸爸知道什么时候该走开
A father knows when he's not needed.

201
00:09:31,870 --> 00:09:33,190
我没说清楚吗
Was I not clear

202
00:09:33,920 --> 00:09:36,260
我没有兴趣跟你谈
that I wasn't interested in talking?

203
00:09:37,050 --> 00:09:38,580
你不需要说话
You don't have to talk.

204
00:09:52,660 --> 00:09:53,770
她是谁
Who was she?

205
00:09:56,230 --> 00:09:58,180
很久以前的一位故人
Somebody I knew a long time ago.

206
00:09:56,300 --> 00:09:58,400
{\pos(192,236)}莎拉·兰斯
挚爱的女儿
妹妹

207
00:09:59,270 --> 00:10:02,900
我当时跟她的姐姐在恋爱
I--I was dating her sister,

208
00:10:02,920 --> 00:10:04,170
而且我们的感情越来越认真
And it was getting serious.

209
00:10:04,170 --> 00:10:08,160
但当时  我不知道怎么对待一份认真的感情
But back then, I did not do serious well.

210
00:10:08,810 --> 00:10:11,010
但我很擅长把事情搞砸
But I was excellent at screwing things up.

211
00:10:15,570 --> 00:10:17,380
我开始与莎拉上床
I started sleeping with Sara.

212
00:10:18,940 --> 00:10:21,690
我开始与我女朋友的妹妹上床
I started sleeping with my girlfriend's sister.

213
00:10:25,520 --> 00:10:28,200
我把她带上游艇  她死了
I brought her on the yacht and she died.

214
00:10:30,490 --> 00:10:31,890
就死在我面前
Right in front of me.

215
00:10:33,730 --> 00:10:36,110
我伤害了她的家人
And I hurt-- I hurt her family...

216
00:10:38,650 --> 00:10:40,030
我却毫不在意
I just didn't care.

217
00:10:44,060 --> 00:10:47,030
在沦落荒岛之前  我不是个好人  我...
Before the island, I wasn't a good person. I was...

218
00:10:48,580 --> 00:10:50,810
自私  轻率
selfish and thoughtless

219
00:10:50,810 --> 00:10:52,770
而且很糟糕  那些都...
and awful, and it affected--

220
00:10:53,850 --> 00:10:55,440
影响到别人
really affected people.

221
00:10:57,990 --> 00:10:59,230
我爱的人
People I loved.

222
00:11:00,720 --> 00:11:01,810
因为  海伦娜
'Cause, Helena...

223
00:11:03,910 --> 00:11:05,430
你现在也像处于一座岛上
You're on an island, too.

224
00:11:07,210 --> 00:11:08,520
奥利弗  我...
Oliver, I...

225
00:11:10,020 --> 00:11:11,530
我想让你走进我的内心
I want to let you in.

226
00:11:13,940 --> 00:11:17,770
但迈克尔是我最后一个敞开心扉的人
But...Michael was the last man I opened up to.

227
00:11:20,020 --> 00:11:21,520
我不能再受伤了
I can't be hurt again.

228
00:11:21,590 --> 00:11:23,630
我永远不会伤害你
I'd never hurt you.

229
00:11:26,380 --> 00:11:27,750
我永远不会伤害你
I would never hurt you.

230
00:11:29,340 --> 00:11:30,510
我发誓
I promise.

231
00:11:40,290 --> 00:11:41,120
放松
Relax.

232
00:11:41,130 --> 00:11:42,220
放松  放松
Relax, relax, relax.

233
00:11:42,220 --> 00:11:44,970
轻轻地往后拉
Now, pull back gently.

234
00:11:45,570 --> 00:11:46,240
你需要三根手指
You need all 3 fingers

235
00:11:46,250 --> 00:11:48,570
同时松开弓弦
to come off the bowstring at the same time.

236
00:11:48,750 --> 00:11:51,640
放松  深呼吸
Relax. Breathe.

237
00:11:54,330 --> 00:11:55,420
发射
And release.

238
00:11:59,170 --> 00:12:00,550
这是在浪费时间
This is a waste of time.

239
00:12:00,610 --> 00:12:01,750
我在教你新东西
I'm trying to teach you something.

240
00:12:01,750 --> 00:12:03,710
最低效的杀人方法吗
What, the least effective way to shoot people?

241
00:12:03,710 --> 00:12:05,550
不  是控制力
No. Control.

242
00:12:06,390 --> 00:12:07,840
想用好弓和箭
To use a bow and arrow

243
00:12:08,670 --> 00:12:12,640
需要耐心和操练
requires patience and discipline.

244
00:12:43,490 --> 00:12:44,690
我可以这样持续一整天
I can do this all day.

245
00:12:44,790 --> 00:12:45,490
挺有意思的
It's kind of fun.

246
00:12:45,490 --> 00:12:47,560
我喜欢有耐力的男人
I love a man with stamina.

247
00:12:48,970 --> 00:12:50,960
我们的战斗有相同的地方
Our crusades have something in common.

248
00:12:52,780 --> 00:12:54,680
我的战斗也是始自我父亲
Mine started with my father, too.

249
00:12:54,890 --> 00:12:56,730
他留给我一份名单
He left me with a list.

250
00:12:57,150 --> 00:12:58,420
上面的人需要被提醒
People who need to be reminded

251
00:12:58,420 --> 00:13:00,750
星城可不能免费奉送给他们
that Starling City isn't theirs for the taking.

252
00:13:02,110 --> 00:13:04,160
安东尼·文萨也在上面
Anthony Venza is in here.

253
00:13:04,500 --> 00:13:05,500
他是我爸手下的
He works for my dad.

254
00:13:05,500 --> 00:13:08,060
他干的是非法处方药勾当
He deals illegal prescription pills.

255
00:13:10,480 --> 00:13:11,960
狄格尔  这位是海伦娜
Diggle, this is Helena.

256
00:13:11,960 --> 00:13:14,530
狄格尔是我的...
Diggle's my, uh...

257
00:13:15,490 --> 00:13:16,660
伙伴
associate.

258
00:13:17,060 --> 00:13:18,490
奥利弗的任何伙伴...
Well, any associate of Oliver's is--

259
00:13:18,490 --> 00:13:21,350
对你来说什么都不是  小姐
absolutely nothing to you, ma'am.

260
00:13:23,310 --> 00:13:26,380
我就不打扰你们两个伙伴谈话了
I'll leave you two "associates"...

261
00:13:33,050 --> 00:13:34,290
她知道我的名字
She knows my name.

262
00:13:34,480 --> 00:13:35,560
那可真好
That's lovely.

263
00:13:36,490 --> 00:13:37,490
你可以信任她的
You can trust her.

264
00:13:37,500 --> 00:13:38,620
可惜我就是不信任
Except I don't.

265
00:13:41,040 --> 00:13:42,290
你跟她上床了吗  奥利弗
You sleeping with this girl, Oliver?

266
00:13:42,300 --> 00:13:44,190
我觉得那跟你没有任何关系  狄格尔
Well, I don't think that's any of your business, Diggle.

267
00:13:44,190 --> 00:13:46,380
当你将我拖下水  就与我有关系了
It became my business when you brought me into this.

268
00:13:47,530 --> 00:13:48,240
当我加入的时候
And when I signed on,

269
00:13:48,240 --> 00:13:50,140
我说过我会让你的脑袋保持清醒
I told you I was gonna keep your head straight.

270
00:13:50,590 --> 00:13:53,150
奥利弗  你很寂寞  尽管你都不愿意承认
Well, Oliver, you're lonely. Lonelier than you want to admit.

271
00:13:53,150 --> 00:13:54,750
所以你才觉得你可以改变这个女孩
And that's why you think you can change this girl,

272
00:13:54,750 --> 00:13:56,510
因为你需要那种想法的支撑
because you need to think you can.

273
00:13:56,740 --> 00:13:57,860
你就像一个有毒瘾的人
You're like a dope fiend

274
00:13:57,860 --> 00:13:59,190
自认为可以解决自己的瘾症
who thinks he can deal with his own addiction

275
00:13:59,190 --> 00:14:01,310
方法是帮助另一个吸毒者戒毒成功
by making another addict go straight.

276
00:14:01,520 --> 00:14:03,280
奥利弗  你的所为很危险
Oliver, what you do is dangerous.

277
00:14:03,380 --> 00:14:05,360
一旦你分不清谁是好人  谁是坏人
And getting confused about who's good and who's bad

278
00:14:05,360 --> 00:14:07,070
就容易将自己送上死路
is a good way to get yourself dead.

279
00:14:09,440 --> 00:14:10,400
你说完了吗
You done?

280
00:14:12,890 --> 00:14:13,900
是的  我说完了
Yeah, I'm done.

281
00:14:14,880 --> 00:14:15,840
只是这事说完了
With this.

282
00:14:16,380 --> 00:14:17,900
至于其他事  我不知道
Everything else, I don't know.

283
00:14:19,260 --> 00:14:20,860
我不知道  奥利弗  该你告诉我
I don't know, Oliver. You tell me.

284
00:14:32,460 --> 00:14:33,800
我希望你明晚没有其他安排
I hope you don't have plans tomorrow night,

285
00:14:33,810 --> 00:14:36,060
因为我刚在那家新餐馆预约了桌位
Because I just got us a rez at that new restaurant,

286
00:14:36,060 --> 00:14:37,670
"精致食盐"  开幕之夜
Table salt, opening night.

287
00:14:37,670 --> 00:14:39,690
那地方不是贵得离谱吗
Isn't that place ridiculously expensive?

288
00:14:39,690 --> 00:14:41,440
任何值得一去的地方都很贵
Everywhere worth going is.

289
00:14:42,130 --> 00:14:44,780
当你担心时  额头上就会出现最可爱的小皱纹
You have the cutest crinkle in your forehead when you're worried.

290
00:14:44,780 --> 00:14:46,970
汤米  别闹了  我是认真的
Tommy, stop. This is serious.

291
00:14:46,970 --> 00:14:48,330
我以为你要过上一种更节俭的生活呢
I thought you were going to live more frugally.

292
00:14:48,340 --> 00:14:50,910
我知道  除了我  大家都长成成熟的大人了
Yeah, I know. Everybody is grown up except for me.

293
00:14:50,910 --> 00:14:52,490
连奥利弗都开始工作了
Even Oliver has a job.

294
00:14:52,490 --> 00:14:54,390
他在那家新夜店供职了
He's working on that new night club.

295
00:14:55,400 --> 00:14:57,410
你的表情说明你在思考  你在思考什么
You have thinky face. Why do you have thinky face?

296
00:14:57,410 --> 00:14:59,510
你有没有想过让奥利弗帮你找份工作
Have you ever thought about asking Oliver for a job?

297
00:14:59,510 --> 00:15:00,530
绝对没想过
Not even once.

298
00:15:00,570 --> 00:15:02,650
虽然我不怎么喜欢你这方面
This isn't a quality that I love most about you,

299
00:15:02,650 --> 00:15:05,110
但你确实对夜店很熟悉  也知道怎么制造乐子
but you do know the club scene and how to have fun.

300
00:15:05,860 --> 00:15:07,380
你说的十分有道理
You make some very valid points.

301
00:15:07,590 --> 00:15:09,870
听着  我会处理好的  我晚点跟奥利谈谈
Look, I'll take care of it. I'll talk to Ollie later

302
00:15:09,870 --> 00:15:11,140
到时候看看他的想法
And we'll see what he thinks.

303
00:15:11,630 --> 00:15:13,720
他会觉得这是个超棒的主意
He is gonna think it is a great idea.

304
00:15:16,140 --> 00:15:17,470
你的澳大利亚之行如何
How was your trip to Australia?

305
00:15:18,080 --> 00:15:19,470
我一直都想去的
I've always wanted to go.

306
00:15:19,470 --> 00:15:21,050
南半球的澳洲  就...
Down under. It's just--

307
00:15:21,450 --> 00:15:22,850
我对袋鼠有种特别的情节
I have this thing about kangaroos.

308
00:15:22,850 --> 00:15:24,510
更确切说是种恐惧症  它们让我兴奋
More of a phobia. They wig me out.

309
00:15:24,510 --> 00:15:26,320
它们看着很邪恶  我确定它们的照片
They look evil, and I'm sure their picture's up

310
00:15:26,320 --> 00:15:28,320
会出现在那国家的任何东西上面
on like everything everywhere in that country.

311
00:15:28,480 --> 00:15:30,700
你不是有要事要跟我说吗  斯莫克小姐
You had something important to tell me, Ms. Smoak?

312
00:15:30,920 --> 00:15:32,150
是的
Yes, I did.

313
00:15:32,870 --> 00:15:36,370
是关于暴风雨公司的  你妻子的神秘有限公司
It's about tempest. Your wife's mysterious LLC,

314
00:15:36,480 --> 00:15:38,600
她曾把公司资金转向那个公司
the one she diverted company funds to.

315
00:15:39,080 --> 00:15:41,110
我很感激你在此事上的辛勤查证  但是
I appreciate your diligence on this, but, uh,

316
00:15:41,310 --> 00:15:43,500
但那只是我和我妻子间小小的误解
it was a simple misunderstanding between my wife and I.

317
00:15:43,510 --> 00:15:44,310
一切都已经解决了
Everything's been resolved.

318
00:15:44,310 --> 00:15:45,950
不  并没有
No. See, it hasn't.

319
00:15:46,160 --> 00:15:49,110
在汇款方面有些东西让我觉得十分可疑
There was something about the money transfer that felt hinky to me.

320
00:15:49,930 --> 00:15:51,800
你妻子从公司撤走的资金
The money your wife withdrew from the company,

321
00:15:51,800 --> 00:15:53,660
不是只有我一个人在追查
I wasn't the only one who tracked it.

322
00:15:53,680 --> 00:15:55,200
她也在被别人跟踪追查
She was being shadowed by another entity,

323
00:15:55,200 --> 00:15:56,890
不管那人是谁  手段都很高超
And whoever it is, they're good.

324
00:15:57,070 --> 00:15:58,320
国家安全局水准
NSA good.

325
00:15:59,040 --> 00:16:00,140
但是  如你所知
But, as you know,

326
00:16:00,230 --> 00:16:01,340
我也很棒
I'm good, too.

327
00:16:01,690 --> 00:16:03,370
所以尽管他们没有留下
So even though they left almost no trace

328
00:16:03,370 --> 00:16:04,870
曾侵入我们系统的任何证据
of their presence in our system,

329
00:16:05,260 --> 00:16:06,740
我确实找到了一样东西
I did manage to find one thing.

330
00:16:07,830 --> 00:16:09,110
其实是一张图片
Well, one image.

331
00:16:11,210 --> 00:16:13,390
你知道那个标志代表什么吗  先生
Does that symbol mean something to you, sir?

332
00:16:14,600 --> 00:16:15,560
不知道
No.

333
00:16:17,070 --> 00:16:18,390
我在意的是
What means something to me

334
00:16:18,830 --> 00:16:20,220
我手下的一名员工
is one of my employees

335
00:16:20,580 --> 00:16:23,860
未经授权就探查我妻子的私事
prying into my wife's private business without authorization.

336
00:16:23,980 --> 00:16:25,310
如果此事再有下次
And should it happen again,

337
00:16:26,130 --> 00:16:28,000
我就将你停职
I'll have you suspended.

338
00:16:28,520 --> 00:16:29,710
清楚了吗
Is that clear?

339
00:16:31,260 --> 00:16:32,530
十分清楚
Crystal.

340
00:16:51,820 --> 00:16:52,980
你朋友呢
Where's your friend?

341
00:16:52,980 --> 00:16:54,480
今晚只有你我二人
Just the two of us tonight.

342
00:16:55,370 --> 00:16:56,690
是吗
Oh, really?

343
00:16:56,960 --> 00:16:58,710
你打算怎么过呢
And what did you have in mind?

344
00:16:58,780 --> 00:17:00,100
进行示范教学
An object lesson.

345
00:17:01,650 --> 00:17:03,120
我们要对付安东尼·文萨了吗
We're going after Anthony Venza?

346
00:17:03,120 --> 00:17:05,750
是的  但要按我的方式进行
Yes. But we're doing it on my terms.

347
00:17:05,800 --> 00:17:07,680
你父亲会失去手下一员大将
Your father loses a piece of his organization,

348
00:17:07,680 --> 00:17:09,770
但过程中不能让无辜的人受伤
but no innocent people get hurt in the process.

349
00:17:11,970 --> 00:17:12,880
这是什么
What is it?

350
00:17:12,880 --> 00:17:13,530
我跟你解释过
I explained to you that

351
00:17:13,530 --> 00:17:15,530
枪是充满情绪和不可预测性的武器
guns were weapons of emotion and unpredictability,

352
00:17:15,530 --> 00:17:17,630
但鉴于你还不擅长箭术
But since you are far from an expert at archery,

353
00:17:18,220 --> 00:17:20,510
可以先用这个暂时凑合
this will have to do, for now.

354
00:17:24,870 --> 00:17:25,990
我喜欢
I like it.

355
00:17:26,560 --> 00:17:27,900
你可不能穿成这样出去
You can't go out like that.

356
00:17:28,750 --> 00:17:30,440
怎么  你还有多的兜帽吗
Why? You got a spare hood?

357
00:17:36,500 --> 00:17:37,700
那会是紫色的吗
Does it come in purple?

358
00:17:42,370 --> 00:17:43,610
我喜欢紫色
I like purple.

359
00:17:45,250 --> 00:17:46,540
这可不是毒品
This isn't crack.

360
00:17:46,880 --> 00:17:48,290
毒品谁都能卖出去
Anyone can sell crack.

361
00:17:48,500 --> 00:17:50,610
只要穿着连帽衫  躲在街角兜售就行
All you need's a street corner and a hoodie.

362
00:17:51,020 --> 00:17:53,750
这可是医药级羟考酮
This is pharmaceutical grade oxycodone.

363
00:17:54,540 --> 00:17:57,120
就像是鱼子酱  就像是香槟
It is caviar. It is champagne.

364
00:17:58,060 --> 00:18:01,040
你将这些卖给富人家庭
And you sell this with fancy houses,

365
00:18:01,050 --> 00:18:04,200
在派对上卖给那些钱多的富二代
at parties with rich kids have got money to burn.

366
00:18:07,610 --> 00:18:08,760
快出去看下
Check it out!

367
00:18:24,410 --> 00:18:25,740
不管你是谁
Whoever you are,

368
00:18:26,230 --> 00:18:28,410
你真觉得自己能完好无缺的离开这儿吗
You really think you're gonna get out of here in one piece?

369
00:18:28,510 --> 00:18:30,000
我也是这么想的
I was thinking the same thing.

370
00:18:31,830 --> 00:18:33,130
安东尼·文萨
Anthony Venza...

371
00:18:36,060 --> 00:18:38,540
你辜负了这座城市
You have failed this city.

372
00:18:57,410 --> 00:19:00,940
求求你  别伤害我
Please...just don't hurt me.

373
00:19:02,910 --> 00:19:06,110
伤一小点儿怎么样
How about just a little?

374
00:19:12,900 --> 00:19:15,620
价值数百万美元的非法毒品被没收
Millions of dollars' worth of illegal drugs confiscated,

375
00:19:15,620 --> 00:19:17,870
这对你父亲的不法行为是一个巨大的打击
a massive blow to your father's criminal proceeds,

376
00:19:17,960 --> 00:19:19,740
并且没人牺牲
and nobody had to die.

377
00:19:20,660 --> 00:19:21,850
这才是正义
Justice.

378
00:19:23,900 --> 00:19:25,090
你怎么看
What do you think?

379
00:19:25,940 --> 00:19:29,650
感觉不错
I think this feels good.

380
00:19:31,970 --> 00:19:33,940
不仅仅是正义这部分
And not just the justice part.

381
00:19:47,660 --> 00:19:49,970
安东尼·文萨昨晚被逮捕
Anthony Venza was arrested last night.

382
00:19:50,130 --> 00:19:51,830
警方没收了一整个仓库的
The police confiscated a warehouse

383
00:19:51,830 --> 00:19:53,400
非法毒品
full of illegal prescription drugs

384
00:19:53,400 --> 00:19:55,610
黑市估价百万以上
with a street value estimated in the millions.

385
00:19:55,970 --> 00:20:00,030
多名未受证实的目击者称
Several unconfirmed witnesses reported

386
00:20:00,040 --> 00:20:00,710
目睹到星城治安维护者离开案发现场
seeing the Starling City vigilante leaving the scene

387
00:20:00,990 --> 00:20:02,870
身边还有一名未知伙伴
with another unknown accomplice...

388
00:20:02,880 --> 00:20:04,190
很可能是名女性
possibly a woman.

389
00:20:07,740 --> 00:20:08,960
年代不好吗
Bad year?

390
00:20:09,880 --> 00:20:11,550
我是指这威士忌
The scotch, I mean.

391
00:20:11,830 --> 00:20:13,110
是啊  抱歉
Yeah. Sorry.

392
00:20:15,620 --> 00:20:17,000
又一个生意上的挫败
Another business setback.

393
00:20:18,720 --> 00:20:19,860
哇
Wow.

394
00:20:21,840 --> 00:20:23,180
你看上去美极了
You look beautiful.

395
00:20:24,790 --> 00:20:26,090
因为奥利弗·奎恩吗
Oliver Queen?

396
00:20:27,800 --> 00:20:30,920
看见你再次开心起来真好
Oh...it's nice to see you happy again.

397
00:20:32,160 --> 00:20:33,390
你抑郁太久了
It's been too long.

398
00:20:38,770 --> 00:20:39,810
是我
Yeah.

399
00:20:42,900 --> 00:20:45,120
对  文萨的事我听说了
Yeah. Yeah, I heard about Venza.

400
00:20:46,640 --> 00:20:48,280
我知道这给我们带来什么
Yeah, I know where that leaves us!

401
00:20:54,700 --> 00:20:55,970
很抱歉我得出去一下
I'm sorry to rush out.

402
00:20:55,970 --> 00:20:58,550
我有一场临时理事会会议
I have this impromptu board of directors meeting

403
00:20:58,550 --> 00:21:01,090
是关于星城现代美术博物馆的
with the Starling City Modern Art Museum.

404
00:21:02,500 --> 00:21:03,770
我虽然不太懂艺术
I don't know much about art,

405
00:21:03,770 --> 00:21:05,560
但是我知道该怎么付钱
But I do know how to pay for it.

406
00:21:05,560 --> 00:21:07,920
完全不担心  大展身手吧
No worries. Whip them into shape.

407
00:21:07,920 --> 00:21:10,540
遵命  先生  回见
Yes, sir. I'll see you when I get back.

408
00:22:47,310 --> 00:22:48,850
才等了30分钟而已
Well, it's only been 30 minutes.

409
00:22:48,850 --> 00:22:51,100
作为开场也不算太糟糕
That's not too bad for an opening.

410
00:22:51,210 --> 00:22:52,620
如果我们还轮不到座位
If they don't seat us soon,

411
00:22:52,620 --> 00:22:54,900
我要到网上去给他们差评
I'm going to write a horrible review online.

412
00:22:55,630 --> 00:22:56,840
让我来试试
Let me see what I can do.

413
00:22:58,610 --> 00:23:01,310
嗨  这件卡沃利你穿着真漂亮
Hey. I'm loving the cavalli.

414
00:23:01,320 --> 00:23:02,930
看  我是汤米·梅林
Uh, look, I'm Tommy Merlyn.

415
00:23:03,020 --> 00:23:05,410
有办法能让我们提前进去吗
Is there any way that we can go to the head of the class?

416
00:23:05,570 --> 00:23:06,600
有预约吗
Is there?

417
00:23:09,810 --> 00:23:11,580
有位置了通知我们  好吗
Let us know when our table's ready, ok?

418
00:23:12,820 --> 00:23:13,780
不如你先吃点
Maybe you can eat

419
00:23:13,780 --> 00:23:15,160
吧台后面的花生什么的
some of those fancy peanuts from behind the bar.

420
00:23:15,160 --> 00:23:16,540
嘿
Hey!

421
00:23:21,320 --> 00:23:22,960
嗨  奥利弗  这位是
Hey, Oliver and someone.

422
00:23:22,960 --> 00:23:24,760
汤米  劳蕾尔  这是海伦娜
Tommy, Laurel, this is Helena.

423
00:23:25,210 --> 00:23:27,090
-很高兴认识你  -我也是
- Nice to meet you.  - Pleasure.

424
00:23:28,660 --> 00:23:29,700
我也是
Likewise.

425
00:23:29,700 --> 00:23:30,850
你看起来真漂亮
You look beautiful.

426
00:23:30,870 --> 00:23:32,170
谢谢
Thank you.

427
00:23:32,400 --> 00:23:34,120
奎恩先生  你的桌子已经安排好了
Mr. Queen, your table is ready.

428
00:23:34,120 --> 00:23:35,530
我们的什么时候才能好
When is our table gonna be ready?

429
00:23:35,530 --> 00:23:36,810
轮到你们的时候
When it is.

430
00:23:36,990 --> 00:23:38,280
要不你们和我们一起吧
Why don't you both join us?

431
00:23:38,280 --> 00:23:39,670
不必了吧  我们就随便喝一杯
No, no, we're just gonna have a drink and

432
00:23:39,670 --> 00:23:41,450
-我们很乐意  -你确定吗
- We'd love to.  - Are you sure?

433
00:23:41,870 --> 00:23:43,040
我确定我很饿了
I'm sure I'm hungry.

434
00:23:45,160 --> 00:23:46,170
这
That...

435
00:23:46,370 --> 00:23:48,970
这好极了  听上去不错
That'll be great. That sounds great.

436
00:23:49,180 --> 00:23:50,300
去吧
There you go.

437
00:23:52,810 --> 00:23:56,280
我差点忘了有次你把你爸妈的泳池灌满了啤酒
I had forgotten that you filled your parents' pool with beer.

438
00:23:56,620 --> 00:23:58,070
用了多少箱啤酒来着
How many cases did that take?

439
00:23:58,070 --> 00:23:59,590
大约有一千箱吧
Roughly a thousand or so.

440
00:24:01,070 --> 00:24:02,800
你知道吗  他爸爸气得要命
You know, his father was so pissed,

441
00:24:02,800 --> 00:24:04,630
我以为他真的要把你淹进去
I thought he was actually going to drown you in it.

442
00:24:04,630 --> 00:24:05,960
是啊  被啤酒淹死
Yeah, well, death by beer,

443
00:24:05,960 --> 00:24:07,630
也算不错的死法了  对吧  海伦娜
there's worse ways to go. Right, Helena?

444
00:24:07,630 --> 00:24:09,080
没有什么好的死法
Well, there are no good ways to die.

445
00:24:11,040 --> 00:24:13,440
你和汤米是怎么认识的
So, uh, how did you and Tommy meet?

446
00:24:14,570 --> 00:24:17,020
事实上  我们认识都是从...
Actually, we've all known each other since--

447
00:24:17,020 --> 00:24:18,460
我们从小就认识了
We've all known each other forever.

448
00:24:19,520 --> 00:24:21,390
你们三个有很多故事啊
You 3 have a lot of history.

449
00:24:21,400 --> 00:24:22,890
有时觉得有点太多了
Sometimes a little too much.

450
00:24:24,360 --> 00:24:26,590
那么  你的夜店开得顺利啊
So, how's the night club coming along?

451
00:24:26,590 --> 00:24:29,730
比我想象的要慢一点  我最近挺忙的
Slower than I expected it to. I've, uh, I've been busy.

452
00:24:29,730 --> 00:24:31,620
那你肯定希望有人能帮你吧
Well, then you must be happy to have the extra help, then.

453
00:24:31,620 --> 00:24:33,570
-此话怎讲  -劳蕾尔  我确信奥利弗
- What do you mean?  - Laurel, I'm sure that Oliver

454
00:24:33,570 --> 00:24:35,450
现在应该不想谈工作的事
doesn't want to talk about work right know.

455
00:24:35,450 --> 00:24:36,790
你没问过他
You didn't ask him?

456
00:24:37,280 --> 00:24:38,390
问我什么
Ask me what?

457
00:24:38,590 --> 00:24:41,810
汤米想  汤米想和你谈谈
Tommy wanted...Tommy said that he was gonna talk to you

458
00:24:41,810 --> 00:24:43,930
到你的夜店打工的事儿
about working for you at your night club.

459
00:24:45,490 --> 00:24:46,620
真的吗
Really?

460
00:24:47,420 --> 00:24:49,180
不好意思  我以为你不想
Sorry. I didn't think that you wanted

461
00:24:49,180 --> 00:24:50,660
要有任何责任
any responsibility at all.

462
00:24:50,660 --> 00:24:52,000
啊是啊  这种鬼话谁信啊
Oh, yeah, who'd believe that?

463
00:24:52,240 --> 00:24:54,310
你不是一直想要和汤米一起合伙吗
You've always wanted to get into business with Tommy.

464
00:24:54,560 --> 00:24:56,380
我是说  还记得我们那次去阿斯彭
I mean, don't you remember when we went to Aspen

465
00:24:56,390 --> 00:24:58,120
你们不是想要一起开家滑雪旅馆吗
and you wanted to open a ski lodge?

466
00:24:58,130 --> 00:24:59,920
那次去阿斯彭我唯一记得的
The only thing that I remember from Aspen

467
00:24:59,920 --> 00:25:02,730
就是你爸知道我们同床共枕以后暴跳如雷
was your father being furious we shared a room with one bed.

468
00:25:04,840 --> 00:25:06,270
等等
Wait, um...

469
00:25:07,190 --> 00:25:08,800
所以你们以前在一起过
So you two were together...

470
00:25:10,010 --> 00:25:11,870
然后你和他最好的朋友约会
and now you're dating his best friend?

471
00:25:11,870 --> 00:25:14,930
是啊  我们就像是演真人秀  不是吗
Yeah, we're just prime for a reality show, aren't we?

472
00:25:18,460 --> 00:25:22,350
汤米  你来我这儿工作  肯定会很有意思
Tommy, you working for me, that could be fun.

473
00:25:22,350 --> 00:25:24,860
我感觉不太好  我要出去透透气
I don't feel so good. I'm gonna step outside.

474
00:25:27,570 --> 00:25:29,290
我得去看看他
I should probably go check on him.

475
00:25:29,290 --> 00:25:31,230
海伦娜  很高兴认识你
Helena, it was very nice to meet you.

476
00:25:38,510 --> 00:25:40,150
汤米  你干嘛不开心
Tommy, why are you so upset?

477
00:25:40,150 --> 00:25:42,270
你为什么一定要和奥利弗说工作的事情
Why did you have to say something to Oliver about the job?

478
00:25:42,280 --> 00:25:43,770
这本来是你应该做的
You were supposed to talk to him.

479
00:25:43,770 --> 00:25:44,860
但我不想说
Well, I hadn't.

480
00:25:44,970 --> 00:25:47,330
好吧  我没发现  我只是想帮忙
Ok, I didn't realize. I was only trying to help.

481
00:25:47,330 --> 00:25:49,100
不  你是想让奥利弗来帮忙
No, you were trying to get Oliver to help.

482
00:25:49,280 --> 00:25:51,890
这就是你  总是奔向你的白马王子
It's typical Laurel. Always running to a white knight.

483
00:25:53,360 --> 00:25:54,570
是奥利弗和劳蕾尔
It's Oliver and Laurel.

484
00:25:55,070 --> 00:25:56,260
一直都是
It always has been.

485
00:25:57,100 --> 00:25:58,350
这点不会改变的
That's not gonna change.

486
00:25:59,450 --> 00:26:00,850
我和奥利弗已经结束了
Oliver and I are over.

487
00:26:00,870 --> 00:26:01,610
真的吗  可你看上去
Oh, really? Because you

488
00:26:01,610 --> 00:26:03,380
真的很不喜欢他的新女朋友
seemed awfully bothered by his new girlfriend.

489
00:26:03,380 --> 00:26:04,670
难道我应该喜欢她吗
What, am I supposed to like her?

490
00:26:04,800 --> 00:26:07,250
我不想成为奥利弗的慈善对象  知道吗
I do not want to be Oliver's charity case, OK?

491
00:26:08,010 --> 00:26:09,420
这会每天提醒我
To every day be reminded

492
00:26:09,590 --> 00:26:11,910
我不能给你他能给的一切
that I can't give you everything he could?

493
00:26:13,840 --> 00:26:15,160
知道吗  失去你
You know, losing a fortune

494
00:26:15,260 --> 00:26:17,240
比失去财富更让我难过
I think is going to be easier than losing you,

495
00:26:17,240 --> 00:26:18,750
我们何不到此为止呢
So why don't we just stop now.

496
00:26:24,540 --> 00:26:26,460
我很抱歉
Hey. I'm sorry.

497
00:26:27,810 --> 00:26:28,610
我怎么会知道
How am I supposed to know

498
00:26:28,610 --> 00:26:29,690
桌上氛围会变得那么奇怪
it's gonna get so weird in there?

499
00:26:29,690 --> 00:26:32,810
不  是我抱歉  抱歉我竟然听了你的话
No, I'm sorry. Sorry I ever listened to you.

500
00:26:33,730 --> 00:26:34,760
海伦娜  你...
Helena, what--

501
00:26:34,770 --> 00:26:36,860
你知道我的痛苦经历
You know what I've been through.

502
00:26:37,610 --> 00:26:39,410
我告诉过你我不能再受伤了
I told you I couldn't be hurt again.

503
00:26:39,690 --> 00:26:41,000
我没想伤害你
I'm not trying to hurt you.

504
00:26:42,510 --> 00:26:44,850
那让我和你的挚爱一起吃饭
So, making me have dinner with the love of your life

505
00:26:44,850 --> 00:26:46,350
是什么意思  奥利弗
is what, Oliver?

506
00:26:46,950 --> 00:26:49,500
劳蕾尔就是那个和你之间变得严肃的女孩
Laurel was the girl things were getting too serious with,

507
00:26:49,500 --> 00:26:52,780
你就是在这个女孩的妹妹坟墓前打动我的
the girl whose sister's grave you used to manipulate me.

508
00:26:53,080 --> 00:26:54,620
我看到你看她的眼神了
I saw the way you looked at her.

509
00:26:54,870 --> 00:26:56,240
那种爱是至死不渝的
That kind of love doesn't die.

510
00:26:57,070 --> 00:26:58,300
你还爱她
You still love her.

511
00:26:58,550 --> 00:26:59,600
不爱了
I don't.

512
00:27:01,680 --> 00:27:03,060
你别这样
Hey. Don't.

513
00:27:03,850 --> 00:27:04,890
别碰我
Don't touch me.

514
00:27:05,300 --> 00:27:07,220
我不想跟你说话了
I am done talking.

515
00:27:27,480 --> 00:27:28,790
我是来道歉的
I came to apologize.

516
00:27:33,050 --> 00:27:34,520
我知道你只是想帮我
I know you were just trying to help.

517
00:27:35,480 --> 00:27:37,420
是我没有做好面对现实的准备
I guess I wasn't ready to face reality.

518
00:27:39,060 --> 00:27:40,990
我和你之间刚刚开始这段新关系
This is just so new, you and me,

519
00:27:40,990 --> 00:27:42,570
所以我不想让你看到...
and I didn't want you to see...

520
00:27:43,940 --> 00:27:45,050
我害怕了
I'm scared.

521
00:27:47,540 --> 00:27:49,990
我都快30岁了  但是至今没有
I'm almost 30 years old and I've never been given

522
00:27:49,990 --> 00:27:51,980
对自己的生活负过一点责任
an ounce of responsibility in my life.

523
00:27:52,720 --> 00:27:55,490
而你呢  总是干劲十足
You, you are driven

524
00:27:55,730 --> 00:27:58,710
聪明伶俐  即使我没有破产
and intelligent. You're a million times too good for me,

525
00:27:58,710 --> 00:28:00,190
我也远远配不上你
even before I was broke.

526
00:28:00,510 --> 00:28:01,930
可是现在  我能拿出手的
And now I have absolutely nothing

527
00:28:01,930 --> 00:28:03,230
真是什么都没有了
to bring to whatever this is.

528
00:28:04,850 --> 00:28:06,230
我从未在乎过钱
I never cared about the money.

529
00:28:07,180 --> 00:28:09,020
说实话  亿万富翁
And truth be told, billionaire

530
00:28:09,020 --> 00:28:11,050
真的不是你的魅力之处
was your least attractive quality.

531
00:28:12,580 --> 00:28:15,060
很抱歉  让你和奥利弗工作的事
I am so sorry if I pushed you too hard

532
00:28:15,060 --> 00:28:16,650
我把你逼得太紧了
on the job with Oliver.

533
00:28:17,140 --> 00:28:19,330
我是觉得你跟着他工作是个不错的主意
I just--I thought you working for him was a good idea

534
00:28:19,330 --> 00:28:20,790
毕竟他是你的朋友
because he's your friend.

535
00:28:21,340 --> 00:28:23,380
找朋友帮忙是理所应当的
And it's OK to ask a friend for help.

536
00:28:25,080 --> 00:28:26,500
这样你也不会失去你的威望
You won't lose your street cred.

537
00:28:28,110 --> 00:28:29,750
失去威望我无所谓
I'm happy to lose my street cred.

538
00:28:29,750 --> 00:28:31,940
我只是不想失去你
I just don't want to lose you.

539
00:28:34,990 --> 00:28:39,400
我不是说事情会很容易
Well... I'm not saying that it's gonna be easy...

540
00:28:42,020 --> 00:28:44,320
但是如果你需要个依靠的话  我随时都在
but I'm here for you if you need someone to lean on.

541
00:28:45,710 --> 00:28:47,390
两个人在一起的时候就是这样
That's what people do when they're together.

542
00:28:49,010 --> 00:28:50,840
男女朋友的那种在一起吗
Together like boyfriend-girlfriend?

543
00:28:52,060 --> 00:28:56,160
别毁了这个美好的瞬间
Mm. Do not ruin this moment.

544
00:28:56,620 --> 00:28:58,860
你一直进行地挺顺利的
It was going so well for you.

545
00:29:10,510 --> 00:29:12,030
没想到你今晚会叫我
Didn't expect to hear from you tonight.

546
00:29:13,660 --> 00:29:14,870
有什么事吗
Something happen?

547
00:29:17,010 --> 00:29:18,260
我觉得你是对的
I think you were right.

548
00:29:20,590 --> 00:29:22,720
好吧  哪件事
OK. About which part?

549
00:29:23,490 --> 00:29:24,590
所有的事
All of it.

550
00:29:28,240 --> 00:29:29,420
我应该听你的
I should have listened to you.

551
00:29:33,480 --> 00:29:35,800
奥利弗  你说你想帮她改变
Oliver, you said you wanted to help her change.

552
00:29:36,390 --> 00:29:39,180
可事实是  她已经改变了
The thing is, she already did change.

553
00:29:40,990 --> 00:29:42,350
她父亲杀了她的未婚夫的时候
When her father killed her fiance,

554
00:29:42,350 --> 00:29:45,060
她就已经变得既黑暗又扭曲了
she changed into something dark and twisted.

555
00:29:45,120 --> 00:29:46,420
现在你已经明白了  是不是
You see that now, don't you?

556
00:29:46,420 --> 00:29:48,330
不是...不是我不明白  狄格尔
It's not that I--it's not that I couldn't see it, Diggle.

557
00:29:48,330 --> 00:29:51,300
我是...不想明白
I didn't--I didn't want to.

558
00:29:52,980 --> 00:29:55,440
我自己过着双重生活  要做到这点
I'm living a double life, and to do that,

559
00:29:55,440 --> 00:29:57,080
我就得和所有我爱的人
I'm taking all these people that I love

560
00:29:57,080 --> 00:29:58,380
保持好距离
and I'm putting them at arm's length.

561
00:29:58,380 --> 00:30:00,260
我放弃了很多  所以...
I'm giving up a lot, so maybe--

562
00:30:01,670 --> 00:30:04,240
我以为是世界欠我的
maybe I thought the universe owed me one.

563
00:30:05,620 --> 00:30:07,690
可是今晚我看着她的眼睛
But I looked in her eyes tonight,

564
00:30:07,690 --> 00:30:10,940
却无法阻止她越过那条线
and I can't stop her from going over the edge.

565
00:30:10,940 --> 00:30:14,360
她...她早就已经过界了
She's--she's already past it.

566
00:30:29,120 --> 00:30:30,050
{\pos(195,239)}出了什么事

567
00:30:30,330 --> 00:30:32,090
{\pos(195,239)}快离开  快离开

568
00:30:42,840 --> 00:30:45,000
{\pos(192,219)}复仇的时候要挖两个坟墓

569
00:30:45,760 --> 00:30:47,350
{\pos(195,239)}一个为敌人

570
00:30:47,390 --> 00:30:49,410
{\pos(192,217)}一个为自己

571
00:30:49,500 --> 00:30:51,450
我不懂汉语
I don't speak Chinese,

572
00:30:51,450 --> 00:30:54,560
所以我就当你说再见了吧
so I'm just gonna assume you said good-bye.

573
00:31:04,750 --> 00:31:08,690
告诉你的情妇  弗兰克·波提纳尔向她问好
Tell your mistress Frank Bertinelli sends his regards.

574
00:31:22,170 --> 00:31:24,130
您找我有什么事吗  斯蒂尔先生
You wanted to see me, Mr. Steele?

575
00:31:24,410 --> 00:31:26,840
我有没有跟你说过  快到圣诞节了
Did I mention, it's almost Christmas,

576
00:31:26,840 --> 00:31:28,340
每年的这个时候  发生的自杀事件
and many of the suicides this time of year

577
00:31:28,340 --> 00:31:31,580
很多是由于突然意外失业造成的
are due to sudden and unexpected joblessness?

578
00:31:34,740 --> 00:31:37,620
我想让你尽你所能查查这个笔记本
I want you to find out all you can about that notebook.

579
00:31:37,620 --> 00:31:39,520
制造厂商  购买方式
Where it was made, how it was purchased,

580
00:31:39,520 --> 00:31:41,220
-好  -以及意义所在
- Yes, sir. - and what it could mean.

581
00:31:41,220 --> 00:31:42,720
巧妙地查...
Felicity...

582
00:31:43,090 --> 00:31:45,520
我让公司保安部门的负责人约西亚·哈德森
I asked Josiah Hudson, our head of security,

583
00:31:45,520 --> 00:31:47,980
调查同一事件
to look into the same subject matter.

584
00:31:48,530 --> 00:31:53,400
他第二天就离奇死亡了
He died the next day under questionable circumstances.

585
00:31:54,200 --> 00:31:55,810
所以我要问问你
What I may be asking of you,

586
00:31:55,810 --> 00:31:57,590
关于这个秘密任务
this mystery,

587
00:31:58,310 --> 00:32:00,430
你确定你要做吗
are you sure you want to do this?

588
00:32:01,340 --> 00:32:03,030
我讨厌秘密
I hate mysteries.

589
00:32:03,150 --> 00:32:04,680
它们让我生气
They bug me.

590
00:32:05,040 --> 00:32:06,830
所以要解决掉
They need to be solved.

591
00:32:35,180 --> 00:32:36,370
我是狄格
It's Dig.

592
00:32:36,370 --> 00:32:38,050
什么情况
What's the situation?

593
00:32:38,290 --> 00:32:39,840
战争
War.

594
00:32:44,610 --> 00:32:47,210
老板  刚得到消息  有人袭击了芝山
Boss, we just got word-- somebody hit Zhishan.

595
00:32:47,210 --> 00:32:48,700
他死了
He's dead.

596
00:32:49,730 --> 00:32:52,380
好  这样我们就知道接下来要发生什么了
All right. Then we know what's coming next.

597
00:32:53,190 --> 00:32:55,220
告诉大家都提高警惕
Tell everyone to strap up.

598
00:33:05,820 --> 00:33:06,990
{\pos(193,239)}不留活口

599
00:33:13,000 --> 00:33:15,760
里科没有回复对讲机  去看看
Ricco's not answering his walkie. Check it out.

600
00:33:59,160 --> 00:34:00,300
弗兰克·波提纳尔
Frank Bertinelli--

601
00:34:00,310 --> 00:34:02,190
这是为芝山报仇
This is for Zhishan.

602
00:34:07,090 --> 00:34:08,530
快跑
Run.

603
00:34:38,220 --> 00:34:40,720
海伦娜
Oh--Helena.

604
00:34:40,770 --> 00:34:41,700
这是怎么回事
What is this?

605
00:34:41,700 --> 00:34:44,910
替迈克尔报一箭之仇
Payback for Michael.

606
00:34:44,910 --> 00:34:47,500
我知道是你杀了他  赛瓦缇告诉我了
I know you had him killed. Salvati told me.

607
00:34:47,500 --> 00:34:49,880
我是为了保护这个家才这么做
I did that to protect the family!

608
00:34:49,880 --> 00:34:51,450
既然你让我一无所有
I had to take everything away from you

609
00:34:51,450 --> 00:34:55,600
那么我也要以牙还牙
because you took everything away from me.

610
00:34:57,710 --> 00:34:59,390
你终于知道这是什么感觉了吧
You finally know what it feels like

611
00:34:59,390 --> 00:35:02,180
发现竟是自己的亲人
to find out your own blood is responsible

612
00:35:02,180 --> 00:35:05,750
把你整个世界都摧毁了
for the death of your entire world.

613
00:35:40,370 --> 00:35:41,860
住手
No!

614
00:35:48,940 --> 00:35:50,570
海伦娜
Helena?

615
00:35:51,070 --> 00:35:52,550
海伦娜
Helena.

616
00:36:22,690 --> 00:36:25,340
海伦娜  放松  放松
Helena, easy. Easy.

617
00:36:25,340 --> 00:36:26,970
你很幸运
You were lucky.

618
00:36:28,150 --> 00:36:30,420
我该满怀感激吗
Am I supposed to be grateful?

619
00:36:30,680 --> 00:36:31,430
海伦娜
Helena--

620
00:36:31,430 --> 00:36:33,170
他禽兽不如
He's a monster.

621
00:36:33,170 --> 00:36:36,060
他是罪犯  你为什么还要救他
A criminal. Why would you save him?

622
00:36:36,430 --> 00:36:39,790
我不是救他  是救你
I didn't save him. I saved you.

623
00:36:40,020 --> 00:36:41,900
你以为你杀过人了
You think that because you've killed,

624
00:36:41,900 --> 00:36:44,090
就明白双手染满鲜血的感觉吗
you understand what it's like to have blood on your hands.

625
00:36:44,090 --> 00:36:46,050
你不明白  你不明白
You don't understand. You don't understand

626
00:36:46,050 --> 00:36:47,950
那么做带来的伤害
the toll that it takes on you,

627
00:36:47,950 --> 00:36:50,450
尤其要杀的人是你自己的父亲
especially when it's your father.

628
00:36:50,450 --> 00:36:52,220
我不会就此收手的
I'm not going to stop.

629
00:36:52,220 --> 00:36:53,850
警察会把他关起来
The police have him in custody.

630
00:36:53,850 --> 00:36:55,650
他将被拘留  然后监禁
He's going to jail and then on to prison.

631
00:36:55,660 --> 00:36:57,720
他们手上没有指控他的证据
They don't have any evidence on him.

632
00:36:57,730 --> 00:36:59,300
但现在有了
They do now.

633
00:37:01,130 --> 00:37:02,320
那台电脑
The laptop.

634
00:37:02,320 --> 00:37:04,050
他要被除掉了  海伦娜
He's going away, Helena,

635
00:37:04,050 --> 00:37:05,650
再也不能作恶了
for the rest of his life.

636
00:37:05,650 --> 00:37:08,930
这就是正义
This...is justice.

637
00:37:08,930 --> 00:37:10,820
那么我猜你之前说得对
Then I guess you were right.

638
00:37:10,820 --> 00:37:13,190
我更喜欢复仇
I'm more interested in revenge.

639
00:37:13,370 --> 00:37:15,280
别妨碍我  奥利弗
Stay out of my way, Oliver,

640
00:37:15,280 --> 00:37:18,360
否则你的秘密可就不保了
or I'll make sure your secret doesn't stay secret.

641
00:37:19,350 --> 00:37:20,800
海伦娜
Helena.

642
00:37:23,840 --> 00:37:25,480
我所做的
What I did,

643
00:37:27,120 --> 00:37:28,950
我所做的这一切
everything that I've done,

644
00:37:28,950 --> 00:37:32,700
都是因为我在乎你
I've done because I care about you.

645
00:37:34,210 --> 00:37:36,510
可我不在乎你
Too bad I can't say the same.

646
00:37:50,410 --> 00:37:51,870
你好啊
Hey, you.

647
00:37:52,000 --> 00:37:52,960
谢谢你打这个电话
Thanks for the call.

648
00:37:52,970 --> 00:37:55,350
谁让我是前任大嫂呢
What are ex-sisters-in-law for?

649
00:38:02,090 --> 00:38:05,870
辣奶酪薯条配墨西哥胡椒
Chili cheese fries with jalapenos. Hmm.

650
00:38:08,370 --> 00:38:10,970
我从来没遇过这样的求助呢
That's a cry for help if I've ever seen one.

651
00:38:12,630 --> 00:38:13,640
我不知道现在这样
I don't know what hurts worse,

652
00:38:13,650 --> 00:38:17,600
和被蕾丝毒弹射中  哪种更伤人
this or getting shot with a curare-laced bullet.

653
00:38:17,600 --> 00:38:19,990
亲身体验  当然是毒弹
Been there, done that. Definitely the bullet.

654
00:38:24,910 --> 00:38:27,510
奥利弗  我不擅长当知心姐姐  但
You know, Oliver, I'm no expert at this, but...

655
00:38:29,060 --> 00:38:33,180
我认为爱不是去改变或者拯救一个人
I don't think love is about changing or saving a person.

656
00:38:34,330 --> 00:38:35,600
是找到那个早已
I think it's about finding the person

657
00:38:35,600 --> 00:38:37,670
合适你的的人
who's already the right fit.

658
00:38:40,980 --> 00:38:42,580
有一天你会找到的
One day you will.

659
00:38:42,690 --> 00:38:45,800
我觉得自己已经把某条路给断了
I think I burnt that particular bridge.

660
00:38:47,000 --> 00:38:48,740
事实上  是炸掉了
Napalmed it, actually.

661
00:38:48,740 --> 00:38:50,630
这么说事情并不像你计划中那么顺利
So things didn't work out exactly as you planned.

662
00:38:50,630 --> 00:38:52,640
你的确救了弗兰克·波提纳尔一条命
You did save Frank Bertinelli's life.

663
00:38:52,640 --> 00:38:54,040
他得在那里头待上一阵子了
He'll be doing time for a while.

664
00:38:54,040 --> 00:38:55,770
邪不胜正
Justice wins out.

665
00:38:56,500 --> 00:39:01,020
海伦娜却不明白这一点
Helena doesn't see it that way.

666
00:39:01,280 --> 00:39:04,300
你甘愿冒险  敞开心扉
You opened up, took a risk with your heart.

667
00:39:05,060 --> 00:39:06,410
这是几个月前的奥利弗
The Oliver I met a few months ago

668
00:39:06,410 --> 00:39:08,500
无法做到的事情
would not have been able to do that.

669
00:39:10,600 --> 00:39:12,850
当你遇到对的人
And when you meet the right person,

670
00:39:12,850 --> 00:39:14,660
你就会准备好的
you'll be ready for her.

671
00:39:30,110 --> 00:39:30,930
你在干什么
What are you doing?

672
00:39:30,930 --> 00:39:33,400
我得先关灯再做
It needs to be dark in here for me to do this.

673
00:39:33,560 --> 00:39:35,440
如果我来得及斟酌一下这句话
If I had had more time to think of that sentence

674
00:39:35,440 --> 00:39:37,440
应该会说得纯洁很多
it wouldn't have sounded so dirty.

675
00:39:37,850 --> 00:39:39,290
你瞧
Look.

676
00:39:44,310 --> 00:39:46,020
我什么都看不见
I don't see anything.

677
00:39:46,020 --> 00:39:47,600
我从应用科学部找来了这眼镜
I got these from applied sciences.

678
00:39:47,600 --> 00:39:49,250
戴上它就能看见紫外线谱中
They're able to pick up the subvisible variations

679
00:39:49,250 --> 00:39:51,090
肉眼看不见的射线
in the UV spectrum.

680
00:39:51,830 --> 00:39:54,150
现在你再看那个本子
Now look at the book again.

681
00:40:21,340 --> 00:40:22,910
话说
Now, look,

682
00:40:23,520 --> 00:40:24,740
我为昨晚的事情向你道歉
I'm sorry about last night.

683
00:40:24,740 --> 00:40:26,390
是我当时吃饭时
It just--I let it get too far

684
00:40:26,390 --> 00:40:28,920
做得过火了  那实在是
sitting at the same table. That was...

685
00:40:29,380 --> 00:40:30,030
实在是不明智
That was stupid.

686
00:40:30,030 --> 00:40:33,170
不  是我太傻了
No. I was stupid.

687
00:40:34,400 --> 00:40:38,420
我没有对你完全坦诚
I haven't been entirely honest with you.

688
00:40:40,280 --> 00:40:41,800
我爸爸把我钱断了
My dad cut me off.

689
00:40:41,800 --> 00:40:43,570
他冻结了我的资金
He froze all my funds.

690
00:40:43,570 --> 00:40:46,340
我现在身无分文
I am living on fumes.

691
00:40:47,430 --> 00:40:48,790
真的吗
Really?

692
00:40:49,960 --> 00:40:51,210
那你怎么什么都不说
Why didn't you say anything?

693
00:40:51,210 --> 00:40:53,330
尴尬  羞愧  嫉妒
Embarrassment, shame, jealousy,

694
00:40:53,330 --> 00:40:55,850
可能还有其他我还不习惯的情绪
probably a few other emotions I'm not used to feeling.

695
00:40:55,850 --> 00:40:59,370
汤米  我的钱就是你的钱
Tommy, my trust fund is your trust fund.

696
00:41:00,920 --> 00:41:02,390
不
No.

697
00:41:02,490 --> 00:41:03,650
这是个简单的解决方法
That is the easy answer.

698
00:41:03,660 --> 00:41:07,410
相信我  我喜欢这种答案
And believe me, I have loved easy answers.

699
00:41:08,450 --> 00:41:10,530
可我需要的是一份工作
What I need is a job.

700
00:41:12,220 --> 00:41:14,170
我想改变
I'm trying to change.

701
00:41:14,390 --> 00:41:17,400
还不确定要变成什么样  但是
Not sure into what yet, but...

702
00:41:18,230 --> 00:41:21,120
我不想再当以前的那个我了
I don't want to be what I was anymore.

703
00:41:23,010 --> 00:41:24,200
碰巧我这儿
It just so happens that I have

704
00:41:24,200 --> 00:41:25,600
正好缺一个
a general manager position

705
00:41:25,600 --> 00:41:28,960
总经理
that is available.

706
00:41:28,960 --> 00:41:31,180
你或许就是合适的人选
You're probably the guy for the job.

707
00:41:31,180 --> 00:41:33,310
我是不是该小心点  你笑得不怀好意呀
Will I be getting dental? This smile wasn't cheap.

708
00:41:33,310 --> 00:41:35,520
我会好好考虑的  谢谢
I'll look into that. Thank you.

709
00:41:37,680 --> 00:41:38,430
谢谢你
Thank you.

710
00:41:38,430 --> 00:41:39,870
不客气
You're welcome.

711
00:41:44,900 --> 00:41:46,160
你还好吗
You ok?

712
00:41:46,160 --> 00:41:47,710
会好起来的
I will be.

713
00:41:48,230 --> 00:41:50,300
海伦娜怎么样了
Something happen with Helena?

714
00:41:50,660 --> 00:41:52,500
我们分道扬镳了
We had a falling out.

715
00:41:53,360 --> 00:41:57,000
但我有预感还会再见到她
But I have a feeling that I will be seeing her again.

