1
00:00:42,000 --> 00:00:47,000
{\pos(190,270)}本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

3
00:00:47,100 --> 00:00:52,000
{\pos(190,278)}翻译：小榴莲   小黎   天朝直属    vivi    圈圈   Luna_3

5
00:00:52,100 --> 00:00:57,000
{\pos(190,278)}初校：DJ   陈小圈   苹果    时间轴：加森   小仓鼠   搁浅

7
00:00:57,100 --> 00:01:02,000
{\pos(190,278)}后期：冰河   监制：苹果

9
00:02:57,710 --> 00:03:02,530
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)绿   箭

10
00:02:57,710 --> 00:03:02,530
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)第一季 第四集

11
00:00:00,300 --> 00:00:02,930
我是奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.

12
00:00:02,930 --> 00:00:04,460
五年里  我被困孤岛
For 5 years, I was stranded

13
00:00:04,470 --> 00:00:06,770
只有一个目标
on an island with only one goal--

14
00:00:06,770 --> 00:00:08,120
生存
survive.

15
00:00:08,120 --> 00:00:10,160
奥利弗·奎恩还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.

16
00:00:10,160 --> 00:00:12,820
现在我要完成父亲的遗愿
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish...

17
00:00:12,830 --> 00:00:14,880
你能撑过去的
You can survive this.

18
00:00:14,890 --> 00:00:16,780
用他留给我的名单
To use the list of names he left me

19
00:00:16,780 --> 00:00:20,200
扳倒那些荼毒城市的人
And bring down those who are poisoning my city.

20
00:00:21,420 --> 00:00:24,560
要做这些  我只能伪装成另一个人
To do this, I must become someone else.

21
00:00:25,660 --> 00:00:29,660
成为另一个存在
I must become something else.

22
00:00:29,660 --> 00:00:31,880
《绿箭》前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...

23
00:00:31,880 --> 00:00:33,560
如果你不和我保持距离
How am I supposed to stay away from you

24
00:00:33,560 --> 00:00:35,380
我怎么能离你远点呢
if you won't stay away from me?

25
00:00:35,380 --> 00:00:37,830
约翰·狄格尔  从现在起他会跟随你左右
John Diggle. He'll be accompanying you from now on.

26
00:00:37,830 --> 00:00:38,870
我想我已经开始了解
I think I'm just beginning to understand

27
00:00:38,880 --> 00:00:40,740
你到底是什么样的人了
the kind of man you are.

28
00:01:31,750 --> 00:01:35,430
-你好  -奥利弗
- Hey. - Oliver?

29
00:01:41,350 --> 00:01:43,220
你是那个治安维持者
You're that vigilante.

30
00:01:46,840 --> 00:01:49,030
放松  狄格  你中毒了
Easy, Dig. You were poisoned.

31
00:01:49,030 --> 00:01:50,690
贱人
Son of a bitch.

32
00:01:56,820 --> 00:01:58,170
我本可以带你去任何地方
I could have taken you anywhere,

33
00:01:58,170 --> 00:01:59,960
本可以带你回家
could have taken you home.

34
00:02:01,340 --> 00:02:03,000
但我把你带到这儿
I brought you here.

35
00:02:03,920 --> 00:02:05,660
你真是在岛上待得丢掉理智了
You really did lose your mind on that island.

36
00:02:05,660 --> 00:02:06,970
也找着了点儿东西
Found a couple things along the way.

37
00:02:06,970 --> 00:02:08,090
比如呢  箭术课程
Like what, archery classes?

38
00:02:08,090 --> 00:02:09,530
明白
Clarity.

39
00:02:11,310 --> 00:02:15,280
星城正走向末路
Starling city is dying.

40
00:02:16,640 --> 00:02:20,340
它被一些犯罪高手荼毒
It is being poisoned by a criminal elite

41
00:02:20,790 --> 00:02:24,640
他们不顾手上的鲜血
who don't care who they hurt,

42
00:02:24,740 --> 00:02:26,990
只顾保全自己的财富和权力
as long as they maintain their wealth and power.

43
00:02:26,990 --> 00:02:28,610
你想做什么
What are you gonna do,

44
00:02:28,620 --> 00:02:30,600
一个人把他们全扳倒吗
take 'em all down by your lonesome?

45
00:02:30,600 --> 00:02:32,020
不
No.

46
00:02:34,470 --> 00:02:36,720
我希望你加入我
Now, I want you to join me.

47
00:02:37,220 --> 00:02:40,360
出身坎大哈特种部队  好极了
Special forces out of Kandahar. It's perfect.

48
00:02:41,800 --> 00:02:43,160
你是军人
You're a fellow soldier.

49
00:02:43,160 --> 00:02:45,520
奥利弗  你不是军人
Oliver, you're not a soldier.

50
00:02:46,470 --> 00:02:48,200
你是罪犯
You're a criminal.

51
00:02:50,040 --> 00:02:51,640
还是凶手
And a murderer.

52
00:03:18,230 --> 00:03:19,740
你去哪了
Where were you?

53
00:03:21,160 --> 00:03:22,630
什么
What?

54
00:03:24,090 --> 00:03:25,420
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?

55
00:03:25,420 --> 00:03:26,400
我听说枪击的事了
I heard about the shooting,

56
00:03:26,400 --> 00:03:28,430
所以来确认一下你没事
and I wanted to make sure you were ok.

57
00:03:28,430 --> 00:03:29,890
真的吗
You did?

58
00:03:30,270 --> 00:03:31,750
是的
Yeah.

59
00:03:32,270 --> 00:03:33,270
我敲了门
I knocked on the door,

60
00:03:33,270 --> 00:03:35,700
看到一家子为你担心
and I found a family terrified for you.

61
00:03:35,700 --> 00:03:38,010
他们不知道你在哪儿
They had no idea where you were.

62
00:03:38,580 --> 00:03:40,650
奥利弗  你就那么自私
Oliver, are you so self-centered

63
00:03:40,650 --> 00:03:42,740
不想想关心你的人
that you don't think that people who care about you

64
00:03:42,740 --> 00:03:45,510
在你们遭遇枪击后多么想知道你的去向吗
are gonna wonder where you are after you all got shot at?

65
00:03:45,510 --> 00:03:46,980
你说得对
You're right.

66
00:03:47,430 --> 00:03:50,710
很久以前我就对你的自私习以为常了
I made peace with your selfishness a long time ago,

67
00:03:51,610 --> 00:03:53,800
但是莫伊拉  西娅  沃尔特
But Moira, Thea, and Walter,

68
00:03:53,800 --> 00:03:55,720
他们不该承受这些
They don't deserve that.

69
00:03:55,790 --> 00:03:57,580
他们应该得到更好的人
They deserve better,

70
00:03:58,070 --> 00:04:00,820
一个会关心别人的人
someone who doesn't care only about himself.

71
00:04:05,290 --> 00:04:06,800
劳蕾尔
Laurel...

72
00:04:11,570 --> 00:04:13,650
谢谢你过来
Thank you for coming.

73
00:04:13,650 --> 00:04:16,530
我是担心其他人的安危  奥利弗
I care about the lives of other people, Oliver.

74
00:04:17,460 --> 00:04:19,650
也许你该有时尝尝这种滋味
Maybe you should try it sometime.

75
00:04:26,360 --> 00:04:28,130
天呐
Oh, man.

76
00:04:29,980 --> 00:04:31,770
真狠啊
That was harsh.

77
00:04:33,470 --> 00:04:35,000
你还好吧
You ok?

78
00:04:35,380 --> 00:04:36,920
没事
Sure.

79
00:04:38,120 --> 00:04:41,270
今天晚上第二次 我的朋友
Second time tonight that a friend of mine has

80
00:04:41,500 --> 00:04:43,300
让我洗心革面  重新做人
taken me to the woodshed.

81
00:04:43,300 --> 00:04:45,120
多少让人心力憔悴
Kind of tires you out.

82
00:04:46,670 --> 00:04:49,090
晚安
Good night.

83
00:05:14,050 --> 00:05:15,610
生存

84
00:05:17,240 --> 00:05:19,420
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do with that?

85
00:05:19,730 --> 00:05:21,190
生存

86
00:05:22,030 --> 00:05:24,080
你是说"鸟"吗
Does that mean "Bird"?

87
00:05:24,740 --> 00:05:25,420
生存

88
00:05:25,420 --> 00:05:27,820
我不会说中文
I don't speak chinese!

89
00:05:37,510 --> 00:05:39,240
对不起  劳蕾尔
I'm sorry, Laurel.

90
00:05:39,240 --> 00:05:40,990
真的对不起
I'm so sorry.

91
00:05:46,780 --> 00:05:48,420
没有强行入室的迹象
There were no signs of forced entry

92
00:05:48,420 --> 00:05:50,380
或挣扎的痕迹
or any evidence of a struggle,

93
00:05:50,380 --> 00:05:52,740
但数小时后  警方发现了沾满血的
But, hours later, the police found that the bloodstained...

94
00:05:52,740 --> 00:05:54,570
菜刀
kitchen knife and the...

95
00:05:54,570 --> 00:05:56,230
你也睡不着吗
Couldn't sleep, either?

96
00:05:56,350 --> 00:06:00,070
是啊  你在看什么
No. What are you watching?

97
00:06:00,330 --> 00:06:01,580
彼得·德克兰
Peter Declan.

98
00:06:01,580 --> 00:06:04,670
他杀了自己的妻子
A guy who killed his wife.

99
00:06:04,670 --> 00:06:05,890
抛开越来越多的证据不谈
Despite the growing list of evidence...

100
00:06:05,890 --> 00:06:07,890
这个人在婴儿房
Right. This guy killed his wife

101
00:06:07,890 --> 00:06:11,480
杀了自己的妻子  疯子
in their baby's room. Psycho.

102
00:06:11,480 --> 00:06:13,440
卡米尔是我的全部
Camille was everything to me.

103
00:06:14,280 --> 00:06:17,140
我宁愿自杀也不会杀她
I couldn't kill her any more than I could kill myself.

104
00:06:17,140 --> 00:06:19,060
那你为什么睡不着呢
So why can't you sleep?

105
00:06:19,930 --> 00:06:21,470
做噩梦了
Bad dreams.

106
00:06:21,690 --> 00:06:23,370
梦到什么了
About?

107
00:06:23,640 --> 00:06:25,200
劳蕾尔
Laurel.

108
00:06:25,760 --> 00:06:27,670
你为什么不表态
So why don't you make a play?

109
00:06:27,670 --> 00:06:29,490
我是说  她特地过来
I mean, she did come over here

110
00:06:29,490 --> 00:06:31,760
看你有没有受伤
just to make sure you didn't get shot.

111
00:06:33,430 --> 00:06:34,380
这是有原因的
There are reasons.

112
00:06:34,380 --> 00:06:36,220
什么原因
Mm, what are they?

113
00:06:36,400 --> 00:06:38,820
除去你睡过她妹妹
Besides you sleeping with her sister

114
00:06:38,820 --> 00:06:40,590
她妹妹死了
and her sister dying

115
00:06:40,590 --> 00:06:42,050
他父亲恨你入骨
and her father hating your guts

116
00:06:42,050 --> 00:06:43,440
还有你回来以后
and you basically being a jerk

117
00:06:43,440 --> 00:06:46,530
对所有人都很混蛋
to everybody since you've been back?

118
00:06:47,260 --> 00:06:49,250
那些是主要原因
Those are the top ones.

119
00:06:53,170 --> 00:06:56,820
我知道有时候似乎不是这样  但是
I know that it might not seem like it sometimes, but...

120
00:07:00,150 --> 00:07:02,830
我不是以前的我了
I'm not the same person I used to be.

121
00:07:02,830 --> 00:07:04,590
给她看呀
So show her.

122
00:07:05,260 --> 00:07:06,840
做你自己
Be yourself.

123
00:07:06,840 --> 00:07:09,310
新的自己
I mean your new self.

124
00:07:21,040 --> 00:07:22,730
睡得好吗
How did you sleep?

125
00:07:22,730 --> 00:07:24,680
挺好的  谢谢
Just fine. Thank you.

126
00:07:25,860 --> 00:07:26,900
有客人
We have a visitor.

127
00:07:26,900 --> 00:07:30,550
是狄格尔先生的接班人
Hmm. Mr. Diggle's replacement.

128
00:07:31,430 --> 00:07:33,040
接班人
Replacement?

129
00:07:33,040 --> 00:07:36,940
对  今早他递交了辞呈
Yes. He tendered his resignation this morning.

130
00:07:36,940 --> 00:07:38,320
他有说为什么吗
Did he say why?

131
00:07:38,320 --> 00:07:41,550
他说他看不惯你的夜生活
He said he didn't approve of the way you spend your evenings,

132
00:07:41,550 --> 00:07:45,120
特别是从你总是甩开他开始
particularly given that they always begin with you ditching him.

133
00:07:47,560 --> 00:07:49,350
奎恩先生  我是罗布·斯科特
Mr. Queen, Rob Scott.

134
00:07:49,350 --> 00:07:50,480
我是你的新保镖
I'll be your new body man.

135
00:07:50,480 --> 00:07:51,920
你这握手很有力  罗布
That's a firm grip you got there, Rob.

136
00:07:51,920 --> 00:07:54,990
五年市政局纪念厅特警队训练出来的
That's 5 years SWAT with monument point M.C.U.

137
00:07:55,360 --> 00:07:56,810
我已经觉得安全多了
I feel safer already.

138
00:07:56,820 --> 00:08:00,830
谢天谢地我们再不会听到这人渣的消息了
Ah, thank god we don't have to hear about this awful man anymore.

139
00:08:03,900 --> 00:08:06,910
德克兰被判死刑

140
00:08:03,270 --> 00:08:07,050
德克兰的死刑将于两天后的午夜执行
Declan's execution is set for midnight 2 days from now.

141
00:08:07,050 --> 00:08:08,940
卡米尔·德克兰的前雇主
Camille Declan's former employer,

142
00:08:08,940 --> 00:08:11,020
杰森·布洛德  发表声明
Jason Brodeur, released a statement

143
00:08:11,020 --> 00:08:13,900
表示"我希望卡米尔能够
saying, quote, "I hope this gives Camille

144
00:08:13,910 --> 00:08:15,340
获得她应得的平静"
the peace she deserves."

145
00:08:15,340 --> 00:08:17,110
杰森·布洛德
Jason Brodeur?

146
00:08:17,540 --> 00:08:18,290
什么
What?

147
00:08:18,290 --> 00:08:21,440
去世的妻子在杰森·布洛德手下工作
The dead wife worked for Jason Brodeur.

148
00:08:21,830 --> 00:08:24,000
明摆着的  怎么
Apparently so. What--

149
00:08:24,000 --> 00:08:25,070
为什么这么说
Why?

150
00:08:25,070 --> 00:08:26,120
没什么
No reason.

151
00:08:26,120 --> 00:08:28,260
比方说  罗布  我想进城
Say, Rob, I want to go into town.

152
00:08:28,260 --> 00:08:29,690
你能帮我把车开来吗
Could you please get the car for me?

153
00:08:29,690 --> 00:08:30,920
无冒犯之意  奎恩先生
No offense, Mr. Queen,

154
00:08:30,920 --> 00:08:32,630
但是我已被告知你会想方设法
but I have been filled in on your tendency

155
00:08:32,630 --> 00:08:34,020
摆脱束缚
to slip the leash.

156
00:08:34,020 --> 00:08:35,390
如果这对你来说并无差别  我更愿意
If it's all the same to you, I'd prefer

157
00:08:35,390 --> 00:08:37,570
时刻盯牢你
keeping you in my sights at all times.

158
00:08:39,120 --> 00:08:41,190
我们离城里二十英里远
We're 20 miles from the city.

159
00:08:41,200 --> 00:08:42,910
如果你不开车送我
If you don't drive me,

160
00:08:42,910 --> 00:08:45,070
那我怎么进城
how else am I gonna get there?

161
00:08:46,720 --> 00:08:48,250
对吧
Right?

162
00:08:53,010 --> 00:08:54,590
我很中意他
I like him.

163
00:09:06,710 --> 00:09:09,080
{\pos(105,186)}奎恩工业

164
00:09:10,630 --> 00:09:14,100
人们说彼得·德克兰冷血地残杀了妻子
They say Peter Declan murdered his wife in cold blood.

165
00:09:14,100 --> 00:09:15,910
他没有不在场证明
He had no alibi,

166
00:09:15,910 --> 00:09:18,150
而且所有证据都指向凶手是他
and all the evidence pointed toward him.

167
00:09:18,150 --> 00:09:21,970
他被审讯  判罪  判处死刑
He was tried, convicted, and sentenced to death,

168
00:09:21,970 --> 00:09:23,860
一目了然的案子
an open-and-shut case,

169
00:09:23,860 --> 00:09:25,690
除了一点
except for one thing.

170
00:09:25,690 --> 00:09:29,080
德克兰的妻子卡米尔为杰森·布洛德工作
Declan's wife Camille worked for Jason Brodeur.

171
00:09:30,120 --> 00:09:32,160
{\pos(227,48)}杰森·布洛德

172
00:09:29,080 --> 00:09:32,480
而杰森·布洛德在名单上
And Jason Brodeur is on the list.

173
00:09:32,490 --> 00:09:34,750
星报
弑妻凶手被判死刑

174
00:09:37,880 --> 00:09:38,930
布洛德先生
Mr. Brodeur.

175
00:09:38,930 --> 00:09:41,710
在欣赏自己的杰作吗
Admiring your handiwork?

176
00:09:43,010 --> 00:09:44,950
你本该让我把他俩全杀了
You should have just let me kill both of 'em.

177
00:09:44,950 --> 00:09:47,000
彼得·德克兰可以多活一阵
Peter Declan is worth more alive.

178
00:09:47,000 --> 00:09:49,650
"亲夫弑妻"做头条比
"Husband Kills Wife" is a much better headline

179
00:09:49,650 --> 00:09:52,550
"知情者揭露废弃物倾倒事件"更适合
than "Whistle-blower Uncovers Toxic Dumping."

180
00:09:52,650 --> 00:09:53,550
你说呢
Don't you think?

181
00:09:53,550 --> 00:09:55,380
不论怎样  两天以后
Either way, 48 hours,

182
00:09:55,380 --> 00:09:57,400
这一切就都结束了
all this'll be over.

183
00:10:02,680 --> 00:10:03,940
此次谋杀事件
The odds are good that Brodeur

184
00:10:03,950 --> 00:10:05,720
布洛德参与其中的可能性很高
is involved in this woman's murder,

185
00:10:05,720 --> 00:10:09,160
也就是说一个无辜之人即将面临死刑
which means an innocent man is facing execution.

186
00:10:09,930 --> 00:10:12,060
他需要一个好律师
He'll need a good attorney.

187
00:10:12,650 --> 00:10:14,620
那我可以认为完全没必要
So I take it there's absolutely no point

188
00:10:14,620 --> 00:10:16,710
问你有没有空喝一杯
in asking if you'd like to grab a drink?

189
00:10:16,720 --> 00:10:20,340
我没法去  得去审核费尔南斯案的笔录
I can't. I have to go over transcripts for the Fernands case.

190
00:10:20,900 --> 00:10:23,970
如果你不是工作和家两点一线的
You know, if you go somewhere that's not work or your home,

191
00:10:23,970 --> 00:10:25,600
那你能遇到什么人的几率会一下提高
your odds of meeting someone increase by,

192
00:10:25,600 --> 00:10:26,730
无数个百分点
like, a gazillion percent.

193
00:10:26,730 --> 00:10:27,830
此言差矣
Oh, that's not true.

194
00:10:27,830 --> 00:10:29,370
我回家路上还是可能被抢
I could still get mugged on the way home.

195
00:10:29,370 --> 00:10:32,910
那样的话  我可希望抢劫犯帅气又单身
In that case, I hope he's cute and single.

196
00:10:32,910 --> 00:10:34,800
晚安  乔安娜
Good night, Joanna.

197
00:11:01,510 --> 00:11:03,100
你好  劳蕾尔
Hello, Laurel.

198
00:11:08,500 --> 00:11:10,260
别动
Don't move!

199
00:11:11,870 --> 00:11:13,000
我不会伤害你
I'm not gonna hurt you.

200
00:11:13,000 --> 00:11:15,480
离我远点  我父亲是警察
Stay back. My father's a cop.

201
00:11:15,480 --> 00:11:17,060
你犯了个大错
You are making a huge mistake.

202
00:11:17,060 --> 00:11:19,120
我并非你想的那样
I'm not the person you think I am,

203
00:11:19,120 --> 00:11:20,580
而且我需要你的帮助
and I need your help.

204
00:11:20,580 --> 00:11:23,050
彼得·德克兰将于两天后处决死刑
Peter Declan is gonna be executed in 48 hours.

205
00:11:23,050 --> 00:11:24,850
我认为他是无辜的
I think he's innocent.

206
00:11:24,850 --> 00:11:27,480
德克兰的妻子本来要告发杰森·布洛德
Declan's wife was gonna blow the whistle on Jason Brodeur.

207
00:11:27,480 --> 00:11:29,030
是布洛德将其谋害的
Brodeur had her murdered.

208
00:11:29,030 --> 00:11:31,710
星城有上千律师
There are a thousand lawyers in Starling City.

209
00:11:32,520 --> 00:11:34,040
为什么偏找我
Why me?

210
00:11:38,090 --> 00:11:40,250
我们都想帮忙
We're both trying to help.

211
00:11:41,460 --> 00:11:43,980
你怎么能确定我会帮你
What makes you sure I'm gonna help you?

212
00:11:45,300 --> 00:11:46,540
因为我知道你会不惜一切
Because I know you'd do anything

213
00:11:46,540 --> 00:11:49,310
挽救一条无辜的生命
to save the life of an innocent man.

214
00:12:02,730 --> 00:12:05,800
陪审团已判你有罪  德克兰先生
A jury has charged you as guilty, Mr. Declan.

215
00:12:05,890 --> 00:12:07,700
所有证据矛头都指向我
The evidence was stacked against me,

216
00:12:07,700 --> 00:12:09,900
但是我没有杀我妻子
but I didn't kill my wife.

217
00:12:10,030 --> 00:12:12,910
我没有从我女儿手中夺走她母亲的生命
I didn't take my daughter's mother from her.

218
00:12:15,160 --> 00:12:17,720
凶器是是你厨房的刀
The murder weapon was a knife

219
00:12:17,720 --> 00:12:20,340
上面有你的指纹
from your kitchen with your prints on it.

220
00:12:20,340 --> 00:12:22,780
刀和卡米尔的血迹
It was found, along with Camille's blood,

221
00:12:22,780 --> 00:12:24,280
是在你的汽车后备箱找到的
in the trunk of your car.

222
00:12:24,280 --> 00:12:27,210
你的邻居说他们当晚听到争吵
Your neighbors said they heard an argument that night.

223
00:12:27,210 --> 00:12:30,530
我们在争吵关于杰森·布洛德的事
We had a knockdown fight over Jason Brodeur.

224
00:12:31,260 --> 00:12:32,870
卡米尔在他手下工作
Camille worked for him,

225
00:12:32,880 --> 00:12:36,890
他的公司一直都向贫民区倾倒有毒废弃物
and his company had been dumping toxic waste into the glades.

226
00:12:36,890 --> 00:12:37,770
卡米尔告诉我
Now, Camille told me that

227
00:12:37,770 --> 00:12:39,780
她要把这事告诉负责人
she'd gone and told a supervisor about it.

228
00:12:39,780 --> 00:12:42,280
我很担心我家人的安全
I was afraid for my family's safety.

229
00:12:42,280 --> 00:12:44,160
我们吵得
And we argued

230
00:12:44,920 --> 00:12:47,490
很大声  没错
very loudly, yes.

231
00:12:47,700 --> 00:12:49,540
伊泽开始大哭
Izzy started crying,

232
00:12:49,540 --> 00:12:52,070
于是卡米尔就去待在她房间
so Camille went and stayed in her room.

233
00:12:59,820 --> 00:13:02,850
早上我去道歉
In the morning, I went to apologize, and

234
00:13:03,260 --> 00:13:05,170
那时我才发现她
that's when I found her.

235
00:13:06,920 --> 00:13:08,480
所以我抱起伊泽
So I just grabbed Izzy,

236
00:13:08,480 --> 00:13:11,890
跑到外面  打了911
and I ran outside, and I called 911.

237
00:13:16,130 --> 00:13:18,570
我是无辜的  兰斯小姐
I'm innocent, Ms. Lance.

238
00:13:22,010 --> 00:13:24,430
{\pos(183,169)}奎恩集团

239
00:13:23,100 --> 00:13:24,840
看来有人忘记
Well, it looks like someone forgot

240
00:13:24,840 --> 00:13:26,770
和他妻子约好的午饭了
a lunch date with his wife.

241
00:13:26,770 --> 00:13:27,910
你什么意思
What do you mean?

242
00:13:27,910 --> 00:13:29,930
离午饭还有
Lunch isn't for another--

243
00:13:31,310 --> 00:13:33,120
45分钟前  非常抱歉
45 minutes ago. I'm so sorry.

244
00:13:33,120 --> 00:13:36,140
没关系  餐厅给我们留着位子呢
It's all right. The restaurant is holding our table.

245
00:13:36,140 --> 00:13:37,850
出了什么事吗
Is there something wrong?

246
00:13:38,330 --> 00:13:40,600
监察部查到一些东西
Compliance department has tagged something,

247
00:13:40,600 --> 00:13:42,390
有260万从
$2.6 million withdrawal

248
00:13:42,390 --> 00:13:44,440
温哥华的子公司之一被取走
from one of our Vancouver subsidiaries.

249
00:13:44,440 --> 00:13:46,490
什么  你是说  有人
What--you mean-- are you saying that someone

250
00:13:46,490 --> 00:13:48,970
从公司挪用了260万公款吗
embezzled $2.6 million from the company?

251
00:13:48,970 --> 00:13:50,890
很可能是个记账失误
Well, it's probably a bookkeeping error,

252
00:13:50,890 --> 00:13:52,220
但可以理解
but compliance is understandably

253
00:13:52,220 --> 00:13:54,580
监察部担心国税局的账务审核
worried about an IRS audit.

254
00:13:58,220 --> 00:14:00,320
但是别担心  肯定没什么大事
But don't worry. I'm sure it's nothing.

255
00:14:00,320 --> 00:14:01,750
来吧  我们要晚了
Come on. We're gonna be late.

256
00:14:02,690 --> 00:14:05,000
我是说  更迟了
I mean, later.

257
00:14:06,410 --> 00:14:08,180
我不负责这件案子
Well, I wasn't the lead on this,

258
00:14:08,190 --> 00:14:10,760
不过据我所知  我们有指纹
but from what I recall, we had fingerprints.

259
00:14:10,760 --> 00:14:14,380
我们有血迹  有动机  什么都有
We had blood. We got motive, everything.

260
00:14:16,170 --> 00:14:17,530
布洛德看起来就像是那种
Brodeur seems like the type of guy

261
00:14:17,530 --> 00:14:20,300
拥有强大财力的人想要陷害的人
with resources needed to frame someone.

262
00:14:20,300 --> 00:14:22,430
劳蕾尔  24小时内
Laurel, in 24 hours,

263
00:14:22,430 --> 00:14:23,550
彼得·德克兰的胳膊上就会
Peter Declan is lying down

264
00:14:23,550 --> 00:14:25,650
挨上一针  并且一直睡下去
with a needle in his arm, and he's not getting up.

265
00:14:25,650 --> 00:14:27,400
如果试想我们抓错了人
If I thought for a second we didn't have the right guy,

266
00:14:27,400 --> 00:14:28,990
你认为我现在除了试着了解真相之外
do you think there's anything else I'd be doing right now

267
00:14:28,990 --> 00:14:31,190
还有什么能做的
except trying to get at what really happened?

268
00:14:31,190 --> 00:14:33,710
德克兰说她妻子去见她的主管
Declan said his wife went to her supervisor

269
00:14:33,710 --> 00:14:36,490
指控布洛德倾倒有毒废物
with allegations that Brodeur was dumping toxic waste.

270
00:14:36,490 --> 00:14:39,340
对  但那个主管
Yeah, but that supervisor,

271
00:14:39,340 --> 00:14:40,970
他说那从没发生过
he said that never happened.

272
00:14:40,980 --> 00:14:42,290
我看看  他叫什么
Let me see. What was his name?

273
00:14:42,290 --> 00:14:44,410
这里  伊斯托克  马特·伊斯托克
Here you go. Istook, Matt istook.

274
00:14:44,410 --> 00:14:46,730
他说他那天根本都没看见过卡米尔
He said he didn't even see Camille that day.

275
00:14:47,570 --> 00:14:48,800
满意了
Happy now?

276
00:14:48,800 --> 00:14:50,330
是的
Yes.

277
00:14:53,220 --> 00:14:54,790
在你开始为罪犯辩护之前
You know, I thought it'd be a cold day in hell

278
00:14:54,790 --> 00:14:56,320
我觉得这根本不可能发生
before you started defending criminals.

279
00:14:56,320 --> 00:14:58,380
我不确定德克兰是否是罪犯
I'm not so sure Declan's a criminal.

280
00:14:58,680 --> 00:15:00,640
就像你说的  他还有时间
Like you said, he's on a clock.

281
00:15:01,230 --> 00:15:03,220
不能有任何疏漏
Can't leave any stone unturned.

282
00:15:06,090 --> 00:15:06,990
好的
Oh, yeah.

283
00:15:13,700 --> 00:15:14,990
你打算什么时候告诉我
So when are you gonna tell me?

284
00:15:15,180 --> 00:15:16,050
什么
Hmm?

285
00:15:16,520 --> 00:15:18,320
你的胳膊怎么了
About what happened to your arm.

286
00:15:18,960 --> 00:15:21,330
是我的肩膀  没事了
Oh, it's my shoulder, and it's--it's fine.

287
00:15:21,600 --> 00:15:23,260
我知道奎恩那家伙是个麻烦
I knew that Queen guy was trouble.

288
00:15:23,340 --> 00:15:25,440
我可没说是因为保护奎恩而受的伤
Hey, I never said this happened protecting Queen.

289
00:15:27,300 --> 00:15:28,140
是吗
Oh, yeah?

290
00:15:29,050 --> 00:15:30,370
那他干嘛来这里
Then what's he doing here?

291
00:15:34,460 --> 00:15:35,660
这里很安全  先生
Area is secure, sir.

292
00:15:35,760 --> 00:15:37,220
非常感谢  罗勃
Thank you very much, Rob.

293
00:15:40,000 --> 00:15:43,160
你好  狄格尔的嫂子卡莉
Hello, Diggle's sister-in-law Carly.

294
00:15:43,300 --> 00:15:45,780
-奥利弗·奎恩  -我知道你是谁
- I'm Oliver Queen. - I know who you are.

295
00:15:45,780 --> 00:15:47,140
不  你不知道
No, you really don't.

296
00:15:51,900 --> 00:15:52,720
你好
Hello.

297
00:15:55,870 --> 00:15:59,630
当我到家时  我不由得注意到居然没有警车
I couldn't help but notice a distinct lack of police cars when I got home.

298
00:15:59,630 --> 00:16:01,860
我就知道你不会告发我
I knew you wouldn't drop a dime on me.

299
00:16:01,860 --> 00:16:05,000
所以你考虑过我的提议吗
So have you considered my offer?

300
00:16:05,030 --> 00:16:05,860
提议
Offer.

301
00:16:06,110 --> 00:16:07,280
那还真是个有趣的说法
That's one hell of a way to put it.

302
00:16:07,280 --> 00:16:08,350
这是提议
It is an offer.

303
00:16:09,390 --> 00:16:11,750
这是提议去做
It's a chance to do the kind of good

304
00:16:11,750 --> 00:16:13,760
不得不参军才能做到的那种善事
that compelled you to join the military.

305
00:16:14,300 --> 00:16:15,230
得了吧
Please.

306
00:16:16,040 --> 00:16:18,270
你是含着金汤匙出生的  奎恩
You were born with a platinum spoon in your mouth, Queen.

307
00:16:18,270 --> 00:16:20,790
你在一个没有客房服务的岛上待了五年
What, you spent 5 years on an island with no room service,

308
00:16:20,790 --> 00:16:22,510
突然间就找到了信仰
and suddenly you found religion?

309
00:16:26,140 --> 00:16:27,390
这是我父亲的
This was my father's.

310
00:16:33,290 --> 00:16:34,640
我埋葬他时找到的
I found it when I buried him.

311
00:16:36,680 --> 00:16:38,930
我记得你说过你父亲是死于沉船
I thought you said your father died when the boat went down.

312
00:16:38,930 --> 00:16:40,180
我们俩都登上了救生筏
We both made it to a life raft,

313
00:16:40,180 --> 00:16:41,900
但是食物和水不够我们两个人的
but there wasn't enough food and water

314
00:16:41,900 --> 00:16:44,130
所以他开枪自杀了
for both of us, so he shot himself in the head.

315
00:16:45,350 --> 00:16:48,270
他那么做除了是为了让我活下去
And as much as he was doing it to give me a chance to survive,

316
00:16:48,280 --> 00:16:50,860
我相信也是在赎罪
I believe that he was also atoning for his sins.

317
00:16:52,150 --> 00:16:54,730
我要纠正我家人犯下的错误
I need to right the wrongs done by my family,

318
00:16:56,140 --> 00:16:58,570
我现在在给你提供
and I'm offering you the chance

319
00:16:58,570 --> 00:17:00,970
纠正你所犯下错误的机会
to right the wrongs done to yours.

320
00:17:01,220 --> 00:17:02,290
奥利弗  你在说些什么
Oliver, what are you talking about?

321
00:17:02,290 --> 00:17:04,100
警察永远不会抓住杀害你哥哥的人
The police never caught your brother's shooter.

322
00:17:04,100 --> 00:17:06,030
别把安迪扯进来
Hey, you leave Andy out of this.

323
00:17:06,030 --> 00:17:07,610
子弹上带有箭毒
The bullets were laced with curare.

324
00:17:07,610 --> 00:17:08,950
那是弗洛伊德·劳顿的手法
That's Floyd Lawton's M.O.

325
00:17:08,950 --> 00:17:13,520
他是我曾阻止过的一个狙击手
He is the sniper that I stopped.

326
00:17:14,760 --> 00:17:17,380
你是想告诉我你放倒了杀害安迪的人
Are you trying to tell me that you took down Andy's killer?

327
00:17:17,390 --> 00:17:20,510
我是在给你机会
I'm-- I'm giving you the chance,

328
00:17:21,680 --> 00:17:25,520
帮助别人的家人的机会
a chance to help other people's families.

329
00:17:25,780 --> 00:17:27,440
你还记得这个城市的人
Do you remember when the people

330
00:17:27,440 --> 00:17:30,020
互相帮助的时候吗
in this city helped each other?

331
00:17:30,320 --> 00:17:31,930
他们不会再帮助别人了
They can't do that anymore,

332
00:17:31,930 --> 00:17:33,650
因为一伙人
because a group of people,

333
00:17:34,650 --> 00:17:36,300
像我父亲那样的人
people like my father,

334
00:17:37,640 --> 00:17:40,510
他们踩着别人的喉咙向上爬
they see nothing wrong with raising themselves up

335
00:17:40,510 --> 00:17:43,390
还不觉得有什么错
by stepping on other people's throats.

336
00:17:44,290 --> 00:17:45,800
需要有人来停止
It does need to stop,

337
00:17:45,920 --> 00:17:47,800
如果法官不出手
and if it's not gonna be the courts

338
00:17:47,800 --> 00:17:49,640
如果警察不出手
and it's not gonna be the cops...

339
00:17:51,960 --> 00:17:53,470
那就由我来做
then it's gonna be me.

340
00:17:58,370 --> 00:17:59,600
我希望还有你
And, I hope, you.

341
00:18:04,450 --> 00:18:05,890
我要去趟洗手间  罗勃
I'm gonna go to the washroom, Rob.

342
00:18:18,920 --> 00:18:20,560
他已经跑远了  伙计
Oh, that boy's long gone, man.

343
00:18:24,290 --> 00:18:26,160
你还在追查钱的流向
You still following the money trail?

344
00:18:26,160 --> 00:18:28,460
这事不是应该由会计来做吗
Don't we have accountants for that sort of thing?

345
00:18:28,460 --> 00:18:31,330
这种情况下他们没什么用
They're being singularly ineffective in this instance.

346
00:18:31,480 --> 00:18:32,610
那么
Well, then...

347
00:18:33,190 --> 00:18:35,750
幸运的是我已经解开这个谜团了
It's fortunate that I've solved the mystery.

348
00:18:37,800 --> 00:18:39,430
我想我就是犯人
I think I'm the culprit.

349
00:18:40,510 --> 00:18:43,420
260万是个特殊的数字
2.6 million is a rather specific figure.

350
00:18:43,500 --> 00:18:46,400
那正是公司三年前投资到一家
That's the exact amount the company invested

351
00:18:46,400 --> 00:18:48,900
朋友的初创企业里的精确数额
in a friend's start-up venture 3 years ago.

352
00:18:50,140 --> 00:18:52,790
我会呼叫会计  让他们负责处理好
I will call accounting. They'll clean it all up.

353
00:18:52,790 --> 00:18:54,540
然后就没什么好担心的了
Then there's nothing to worry about.

354
00:18:54,610 --> 00:18:55,860
好的
Ok.

355
00:19:05,290 --> 00:19:07,930
你在这个德克兰的案子上可真是花了不少时间
You really are putting a lot of hours into this Declan thing.

356
00:19:08,520 --> 00:19:10,200
你真相信他是清白的
You actually think he's innocent.

357
00:19:10,200 --> 00:19:11,160
有人相信
Someone does.

358
00:19:11,240 --> 00:19:12,420
你这样说了
So you said,

359
00:19:12,910 --> 00:19:14,390
但你没说是谁
but you didn't say who.

360
00:19:23,200 --> 00:19:24,390
守护天使
The guardian angel.

361
00:19:25,700 --> 00:19:27,390
戴兜帽的那个家伙吗
The guy in the hood?

362
00:19:28,360 --> 00:19:29,660
你是在开玩笑吧
Look, you're-- you're kidding.

363
00:19:29,670 --> 00:19:32,170
他跟踪我  要我查看德克兰的案子
He tracked me down and asked me to look into the Declan case.

364
00:19:32,170 --> 00:19:33,450
你见过他了
But you've met him?

365
00:19:34,290 --> 00:19:37,000
他相悖于我曾被告知要去相信的一切
But he goes against everything that I was ever taught to believe in.

366
00:19:37,830 --> 00:19:40,470
他违反了法律  谁知道还有什么
He breaks the law and God knows what else.

367
00:19:40,470 --> 00:19:43,270
你怎么能不害怕他会对你些什么
How are you not afraid that he is gonna do God knows what to you?

368
00:19:43,280 --> 00:19:44,240
他不会的
He won't.

369
00:19:45,640 --> 00:19:47,040
我不清楚  我能感觉得到
I don't know. I can feel it.

370
00:19:47,080 --> 00:19:48,590
我是让你去见见别人
You know, when I told you to meet someone,

371
00:19:48,590 --> 00:19:50,760
但这和我的本意差太远了
this is far, far away from what I meant.

372
00:19:56,100 --> 00:19:57,400
我收到了你的信息
I got your message.

373
00:19:58,900 --> 00:20:01,670
为什么我们不能面对面交谈
Is there a reason we can't do this face to face?

374
00:20:02,080 --> 00:20:03,700
你见过彼得·德克兰了
You've met with Peter Declan.

375
00:20:04,510 --> 00:20:05,740
你是对的
You were right.

376
00:20:06,950 --> 00:20:08,260
他很有可能是清白的
He might be innocent.

377
00:20:09,470 --> 00:20:11,550
德克兰说他的妻子在遇害当天
Declan said his wife blew the whistle on Brodeur

378
00:20:11,550 --> 00:20:12,930
揭发了布洛德
the day she was murdered.

379
00:20:13,690 --> 00:20:16,860
我们要找出她向谁告发了布洛德  来做证人
Then we need to get whoever she told about Brodeur to testify.

380
00:20:18,850 --> 00:20:20,190
那个人已经作证了
He already has.

381
00:20:22,000 --> 00:20:24,940
马特·伊斯托克  卡米尔的主管
Matt Istook, Camille's supervisor.

382
00:20:25,700 --> 00:20:28,590
只是  他说她什么也没对他说过
Only, he says that she didn't say a word to him.

383
00:20:28,850 --> 00:20:30,070
他可能在说谎
He could be lying.

384
00:20:30,070 --> 00:20:32,250
如果真在说谎  那他的确很有说服力
Well, if he is, then he's very convincing.

385
00:20:33,800 --> 00:20:35,860
他让陪审团和警察都相信了他
He had the jury and police believing him.

386
00:20:35,860 --> 00:20:37,890
他还没有被我审问过
He hasn't been questioned by me.

387
00:20:40,350 --> 00:20:41,550
我做律师
I didn't become a lawyer

388
00:20:41,550 --> 00:20:43,540
不是为了违法或是伤害谁
to break the law or hurt anybody.

389
00:20:44,700 --> 00:20:46,280
我做的是必要的事
I do what's necessary,

390
00:20:46,690 --> 00:20:48,750
正是彼得·德克兰这种人需要的
what people like Peter Declan need.

391
00:20:50,760 --> 00:20:52,370
如果你做的没错
If what you're doing isn't wrong...

392
00:20:54,500 --> 00:20:56,770
为什么还用兜帽遮住脸
Then why are you hiding your face with a hood?

393
00:20:58,580 --> 00:21:00,760
为了保护我在乎的人
To protect the ones I care about.

394
00:21:02,480 --> 00:21:03,810
听起来很寂寞
That sounds lonely.

395
00:21:04,190 --> 00:21:05,140
有时会
It can be.

396
00:21:07,900 --> 00:21:09,210
但不是今天
But not today.

397
00:21:25,500 --> 00:21:26,750
我有个问题
I've got one question.

398
00:21:27,410 --> 00:21:28,740
我为什么被解雇了
Why am I being fired?

399
00:21:29,950 --> 00:21:31,410
-你是斯莫克小姐  对吗  -是我
- Ms. Smoke, isn't it? - Yes.

400
00:21:31,500 --> 00:21:32,640
我毫无疑问是
And I am without a doubt

401
00:21:32,640 --> 00:21:35,370
技术部门最有价值的员工  没有之一
the single most valuable member of your technical division.

402
00:21:35,370 --> 00:21:37,950
就连我所谓的主管都比不过我
That's including my so-called "supervisor".

403
00:21:38,500 --> 00:21:41,460
让我走会是这个公司的巨大损失
Letting me go would be a major error for this company.

404
00:21:42,620 --> 00:21:45,390
我同意  所以你没有被解雇
I agree, which is why you're not being fired.

405
00:21:45,960 --> 00:21:48,100
我以为你把我叫上来
Uh, I assumed when you brought me up here,

406
00:21:48,100 --> 00:21:49,080
是因为
it was because...

407
00:21:51,440 --> 00:21:53,780
是因为我想让你帮我调查点东西
It's because I wanted you to look into something for me.

408
00:21:55,650 --> 00:21:57,660
三年前一次失败的投资
A variance of $2.6 million

409
00:21:57,660 --> 00:21:59,870
所留下来的两百六十万的资金异常
on a failed investment from 3 years ago.

410
00:21:59,870 --> 00:22:01,470
是由我太太授权过的
It was authorized by my wife.

411
00:22:01,820 --> 00:22:03,620
我希望你能为我查明
I was hoping you could find out

412
00:22:03,620 --> 00:22:06,000
一些交易的细节
some of the details of the transaction for me.

413
00:22:06,100 --> 00:22:06,770
查明
Find out...

414
00:22:06,770 --> 00:22:09,160
谨慎一点去挖
Dig up discreetly.

415
00:22:10,400 --> 00:22:11,390
我现在是你的人了
I'm your girl.

416
00:22:15,840 --> 00:22:17,090
我是说  我不是你的人
I mean, I'm not your girl.

417
00:22:17,090 --> 00:22:18,910
我刚刚不是在挑逗你
I wasn't making a pass at you.

418
00:22:21,300 --> 00:22:23,440
谢谢你没有解雇我
Thank you for not firing me.

419
00:22:36,330 --> 00:22:37,330
什么玩...
What the...

420
00:22:46,210 --> 00:22:47,450
马特·伊斯托克
Matt Istook.

421
00:22:50,850 --> 00:22:53,230
你是那个人  戴兜帽的家伙
You're him, that hood guy.

422
00:22:53,230 --> 00:22:55,010
你是那个不断威胁城市的人
You're the guy that's been terrorizing the city.

423
00:22:55,010 --> 00:22:56,200
彼得·德克兰
Peter Declan,

424
00:22:56,200 --> 00:22:58,540
你的谎话把他送进了死囚牢房
your lies helped put him on death row.

425
00:22:58,620 --> 00:23:00,760
现在你可以选择告诉我真相
Now, either it's time to tell me the truth,

426
00:23:00,760 --> 00:23:03,480
或者坐上10:15的列车去见上帝
or it's time for the 10:15 to blood haven.

427
00:23:03,480 --> 00:23:04,240
好  好
O-ok.

428
00:23:04,240 --> 00:23:07,720
我  布洛德付我钱叫我
Ok, I-- Brodeur paid me to--

429
00:23:07,720 --> 00:23:09,470
说卡米尔从未对我说过什么
to say that Camille never spoke to me,

430
00:23:09,470 --> 00:23:11,820
但我和她的死无关
but I didn't have anything to do with her death.

431
00:23:11,820 --> 00:23:13,980
天哪  求求你  叫我做什么都行
Oh, god, please. I'll do anything.

432
00:23:13,980 --> 00:23:15,200
你  你可以把文件拿走
Y-you could have the file.

433
00:23:15,200 --> 00:23:17,210
什么文件  卡米尔给我的文件
What file? Camille gave me a file

434
00:23:17,210 --> 00:23:18,980
里面有对杰森·布洛德不利的证据
of evidence against Jason Brodeur.

435
00:23:18,980 --> 00:23:20,330
-它在哪  -让我走
- Where is it?! - Let me go,

436
00:23:20,340 --> 00:23:21,150
我就告诉你
and I'll tell you.

437
00:23:22,420 --> 00:23:26,560
等等  等等  别走  在我的书桌里
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Don't go! It's in my desk!

438
00:23:26,560 --> 00:23:28,000
那份文件  在我办公室的书桌里
The file, it's in my desk at the office!

439
00:23:28,000 --> 00:23:29,740
你可以拿走  快放我走
You can have it! Get me out of here!

440
00:23:42,390 --> 00:23:43,260
那是什么
What is that?

441
00:23:44,440 --> 00:23:45,730
我好饿
I'm so hungry.

442
00:23:49,130 --> 00:23:50,580
闻起来好香啊
It smells really good.

443
00:23:55,830 --> 00:23:57,620
好吧  不分就不分
Hey, fine. Don't share.

444
00:24:05,030 --> 00:24:06,150
生存

445
00:24:14,780 --> 00:24:16,440
我才不会杀那只鸟呢
I'm not gonna kill the bird.

446
00:24:19,750 --> 00:24:20,910
生存

447
00:24:39,290 --> 00:24:41,050
马特·伊斯托克的敬意
Compliments of Matt Istook.

448
00:24:42,170 --> 00:24:42,950
这里面是什么
What's in here?

449
00:24:42,950 --> 00:24:45,430
扳倒杰森·布洛德的筹码
Leverage on Jason Brodeur,

450
00:24:45,990 --> 00:24:48,230
足够救彼得·德克兰的命
enough to help save Peter Declan's life.

451
00:24:48,230 --> 00:24:49,450
作为一名律师
As an attorney,

452
00:24:49,450 --> 00:24:51,570
我不应该拿到这样的文件
I never would have gotten a file like this.

453
00:24:52,190 --> 00:24:54,200
我一直认为法律是神圣的
I always thought the law was sacred,

454
00:24:54,200 --> 00:24:55,740
它可以解决一切
i-it fixed everything.

455
00:24:55,770 --> 00:24:56,950
那现在呢  劳蕾尔
And now, Laurel?

456
00:24:57,990 --> 00:24:59,200
现在你怎么认为
Now what do you think?

457
00:25:00,750 --> 00:25:02,380
我认为这个城市有太多人
I think there's too many people in this city

458
00:25:02,380 --> 00:25:04,080
只在乎他们自己
who only care about themselves...

459
00:25:05,840 --> 00:25:07,170
自私的人们
People who are selfish.

460
00:25:09,330 --> 00:25:10,680
我认为他们需要
I think they need someone who cares

461
00:25:10,690 --> 00:25:12,400
在乎他人性命的人
about the lives of other people...

462
00:25:15,400 --> 00:25:16,450
像你一样的人
Someone like you.

463
00:25:16,450 --> 00:25:21,660
*神啊  请给我你的庇护*
*God, give me your shelter*

464
00:25:36,940 --> 00:25:38,620
噢  天哪
Oh, my god.

465
00:25:38,930 --> 00:25:40,870
你的脸怎么了
What is wrong with your face?

466
00:25:41,010 --> 00:25:41,820
什么意思
What do you mean?

467
00:25:41,820 --> 00:25:43,670
你脸上有点特奇怪的东西
There's something really weird on it,

468
00:25:43,670 --> 00:25:45,660
像是你的嘴
like this thing with your mouth.

469
00:25:45,660 --> 00:25:48,810
看起来  就像是在微笑
It--it looks like it's in the shape of a smile.

470
00:25:48,810 --> 00:25:50,720
-你真逗  -所以你为什么这么开心
- That's cute. - So why are you grinning?

471
00:25:50,720 --> 00:25:53,530
我采纳了你关于劳蕾尔的建议
I took your advice with Laurel

472
00:25:54,200 --> 00:25:55,320
做我自己
to be myself.

473
00:25:55,320 --> 00:25:56,510
然后呢
And...

474
00:25:56,650 --> 00:25:57,720
很管用
It's helping.

475
00:25:57,890 --> 00:26:00,260
我是恋爱关系达人哪  哥
Got mad relationship skills, bro.

476
00:26:00,590 --> 00:26:03,130
如果你想找个很潮的求婚地点记得来找我
Let me know if you need trendy places to propose.

477
00:26:03,130 --> 00:26:05,200
我觉得你有点操之过急了
I think you're getting a little bit ahead of yourself.

478
00:26:05,350 --> 00:26:06,420
一点点
Mm. Little bit.

479
00:26:09,330 --> 00:26:10,130
罗布
Rob.

480
00:26:11,850 --> 00:26:12,970
下次得跟上了
You gotta keep up.

481
00:26:25,390 --> 00:26:26,410
你看起来很忙
Hey, you look busy.

482
00:26:27,690 --> 00:26:28,890
是德克兰的案子吗
Is that the Declan case?

483
00:26:28,900 --> 00:26:30,580
在马特·伊斯托克的事情上
You know, it was a funny development

484
00:26:30,580 --> 00:26:31,810
有个很有趣的进展
on Matt Istook.

485
00:26:31,810 --> 00:26:33,170
他向警方报案
He, uh, filed a police report.

486
00:26:33,170 --> 00:26:35,140
说那个兜帽人昨晚骚扰了他
He said the hood harassed him last night.

487
00:26:35,140 --> 00:26:35,760
有趣就在于
And that's funny,

488
00:26:35,760 --> 00:26:38,150
我刚把他的名字告诉我女儿
because I gave my daughter Istook's name.

489
00:26:38,150 --> 00:26:40,510
-爸爸  -他自以为在维护治安
- Dad-- - He's a vigilante.

490
00:26:41,220 --> 00:26:42,220
可他是个罪犯
He's a damn criminal,

491
00:26:42,220 --> 00:26:43,900
如果你跟他一起  你就会变成他的同党
and you working with him, that makes you an accessory.

492
00:26:43,900 --> 00:26:46,400
我是在救一个无辜的人的性命
I am trying to save an innocent man's life.

493
00:26:47,780 --> 00:26:48,590
不行
No.

494
00:26:49,640 --> 00:26:51,180
你在违法
You're breaking the law.

495
00:26:51,190 --> 00:26:52,530
如果不是警方一开始
Well, I wouldn't have to if the police

496
00:26:52,530 --> 00:26:54,410
就没有尽职  我也没必要这么做
would have done their job right in the first place.

497
00:26:57,830 --> 00:26:58,900
我问过你是如何接到这个案子的
I asked you how you got this case.

498
00:26:58,900 --> 00:27:01,590
你当着我的面说了谎  对吗
You lied to me straight to my face, eh?

499
00:27:04,210 --> 00:27:05,910
我还以为我们不会这样
I thought you and I didn't do that.

500
00:27:07,940 --> 00:27:08,950
我猜我想错了
Guess I was wrong.

501
00:27:13,290 --> 00:27:15,660
法官  单是此份文件的出现
You honor, the mere existence of the file

502
00:27:15,660 --> 00:27:18,180
就证明伊斯托克先生
proves that Mr. Istook perjured himself

503
00:27:18,180 --> 00:27:19,870
为了杰森·布洛德的利益作伪证
for Jason Brodeur's benefit.

504
00:27:19,870 --> 00:27:21,040
这是诽谤
That's slander.

505
00:27:21,140 --> 00:27:22,800
我是贾里德·斯万斯特洛姆  法官
Jared Swanstrom, your honor.

506
00:27:22,800 --> 00:27:25,350
我代表杰森·布洛德和布洛德化工
I represent Jason Brodeur and Brodeur Chemical.

507
00:27:25,630 --> 00:27:27,770
鉴于司法公正  您应该
The interest of justice requires you

508
00:27:27,770 --> 00:27:29,560
暂缓被告的行刑
to stay the defendant's execution

509
00:27:29,560 --> 00:27:32,420
因为案件出现了新证据
pending exploration of the newly discovered evidence.

510
00:27:32,420 --> 00:27:35,240
兰斯小姐  我们的法院不是为司法公正服务的
Ours isn't a court of justice, Ms. Lance.

511
00:27:35,240 --> 00:27:36,540
而是为法律服务
It's a court of law.

512
00:27:36,600 --> 00:27:38,720
根据法律  你所提供的证据
And under the law, I don't think your evidence

513
00:27:38,720 --> 00:27:41,230
不足以申请暂缓执行
is sufficient to warrant a stay of execution.

514
00:27:42,080 --> 00:27:44,300
申请人身保护权被驳回
Your motion for habeas corpus is denied.

515
00:27:47,550 --> 00:27:48,510
这事还没完
This isn't over.

516
00:27:49,060 --> 00:27:50,410
我已经找到了突破口
I've got the loose end now,

517
00:27:50,410 --> 00:27:51,370
所以不论发生什么
and no matter what happens,

518
00:27:51,380 --> 00:27:54,280
我都会坚持下去直到把你打垮
I am going to pull on it until your whole world unravels.

519
00:27:56,870 --> 00:27:58,680
德克兰的律师把我扯进来了
Declan's lawyer's pulling me into this.

520
00:27:58,680 --> 00:27:59,850
我要进监狱了
I'm gonna go to prison.

521
00:28:00,190 --> 00:28:00,720
即使不是因为谋杀罪
If not for murder,

522
00:28:00,720 --> 00:28:02,410
也是因为这...这个倾倒垃圾的事
then this-- this dumping thing.

523
00:28:02,410 --> 00:28:03,300
不会的
That won't happen.

524
00:28:03,910 --> 00:28:04,880
我们会采取措施的
There are steps we can take.

525
00:28:04,880 --> 00:28:07,090
你也看到了  她追着我不放
You saw her. She's going after me.

526
00:28:07,620 --> 00:28:09,220
经过今天法院里发生的事
She's gonna want to meet with her client

527
00:28:09,220 --> 00:28:10,900
她肯定会去和委托人见面
after what happened in court today.

528
00:28:11,160 --> 00:28:13,270
铁山监狱里我们有人
We have friends up in Iron Heights.

529
00:28:13,910 --> 00:28:15,990
那里可是个危险的地方
Prison can be a dangerous place.

530
00:28:21,300 --> 00:28:22,570
事情还没完
We're not done yet.

531
00:28:23,800 --> 00:28:24,740
我是名律师
I'm an attorney.

532
00:28:24,740 --> 00:28:27,370
相信我  已经结束了
Trust me. We're done.

533
00:28:29,410 --> 00:28:31,640
你需要什么才能还彼得·德克兰自由
What do you need to free Peter Declan?

534
00:28:31,900 --> 00:28:32,940
到了现在这个时候
At this point,

535
00:28:33,850 --> 00:28:36,770
只有布洛德签名的书面认罪才行
nothing short of a signed confession from Brodeur.

536
00:28:38,200 --> 00:28:39,210
你要去哪里
Where are you going?

537
00:28:39,210 --> 00:28:40,460
去让他认罪
To get a confession.

538
00:28:42,230 --> 00:28:43,510
那家公司奎恩夫人
The company Mrs. Queen--

539
00:28:43,790 --> 00:28:45,230
还是斯蒂尔夫人
or Steele.

540
00:28:45,430 --> 00:28:47,200
或者奎恩-斯蒂尔夫人
Mrs. Queen-Steele.

541
00:28:47,210 --> 00:28:48,140
她冠多重姓吗
She hyphenate?

542
00:28:48,140 --> 00:28:50,100
她看起来像喜欢冠多重姓的人
She seems like a woman who would hyphenate.

543
00:28:52,660 --> 00:28:53,240
对了
Right.

544
00:28:53,240 --> 00:28:55,680
她投资的公司其实并不存在
The company she invested in doesn't exist.

545
00:28:55,690 --> 00:28:56,670
什么意思
I don't understand.

546
00:28:56,670 --> 00:28:58,780
没有投资  钱是用来
There was no investment. The money was used

547
00:28:58,780 --> 00:29:01,370
建立了一家叫暴风雨的境外有限责任公司
to set up an offshore LLC called Tempest.

548
00:29:01,560 --> 00:29:02,320
我不记得
I don't recall that name

549
00:29:02,320 --> 00:29:04,050
奎恩联合企业旗下有这个名字的公司
being under the Queen Consolidated banner.

550
00:29:04,050 --> 00:29:05,050
确实不在
'cause it's not.

551
00:29:05,090 --> 00:29:06,990
这家公司未在政府注册过
There's nothing registered with the secretary of state.

552
00:29:06,990 --> 00:29:08,220
没有联邦税收记录
No federal tax records.

553
00:29:08,220 --> 00:29:09,940
没有专利申请记录
No patent applications filed.

554
00:29:09,940 --> 00:29:11,530
但是2009年
But in 2009,

555
00:29:11,530 --> 00:29:14,700
暴风雨公司在星城买了一个仓库
Tempest purchased a warehouse in Starling City.

556
00:29:21,580 --> 00:29:22,620
闷闷不乐也该够了
Enough moping.

557
00:29:24,340 --> 00:29:25,920
你辞职了  事情结束了
You quit. It's done.

558
00:29:25,920 --> 00:29:27,750
我建议你往前看
My advice would be to move on.

559
00:29:27,750 --> 00:29:30,150
要是有那么简单就好了
Well, if it were only that easy.

560
00:29:30,150 --> 00:29:31,090
就是这么简单
Except it is.

561
00:29:31,090 --> 00:29:32,980
做私人保镖太危险了
Personal security is dangerous.

562
00:29:32,980 --> 00:29:34,660
你侄子已经失去了父亲
Your nephew already lost his father.

563
00:29:34,670 --> 00:29:36,740
不能再失去叔叔了
He can't lose his uncle, too.

564
00:29:39,640 --> 00:29:40,280
杀安迪的人没抓到
Does it ever bother you

565
00:29:40,280 --> 00:29:42,090
你觉得困扰吗
they never caught the guy who killed Andy?

566
00:29:45,900 --> 00:29:47,690
我在阿富汗的时候
You know, when I was in Afghanistan,

567
00:29:47,980 --> 00:29:50,360
我认真地完成份内的工作
I had a job, and I did it.

568
00:29:52,540 --> 00:29:54,210
我会力所能及地帮助别人
And when I could, i would help out the people there

569
00:29:54,210 --> 00:29:56,690
这样至少我离开的时候
so that, in some small way, when I left,

570
00:29:56,690 --> 00:29:58,430
我会觉得我让那里变得更好了
I could believe I left it a better place.

571
00:30:01,140 --> 00:30:02,620
但是自从我回来
But ever since I've been home,

572
00:30:02,620 --> 00:30:04,410
我所做的就只是保护混蛋
all I do is protect punks

573
00:30:04,420 --> 00:30:05,780
纵容那些富商
and spoiled one percenters.

574
00:30:05,780 --> 00:30:06,800
确实是
Yeah.

575
00:30:07,930 --> 00:30:10,100
我想念那种有所作为的感觉
I miss feeling like I'm making a difference in the world.

576
00:30:10,100 --> 00:30:11,620
那就不要做私人保镖了
Then get out of personal security

577
00:30:11,620 --> 00:30:13,190
去做一些你深信不疑的事
and go do something you believe in.

578
00:30:13,190 --> 00:30:14,320
要是我相信的是错的呢
Yeah, what if it's wrong?

579
00:30:14,320 --> 00:30:16,260
约翰  如果一件事你深信不疑
John, if you believe in something,

580
00:30:16,570 --> 00:30:17,820
怎么可能是错的呢
how can it be wrong?

581
00:30:19,120 --> 00:30:20,480
杰森·布洛德
Jason Brodeur

582
00:30:21,090 --> 00:30:22,080
你到底想要什么
What do you want?

583
00:30:22,080 --> 00:30:23,520
要你去认罪  说是你安排
You're gonna confess that you arranged

584
00:30:23,530 --> 00:30:25,690
雇人谋杀彼得·德克兰的妻子的
to have Peter Declan's wife murdered.

585
00:30:25,870 --> 00:30:27,350
这样让我替他蹲监狱吗
What, so I can take his place in prison?

586
00:30:27,350 --> 00:30:29,850
是让你去阻止死刑的执行
So you can avoid the death penalty.

587
00:30:29,860 --> 00:30:31,150
但如果我死了
Except if I'm dead,

588
00:30:31,240 --> 00:30:33,400
你也就找不到杀卡米尔的凶手了
well, then, you've got no one to pin Camille's murder on.

589
00:30:33,580 --> 00:30:36,410
你需要我来证明彼得·德克兰无罪
You need me to exonerate Peter Declan.

590
00:30:36,410 --> 00:30:37,270
或许你可以逼我
Maybe you could try to force me

591
00:30:37,270 --> 00:30:39,020
签份认罪书之类的
to sign a confession or something.

592
00:30:40,490 --> 00:30:42,040
这样你就签不了了
That might be difficult.

593
00:30:44,080 --> 00:30:45,170
我的手
My hand!

594
00:30:48,900 --> 00:30:51,630
接电话
Just answer it.

595
00:30:53,010 --> 00:30:54,490
-什么事  -我是安科夫
- What?  - It's Ankov.

596
00:30:54,590 --> 00:30:56,490
准备动手了  一小时后
It's going down, one hour.

597
00:30:56,970 --> 00:30:58,480
一小时后要动手干什么
What's going down in an hour?

598
00:31:00,720 --> 00:31:01,720
什么
What?!

599
00:31:02,200 --> 00:31:03,370
就这么说吧
Let's just say...

600
00:31:03,820 --> 00:31:05,680
彼得·德克兰的死刑执行
Peter Declan's execution.

601
00:31:06,200 --> 00:31:08,410
被提前了
It's getting moved up.

602
00:31:12,230 --> 00:31:13,440
你得听我说
OK, you have to listen to me.

603
00:31:13,440 --> 00:31:14,850
我们还有机会
We still have a shot.

604
00:31:14,860 --> 00:31:16,710
你还记得我提起过的那个朋友吗
Do you remember the friend that I mentioned,

605
00:31:16,710 --> 00:31:18,080
那个相信你的人
the one who believes in you?

606
00:31:18,240 --> 00:31:19,960
他正在努力想办法呢
He is working on something.

607
00:31:26,360 --> 00:31:27,330
我告诉过你
I told you,

608
00:31:27,980 --> 00:31:30,410
杰森·布洛德有权有势
Jason Brodeur is powerful.

609
00:31:36,170 --> 00:31:37,650
是时候打开牢笼了
Time to unlock the cages.

610
00:31:38,390 --> 00:31:39,570
我之前也有过这种情况
I've been here before.

611
00:31:39,870 --> 00:31:42,980
律师总会让你抱有一丝丝希望
These lawyers holding out these little nuggets of hope.

612
00:32:00,630 --> 00:32:02,610
封锁所有区域  隔离C区
Secure all quaters, seal block C.

613
00:32:02,640 --> 00:32:03,500
典狱长在C区
The warden's setting up

614
00:32:03,500 --> 00:32:05,190
设立了安全隔离
a secure perimeter in "C" Block.

615
00:32:05,380 --> 00:32:06,610
待在这里  兰斯小姐
Stay here, Ms. Lance.

616
00:32:07,020 --> 00:32:08,060
等等
Wait!

617
00:32:29,800 --> 00:32:31,070
我们走
Let's go.

618
00:33:18,630 --> 00:33:19,760
停下
Stop.

619
00:33:27,460 --> 00:33:28,600
不要动
Don't move!

620
00:33:46,260 --> 00:33:47,420
劳蕾尔
Laurel.

621
00:33:49,310 --> 00:33:50,350
亲爱的
Sweetie.

622
00:33:51,750 --> 00:33:52,690
你这是...
What are you--

623
00:33:53,760 --> 00:33:54,660
我没事
I'm all right.

624
00:33:54,660 --> 00:33:55,650
你确定
You sure?

625
00:33:55,900 --> 00:33:57,700
抱歉之前对你说的那些话
I'm sorry about what I said to you.

626
00:33:57,700 --> 00:33:58,320
是  好吧  你是对的
Yeah, well, you were right.

627
00:33:58,320 --> 00:34:00,740
安科夫刚刚承认谋杀了卡米尔·德克兰
Ankov just copped to Camille Declan's murder.

628
00:34:00,980 --> 00:34:02,070
我们抓错人了
We got the wrong guy.

629
00:34:03,210 --> 00:34:04,340
现在听我说  劳蕾尔
Now, listen to me, Laurel.

630
00:34:04,370 --> 00:34:05,780
关于他  我也是对的
I'm right, too, about him.

631
00:34:05,970 --> 00:34:07,080
他很危险
He's dangerous.

632
00:34:07,220 --> 00:34:08,320
他违背了法律
He's outside the law.

633
00:34:08,330 --> 00:34:09,470
我知道
I know.

634
00:34:12,220 --> 00:34:13,380
他是杀人犯
He's a killer.

635
00:34:15,980 --> 00:34:17,700
他原本会杀了那个男人
He would've kill that man

636
00:34:18,210 --> 00:34:19,720
我看着那双眼睛
I looked into his eyes,

637
00:34:20,580 --> 00:34:22,490
像是已经失去了人性
it's like he has no one was.

638
00:34:29,920 --> 00:34:32,940
求你了
Hey, please.

639
00:34:35,200 --> 00:34:36,420
我快饿死了
I'm starving.

640
00:34:38,410 --> 00:34:40,030
我从没杀过任何东西
I never killed anything before.

641
00:35:01,120 --> 00:35:02,290
对不起
I'm sorry.

642
00:35:18,010 --> 00:35:19,440
让我给你找个新家吧  亲爱的
Let's get you home, sweetie.

643
00:35:20,230 --> 00:35:22,120
他到底是怎么进到监狱里的
How'd he get into that prison, anyway, huh?

644
00:35:22,690 --> 00:35:25,610
一个穿着套装戴着兜帽的成年男子
A grown man in an outfit and a hood,

645
00:35:26,000 --> 00:35:27,880
进去那里不觉得有些显眼吗
that kind of stands out a little, doesn't it?

646
00:35:27,880 --> 00:35:29,860
事实上他这次并没穿成那个样子
He actually wasn't wearing the outfit this time.

647
00:35:30,280 --> 00:35:31,830
他穿着狱警的制服
He was in a prison guard uniform

648
00:35:32,580 --> 00:35:33,840
戴着面罩
and a ski mask.

649
00:35:36,800 --> 00:35:38,450
-怎么了  -没什么
- What?  - Nothing.

650
00:35:38,540 --> 00:35:39,740
只是有个想法
I just had an idea.

651
00:35:40,850 --> 00:35:42,090
上车吧
Get in the car.

652
00:36:37,900 --> 00:36:42,540
{\pos(190,169)}"金牌奎恩"号

653
00:36:50,120 --> 00:36:53,260
{\pos(190,169)}"金牌奎恩"号

654
00:36:57,050 --> 00:36:59,120
好了  这里有监控录像带
Ok, here's the security footage

655
00:36:59,120 --> 00:37:00,250
是交易大厅枪击案的
from the exchange building shooting,

656
00:37:00,250 --> 00:37:01,820
但我已经仔细看过了
but I've already scrubbed through all of it.

657
00:37:01,830 --> 00:37:03,330
是吗  那我们再看一遍吧
Yeah? Well, we're gonna do it again.

658
00:37:04,980 --> 00:37:05,830
听好了  当你监察
So, listen, when you went through

659
00:37:05,840 --> 00:37:07,480
监控录像带的时候  主要留意
the camera security tapes, you were looking for

660
00:37:07,480 --> 00:37:09,060
一个穿着绿色套服戴绿色兜帽的人
a guy in a green outfit and a green hood, right?

661
00:37:09,060 --> 00:37:10,330
你想让我看什么
What do you want me to look for,

662
00:37:10,340 --> 00:37:12,210
一个戴假发穿芭蕾短裙的男人吗
a man in a wig and a tutu?

663
00:37:12,740 --> 00:37:13,630
我想让你留意任何
I want you to look for anything

664
00:37:13,630 --> 00:37:15,260
不正常的画面  好吗  赶紧看吧
that's out of the ordinary, ok? Just look.

665
00:37:23,670 --> 00:37:24,340
等等  等下
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait. Wait.

666
00:37:24,340 --> 00:37:26,040
后退十秒  那是什么
Go back 10 seconds. What is that?

667
00:37:29,560 --> 00:37:30,800
打死我也想不到
I'll be damned.

668
00:37:33,980 --> 00:37:35,130
再放一遍
Play that again.

669
00:37:39,150 --> 00:37:40,210
谢谢你  劳蕾尔
Thank you, Laurel.

670
00:37:40,920 --> 00:37:42,000
别谢我
Don't thank me.

671
00:37:42,370 --> 00:37:45,880
要谢就谢布洛德的保镖安科夫背叛了他
Thank Brodeur's bodyguard Ankov for flipping him.

672
00:37:47,400 --> 00:37:49,080
我想你会非常想见某人
I think there's someone that wants to see you.

673
00:37:49,890 --> 00:37:50,910
伊泽
Lzzy.

674
00:38:07,020 --> 00:38:09,740
至少五个联邦  州  以及地方政府
At least 5 federal, state, and local agencies

675
00:38:09,740 --> 00:38:11,000
涉嫌从布洛德化学工厂谋取贿赂
are seeking millions of dollars

676
00:38:08,820 --> 00:38:10,590
杰森·布洛德被捕  彼得·德克兰无罪释放

677
00:38:11,400 --> 00:38:13,430
涉及罚金
in fines and environmental cleanup costs

678
00:38:13,540 --> 00:38:14,930
及环境清理费
from Brodeur chemical,

679
00:38:16,220 --> 00:38:17,560
根据最新消息
in light of new facts

680
00:38:17,680 --> 00:38:20,540
布洛德化学工厂的雇员卡米尔·德克兰
that Brodeur chemical employee Camille Declan

681
00:38:20,750 --> 00:38:23,540
已经揭露布洛德非法倾倒工业废物的事实
had discovered Brodeur was illegally disposing waste

682
00:38:24,300 --> 00:38:25,350
{\pos(195,82)}杰森·布洛德

683
00:38:23,980 --> 00:38:25,670
并且收集到证据
and had collected a file of evidence

684
00:38:25,670 --> 00:38:27,900
于2007年对她的雇主提出指控
against her employer

685
00:38:27,900 --> 00:38:28,690
正是在她死前
before her murder in 2007.

686
00:38:29,700 --> 00:38:32,480
彼得·德克兰  由于先前被指控杀妻
Peter Declan, who was convicted of killing his wife,

687
00:38:32,490 --> 00:38:35,470
已被无罪释放  而这个案子也即将展开调查
has been released, and the case has been reopened.

688
00:38:49,610 --> 00:38:50,630
生存

689
00:38:51,760 --> 00:38:52,880
是啊
Yeah.

690
00:38:53,660 --> 00:38:55,180
是鸟  我懂
Bird. I know.

691
00:38:55,490 --> 00:38:58,240
生存 不是 鸟 的意思
生存 NOT MEAN "BIRD."

692
00:38:58,910 --> 00:39:01,290
生存 是 活着
生存 MEAN "SURVIVE."

693
00:39:02,520 --> 00:39:03,790
你会说英语
You speak English.

694
00:39:04,750 --> 00:39:06,770
如果你想在这个地方活下去
You want survive this place,

695
00:39:07,900 --> 00:39:10,540
绝不是只会杀鸟这么简单
bird not last thing you kill.

696
00:39:15,620 --> 00:39:17,130
要把她忘了
And forget her.

697
00:39:18,130 --> 00:39:19,900
整天看着她
You look at that all day,

698
00:39:20,650 --> 00:39:23,400
是不会帮你在这里生存的
you not survive this place.

699
00:39:39,210 --> 00:39:40,480
你想见我
You wanted to see me?

700
00:39:42,480 --> 00:39:43,890
你看起来很紧张  莫伊拉
You look nervous, Moira.

701
00:39:44,520 --> 00:39:46,420
有理由吗
Hmm. Do I have a reason to be?

702
00:39:48,190 --> 00:39:49,180
我们是一根绳上的蚂蚱
We all do.

703
00:39:56,440 --> 00:39:58,490
现实社会的罗宾汉
A modern-day Robin hood.

704
00:39:59,550 --> 00:40:01,100
难道你是在担心你的财产
What, are you worried that your net worth

705
00:40:01,100 --> 00:40:02,510
会让你成为攻击目标吗
makes you a target?

706
00:40:04,880 --> 00:40:08,080
詹森·布罗德  亚当·亨特
Jason Brodeur, Adam Hunt,

707
00:40:08,730 --> 00:40:10,070
沃伦·帕特尔
Warren Patel.

708
00:40:10,690 --> 00:40:12,320
你没看出其中的联系吗  莫伊拉
Tell me you see a connection, Moira.

709
00:40:13,060 --> 00:40:14,510
他不是以富人为攻击目标
He's not targeting the rich.

710
00:40:14,510 --> 00:40:15,780
对  他不是
No, he's not.

711
00:40:16,540 --> 00:40:17,860
他在拿名单当靶子
He's targeting the list.

712
00:40:26,020 --> 00:40:27,630
你是来应聘保镖的吗
You here for the bodyguard position?

713
00:40:27,630 --> 00:40:30,130
因为新来的刚刚辞职
'cause the new guy just quit.

714
00:40:30,610 --> 00:40:31,790
不  我不是
No, I'm not.

715
00:40:33,320 --> 00:40:34,630
我是来应征其它职位的
I'm here about the other position.

716
00:40:38,110 --> 00:40:39,260
事先讲清楚
Just to be clear,

717
00:40:40,360 --> 00:40:42,250
我不是要来当你的同伙
I'm not signing on to be a sidekick.

718
00:40:42,820 --> 00:40:43,870
但  你是对的
But you're right.

719
00:40:44,660 --> 00:40:46,040
为这座城市而战迫在眉睫
Fighting for this city needs to be done,

720
00:40:46,040 --> 00:40:47,740
无论有我还是没我  你都会去做
and you're gonna do this with or without me.

721
00:40:48,280 --> 00:40:49,790
-是的  -但有了我
- Yeah.  - But with me,

722
00:40:50,080 --> 00:40:51,940
就会少些伤亡  包括你
There'll be fewer casualties, including you.

723
00:40:52,290 --> 00:40:54,690
狄格  我不是在找人保护我
Diggle, I'm not looking for anybody to save me.

724
00:40:55,700 --> 00:40:56,800
也许不是
Maybe not,

725
00:40:57,650 --> 00:40:59,580
但你需要统一战线的人
but you need someone just the same.

726
00:41:00,270 --> 00:41:01,840
你是在打一场仗  奎恩
You are fighting a war, Queen,

727
00:41:02,250 --> 00:41:04,880
除非你不知道自己在打什么样的仗
except you have no idea what war does to you,

728
00:41:05,130 --> 00:41:07,890
它是怎样一点点剥落你的灵魂
how it scrapes off little pieces of your soul.

729
00:41:10,060 --> 00:41:11,700
而你需要有人提醒你
And you need someone to remind you

730
00:41:12,970 --> 00:41:14,230
你是谁
of who you are,

731
00:41:14,440 --> 00:41:15,950
保持你的初衷
not this thing you're becoming.

732
00:41:23,300 --> 00:41:24,280
奥利弗·奎恩
Oliver Queen.

733
00:41:24,280 --> 00:41:25,250
发生了什么
What is this?

734
00:41:25,250 --> 00:41:26,480
你不能无缘无故闯进来
You can't just barge in here.

735
00:41:26,480 --> 00:41:28,620
是吗  我有警徽和配枪  这样就可以了吗
Yeah? Well, I got a badge and a gun that say different.

736
00:41:28,900 --> 00:41:30,280
到底发生什么了
Hey, what the hell's going on?!

737
00:41:30,280 --> 00:41:32,550
兰斯探长  奥利弗·奎恩你由于涉嫌
Detective Lance-- Oliver Queen, you're under arrest on suspicion

738
00:41:32,670 --> 00:41:34,680
妨碍法律公正及重大人身伤害罪而被捕
of obstruction of justice, aggravated assault...

739
00:41:34,680 --> 00:41:35,700
沃尔特  阻止他们
Walter, stop them!

740
00:41:35,700 --> 00:41:37,860
非法侵入民宅  用维护治安做借口
Trespassing, acting as a vigilante...

741
00:41:38,080 --> 00:41:39,610
你们疯了吗
are you out of your mind?!

742
00:41:39,610 --> 00:41:40,680
以及谋杀
And murder.

743
00:41:41,380 --> 00:41:42,990
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.

744
00:41:43,030 --> 00:41:44,270
投降吧你
Give up that right...

