1
00:02:18,000 --> 00:02:23,000
{\pos(70,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:02:18,000 --> 00:02:23,000
{\pos(70,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:02:18,000 --> 00:02:23,000
{\pos(60,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:02:18,000 --> 00:02:23,000
{\pos(86,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:02:18,000 --> 00:02:23,000
{\pos(100,254)}人人影视
YYeTs.com

6
00:02:18,000 --> 00:02:23,000
{\pos(101,267)}原创翻译  双语字幕

8
00:02:18,000 --> 00:02:23,000
{\pos(240,267)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

9
00:02:23,100 --> 00:02:28,000
{\pos(190,278)}翻译：小榴莲   小黎   鱼小姐   圈圈   狂舞之鹤  绒布熊

11
00:02:28,100 --> 00:02:33,000
{\pos(190,278)}翻译：vivi的夏天  Luna_3   初校：陈小圈   Liv   glorydai   苹果    

13
00:02:33,100 --> 00:02:38,000
{\pos(190,278)}时间轴：加森   仓鼠sama   后期：冰河   监制：苹果

15
00:02:54,660 --> 00:02:59,600
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)绿   箭

16
00:02:54,660 --> 00:02:59,600
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)第一季 第五集

17
00:00:00,800 --> 00:00:03,120
我的名字叫奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.

18
00:00:03,240 --> 00:00:05,460
五年里  我被困孤岛
For 5 years I was stranded on an island

19
00:00:05,460 --> 00:00:07,060
只有一个目标
with only one goal--

20
00:00:08,170 --> 00:00:09,340
生存
Survive.

21
00:00:09,650 --> 00:00:09,800
奥利弗·奎恩还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.

22
00:00:09,530 --> 00:00:11,030
{\pos(203,207)}最新新闻  失踪亿万富翁重现人间

23
00:00:11,310 --> 00:00:12,310
现在我要完成父亲的遗愿
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish...

24
00:00:11,830 --> 00:00:12,590
{\pos(213,226)}缺乏证据
地检澄清亚当·亨特之犯罪行为

25
00:00:12,620 --> 00:00:13,500
{\pos(208,278)}星城卫士
银行抢劫案警方出击

26
00:00:14,320 --> 00:00:16,320
用他留给我的名单
To use the list of names he left me

27
00:00:16,320 --> 00:00:19,350
扳倒那些荼毒城市的人
to bring down those who are poisoning city.

28
00:00:20,380 --> 00:00:23,100
要做这些  我只能伪装成另一个人
Do this, I must become someone else.

29
00:00:24,410 --> 00:00:28,080
成为另一个存在
I must become something else.

30
00:00:28,110 --> 00:00:29,570
《绿箭》前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...

31
00:00:29,570 --> 00:00:32,150
眼前的人不再是当年失踪的奥利弗了
The Oliver you lost might not be the one they found.

32
00:00:32,150 --> 00:00:33,450
当你被困在那座岛上
When you were stuck on that island

33
00:00:33,450 --> 00:00:35,160
筹划着拯救整个城市的伟业
plotting your grand plan to save the city,

34
00:00:35,160 --> 00:00:37,020
我不认为你停下来想过
I don't think you stopped to consider the effect

35
00:00:37,020 --> 00:00:38,370
这件事对你周围的人会有什么样的影响
it would have on the people in your life.

36
00:00:38,640 --> 00:00:39,650
你说错了
You're wrong.

37
00:00:39,650 --> 00:00:41,820
不能告诉我家人事实
Not being able to tell my family the truth,

38
00:00:41,820 --> 00:00:43,980
对我的伤害要比任何人都深
It doesn't hurt anyone worse than it hurts me.

39
00:00:43,980 --> 00:00:46,040
我给了你承诺  却没有履行
I made you a promise. I couldn't keep it.

40
00:00:46,040 --> 00:00:49,810
在被赐予我的孩子重回身边的奇迹以后
After being granted the miracle of having my child returned to me,

41
00:00:49,810 --> 00:00:52,220
你却几乎完全不想和我待在一起
that you seem to have little or no interest in being with me

42
00:00:52,220 --> 00:00:53,420
也不想告诉我真相
or telling me the truth.

43
00:00:53,430 --> 00:00:54,980
你得对我敞开心扉  奥利
You got to let me in, Ollie.

44
00:00:54,980 --> 00:00:57,510
你总得对谁敞开心扉吧
You gotta let someone in.

45
00:01:18,500 --> 00:01:19,390
喂
Hello.

46
00:01:19,390 --> 00:01:21,060
老妈说我应该提醒你一下
Hi, mom said I'm supposed to remind you

47
00:01:21,060 --> 00:01:22,930
别忘了回家吃午饭
to pick up for lunch.

48
00:01:23,050 --> 00:01:24,640
我今天应该回家吃午饭吗
Was I supposed to have lunch with her today?

49
00:01:24,640 --> 00:01:27,000
她说她给你留了五条简讯
She said she left you like 5 messages.

50
00:01:27,200 --> 00:01:29,900
只不过是咬咬牙  跟她一起吃个科布沙拉
Just bite the bullet and have a cobb salad with the woman.

51
00:01:29,900 --> 00:01:31,610
西娅  有时真记不清
You know, Thea, sometimes it's difficult to remember

52
00:01:31,610 --> 00:01:33,290
你们谁才是我妈
which one of you is my mother.

53
00:01:33,120 --> 00:01:35,550
{\pos(174,154)}奎恩联合企业

54
00:01:34,300 --> 00:01:36,100
奎恩夫人  我只求一个机会
Mrs. Queen, all I'm asking for

55
00:01:36,100 --> 00:01:38,740
我们坐下来  谈一谈我们的建议
is a chance to sit down and discuss our proposal. Hmm?

56
00:01:38,740 --> 00:01:41,420
如果仅此而已  那我可以节省大家的时间
If that's all it is, then I can save us both the time.

57
00:01:41,420 --> 00:01:42,400
我拒绝
It's rejected.

58
00:01:42,400 --> 00:01:43,620
明白了  可以问为什么吗
I see. May I ask why?

59
00:01:43,620 --> 00:01:46,160
我真得回答你吗  科帕尼先生
Do I really need to answer that, Mr. Copani?

60
00:01:47,440 --> 00:01:48,690
现在  失陪了
Now, if you'll excuse me,

61
00:01:48,690 --> 00:01:50,960
我要跟我儿子一起吃午饭
I'm meeting my son for lunch.

62
00:02:03,830 --> 00:02:05,050
趴下
Get down!

63
00:02:11,360 --> 00:02:12,600
妈  你还好吗
Mom? Are you ok?

64
00:02:12,600 --> 00:02:13,880
-我没事  -伤到了没
- I'm all right. - Are you hurt?

65
00:02:13,890 --> 00:02:15,640
-不  我...我... -确定吗
- No, I'm...I'm... - Are you sure?

66
00:02:15,640 --> 00:02:16,570
-我没事  -你确定你没事吗
- I'm fine. - You're sure you're fine?

67
00:02:16,570 --> 00:02:17,670
报警
Call 9-1-1!

68
00:03:01,700 --> 00:03:03,460
{\pos(92,232)}星城医院
急诊入口

69
00:03:08,850 --> 00:03:09,760
你好
Hi.

70
00:03:10,580 --> 00:03:11,520
你还好吗
Are you ok?

71
00:03:11,920 --> 00:03:12,860
我没事
I'm fine.

72
00:03:13,580 --> 00:03:14,690
我没事
I'm fine.

73
00:03:16,340 --> 00:03:17,780
有没有联系到沃尔特
Did you reach Walter?

74
00:03:18,070 --> 00:03:19,580
没  不好意思
No. I'm sorry.

75
00:03:19,590 --> 00:03:21,900
如我跟你母亲和妹妹说的
As I was telling your mother and sister,

76
00:03:21,910 --> 00:03:23,190
CT显示
the cat-scan showed

77
00:03:23,190 --> 00:03:24,750
是二级脑震荡
a grade two concussion.

78
00:03:24,750 --> 00:03:26,710
她可以回家  只要有人陪着就行
She can go home so long as someone stays with her

79
00:03:26,720 --> 00:03:28,850
只是确保没有什么后遗症
just to make sure there are no after effects.

80
00:03:28,890 --> 00:03:29,850
谢谢
Thank you.

81
00:03:32,070 --> 00:03:33,370
对不起  我不该把你丢下
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have left you.

82
00:03:33,370 --> 00:03:34,750
我以为你没事
I thought you were fine.

83
00:03:34,750 --> 00:03:36,640
那你以为你当时在做什么
What did you think you were doing anyway?

84
00:03:37,000 --> 00:03:39,920
我想去看那个人的车牌
Yeah, I wanted to get the license plate of the guy

85
00:03:39,920 --> 00:03:40,670
那个对你开枪的人
who took a shot at you.

86
00:03:40,670 --> 00:03:43,550
-真愚蠢  -是
- Well, that was foolish. - Yeah.

87
00:03:51,870 --> 00:03:53,610
那你看到牌照了吗
So did you get the license plate?

88
00:03:53,820 --> 00:03:55,450
没有  给他溜走了
No. He got away.

89
00:03:55,520 --> 00:03:58,340
你想当英雄还是省省吧
Maybe you should spend a little less time trying to be a hero.

90
00:03:58,800 --> 00:04:00,750
明显不擅长
You're obviously not very good at it.

91
00:04:01,050 --> 00:04:01,750
这说法很可爱
That's cute.

92
00:04:01,750 --> 00:04:03,060
我可不是这个意思
I wasn't trying to be.

93
00:04:03,100 --> 00:04:06,720
你把受伤的她一个人留在街上
You left her on the street, alone and hurt.

94
00:04:06,720 --> 00:04:07,900
留在街上
In the street.

95
00:04:09,550 --> 00:04:11,310
真的是去追车牌吗
To get a license plate?

96
00:04:16,300 --> 00:04:17,560
你不信我吗
You don't believe me?

97
00:04:18,190 --> 00:04:21,520
我爱你  妈也爱你
I love you. Mom loves you.

98
00:04:22,920 --> 00:04:25,740
但你不对我们开诚布公就难了
But it's getting hard when you won't be truthful with us.

99
00:04:35,590 --> 00:04:36,640
侦探们
Detectives.

100
00:04:37,190 --> 00:04:38,670
有没有开枪者的线索
Do you have any leads on the shooter?

101
00:04:38,670 --> 00:04:40,650
还没有  你看清楚他了吗
Not yet. Did you get a good look at him?

102
00:04:40,660 --> 00:04:42,210
没  他戴了头盔
No. He was wearing a helmet.

103
00:04:42,220 --> 00:04:44,280
别担心  我们会找到他的
Don't worry. We'll find him.

104
00:04:44,510 --> 00:04:45,760
我的安全主管正赶过来
My head of security is on his way.

105
00:04:45,760 --> 00:04:47,490
我希望我母亲病房外有人站岗
I want to make sure there are men outside my mother's door.

106
00:04:47,490 --> 00:04:49,100
她需要保护
She needs to be protected.

107
00:04:49,280 --> 00:04:50,580
其实你们全家
Well, you know your family's

108
00:04:50,580 --> 00:04:52,250
都在我的优先保护名单里
at the tippy-toppy of the my list of priorities,

109
00:04:52,250 --> 00:04:54,010
但牵涉到跟她在一起的人
but the guy that she was with was connected,

110
00:04:54,010 --> 00:04:56,170
和黑帮有关
mobbed up to the eyeballs connected.

111
00:04:56,260 --> 00:04:57,860
她不是目标
She wasn't the target.

112
00:05:01,550 --> 00:05:02,820
不用谢了
And you're welcome.

113
00:05:13,140 --> 00:05:14,270
其实我比这个人
Technically I did get here

114
00:05:14,270 --> 00:05:16,000
早到了差不多十秒
like 10 seconds before this guy.

115
00:05:19,970 --> 00:05:21,040
零钱不用找了
Keep the change.

116
00:05:23,200 --> 00:05:25,770
汤米  你这么晚来有何要事
So, Tommy, what brings you by so late?

117
00:05:25,830 --> 00:05:27,750
我猜得很对
Well, I assumed, rightly,

118
00:05:27,750 --> 00:05:29,150
你今晚会在家工作
that you would be at home working tonight,

119
00:05:29,150 --> 00:05:31,260
而且我猜你可能饿了
and I also assumed that you might be hungry.

120
00:05:31,260 --> 00:05:32,760
也猜对了
Also rightly.

121
00:05:33,850 --> 00:05:34,900
这可不一定
I don't know.

122
00:05:35,210 --> 00:05:38,510
这是马里奥店的蘑菇橄榄披萨
This is a mushroom and olive pizza from Mario's.

123
00:05:38,530 --> 00:05:40,380
这款披萨很美味
That is damn good pie.

124
00:05:41,730 --> 00:05:43,660
好吧  你带了什么
All right, what do you have to offer?

125
00:05:43,660 --> 00:05:46,030
托罗店的脆米香辣金枪鱼寿司
Spicy tuna on crispy rice from Toro's.

126
00:05:46,080 --> 00:05:49,190
真可恨  梅林
Ohh. Damn you, Merlyn.

127
00:05:49,760 --> 00:05:51,710
希望你只是来送寿司的
I hope sushi was all you had in mind.

128
00:05:51,760 --> 00:05:55,500
其实  我想问你点事情
Uh, actually, there was something that I wanted to ask you.

129
00:05:55,830 --> 00:05:56,880
问什么
And what's that?

130
00:05:57,240 --> 00:05:58,390
你愿意和我出去吃饭吗
Will you go out with me?

131
00:05:59,180 --> 00:06:01,240
像  约会那种
Like on a date.

132
00:06:01,240 --> 00:06:03,370
你给我带寿司  却又请我出去吃
You brought me dinner to ask me to dinner?

133
00:06:03,370 --> 00:06:07,320
我还帮你举办了大型慈善活动
Well, I also did throw you a really big charity gala.

134
00:06:07,320 --> 00:06:08,690
我以为你是为了
See, I thought you threw it

135
00:06:08,690 --> 00:06:10,560
能够获益的那几百人而举办的
for the hundreds of people it would benefit.

136
00:06:10,560 --> 00:06:12,420
没错  为了那几百人
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Hundreds of people.

137
00:06:13,230 --> 00:06:14,270
再加上你
Plus one more.

138
00:06:14,280 --> 00:06:17,210
-汤米  -劳蕾尔  我明白了
- Tommy. - Laurel, I get it.

139
00:06:17,280 --> 00:06:19,160
咱们发展的顺序完全错了
Ok, this is all happening for us in the wrong order.

140
00:06:19,160 --> 00:06:22,190
开始我们做了多年好友
You know, first we're friends for many years,

141
00:06:22,190 --> 00:06:25,690
然后短暂地做了炮友
and then briefly we are friends with benefits,

142
00:06:25,690 --> 00:06:27,990
异常愉悦的经历
extremely excellent benefits.

143
00:06:28,100 --> 00:06:30,910
现在我只希望我们能两个人
And now I am just hoping that we can be two people

144
00:06:30,910 --> 00:06:33,640
同时坐在同家餐厅的
sitting at the same restaurant at the same table

145
00:06:33,640 --> 00:06:35,000
一张桌子前
at the same time.

146
00:06:35,540 --> 00:06:36,320
我这么说的时候
See, when I say it like that,

147
00:06:36,330 --> 00:06:38,330
听起来不可怕  对吗
it doesn't sound so scary, does it?

148
00:06:46,150 --> 00:06:47,880
奥利弗  你母亲差点被杀
Oliver, your mom was nearly killed.

149
00:06:47,890 --> 00:06:49,740
我觉得你可以休息一天别训练了
I think you can take a day off from training.

150
00:06:50,910 --> 00:06:52,430
我母亲不是目标
My mother wasn't the target.

151
00:06:53,180 --> 00:06:54,830
这个人才是  保罗·科帕尼
This man was. Paul Copani.

152
00:06:54,830 --> 00:06:57,070
被枪击时  他正要和她达成一项交易
He was trying to close a deal with her when they were shot at.

153
00:06:58,080 --> 00:07:00,260
科帕尼为波提纳尔建筑
Copani works for Bertinelli Construction

154
00:07:00,490 --> 00:07:01,940
和弗兰克·波提纳尔工作
and Frank Bertinelli.

155
00:07:02,330 --> 00:07:03,540
黑手党老大
The mob boss?

156
00:07:03,640 --> 00:07:04,890
我做了些调查
I did some digging.

157
00:07:05,610 --> 00:07:06,630
科帕尼不是波提纳尔组织里
Copani isn't the first member

158
00:07:06,630 --> 00:07:08,350
第一个遭到袭击的成员
of Bertinelli's crew who's been hit.

159
00:07:08,350 --> 00:07:09,590
你做了些调查
You did some digging?

160
00:07:09,960 --> 00:07:11,750
波提纳尔树敌众多
Bertinelli has a lot of enemies.

161
00:07:12,170 --> 00:07:15,070
找出针对他组织的幕后黑手的最好方法
The best way to figure out who's trying to target his organization

162
00:07:15,490 --> 00:07:16,890
就是打入组织内部
is to get inside of it.

163
00:07:17,340 --> 00:07:19,020
让我来理理  奥利弗
So let me get this right, Oliver.

164
00:07:19,020 --> 00:07:21,180
你母亲被枪击  差点被杀
Your mother's shot at, nearly killed,

165
00:07:21,260 --> 00:07:22,800
而你感性的处理方法
and the way you process this emotionally

166
00:07:22,800 --> 00:07:25,770
是去黑手党做卧底
is by going undercover with the mob.

167
00:07:25,780 --> 00:07:27,610
我没想感性地处理任何事
I'm not trying to process anything emotionally.

168
00:07:27,610 --> 00:07:30,200
也许那就是你的问题  老兄
Yeah, well, maybe that's your problem, man.

169
00:07:30,650 --> 00:07:33,440
你有没有想过就陪在你家人身边
You ever thought about just being there for your family?

170
00:07:35,350 --> 00:07:36,970
我今天尝试了去陪西娅
I tried that today with Thea.

171
00:07:37,750 --> 00:07:39,150
她说我对她有所隐瞒
She told me I wasn't being honest with her,

172
00:07:39,150 --> 00:07:40,380
她是对的
and she's right.

173
00:07:41,000 --> 00:07:42,470
我没法跟她解释清楚
I can't very well explain to her

174
00:07:42,470 --> 00:07:45,570
我把母亲一人留在街上  任其受伤流血
that I left our mother alone and bleeding on the pavement

175
00:07:45,570 --> 00:07:48,850
是因为我能急速奔跑  几乎抓住袭击者
because I'm fast enough to almost run down the attacker.

176
00:07:52,330 --> 00:07:56,100
但是我能做的  是保护我的家人
But what I can do is protect my family.

177
00:07:57,690 --> 00:08:01,590
狄格尔  一旦我找出这人是谁
And, Diggle, when I found out who this guy is,

178
00:08:03,140 --> 00:08:04,330
他死定了
he's a dead man.

179
00:08:48,420 --> 00:08:49,410
闪电妞
Speedy.

180
00:08:49,420 --> 00:08:50,350
你要去哪
Where you going?

181
00:08:50,560 --> 00:08:52,250
去夜店玩  要是你待在家里
Clubbing, which is difficult to do

182
00:08:52,250 --> 00:08:54,320
而非去真正的夜店就很难办到了
when you're in a house and not in an actual club.

183
00:08:54,670 --> 00:08:56,770
我今晚必须出去
I have to go out tonight.

184
00:08:57,220 --> 00:08:58,770
我以为你会照看妈妈
I thought you'd be watching mom.

185
00:08:58,780 --> 00:09:00,720
我已经陪了她一整天
I spent the whole day with her.

186
00:09:00,780 --> 00:09:02,550
我以为晚上该轮到你了
I thought you were taking the night shift.

187
00:09:02,550 --> 00:09:05,280
对不起  但这件事  很重要
I'm sorry, but this thing, it's important.

188
00:09:05,930 --> 00:09:09,010
有时候  奥利  我真的不懂你
You know, sometimes, Ollie, I just don't get you.

189
00:09:09,460 --> 00:09:11,710
我说有时  是指一直以来
And by sometimes, I mean ever.

190
00:09:11,710 --> 00:09:14,360
其实今天不只你这么说我
You're actually not the first person to say that to me today.

191
00:09:14,360 --> 00:09:15,940
我怎么一点都不惊讶呢
Why am I not surprised?

192
00:09:17,380 --> 00:09:18,840
裙子真漂亮  你要去哪
Oh, nice dress. Where you heading?

193
00:09:18,840 --> 00:09:21,480
显然是回楼上去
Upstairs. Apparently.

194
00:09:22,550 --> 00:09:23,560
这故事可长了
Long story.

195
00:09:24,120 --> 00:09:25,970
我听说你母亲的事了  她还好吗
Hey, I heard about your mom. Is she all right?

196
00:09:25,970 --> 00:09:28,710
她在楼上休息  受了不少惊吓
She's resting upstairs. More shaken up than anything.

197
00:09:28,790 --> 00:09:31,040
我有点生意上的事得去处理了
I got to run to this business thing,

198
00:09:31,040 --> 00:09:32,810
不过很感谢你过来一趟
But I do appreciate you stopping by.

199
00:09:32,810 --> 00:09:35,460
不客气  只要你母亲没事就好
It's no problem. Just so long as your mom's all right.

200
00:09:35,460 --> 00:09:36,380
是啊
Yeah.

201
00:09:37,060 --> 00:09:38,700
对了  还有一件事
Hey, one more thing.

202
00:09:40,460 --> 00:09:41,540
主要是我不希望你
Mainly because I don't want you

203
00:09:41,540 --> 00:09:43,440
从别人口中得知此事
to find this out from someone else,

204
00:09:43,870 --> 00:09:46,760
尤其是从劳蕾尔那儿知道
that someone else especially being Laurel.

205
00:09:48,510 --> 00:09:52,210
我们准备共进晚餐  约会那种
we're going to dinner. As in a date.

206
00:09:53,020 --> 00:09:55,120
那...真是不错
That's...that's good.

207
00:09:55,330 --> 00:09:57,340
劳蕾尔该有个好伴侣
Laurel deserves someone special,

208
00:09:57,340 --> 00:09:58,410
你也是
and so do you.

209
00:09:58,900 --> 00:09:59,890
谢谢  兄弟
Thanks, man.

210
00:10:00,020 --> 00:10:00,910
我得走了
I gotta run to this thing.

211
00:10:00,910 --> 00:10:02,710
好的  没问题  以后再聊
All right. Absolutely. I'll catch you later.

212
00:10:02,710 --> 00:10:04,220
对了  汤米
Oh, and, Tommy,

213
00:10:04,920 --> 00:10:06,680
如果你敢伤害她  我就拧断你脖子
if you hurt her, I'll snap your neck.

214
00:10:07,760 --> 00:10:08,940
开玩笑呢
I'm just kidding.

215
00:10:20,400 --> 00:10:21,680
波提纳尔先生
Mr. Bertinelli.

216
00:10:22,700 --> 00:10:23,500
叫我弗兰克就行
Call me Frank.

217
00:10:23,500 --> 00:10:25,220
那么就叫我奥利弗吧
Ahh. Call me Oliver.

218
00:10:27,020 --> 00:10:29,130
感谢你愿意到我家来见我
Thank you for agreeing to meet me at my home.

219
00:10:29,130 --> 00:10:30,860
我父亲常说客厅才是
My father used to say that living rooms

220
00:10:30,860 --> 00:10:32,350
最好的会议室
make the best conference rooms.

221
00:10:32,350 --> 00:10:33,830
这句话我得记牢了
Oh, I'm gonna steal that.

222
00:10:34,840 --> 00:10:36,690
尼克·赛瓦缇  我的助手
Nick Salvati, my associate.

223
00:10:36,690 --> 00:10:37,610
你好
How do you do?

224
00:10:38,250 --> 00:10:39,330
我们喝点东西吧
Let's have a drink.

225
00:10:50,470 --> 00:10:52,090
你想看什么节目
So what are you in the mood for?

226
00:10:52,450 --> 00:10:55,810
看主妇烹饪真人秀
We could watch reality housewife cooking show

227
00:10:56,490 --> 00:10:58,360
还是《医生警探》呢
or Cop Docs.

228
00:10:58,750 --> 00:11:01,120
讲医生们不互相乱搞的时候
It's where doctors run around fighting crime

229
00:11:01,120 --> 00:11:03,310
四处打击犯罪
when they're not all sleeping with each other.

230
00:11:04,430 --> 00:11:06,250
随便你  亲爱的
Whatever you want, sweetheart.

231
00:11:06,250 --> 00:11:08,250
是你放弃了晚上的外出留下来陪我
You're the one who's given up your evening out.

232
00:11:08,250 --> 00:11:10,410
不然似乎也没有其他人
Oh, it's not like there's anybody else

233
00:11:10,420 --> 00:11:12,050
可以陪你了
who could be staying with you.

234
00:11:12,350 --> 00:11:14,270
等等  还真有一位
Oh, wait, yes, there is.

235
00:11:14,630 --> 00:11:16,430
别对你哥哥太严厉了
Don't be too harsh on your brother.

236
00:11:17,900 --> 00:11:18,950
为什么
Why not?

237
00:11:19,490 --> 00:11:22,010
你难道不对他的谎话心生厌烦吗
I mean, aren't you getting sick of his lies?

238
00:11:24,040 --> 00:11:25,900
西娅  每个人都有秘密
Thea, everyone has secrets.

239
00:11:27,360 --> 00:11:31,720
大家都有不想告人的事情
We all have things that we want to keep to ourselves.

240
00:11:33,900 --> 00:11:35,860
有时候我真不理解他
I just don't get him sometimes.

241
00:11:37,870 --> 00:11:38,930
我明白
I know.

242
00:11:41,000 --> 00:11:42,160
我明白
I know.

243
00:11:46,650 --> 00:11:49,790
在医院的时候  我又见到兰博医生
You know, being in that hospital and seeing Dr. Lamb again,

244
00:11:50,280 --> 00:11:53,160
不禁想起奥利弗回家的那天
it made me remember the day that Oliver came home.

245
00:11:56,400 --> 00:11:58,000
兰博医生当时跟我说
It was Dr. Lamb that told me

246
00:11:58,010 --> 00:11:59,500
眼前的他可能
that the Oliver we'd lost

247
00:11:59,500 --> 00:12:02,090
不再是当年失踪的奥利弗了
might not be the Oliver that they'd found.

248
00:12:02,190 --> 00:12:04,470
有时候很容易就忘了
I think it's easy to forget,

249
00:12:04,480 --> 00:12:07,700
他有五年被隔离在文明世界外
but he lived apart from civilization for 5 years.

250
00:12:09,940 --> 00:12:12,710
那又如何  这样就能为所欲为了吗
So what, he gets like a free pass?

251
00:12:12,720 --> 00:12:14,560
不不不  不是这样
No. No, no, no, not at all.

252
00:12:14,560 --> 00:12:15,850
我
I...

253
00:12:16,770 --> 00:12:20,770
我只是认为不该再用过去的眼光看他
I just think we need to stop judging him for the Oliver he was

254
00:12:20,770 --> 00:12:24,030
应该开始接受现在的这个奥利弗
and start accepting him for the Oliver that he is.

255
00:12:26,940 --> 00:12:29,790
奥利弗  实不相瞒
So, Oliver, I'll be honest with you.

256
00:12:30,660 --> 00:12:32,260
我很惊讶你会联系我
I was surprised to hear from you.

257
00:12:32,320 --> 00:12:34,190
我看新闻还以为
It was my impression from the local news

258
00:12:34,190 --> 00:12:35,430
你不打算插手
that you weren't going to be involved

259
00:12:35,430 --> 00:12:36,930
家族事业呢
with your family's business.

260
00:12:36,980 --> 00:12:38,440
显然我离开的这五年里
Well, apparently there were a few catch phrases

261
00:12:38,440 --> 00:12:40,300
错过不少流行语
that I missed while I was away for 5 years.

262
00:12:40,300 --> 00:12:42,400
其中之一就是"烂流媒体"
One of them being "lamestream media".

263
00:12:43,570 --> 00:12:44,810
但媒体从来搞不清真相
The press never gets anything right.

264
00:12:44,810 --> 00:12:46,830
这点我略知一二
Oh, I know a thing or two about that.

265
00:12:48,490 --> 00:12:50,750
奥利弗  恕我直言
So, Oliver, I'll be blunt.

266
00:12:50,970 --> 00:12:51,840
我想得到奎恩联合企业
I want the contract

267
00:12:51,840 --> 00:12:55,010
新的应用科学部的建筑合约
to build Queen Consolidated's new applied sciences division.

268
00:12:55,040 --> 00:12:56,680
我也想把项目给你
And I am inclined to give it to you.

269
00:12:56,680 --> 00:12:58,840
你母亲似乎不这么想
Your mother wasn't quite so enthusiastic.

270
00:12:59,930 --> 00:13:01,200
对了  她现在情况还好吗
How is she, by the way?

271
00:13:01,200 --> 00:13:03,130
她正在家休养  谢谢
She's recuperating at home. Thank you.

272
00:13:03,750 --> 00:13:05,300
发生这种事实在太可怕了
What a terrible thing that happened.

273
00:13:05,300 --> 00:13:07,320
弗兰克  我对保罗·科帕尼的事
And, Frank, I was very sorry to hear

274
00:13:07,320 --> 00:13:09,580
深表遗憾
about what happened to Paul Copani.

275
00:13:10,250 --> 00:13:11,740
保罗是我的好朋友
Paul was a good friend.

276
00:13:11,980 --> 00:13:13,300
他人很好
He was a good man.

277
00:13:15,120 --> 00:13:17,260
这座城暴力四伏
Yeah. The violence in this city.

278
00:13:17,370 --> 00:13:19,290
有时候我也奇怪为何还留在这里
You know, sometimes I wonder why I stay.

279
00:13:19,360 --> 00:13:20,820
我也有同感
I've had the same thought.

280
00:13:22,150 --> 00:13:23,490
那你为什么要回来呢
So why did you come back?

281
00:13:24,600 --> 00:13:25,540
离开那座岛之后
After that island,

282
00:13:25,540 --> 00:13:27,120
你在世界任何地方落脚都不成问题
you could have settled anywhere in the world.

283
00:13:27,200 --> 00:13:29,210
因为星城是我的家
Because Starling City is my home.

284
00:13:34,120 --> 00:13:35,530
无论你选择或途经哪条路
No matter which way you go or turn,

285
00:13:35,530 --> 00:13:37,160
最后总是会回家的
you always end up at home.

286
00:13:39,120 --> 00:13:41,640
奥利弗  这是我女儿海伦娜
Oliver, this is my daughter Helena.

287
00:13:42,160 --> 00:13:43,160
你好
Hello.

288
00:13:43,760 --> 00:13:44,870
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.

289
00:13:45,440 --> 00:13:46,300
我要出去了
I'm heading out.

290
00:13:46,300 --> 00:13:47,430
好
All right.

291
00:13:47,510 --> 00:13:49,030
带上个保镖
Take one of the guys with you.

292
00:13:49,230 --> 00:13:51,050
我能自己照顾自己
I can take care of myself.

293
00:13:52,240 --> 00:13:53,680
你必须带  亲爱的
I wasn't asking, sweetie.

294
00:13:54,380 --> 00:13:56,980
弗兰克  你要求召开的会议
Frank, that meeting you requested.

295
00:13:57,420 --> 00:13:58,580
可以召开了
They can do it.

296
00:13:59,390 --> 00:14:00,340
马上
Now.

297
00:14:03,140 --> 00:14:04,610
我可以下次再来
I can come back another time.

298
00:14:04,610 --> 00:14:07,340
不  不用  能...
No, no, no. Just, uh.

299
00:14:09,100 --> 00:14:11,490
能稍等一下吗
Just excuse us for a moment, would you?

300
00:14:11,490 --> 00:14:12,520
谢谢
Thank you.

301
00:14:15,730 --> 00:14:17,090
奥利弗·奎恩
Oliver Queen.

302
00:14:17,230 --> 00:14:19,070
富人中的林赛·罗韩 (堕落明星)
The rich man's Lindsay Lohan.

303
00:14:20,940 --> 00:14:22,130
你...
Look, um...

304
00:14:24,550 --> 00:14:26,160
我得去参加另一个会议
I've got to go to this other meeting,

305
00:14:26,170 --> 00:14:27,900
但是我需要有人带他去进餐
but I need someone to take him to dinner.

306
00:14:27,900 --> 00:14:29,840
所以你就利用自己的女儿
So you pimp out your daughter.

307
00:14:29,840 --> 00:14:33,010
不  我是请求她帮我拿下一笔生意
No. I ask her to help me close a business deal.

308
00:14:33,280 --> 00:14:35,850
提醒你我们的家族事业正在走向衰亡
A reminder that the family business is dying

309
00:14:35,850 --> 00:14:37,480
我们需要签下这份合同
and that we need this contract,

310
00:14:37,480 --> 00:14:39,320
而奥利弗·奎恩能让我们如愿以偿
and Oliver Queen can give it to us.

311
00:14:39,330 --> 00:14:40,680
拜托了  亲爱的
Please, sweet pea.

312
00:14:40,680 --> 00:14:41,690
为了我们
For us.

313
00:14:42,170 --> 00:14:43,760
为了我  好吗
For me. Hmm?

314
00:14:44,970 --> 00:14:46,100
这才是我的乖女儿
That's my girl.

315
00:14:46,900 --> 00:14:50,420
奥利弗  很抱歉  我有事要处理
Oliver, I'm so sorry. Something has come up.

316
00:14:50,450 --> 00:14:52,810
但是海伦娜会很乐意带你去进餐
But Helena would love to take you to dinner

317
00:14:52,810 --> 00:14:54,300
并进一步商讨合同事宜
and discuss the deal further.

318
00:14:54,510 --> 00:14:57,380
我更愿意和你本人亲自商讨
Oh. I was hoping to speak with you.

319
00:14:57,380 --> 00:15:00,410
就跟你代表你的家族一样
Well, as you speak for your family,

320
00:15:00,410 --> 00:15:02,200
我女儿代表我们家族
my daughter also speaks for ours.

321
00:15:02,770 --> 00:15:06,000
真的...真的没这个必要
It's...it's really not necessary.

322
00:15:07,740 --> 00:15:09,260
这是我的荣幸
It would be my pleasure.

323
00:15:09,260 --> 00:15:10,260
我也是
Sure.

324
00:15:11,770 --> 00:15:13,190
期待我们的合作
I look forward to working together.

325
00:15:34,450 --> 00:15:35,570
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.

326
00:15:35,740 --> 00:15:37,210
为了朋友应该的
Anything for a friend.

327
00:15:38,160 --> 00:15:43,220
我们不管你的债
&%#2~*

328
00:15:44,370 --> 00:15:46,910
不是我们袭击的你的人
We're not responsible for the attacks on your people.

329
00:15:46,910 --> 00:15:49,010
对我生意的袭击
These attacks on my business

330
00:15:49,240 --> 00:15:51,460
是我们家族的血仇
are my family's life blood.

331
00:15:52,320 --> 00:15:53,670
他们最好现在收手
They stop now,

332
00:15:54,090 --> 00:15:55,400
否则我会找你算账的
or I'm coming for you.

333
00:16:03,700 --> 00:16:07,070
黑社会激怒你想得到什么
What does the triad have to gain by provoking you now?

334
00:16:07,370 --> 00:16:10,700
要是按常理出牌就不会有人创立黑社会了
Well, no one ever credited the triad with rational thinking.

335
00:16:13,560 --> 00:16:15,080
如果不是他们  那会是谁
If not them, then who?

336
00:16:16,090 --> 00:16:18,250
不管是谁  要是我找到幕后主使
Whoever it is, when I find out who's behind this,

337
00:16:18,250 --> 00:16:19,740
我一定让他血债血偿
there will be blood.

338
00:16:19,920 --> 00:16:21,810
听上去好像波提纳尔已经饥不择食
Sounds like Bertinelli's ready to put the screws

339
00:16:21,810 --> 00:16:23,790
谁能保护他他就投奔谁
to everyone who pays him protection money.

340
00:16:23,790 --> 00:16:26,630
他手底下已经有三个最会赚钱的被谋杀了
Yeah, well, 3 of his best earners have been murdered.

341
00:16:26,700 --> 00:16:28,560
他得找地方把损失弥补回来
He's gotta make up the cash somewhere.

342
00:16:28,830 --> 00:16:31,080
这个杀他家人的人
Whoever is pruning the family tree

343
00:16:31,080 --> 00:16:33,160
目的就是让波提纳尔痛苦
is looking to make Bertinelli suffer.

344
00:16:33,290 --> 00:16:35,160
所以你认为凶手是某个家庭成员
So you do think it's one of the other families.

345
00:16:35,170 --> 00:16:36,100
不是
No.

346
00:16:36,470 --> 00:16:37,450
那是谁
Then who?

347
00:16:37,710 --> 00:16:39,060
根据尸检报告
Well, according to the coroner's reports,

348
00:16:39,070 --> 00:16:40,500
受害人都不是一枪毙命
none of the vics took a clean shot.

349
00:16:40,500 --> 00:16:41,880
有一半的子弹没打中
Half the bullets missed.

350
00:16:41,970 --> 00:16:43,520
说明凶手很不专业
Our killer's not a pro.

351
00:16:43,520 --> 00:16:45,480
即使不专业  他也会继续杀人
That's not stopping him from pulling that trigger.

352
00:16:45,490 --> 00:16:46,840
这就看我们的了
That's up to us.

353
00:16:49,230 --> 00:16:51,900
否则事件会演变成全面的黑社会斗争
Or this is gonna blow up into an all-out mob war.

354
00:17:02,610 --> 00:17:04,350
海伦娜  你就和天使一样
You are an angel, Helena.

355
00:17:04,730 --> 00:17:06,050
太美了
So beautiful.

356
00:17:07,640 --> 00:17:10,830
今晚我们一定会好好招待你们的
Well, we are gonna take good care of both of you tonight.

357
00:17:11,290 --> 00:17:13,760
你会代我们向你父亲问好吧
You'll tell your father hello from us?

358
00:17:13,760 --> 00:17:15,370
当然了  拉索先生
Of course, Mr. Russo.

359
00:17:15,960 --> 00:17:16,780
你们聊
I'll give you a minute.

360
00:17:16,780 --> 00:17:17,760
谢谢
Thank you.

361
00:17:21,140 --> 00:17:22,980
我听说你母亲的事故了
I heard about your mother's accident.

362
00:17:23,450 --> 00:17:24,490
她没事吧
Is she gonna be OK?

363
00:17:24,500 --> 00:17:25,830
没事
She's gonna be fine.

364
00:17:26,280 --> 00:17:27,260
谢谢
Thanks.

365
00:17:27,810 --> 00:17:28,850
不客气
I'm glad.

366
00:17:32,220 --> 00:17:37,020
你为什么愿意和我父亲做生意
So, why would you want to go into business with my father?

367
00:17:37,020 --> 00:17:39,400
你知道他的为人以及赚钱方式
You know who he is and how he made his money.

368
00:17:40,100 --> 00:17:42,380
你不支持你家族的事业吗
You don't approve of your family's enterprises?

369
00:17:42,460 --> 00:17:43,750
我们是一家人
We share a name,

370
00:17:43,810 --> 00:17:46,350
这决定了不管我们是否愿意  事实无法改变
and that name defines us whether we want it to or not.

371
00:17:47,120 --> 00:17:48,770
你已经对我做出了判断评价
You've already made judgments about me,

372
00:17:48,780 --> 00:17:51,160
就像我也已经对你做出了评价一样
just like I've already made judgments about you.

373
00:17:51,160 --> 00:17:54,390
对  我是富人中的林赛·罗韩
Right. I'm the rich man's Lindsay Lohan.

374
00:17:55,700 --> 00:17:56,700
抱歉
Sorry.

375
00:17:57,890 --> 00:17:58,910
没关系
That's OK.

376
00:18:02,620 --> 00:18:04,230
我能问你点事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?

377
00:18:04,800 --> 00:18:05,750
问吧
Yeah.

378
00:18:06,460 --> 00:18:08,090
我知道对你来说那场经历就像地狱
I know it must have been hell for you,

379
00:18:08,850 --> 00:18:12,040
独自在那座小岛上待了五年  可是
aone on that island for 5 years, but I'm...

380
00:18:13,660 --> 00:18:14,680
可是什么
But what?

381
00:18:16,670 --> 00:18:18,950
有没有那么一天你会
But was there ever a day when you were just...

382
00:18:20,260 --> 00:18:22,170
庆幸远离了这一切
happy to be away from everything?

383
00:18:22,970 --> 00:18:24,510
没有来自家庭的压力
No pressure from your family,

384
00:18:24,510 --> 00:18:27,290
不用成为大家翘首以盼的人
no need to be the person everyone else expects you to be.

385
00:18:28,040 --> 00:18:29,280
有没有那么一天
Was there ever a day when--

386
00:18:29,280 --> 00:18:34,050
我并没感到失落  而是感到自由
When I didn't feel lost and I felt...free?

387
00:18:37,380 --> 00:18:38,460
不止一天
More than one.

388
00:18:38,460 --> 00:18:40,360
而且
And, uh...

389
00:18:41,940 --> 00:18:43,760
我想念那段时光
those are the days that I miss.

390
00:18:52,450 --> 00:18:54,350
怎么  很辣吗  梅林
What, is it too spicy for you, Merlyn?

391
00:18:54,350 --> 00:18:57,000
不是  不是很辣  我只是
No. No, not really. I'm just, um,

392
00:18:57,160 --> 00:19:00,260
我哭是因为想起早些时候看到的一则
I'm just crying because I was thinking of a Hallmark Commercial

393
00:19:00,270 --> 00:19:03,500
毫马电影台的商业广告  描写一只病猫
I saw earlier today, featuring a sick kitty.

394
00:19:03,500 --> 00:19:04,900
非常感人
It was very emotional.

395
00:19:06,920 --> 00:19:08,230
还需要些什么吗
Will there be anything else?

396
00:19:08,640 --> 00:19:10,280
不了  谢谢
No. Thank you.

397
00:19:10,280 --> 00:19:11,320
不客气
Yeah.

398
00:19:13,030 --> 00:19:14,720
多谢你让我请你吃晚餐
Thanks for letting me take you to dinner.

399
00:19:15,770 --> 00:19:18,020
也多谢你让我选印度菜
Well, thank you for letting me choose Indian.

400
00:19:19,560 --> 00:19:22,500
我读过一位影评家写的文章
You know, I read this article by a film critic once,

401
00:19:22,860 --> 00:19:26,320
他说假如他能实现一个愿望
who said if he could have one wish,

402
00:19:26,540 --> 00:19:28,580
就是在第一次约会的时候
it would be to watch his favorite movie

403
00:19:28,590 --> 00:19:30,630
再看一次他最喜欢的电影
again for the first time.

404
00:19:31,780 --> 00:19:33,240
我希望我们两人去看
I kind of wish that was us.

405
00:19:34,590 --> 00:19:36,970
你希望共进晚餐外加看场电影
So you want dinner and a movie.

406
00:19:37,480 --> 00:19:38,520
不是
No.

407
00:19:39,660 --> 00:19:41,350
我希望我们刚刚相遇
I wish we had just met

408
00:19:42,370 --> 00:19:44,210
一切才刚刚开始
and that all this was just beginning

409
00:19:44,210 --> 00:19:48,910
没那么多回忆是我希望你忘记的
and there wasn't so much of me I wish you'd forget.

410
00:19:49,390 --> 00:19:51,180
接着甜言蜜语吧
Well, keep saying nice things like that

411
00:19:51,180 --> 00:19:54,390
也许下次我会让你选餐厅
and maybe next time I'll let you choose the restaurant.

412
00:19:57,760 --> 00:19:58,960
-梅林先生  -什么事
- Mr. Merlyn... - Yeah?

413
00:19:58,960 --> 00:20:01,610
不好意思  您的信用卡被拒了
I'm sorry, I'm afraid you credit card has been declined.

414
00:20:01,610 --> 00:20:02,860
你有没有多刷几次
Did you swipe it a few times?

415
00:20:02,860 --> 00:20:05,020
有时候这些玩意儿可能会有点不灵光
You know, sometimes those things can be a little glitchy.

416
00:20:05,030 --> 00:20:08,230
我刷了  我想信用卡公司
I did, and, um, I'm afraid the credit card company

417
00:20:08,230 --> 00:20:09,800
想要我收回这张卡
wants me to confiscate it.

418
00:20:11,620 --> 00:20:12,620
抱歉
Sorry.

419
00:20:15,380 --> 00:20:18,270
人们总是问我  我最怀念的是什么
People are always asking me, what did I miss the most?

420
00:20:21,710 --> 00:20:22,830
中央空调
Air conditioning.

421
00:20:22,960 --> 00:20:24,120
卫星无线电
Satellite radio.

422
00:20:24,120 --> 00:20:26,450
意大利干  干
Tagliet--uh--ta--

423
00:20:26,450 --> 00:20:27,280
意大利干面条
Tagliatelle?

424
00:20:27,280 --> 00:20:28,170
没错
Mm. Right.

425
00:20:28,390 --> 00:20:29,900
不过我之所以给他们那些答案
But those are the answers that I give people

426
00:20:29,900 --> 00:20:32,330
是因为那是他们期待的
because those are the answers they're expecting.

427
00:20:32,520 --> 00:20:34,260
为什么你不实话实说呢
Why can't you just be truthful?

428
00:20:34,720 --> 00:20:36,560
我不知道该怎么说实话
I don't know how truthful I can be.

429
00:20:37,650 --> 00:20:39,400
你经历了一场残酷的考验
You've been through a crucible,

430
00:20:39,830 --> 00:20:42,020
这场考验改变了你  为什么不能说
and it changed you. How can it not?

431
00:20:44,760 --> 00:20:45,840
真美
That's beautiful.

432
00:20:46,450 --> 00:20:47,530
你的十字架项链
Your cross.

433
00:20:49,620 --> 00:20:50,910
是件礼物
It's a gift.

434
00:20:51,290 --> 00:20:52,640
我未婚夫送的
From my fiance.

435
00:20:52,650 --> 00:20:53,840
未婚夫
Fiance.

436
00:20:54,820 --> 00:20:56,480
我不知道你订婚了
I didn't know you were engaged.

437
00:20:56,490 --> 00:20:57,430
我没有
I'm not.

438
00:20:57,830 --> 00:20:58,760
再也不算了
Anymore.

439
00:21:00,630 --> 00:21:01,660
他死了
He died.

440
00:21:01,860 --> 00:21:02,940
真遗憾
I'm sorry.

441
00:21:03,790 --> 00:21:04,800
我也觉得
Me, too.

442
00:21:06,050 --> 00:21:08,290
失去他就是对我的残酷考验
That was my crucible.

443
00:21:11,330 --> 00:21:12,670
天呐  感觉真好
Boy, it's nice to...

444
00:21:14,440 --> 00:21:17,580
可以不用伪装自己和人相处真好
It's really nice to be with someone that I can be myself with.

445
00:21:18,020 --> 00:21:20,820
和能与自己感同身受的人相处真好
It's nice to be with someone who knows how hard it can be.

446
00:21:22,200 --> 00:21:23,260
真是抱歉
I'm really sorry.

447
00:21:23,260 --> 00:21:24,230
没关系  接吧
It's ok. Take it.

448
00:21:24,230 --> 00:21:25,200
谢谢
Thank you.

449
00:21:26,730 --> 00:21:27,370
喂
Yeah.

450
00:21:27,370 --> 00:21:29,380
我是狄格  出事了
It's Dig. Something came up.

451
00:21:29,380 --> 00:21:31,520
你必须离开那儿然后给我打电话
You gotta get out of there and call me back.

452
00:21:33,310 --> 00:21:36,030
海伦娜  我得走了  有些事必须去做
Helena, I have to go. There's something that I have to do.

453
00:21:37,050 --> 00:21:40,110
事关我母亲  不然我会
It's about my mother, otherwise I would, uh,

454
00:21:40,370 --> 00:21:41,420
我会留下来
I would stay.

455
00:21:41,420 --> 00:21:42,830
我也会欢迎之至
And I would like that.

456
00:21:46,850 --> 00:21:49,790
如果我让你付钱的话我爸会杀了我的
My father would kill me if I let you pay.

457
00:21:56,660 --> 00:21:57,940
我要坦白一点
I have a confession.

458
00:22:00,810 --> 00:22:02,760
今晚我本不想跟你出来的
I didn't want to go out with you tonight.

459
00:22:02,760 --> 00:22:03,950
我也是
That makes two of us.

460
00:22:03,950 --> 00:22:05,670
我真高兴我没有那么做
I'm really glad that I did.

461
00:22:06,270 --> 00:22:07,700
我也是
That makes two of us.

462
00:22:09,180 --> 00:22:10,270
奥利弗
Oliver.

463
00:22:11,700 --> 00:22:13,600
小心我爸
Be careful with my father.

464
00:22:22,480 --> 00:22:24,930
西娅  你不用敲门  亲爱的
Thea, you don't need to knock, sweetheart.

465
00:22:25,280 --> 00:22:26,290
那我呢
What about me?

466
00:22:27,580 --> 00:22:28,770
我希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.

467
00:22:29,760 --> 00:22:30,960
西娅让我进来的
Thea let me in.

468
00:22:31,320 --> 00:22:32,540
你来做什么
What are you doing here?

469
00:22:32,540 --> 00:22:34,350
我想看看你恢复得怎么样了
I wanted to see how your recovery was going?

470
00:22:34,350 --> 00:22:37,070
你完全可以打电话过来
Well, surely someone of your means has a telephone.

471
00:22:37,070 --> 00:22:38,170
当我有要事相谈时
I like to see someone

472
00:22:38,170 --> 00:22:40,630
我喜欢跟人面对面地说
when I have something important to talk about.

473
00:22:43,750 --> 00:22:45,310
我们曾是朋友  莫伊拉
We used to be friends, Moira.

474
00:22:47,390 --> 00:22:48,810
我还记得那段日子
I still remember that time.

475
00:22:49,730 --> 00:22:52,240
你  我  还有罗伯特
You, me, and Robert.

476
00:22:53,020 --> 00:22:54,980
这也正是我过来的原因
Which is why I came by.

477
00:22:56,640 --> 00:22:59,500
你对星城的未来至关重要
You are a vital part of Starling City's future.

478
00:23:01,240 --> 00:23:02,800
罗伯特害怕那样的未来
Robert feared that future.

479
00:23:04,210 --> 00:23:05,620
他失去了他的信念
He lost his conviction.

480
00:23:07,750 --> 00:23:11,690
像你今天这样与死神擦肩而过的经历
It's been my experience that when someone has a brush with death

481
00:23:11,690 --> 00:23:13,470
我深有体会
like you experienced today,

482
00:23:14,480 --> 00:23:17,390
这样的经历能改变最牢固的信念
even their deepest held convictions can change.

483
00:23:19,340 --> 00:23:20,320
你动摇了吗
Have they?

484
00:23:21,140 --> 00:23:22,110
没有
No.

485
00:23:23,840 --> 00:23:25,320
你不必说出来
You didn't have to say it.

486
00:23:28,650 --> 00:23:30,530
我能看出来
I can see that they haven't.

487
00:23:37,220 --> 00:23:37,760
发生什么了
What happened?

488
00:23:37,760 --> 00:23:39,720
是将要发生什么了
Yeah, it's what's about to happen.

489
00:23:39,950 --> 00:23:41,710
波提纳尔的保镖尼克·赛瓦缇
Bertinelli's enforcer Nick Salvati.

490
00:23:41,710 --> 00:23:43,520
我们刚一起喝过一杯
Yeah. We drank a scotch together.

491
00:23:43,520 --> 00:23:45,280
他看上去挺像真的黑帮的
He seems like a real stand-up mobster.

492
00:23:45,280 --> 00:23:46,540
他现在正挨家挨户地
Yeah, well, he's been paying visits to everyone

493
00:23:46,540 --> 00:23:48,720
向欠他们保护费的人收钱
who owes the mob protection money.

494
00:23:48,720 --> 00:23:50,950
狄格尔  我正在努力寻找向我妈开枪的家伙
Diggle, I'm trying to figure out who took a shot at my mother,

495
00:23:50,950 --> 00:23:53,020
不是要插手所有的犯罪活动
not take on all of organized crime.

496
00:23:53,070 --> 00:23:54,450
听着  奥利弗  赛瓦缇和他的手下
Well, listen, Oliver, Salvati and his goons

497
00:23:54,450 --> 00:23:56,350
今晚已经把四个人送进了医院
have already put 4 people in the hospital tonight,

498
00:23:56,350 --> 00:23:58,390
如果没人来制止他们的话
and if somebody doesn't stop them,

499
00:23:59,060 --> 00:24:01,170
那个开拉索餐厅的倒霉蛋就是下一个了
the poor bastard who owns Russo's is gonna be next.

500
00:24:01,170 --> 00:24:02,960
等等  拉索餐厅
Wait, wait. Russo's?

501
00:24:02,960 --> 00:24:03,980
在亚当路和...
It's at the corner of Adams and...

502
00:24:03,980 --> 00:24:06,210
我知道它在哪儿  狄格尔  我现在就在这儿
I know where it is, Diggle. I'm here right now.

503
00:24:06,230 --> 00:24:07,410
什么
What?

504
00:24:08,380 --> 00:24:10,140
我刚才在和波提纳尔的女儿一起吃饭
I was having dinner with Bertinelli's daughter.

505
00:24:10,140 --> 00:24:12,800
奥利弗  你应该去做卧底的  而不是闪电约会
Oliver, you're supposed to be going undercover, not speed dating.

506
00:24:12,980 --> 00:24:14,320
我没得选择
I didn't have a choice.

507
00:24:14,370 --> 00:24:17,020
好吧  我在网上看过她的照片
Yeah, well, uh, I've seen her on the web.

508
00:24:17,230 --> 00:24:19,390
你还真是牺牲了不少
You made quite the sacrifice.

509
00:24:24,060 --> 00:24:25,350
赛瓦缇来了
Salvati's here.

510
00:24:32,140 --> 00:24:34,280
很抱歉  我们打烊了
I'm sorry, we're closed.

511
00:24:36,870 --> 00:24:39,970
赛瓦缇先生
Oh, Mr. Salvati.

512
00:24:41,160 --> 00:24:42,280
晚上好[意大利语]
Buona sera.

513
00:24:43,570 --> 00:24:45,890
我刚做了些千层面
I have some fresh-made lasagna.

514
00:24:45,890 --> 00:24:48,260
我们不是来吃饭的  拉索先生
We're not here for food, Mr. Russo.

515
00:24:48,640 --> 00:24:49,940
你该缴费了
Your payment's due.

516
00:24:49,940 --> 00:24:52,350
这个月的我已经付过了啊
I already made my payment this month.

517
00:24:52,350 --> 00:24:53,660
你得再付一次
You need to pay again.

518
00:24:53,660 --> 00:24:56,520
求你了  我再付一次我就没法
Please. I can't afford to make another payment if I'm going to--

519
00:24:56,520 --> 00:24:59,750
没法干嘛  没法进货了
Going to what? Restock your bar?

520
00:25:03,130 --> 00:25:04,920
折断他的手指
Break his fingers.

521
00:25:04,920 --> 00:25:06,030
放开他
Leave him alone!

522
00:25:06,030 --> 00:25:06,580
她的也折断
Break hers, too.

523
00:25:06,590 --> 00:25:08,600
不  别碰她
No! Don't touch her!

524
00:25:49,570 --> 00:25:52,950
我不明白  她为什么要对付自己家里
I don't understand. Why is she targeting her family?

525
00:25:52,950 --> 00:25:54,980
不知道  我以为你才是有叛逆问题的那个
I don't know. And here I thought you had parental issues.

526
00:25:54,990 --> 00:25:56,850
我没在开玩笑  狄格尔
It's not a joke, Diggle.

527
00:25:56,850 --> 00:25:59,260
奥利弗  别告诉我你喜欢上她了
Oliver, you're not falling for this girl, are you?

528
00:25:59,490 --> 00:26:02,220
我相信你不会那么疯狂吧
Because I know you can't be that crazy.

529
00:26:02,460 --> 00:26:04,520
海伦娜·赛瓦缇向你母亲开枪
Helena Bertinelli shot at your mother.

530
00:26:04,520 --> 00:26:06,690
她还冷酷无情地杀了四个人
She also murdered 4 men in cold blood.

531
00:26:06,690 --> 00:26:11,660
她这么做一定是有理由的
She has to have reasons for what she's doing.

532
00:26:11,780 --> 00:26:13,330
有理由
Reasons?

533
00:26:14,280 --> 00:26:16,610
从何时起你开始关心坏人的理由了
Since when do you care about the bad guys' reasons?

534
00:26:16,610 --> 00:26:18,880
别忘了  她是个坏人  奥利弗
Oh, she is the bad guy, Oliver.

535
00:26:18,880 --> 00:26:21,580
她是个杀手  不管你现在在想些什么
She's the killer. And whatever's going on in your head,

536
00:26:21,580 --> 00:26:23,290
你最好把这点搞搞清楚
you better get it straight, man.

537
00:26:23,290 --> 00:26:25,710
他的任何举动
Any attempt on his right hand

538
00:26:25,710 --> 00:26:28,760
都可能害死你新朋友的父亲
is gonna send your new friend's father on the warpath.

539
00:26:32,410 --> 00:26:34,090
我知道我在做什么
I know what I'm doing.

540
00:26:38,320 --> 00:26:41,390
现在我明白你家人听你撒谎时的感受了
Now I know how your family feels when you lie to them.

541
00:26:47,050 --> 00:26:48,420
只能看到这个角度吗
Is this the only angle you got?

542
00:26:48,420 --> 00:26:51,290
拉索餐厅的安保系统有些偷工减料
The Russo's chintzed out a bit on their security package.

543
00:26:51,290 --> 00:26:54,250
有人在侧面向这些人开枪
Somebody is in the wings with a gun shooting at these guys.

544
00:26:54,250 --> 00:26:55,310
在这之前能看到什么
What do you got from earlier?

545
00:26:55,310 --> 00:26:57,410
-你是指案发之前吗  -是的
- You mean before the shooting?  - Yeah.

546
00:26:57,590 --> 00:27:00,330
工作会餐  生日会餐  一些不靠谱的约会
A business dinner, a birthday dinner, a couple of blind dates.

547
00:27:00,330 --> 00:27:02,480
有中国客人在吗
Any guests of the Chinese persuasion?

548
00:27:02,480 --> 00:27:04,690
-为什么这么问  -心血来潮
- Why?  - Humor me.

549
00:27:10,660 --> 00:27:13,000
喔  喔  喔  等等  那是什么
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a second. What was that?

550
00:27:13,000 --> 00:27:14,560
你自己来吧
Help yourself.

551
00:27:14,560 --> 00:27:16,030
快点
Come on.

552
00:27:21,260 --> 00:27:23,070
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.

553
00:27:30,630 --> 00:27:31,850
警探
Detective.

554
00:27:31,850 --> 00:27:33,560
没什么事吧
Is everything ok?

555
00:27:35,240 --> 00:27:38,310
你那位带弓箭的朋友
Your, um, your buddy with the arrows

556
00:27:38,310 --> 00:27:39,850
昨晚出现在拉索餐厅
was at Russo's last night.

557
00:27:39,850 --> 00:27:42,200
我当时在那儿有个约会
And I was there earlier with a date.

558
00:27:42,200 --> 00:27:44,890
怎么
So...what?

559
00:27:45,140 --> 00:27:47,220
你又怀疑我是帽兜男了吗
You think I'm the hood guy again?

560
00:27:47,670 --> 00:27:49,190
没有
No.

561
00:27:49,930 --> 00:27:51,300
我怀疑你约会的对象
Your date.

562
00:27:51,300 --> 00:27:53,030
海伦娜·波提纳尔
Helena Bertinelli.

563
00:27:53,030 --> 00:27:55,020
如果我是你  我会离她远点儿
If I were you, I'd stay away from her.

564
00:27:55,020 --> 00:27:57,910
她们家的事情发生得不适时宜
Her family's bad news on a good day.

565
00:27:58,150 --> 00:28:00,810
为什么突然间担心我的安危了
Why the sudden concern for my well-being?

566
00:28:03,780 --> 00:28:06,250
几周前我犯了个错误
A few weeks ago I made a mistake.

567
00:28:07,110 --> 00:28:09,140
我差点害你死掉
I almost got you killed.

568
00:28:10,800 --> 00:28:13,020
所以你觉得欠我一个人情吗
And you felt like you owed me one?

569
00:28:13,160 --> 00:28:15,290
如果真是这样
If I did,

570
00:28:15,290 --> 00:28:17,950
照我看  我已经还清了
as far as I'm concerned, this clears the books.

571
00:28:29,530 --> 00:28:31,130
我能跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you?

572
00:28:31,260 --> 00:28:32,780
老爸
Dad!

573
00:28:32,900 --> 00:28:34,740
要是你没注意到
In case you haven't noticed,

574
00:28:34,740 --> 00:28:36,440
我现在有点儿忙
I'm a little occupied at the moment.

575
00:28:36,440 --> 00:28:38,170
我刚跟会计谈过
I just talked to the accountant.

576
00:28:38,180 --> 00:28:39,510
他说我的账户被冻结了
He said my accounts were frozen.

577
00:28:39,510 --> 00:28:42,220
我所有的信用卡也都被取消了
He said my credit cards were all canceled.

578
00:28:42,430 --> 00:28:46,510
我每年要付桑迪一大笔钱  汤米
I pay Sandy a king's ransom each year in fees, Tommy.

579
00:28:46,620 --> 00:28:50,850
有关钱的问题  会计说什么就是什么
When it comes to money, if he says it's so, it's so.

580
00:28:50,850 --> 00:28:53,250
你觉得这是个玩笑吗
Do you think this is a joke?

581
00:28:54,570 --> 00:28:56,050
不
No.

582
00:28:57,250 --> 00:28:58,840
你才是
You are.

583
00:29:00,410 --> 00:29:03,410
尽管我不得不说  你长期的无责任感和
Although I must say, your chronic irresponsibility

584
00:29:03,410 --> 00:29:07,470
不可救药的懒散已经不好笑了
and terminal laziness has lost its humor.

585
00:29:09,560 --> 00:29:11,430
你现在想知道为什么了
You're wondering why now.

586
00:29:11,580 --> 00:29:14,690
最好问问  为什么不早这样
The better question is, why not sooner?

587
00:29:14,690 --> 00:29:16,150
那是
It's...

588
00:29:16,150 --> 00:29:17,960
是我的信托基金
It's my trust fund.

589
00:29:17,960 --> 00:29:21,290
用的都是我的钱
Which is comprised of my money.

590
00:29:21,870 --> 00:29:24,640
口误了
Oh, excuse me.

591
00:29:26,370 --> 00:29:28,440
曾经用的
Was comprised.

592
00:30:06,150 --> 00:30:07,570
海伦娜
Helena.

593
00:30:08,510 --> 00:30:10,440
你是如何找到我的
How did you find me here?

594
00:30:10,440 --> 00:30:12,780
我从你家里跟出来
I followed you from your house.

595
00:30:14,320 --> 00:30:15,940
他是你的未婚夫
Your fiance?

596
00:30:18,870 --> 00:30:20,340
是的
Yeah.

597
00:30:26,060 --> 00:30:29,090
你说过  失去他是对你的严峻的考验
You said that losing him was your own crucible.

598
00:30:29,690 --> 00:30:31,610
这件事改变了你
That it changed you.

599
00:30:32,160 --> 00:30:33,900
但你没说是如何改变的
You didn't say how.

600
00:30:37,900 --> 00:30:41,690
当你像我对他的爱一样的
When you love someone as much as I loved him,

601
00:30:41,800 --> 00:30:42,900
全心全意爱着一个人
with all of your heart,

602
00:30:42,900 --> 00:30:46,940
当他离开的时候
and you can't just turn that emotion off

603
00:30:46,940 --> 00:30:48,970
你不能就这样忘了这段感情
when they're taken from you.

604
00:30:48,970 --> 00:30:51,090
感觉依旧会刻骨铭心
You still feel things as deeply.

605
00:30:51,100 --> 00:30:55,060
如果你不会再感受到爱的时候
And if it can't be love that you feel, then...

606
00:30:57,460 --> 00:30:59,460
那就会变成恨
Then it becomes hate.

607
00:30:59,570 --> 00:31:01,330
恨谁
Hate for who?

608
00:31:02,090 --> 00:31:03,580
奥利弗
Oliver...

609
00:31:09,300 --> 00:31:11,410
你应该离我远一点
You should stay away from me.

610
00:31:14,070 --> 00:31:15,530
海伦娜
Helena?

611
00:31:22,300 --> 00:31:23,700
上车
Get in.

612
00:31:33,670 --> 00:31:36,750
我父亲一定会杀了你们
My father is going to kill you for this.

613
00:31:44,570 --> 00:31:46,570
很多年前我就想这么做了
I've been wanting to do that for years.

614
00:31:46,570 --> 00:31:48,800
你这个骄纵的婊子
Spoiled bitch.

615
00:31:49,960 --> 00:31:52,290
我早知道内部有人
I knew it was someone from the inside

616
00:31:52,290 --> 00:31:54,840
在暗地里对抗你父亲和我
waging war against your father and me.

617
00:31:54,840 --> 00:31:58,350
但从没想到会这么深入
I just never thought it'd be this inside.

618
00:32:02,310 --> 00:32:04,600
你在拉索店里掉了这个
You dropped this at Russo's.

619
00:32:05,720 --> 00:32:08,440
你比我想象得要聪明  尼克
You're smarter than I gave you credit for, Nicki.

620
00:32:08,440 --> 00:32:10,010
你却没有
You're not.

621
00:32:13,170 --> 00:32:14,830
你是生意人  对吧
You're a businessman, right?

622
00:32:14,830 --> 00:32:16,500
我们来谈笔生意吧
So let's talk business.

623
00:32:16,510 --> 00:32:18,970
你让我们走  我就可以给你一大笔钱
I can offer you a lot of money if you let us go.

624
00:32:18,970 --> 00:32:21,590
这不是钱的问题  有钱人
This isn't about money, richie rich.

625
00:32:21,590 --> 00:32:23,790
这是忠诚的问题
This is about loyalty.

626
00:32:23,790 --> 00:32:25,820
他跟这些一点关系都没有
He's got nothing to do with any of this.

627
00:32:25,820 --> 00:32:27,500
那这他妈的到底怎么回事儿
Then what the hell is it about?

628
00:32:27,500 --> 00:32:31,420
是我父亲杀了迈克尔
My father had Michael murdered.

629
00:32:34,670 --> 00:32:36,440
当然是他干的
Of course he did.

630
00:32:36,520 --> 00:32:38,540
他不想让你知道真相
He didn't want you to know the truth.

631
00:32:38,540 --> 00:32:42,730
你可怜的未婚夫收集了证据
Your rat of a fiance was gathering evidence.

632
00:32:42,730 --> 00:32:45,580
还去跟该死的联邦调查员报告
He was talking to the friggin' FBI.

633
00:32:45,580 --> 00:32:46,840
你一生挚爱
The love of your life

634
00:32:46,840 --> 00:32:49,650
差点毁了你父亲
was going to destroy your father.

635
00:32:49,650 --> 00:32:51,340
你猜错了
You're wrong.

636
00:32:53,040 --> 00:32:54,870
我在迈克尔的包里面发现了笔记本
I found a laptop in Michael's bag,

637
00:32:54,870 --> 00:32:56,250
海伦娜
Helena.

638
00:32:56,250 --> 00:32:59,530
能让你父亲和我在监狱待一辈子的
Everything that could send your father and me to prison

639
00:32:59,530 --> 00:33:01,820
证据都在里面了
for the rest of our lives was on it.

640
00:33:01,820 --> 00:33:04,650
-那个电脑  -是我的
- That computer-- - Was mine.

641
00:33:05,580 --> 00:33:08,940
和联邦调查局报告的不是迈克尔
Michael wasn't the one talking to the FBI.

642
00:33:09,050 --> 00:33:10,860
是我
I was.

643
00:33:11,360 --> 00:33:12,900
你
You?

644
00:33:13,120 --> 00:33:15,120
我父亲是个魔鬼
My father is a monster.

645
00:33:15,120 --> 00:33:16,860
为了保住钱和权利
He doesn't care who he hurts

646
00:33:16,860 --> 00:33:18,420
他不惜一切代价
to keep his money and power,

647
00:33:18,420 --> 00:33:20,100
我要阻止他
and I wanted it to stop.

648
00:33:20,100 --> 00:33:22,710
那么迈克尔的死就是你的错了
Well, then it's your fault Michael's dead.

649
00:33:22,840 --> 00:33:25,070
不能怪你父亲下令杀死他
Not your father for ordering the hit,

650
00:33:25,080 --> 00:33:27,750
亦或是怪我来执行
or me for carrying it out.

651
00:33:29,340 --> 00:33:30,920
全都是你的责任
Yours.

652
00:33:31,420 --> 00:33:33,550
是你杀了迈克尔
You shot Michael.

653
00:33:37,210 --> 00:33:41,290
正中胸部  所以他知道是我干的
In the chest, so he knew it was me.

654
00:33:41,870 --> 00:33:43,370
就
Just...

655
00:33:43,370 --> 00:33:44,820
像
Like...

656
00:33:45,630 --> 00:33:47,140
这样
This.

657
00:34:17,320 --> 00:34:19,770
你会为你所做的事情付出代价
You're gonna burn in hell for what you've done.

658
00:34:19,770 --> 00:34:21,700
那也值得
It'll be worth it.

659
00:34:27,180 --> 00:34:28,650
海伦娜
Helena...

660
00:34:32,280 --> 00:34:34,430
我别无选择  奥利弗
I didn't have a choice, Oliver.

661
00:34:35,370 --> 00:34:37,680
不能让任何人知道我的秘密
No one can know my secret.

662
00:34:45,500 --> 00:34:47,220
没找到任何有效的证据
Csu didn't find any usable prints

663
00:34:47,220 --> 00:34:48,650
除了三个受害者
except for the 3 victims.

664
00:34:48,650 --> 00:34:50,580
其中一个胸口有枪伤
One of them had a gsw to the chest.

665
00:34:50,580 --> 00:34:53,670
那又是谁扭断了赛瓦缇和他同伙的脖子
So who broke the necks of Salvati and his buddy?

666
00:34:54,100 --> 00:34:57,550
听着  兜帽男好久没作案了
Look, it's been a while since the hood broke anyone's neck.

667
00:34:57,550 --> 00:34:59,580
而且我在现场也没发现箭头
And I didn't see any arrows laying around.

668
00:34:59,580 --> 00:35:01,620
我们最好祈祷弗兰克·波提纳尔
We better pray that Frank Bertinelli

669
00:35:01,620 --> 00:35:02,930
将此事归咎于兜帽男
blames the hood for this.

670
00:35:03,650 --> 00:35:05,820
因为一旦他认为这是黑社会所为
'cause if he thinks it's the triad,

671
00:35:05,820 --> 00:35:09,100
星城就要城损人亡了
Starling City is ground zero to world war III.

672
00:35:16,300 --> 00:35:17,850
你还好吗
You ok?

673
00:35:18,630 --> 00:35:20,540
我今天跟我爸爸谈过了
I spoke to my dad today.

674
00:35:20,540 --> 00:35:22,390
我猜聊得很开心吧
I bet that was fun.

675
00:35:22,880 --> 00:35:26,050
他向我解释了昨天信用卡冻结的原因
He explained to me what happened with my credit card yesterday.

676
00:35:26,050 --> 00:35:28,910
以及我的支票  我的存款
And my checking account, my savings account,

677
00:35:28,910 --> 00:35:32,480
我的佣金  我的股票
my brokerage account, my stock portfolio.

678
00:35:34,130 --> 00:35:37,060
他全部冻结了
He cut me off completely.

679
00:35:39,080 --> 00:35:40,610
什么
What?

680
00:35:40,980 --> 00:35:42,980
我的车也被收回了  真有意思
My car got repossessed. That was fun.

681
00:35:42,980 --> 00:35:44,360
还有  我不得不
Oh, and I have to move

682
00:35:44,360 --> 00:35:46,870
在这个月底搬出我的公寓
out of my apartment by the end of the month.

683
00:35:50,010 --> 00:35:52,780
你会没事的  汤米
You are gonna be fine, Tommy.

684
00:35:53,810 --> 00:35:56,780
事实上  你会做得很好
In fact, you are gonna be great.

685
00:35:57,910 --> 00:35:59,900
不管你富有或贫穷
Merlyn money or not.

686
00:36:02,870 --> 00:36:04,640
你知道吗
And you know,

687
00:36:06,570 --> 00:36:10,290
冰箱里有一个蘑菇橄榄马里奥比萨
I have a mushroom and olive Mario pizza

688
00:36:10,290 --> 00:36:13,830
等着被我俩吃掉呢
in my refrigerator waiting to be eaten.

689
00:36:14,910 --> 00:36:17,180
我想已经付过钱了吧  对吗
I suppose it's already paid for, right?

690
00:36:17,180 --> 00:36:18,900
当然
Exactly.

691
00:36:35,720 --> 00:36:37,000
你什么时候回来的
When did you get back?

692
00:36:37,000 --> 00:36:38,570
就在刚刚
Just now.

693
00:36:46,290 --> 00:36:48,680
能见到你太好了
I'm so happy to see you.

694
00:36:50,900 --> 00:36:54,450
但你回家只是因为听说我受伤了吗
But did you come home only because you heard I was hurt?

695
00:36:54,450 --> 00:36:58,840
不  西娅打电话的时候我已经在路上了
No. I was already on my way when Thea called.

696
00:36:58,840 --> 00:37:03,760
我回家是因为我想念我的妻子
I actually came home because I miss my wife.

697
00:37:10,560 --> 00:37:12,060
没事了
It's ok.

698
00:37:13,630 --> 00:37:15,220
她还好吗
Is she all right?

699
00:37:15,220 --> 00:37:16,810
沃尔特回来了
Walter's home.

700
00:37:17,160 --> 00:37:18,880
她会没事的
She's gonna be fine.

701
00:37:18,890 --> 00:37:23,090
听着  很抱歉先前那么对你
Look, I'm sorry if I was a bitch with you earlier.

702
00:37:23,390 --> 00:37:24,450
之前有好几次呢
There were a few times.

703
00:37:24,460 --> 00:37:25,750
你能具体说明下吗
Could you be more specific?

704
00:37:25,750 --> 00:37:27,510
-别得寸进尺了你  -不要担心
- Don't push it.  - Don't worry.

705
00:37:27,510 --> 00:37:29,420
你一点也不惹人厌
You weren't a bitch.

706
00:37:30,160 --> 00:37:33,720
在医院你只是有一点  一点点
At the hospital you were a little... a little bit.

707
00:37:33,940 --> 00:37:37,580
听着  我只是很担心你
Look, I'm just worried about you.

708
00:37:38,770 --> 00:37:40,840
你看起来很孤独
You seem really lonely.

709
00:37:40,840 --> 00:37:43,480
我们都有秘密  奥利
And we all have our secrets, Ollie.

710
00:37:43,480 --> 00:37:45,930
很显然你也有你的秘密
Clearly you have yours.

711
00:37:46,970 --> 00:37:50,860
如果你不想与我们分享也无所谓
And it's fine if you don't want to share them with us,

712
00:37:51,500 --> 00:37:55,580
但我真的认为你应该找其他人聊聊
but I just really think you should share them with someone.

713
00:38:13,630 --> 00:38:15,100
我本该问你为什么在这里的
I'd ask how you got in here,

714
00:38:15,100 --> 00:38:18,660
但星城的治安维持者
but the Sarling City vigilante

715
00:38:18,660 --> 00:38:21,410
总是来无影去无踪  对吗
comes and goes as he pleases, doesn't he?

716
00:38:23,680 --> 00:38:25,290
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?

717
00:38:28,900 --> 00:38:30,810
我看见你打斗的场面
I saw you fight.

718
00:38:33,580 --> 00:38:35,610
还看到了你眼睛的深处
And I saw your eyes.

719
00:38:37,130 --> 00:38:38,430
那个岛对你的种种改变
That island changed you in ways

720
00:38:38,430 --> 00:38:40,580
只有像我这样的人才能懂
that only someone like me could understand.

721
00:38:40,580 --> 00:38:42,000
不对
No.

722
00:38:42,770 --> 00:38:43,960
你现在的所作所为
What you're doing right now,

723
00:38:43,960 --> 00:38:47,890
让你感觉是在伸张正义  但其实不然
I know that if feels like justice, but it's not.

724
00:38:47,890 --> 00:38:49,670
这是复仇
It's revenge.

725
00:38:49,860 --> 00:38:54,450
有时复仇就是伸张正义
Sometimes revenge is justice.

726
00:38:56,430 --> 00:38:57,990
你父亲杀了你的未婚夫
Your father killed your fiance.

727
00:38:57,990 --> 00:39:00,550
那你的父亲又对你做了什么
And what did your father do to you?

728
00:39:02,730 --> 00:39:06,960
难道兜帽下的男人不是在拨乱反正吗
Isn't the man in the hood fighting to set things right?

729
00:39:07,640 --> 00:39:09,810
为什么你的仇恨就是伸张正义呢
Why is your vendetta more valid than mine?

730
00:39:09,810 --> 00:39:12,170
我们都一样  你和我
We're the same, you and I.

731
00:39:13,380 --> 00:39:15,040
不  我们不同
No, we're not.

732
00:39:15,820 --> 00:39:18,140
隐藏在平静的表面下
Hiding in plain sight.

733
00:39:18,440 --> 00:39:23,440
用笑容和谎言做伪装
Concealing our anger with smiles and lies.

734
00:39:24,500 --> 00:39:26,400
休想骗我  奥利弗
Don't lie to me, Oliver.

735
00:39:27,780 --> 00:39:30,180
你和我的感觉是一样的  我懂
You feel the same as I do, I know it.

736
00:39:30,180 --> 00:39:31,930
你为什么哭呢
Why are you crying?

737
00:39:35,490 --> 00:39:37,170
我不知道
I don't know.

738
00:39:38,900 --> 00:39:43,820
也许是因为怨恨在胸太久
Maybe it's because I have been alone in my hate for so long.

739
00:39:45,280 --> 00:39:48,020
-我觉得  -说出事实的感觉真好
- I feel... - It feels so good to tell the truth.

