1
00:03:12,000 --> 00:03:16,000
{\pos(70,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:03:12,000 --> 00:03:16,000
{\pos(70,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:03:12,000 --> 00:03:16,000
{\pos(60,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:03:12,000 --> 00:03:16,000
{\pos(86,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:03:12,000 --> 00:03:16,000
{\pos(100,254)}人人影视
YYeTs.com

6
00:03:12,000 --> 00:03:16,000
{\pos(101,267)}原创翻译  双语字幕

8
00:03:12,000 --> 00:03:16,000
{\pos(240,267)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

9
00:03:16,100 --> 00:03:20,000
{\pos(190,278)}翻译：小榴莲  绒布熊  vivi的夏天  小黎  圈圈  Luna_3  鱼小姐

11
00:03:20,100 --> 00:03:24,000
{\pos(190,278)}初校：爱是李   苹果   时间轴：搁浅   加森

13
00:03:24,100 --> 00:03:28,000
{\pos(190,278)}后期：冰河   监制：苹果

15
00:07:58,950 --> 00:08:03,840
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)绿   箭

16
00:07:58,950 --> 00:08:03,840
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)第一季 第九集

17
00:00:00,620 --> 00:00:03,030
我的名字叫奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.

18
00:00:03,030 --> 00:00:07,130
五年里  我被困孤岛  只有一个目标
For 5 years I was stranded on an island with only one goal--

19
00:00:08,060 --> 00:00:09,420
生存
to survive.

20
00:00:09,430 --> 00:00:11,230
奥利弗·奎恩还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.

21
00:00:11,230 --> 00:00:14,090
现在我要完成父亲的遗愿
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish--

22
00:00:14,090 --> 00:00:15,890
用他留给我的名单
To use the list of names he left me

23
00:00:15,410 --> 00:00:16,210
{\pos(163,107)}亚当·亨特

24
00:00:15,890 --> 00:00:19,300
扳倒那些荼毒城市的人
and bring down those who are poisoning my city.

25
00:00:19,940 --> 00:00:23,160
要做这些  我必须伪装成另一个人
To do this, I must become someone else.

26
00:00:23,440 --> 00:00:27,180
我必须成为另一个存在
I must become something else.

27
00:00:27,350 --> 00:00:29,270
《绿箭》前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...

28
00:00:29,280 --> 00:00:31,370
别再调查这件事了  很危险
Stop looking into this. It's not safe.

29
00:00:31,370 --> 00:00:35,340
意外总是发生在那些过于好奇的人身上
Accidents tend to befall people who are too curious.

30
00:00:35,340 --> 00:00:38,720
费利西蒂  尽你所能查查这个笔记本
Felicity, I want you to find out all you can about that book.

31
00:00:38,720 --> 00:00:41,980
我从应用科学部找来了这眼镜  再看看那个本子
I got these from applied sciences. Look at the book again.

32
00:00:43,830 --> 00:00:46,600
我在哪儿能找到照片中这个人
Where can I find the man in this picture?

33
00:00:49,140 --> 00:00:52,000
岛上很危险  但你没告诉他们我的下落
Island dangerous, but you not tell them where to find me.

34
00:00:52,000 --> 00:00:53,860
我和你一起去
I'm coming with you.

35
00:01:05,110 --> 00:01:08,040
机会只此一次
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.

36
00:01:09,890 --> 00:01:13,240
听着  我所做的都是为了一切进展顺利
Look, all I'm doing is looking to get something going again.

37
00:01:13,690 --> 00:01:15,290
是  我知道
Yeah, I know.

38
00:01:15,830 --> 00:01:17,760
我知道  但是这次
I know, but this time--

39
00:01:22,740 --> 00:01:24,720
一会再打给你
I have to call you back.

40
00:01:26,660 --> 00:01:28,130
干什么
What?

41
00:01:28,380 --> 00:01:30,960
你回过来是想再分一杯羹吗
Did you come back for another pound of flesh?

42
00:01:31,350 --> 00:01:33,330
你会失望的  伙计
You're gonna be disappointed, pal.

43
00:01:33,340 --> 00:01:35,080
多亏了你  我才...
Thanks to you, I'm--

44
00:01:50,170 --> 00:01:52,120
好的  就是这个节奏
Nice. Picking up the pace.

45
00:01:52,120 --> 00:01:53,940
我也可以跟你说同样的话
I could say the same thing about you.

46
00:01:53,950 --> 00:01:56,010
你单枪匹马划掉了你父亲名单上的三个人
You crossed 3 names off your father's list this week alone.

47
00:01:56,010 --> 00:01:58,000
是啊  上面有些人已经开始收手了
Yeah, well, some of these guys are just giving it up now.

48
00:01:58,000 --> 00:01:59,750
我只要去会会他们就行
All I gotta do is pay 'em a visit.

49
00:01:59,750 --> 00:02:02,900
貌似治安维持者的名气要响过某人了
It seems the vigilante's reputation is beginning to precede him.

50
00:02:05,610 --> 00:02:07,180
再来一局
Another round?

51
00:02:08,480 --> 00:02:10,000
不了
No.

52
00:02:12,630 --> 00:02:14,340
我要带我侄子去商场
Gonna take my nephew over to the mall

53
00:02:14,340 --> 00:02:16,260
然后圣诞老人就知道他想要什么礼物了
so he can let Santa know what he wants for Christmas.

54
00:02:16,260 --> 00:02:17,750
圣诞节
Oh. Christmas.

55
00:02:19,680 --> 00:02:20,870
我都没意识到
I didn't even realize.

56
00:02:20,870 --> 00:02:22,980
因为你扮兜帽人花了太多时间
That was because you've been logging in so many hood hours

57
00:02:22,980 --> 00:02:25,030
自从跟海伦娜勾搭上以后
Ever since that thing with Helena.

58
00:02:25,370 --> 00:02:29,440
我是说  岛上没有节日
I meant... There were no holidays on the island.

59
00:02:29,440 --> 00:02:31,520
每天都是...
Every day was...

60
00:02:33,000 --> 00:02:35,020
我怎么活下来的
How do I stay alive?

61
00:02:35,810 --> 00:02:38,410
要做这些事  你得去忘记一些东西
To do that, you had to forget things,

62
00:02:39,110 --> 00:02:40,890
比如圣诞节
Like Christmas.

63
00:02:43,960 --> 00:02:46,750
我爸每年都要办派对
My dad threw a party every year,

64
00:02:46,750 --> 00:02:51,700
每个房间都要放一棵圣诞树
and he would put a Christmas tree in every room.

65
00:02:52,140 --> 00:02:54,700
整个屋子就有一种...
The whole mansion smelled like...

66
00:02:57,170 --> 00:02:59,090
圣诞的气息
It smelled like Christmas.

67
00:03:00,340 --> 00:03:01,560
或许你可以把名单搁一搁
Maybe you can give the list a rest

68
00:03:01,560 --> 00:03:03,880
跟家里人一起享受节日
and just enjoy the holidays with the family.

69
00:03:03,880 --> 00:03:06,900
另外  我听说尼克自己也有一份名单
Besides, I hear Nick has a list of his own.

70
00:03:06,900 --> 00:03:09,240
我赌你在"好人"那栏
I wager you're in the "Nice" Column.

71
00:03:09,990 --> 00:03:11,630
回家过节吧  奥利弗
Go home, Oliver.

72
00:03:29,510 --> 00:03:33,160
你没受伤吧
You not, uh, hurt?

73
00:03:35,740 --> 00:03:37,400
你去哪了啊
Where the hell you been?

74
00:03:38,360 --> 00:03:41,270
我几天前就断水断粮了
I ran out of food and water days ago.

75
00:03:41,770 --> 00:03:44,210
喂  你要去哪
Hey--hey, where are you going?

76
00:03:53,690 --> 00:03:55,170
是你
You--

77
00:03:56,820 --> 00:03:58,170
停手
Stop!

78
00:03:58,170 --> 00:03:59,500
停手
Stop.

79
00:04:00,580 --> 00:04:02,600
就是他绑了我还虐待我
He's the one who tied me up and had me tortured.

80
00:04:02,600 --> 00:04:03,900
全是因为他在找你
All 'cause he was looking for you.

81
00:04:03,910 --> 00:04:06,420
如果你不出现  他已经杀了我
He would've killed me if you didn't show up!

82
00:04:06,420 --> 00:04:08,210
那你来杀他
Then you kill him.

83
00:04:11,330 --> 00:04:13,550
或者他能带你回去
Or he can take you home.

84
00:04:13,950 --> 00:04:15,510
什么
What?

85
00:04:19,480 --> 00:04:21,920
他有飞机
He has a plane.

86
00:04:22,420 --> 00:04:25,450
让你离开这个岛的方法
A way for you off this island.

87
00:04:36,690 --> 00:04:40,060
你看起来真美
Hey. You look very pretty.

88
00:04:40,190 --> 00:04:41,010
有什么大场合吗
What's the occasion?

89
00:04:41,010 --> 00:04:42,900
妈和沃尔特要办一个晚宴
Mom and Walter are having a dinner party

90
00:04:42,900 --> 00:04:45,340
好多大腕会到场
with some big muckety-mucks.

91
00:04:45,460 --> 00:04:47,480
我一生中最棒的夜晚
Best night of my life.

92
00:04:49,370 --> 00:04:52,250
西娅  为什么屋里没有装饰品呢
Thea, why aren't there any decorations up in the house?

93
00:04:52,250 --> 00:04:53,750
什么意思
What do you mean?

94
00:04:53,890 --> 00:04:56,150
没有花环  没有圣诞树
No wreaths, no trees.

95
00:04:56,150 --> 00:04:58,940
大家最近都太忙了
Everyone has just been really busy lately.

96
00:04:58,940 --> 00:05:00,930
我想他们都还没抽时间弄这些
I'm sure they haven't got around to it yet.

97
00:05:00,940 --> 00:05:03,830
妈都没有准备几盒糖果棒吗
Does mom at least have some of those boxes of candy canes?

98
00:05:03,830 --> 00:05:06,380
记不记得我们当年比赛谁先吃完
Remember we used to race to see who'd finish first?

99
00:05:06,390 --> 00:05:08,380
记得  我总赢
Yeah. I always won.

100
00:05:08,380 --> 00:05:10,510
不  你赖皮的
No. You cheated.

101
00:05:10,690 --> 00:05:12,910
她去年开始就不吃糖了
Well, she went sugar-free last year,

102
00:05:12,910 --> 00:05:16,250
恐怕你看不到这些东西了
So I doubt you'll be seeing any of those around.

103
00:05:21,090 --> 00:05:24,280
人们忘了一点  罗宾汉是罪犯
The thing that people forget is that Robin Hood was a criminal.

104
00:05:24,280 --> 00:05:26,330
劫富济贫
And stealing from the rich to give to the poor

105
00:05:26,330 --> 00:05:28,680
明明就是犯罪
is really the job of the democrats.

106
00:05:29,430 --> 00:05:30,700
说正经的  长官
All joking aside, commissioner,

107
00:05:30,700 --> 00:05:32,930
犯罪率五年来第一次下降了
crime is down for the first time in 5 years.

108
00:05:32,930 --> 00:05:36,680
那是因为我们局里的改变开始起效了
That's because of the changes my department has implemented.

109
00:05:36,680 --> 00:05:38,960
或者可能是因为治安维持者的行动
Or perhaps it's because the vigilante's activities

110
00:05:38,960 --> 00:05:42,020
对城市里的罪犯起到了警示作用
have had a chilling effect on the city's criminals.

111
00:05:43,590 --> 00:05:45,400
你怎么看  奥利弗
What are your thoughts, Oliver?

112
00:05:46,790 --> 00:05:50,180
我觉得要给治安维持者取个比"兜帽"好的代号
I think the vigilante needs a better code name than "The hood"

113
00:05:50,180 --> 00:05:51,850
不如叫"兜帽侠"
or "The hood guy."

114
00:05:53,050 --> 00:05:54,230
我同意
I agree.

115
00:05:54,230 --> 00:05:57,220
绿箭侠这个名字怎么样
How about Green Arrow?

116
00:05:57,430 --> 00:05:58,790
逊毙了
Lame.

117
00:06:02,680 --> 00:06:04,120
不好意思
Forgive me.

118
00:06:04,540 --> 00:06:06,180
公司打来的
It's the office.

119
00:06:06,290 --> 00:06:07,780
失陪一下
Excuse me.

120
00:06:09,520 --> 00:06:11,100
我还在聚餐中  斯莫克小姐
I'm in the middle of a dinner party, Ms. Smoak,

121
00:06:11,100 --> 00:06:12,950
所以我希望这件事真的很重要
so I hope this is of some importance.

122
00:06:12,950 --> 00:06:15,270
我想这应该看你怎么定义重要性了
I guess that depends on how you define important.

123
00:06:15,270 --> 00:06:18,460
大多数人会认为找到一本名单
See, most people would consider finding a list of names

124
00:06:18,460 --> 00:06:21,840
用紫外线隐形墨水书写是重点
written in subsonic ultraviolet invisible ink important.

125
00:06:21,840 --> 00:06:23,800
但这我早已知道了  不是吗
But then I already know that, now, don't I?

126
00:06:23,800 --> 00:06:26,320
你知道名单上的七人
Did you know 7 of the names on the list

127
00:06:26,320 --> 00:06:29,290
都在治安维持者的瞄准镜下吗
are guys the vigilante's had in his crosshairs?

128
00:06:29,360 --> 00:06:32,120
当然  如果弓箭也有瞄准镜的话
That is, if bows had crosshairs.

129
00:06:32,120 --> 00:06:33,880
事实上是没有的
which they don't.

130
00:06:34,560 --> 00:06:36,460
这名单挺长的  费利西蒂
Well, it is a rather long list, felicity,

131
00:06:36,460 --> 00:06:38,570
所以有些重复也不足为奇
so I would expect there to be some overlap.

132
00:06:38,570 --> 00:06:39,830
比如道格·米勒
Like Doug Miller.

133
00:06:39,830 --> 00:06:41,130
奎恩联合企业应用科学部门的部长
Head of applied sciences at Queen Consolidated.

134
00:06:41,130 --> 00:06:42,420
他怎么了
What of him?

135
00:06:42,420 --> 00:06:45,530
米勒先生可能会在圣诞长袜里收到一支箭
Mr. Miller may end up getting an arrow in his stocking,

136
00:06:45,560 --> 00:06:47,620
因为他也在名单之列
because he's on the list.

137
00:06:48,360 --> 00:06:52,870
所以这个重要吗
So, important or not?

138
00:07:03,360 --> 00:07:06,310
抱歉  发生了些事情
I'm sorry.  Something's come up.

139
00:07:06,310 --> 00:07:08,040
出什么事儿了
Is everything ok?

140
00:07:08,720 --> 00:07:11,120
治安维持者又行动了
The vigilante has struck again.

141
00:07:11,120 --> 00:07:13,900
他刚才用箭射死了亚当·亨特
He just put an arrow in Adam Hunt.

142
00:07:22,750 --> 00:07:24,960
我得接这通电话  是我的承包商打来的
I really do need to take this call. It's my contractor.

143
00:07:24,960 --> 00:07:26,480
-没事  -失陪
- Of course. - Excuse me.

144
00:07:31,550 --> 00:07:36,180
他女儿到这儿  用钥匙开门  发现她爸
Well, the daughter came over, used her key, found dad.

145
00:07:36,320 --> 00:07:38,420
胸口连中三箭
Hat trick to the chest.

146
00:07:38,830 --> 00:07:40,060
兜帽男
The hood guy.

147
00:07:40,060 --> 00:07:41,720
我一开始也是这么以为
That's what I thought at first.

148
00:07:41,720 --> 00:07:44,100
但这些黑色的箭不是他的一贯作风
But these black arrows aren't consistent with his M.O.

149
00:07:44,100 --> 00:07:45,560
更何况事实上兜帽男
And neither is the fact that the hood

150
00:07:45,560 --> 00:07:48,970
前几个月刚拿走亨特四千万美金
took Hunt for $40 million a few months ago.

151
00:07:48,970 --> 00:07:50,420
又何必现在把他杀掉
It doesn't make sense to kill him now.

152
00:07:50,420 --> 00:07:52,500
事情有些蹊跷
Something doesn't add up.

153
00:07:52,680 --> 00:07:54,900
看来我们要对付一个冒牌货
We're dealing with a copycat.

154
00:08:07,950 --> 00:08:10,800
奎恩工业股份有限公司

155
00:08:10,830 --> 00:08:13,400
谁会用弓箭来杀亚当·亨特呢
Who would kill Adam Hunt with an arrow?

156
00:08:13,910 --> 00:08:15,460
我是说  除你以外
I mean, other than you?

157
00:08:18,320 --> 00:08:19,880
或许是想陷害我
A setup, maybe.

158
00:08:19,890 --> 00:08:22,380
你是说有人为了掩盖杀了亨特的事实
You mean someone looking to cover up killing Hunt

159
00:08:22,380 --> 00:08:23,780
所以把它转嫁成是兜帽男的杰作
by making it look like the work of the hood?

160
00:08:23,780 --> 00:08:25,240
不管他是谁  他很在行
Whoever he was, he's good.

161
00:08:25,240 --> 00:08:27,930
亨特胸口的箭伤非常密集
The grouping on Hunt's chest was tight.

162
00:08:27,930 --> 00:08:29,330
用的应该是复合弓
It's a compound bow, most likely.

163
00:08:29,330 --> 00:08:30,980
这人是个
The guy is a...

164
00:08:32,050 --> 00:08:34,180
这人是个职业弓箭手
The guy's a legitimate archer.

165
00:08:35,410 --> 00:08:36,500
那他应该会选用
So someone who would be particular

166
00:08:36,500 --> 00:08:38,070
特定的弓箭
about his choice of arrows.

167
00:08:38,070 --> 00:08:42,350
我们拿到他的箭  就能查到他在哪儿买的
We get an arrow, we get a bead on where he purchased them.

168
00:08:42,350 --> 00:08:44,050
所以你打算怎么办
So what are you gonna do?

169
00:08:47,940 --> 00:08:50,600
做通常人们需要帮助时候做的事
What anyone does when they need help.

170
00:08:54,750 --> 00:08:56,560
报警
Call a cop.

171
00:08:57,820 --> 00:08:59,570
昆汀·兰斯
Quentin Lance?

172
00:09:01,960 --> 00:09:03,770
请在这儿签名
Sign here, please.

173
00:09:05,990 --> 00:09:07,690
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thanks.  - Thanks.

174
00:09:19,370 --> 00:09:21,260
{\pos(114,66)}无法追踪的号码

175
00:09:27,210 --> 00:09:28,250
兰斯
Lance.

176
00:09:28,260 --> 00:09:29,630
我没杀亚当·亨特
I didn't kill Adam Hunt.

177
00:09:29,630 --> 00:09:30,780
是你
You...

178
00:09:30,780 --> 00:09:33,970
你叫我兜帽男  这昵称真烂
You call me the hood. It's not a great nickname.

179
00:09:33,970 --> 00:09:35,240
你和诺多希多局长说
You told Commissioner Nudocerdo

180
00:09:35,240 --> 00:09:37,340
你们在对付一个冒牌货
that you might be dealing with a copycat,

181
00:09:37,340 --> 00:09:41,050
另一个弓箭手  使我成为你扳倒他的最佳选择
another archer, which makes me your best bet to take him down.

182
00:09:41,050 --> 00:09:42,870
但我需要你的帮助
But I need your help.

183
00:09:43,740 --> 00:09:45,520
我要他凶器中的一支箭
I need one of the arrows from his murder.

184
00:09:45,520 --> 00:09:46,150
我们在追踪线索上
Yeah, we're pretty good

185
00:09:46,150 --> 00:09:47,910
是非常在行的  多谢关心
at pulling down leads off evidence. Thanks.

186
00:09:47,920 --> 00:09:51,890
没我在行  我能做警察做不到的事
Not like I am. I can do things the police can't,

187
00:09:51,900 --> 00:09:53,420
去你们去不了的地方
go places they won't.

188
00:09:53,420 --> 00:09:56,210
我说过了  我都不知道你是
Like I said, I don't even know who--

189
00:09:56,220 --> 00:09:57,750
如果这个弓箭手的目标不止亚当·亨特
If this archer doesn't stop with Adam Hunt,

190
00:09:57,750 --> 00:09:59,280
我们都会有麻烦
we both have a problem.

191
00:09:59,280 --> 00:10:01,050
好好考虑吧
Think about it.

192
00:10:01,730 --> 00:10:03,490
考虑好打给我
Then call me.

193
00:10:03,490 --> 00:10:05,450
电话已经存好了
Number's programmed in.

194
00:10:07,450 --> 00:10:09,460
{\pos(175,154)}奎恩联合企业

195
00:10:12,370 --> 00:10:14,400
道格  多谢你能来
Doug. Thanks for coming.

196
00:10:14,400 --> 00:10:15,620
不用谢
Of course.

197
00:10:15,620 --> 00:10:17,030
应用科学中心的建设
How is the construction coming along

198
00:10:17,040 --> 00:10:18,630
进展如何
on the applied sciences center?

199
00:10:18,630 --> 00:10:20,220
预算超支并且落后于原定计划
Over budget and behind schedule.

200
00:10:20,220 --> 00:10:22,170
不出所料
Exactly as expected.

201
00:10:22,530 --> 00:10:24,480
你想见我就是为了这个吗
Is that what you wanted to see me about?

202
00:10:24,880 --> 00:10:26,360
不
No.

203
00:10:29,150 --> 00:10:33,590
亚当·亨特  他昨晚被治安维持者谋杀了
Adam hunt. He was murdered last night by the vigilante.

204
00:10:33,590 --> 00:10:34,710
我看到新闻了
I read about that.

205
00:10:34,710 --> 00:10:36,010
我有消息称
I've been concerned by the idea

206
00:10:36,010 --> 00:10:38,230
治安维持者可能盯上我们公司的某个员工
that the vigilante might target an employee

207
00:10:38,230 --> 00:10:40,470
或某个管理人员
or officer of this company.

208
00:10:41,090 --> 00:10:43,320
你是头号危险人物
Security red-flagged you.

209
00:10:43,560 --> 00:10:46,610
我  为什么他会来杀我
Me? Why would this guy go after me?

210
00:10:46,610 --> 00:10:49,250
这就是我想让你自己解释清楚的问题了
Well, that's a point I was hoping you could shed some light on.

211
00:10:49,250 --> 00:10:50,610
你难倒我了  据我所知
You got me. From what I've read,

212
00:10:50,610 --> 00:10:52,820
这个治安维持者只盯上那些白领罪犯们
this vigilante only goes after white-collar criminals.

213
00:10:52,820 --> 00:10:56,280
那我们只好希望他届时不会变卦吧
Well, let's just hope he doesn't decide to branch out.

214
00:11:01,470 --> 00:11:03,150
我觉得应该给发明薯条的人
I think there should be a national holiday

215
00:11:03,160 --> 00:11:05,530
一个法定假日
for the guy that invented french fries.

216
00:11:05,850 --> 00:11:08,270
或者至少立个雕像什么的
Or at least a statue or something.

217
00:11:08,990 --> 00:11:13,250
今年没有圣诞派对  对吗
There is no Christmas party, is there?

218
00:11:13,820 --> 00:11:16,570
西娅  爸爸每年都会办一个
Thea, dad threw one of these every year.

219
00:11:16,880 --> 00:11:19,480
所有人都觉得我察觉不到吗
Do people think I just wasn't gonna notice?

220
00:11:19,750 --> 00:11:21,050
嗨  西娅
Hi, Thea.

221
00:11:21,050 --> 00:11:22,850
嗨  肖恩
Hi. Shane.

222
00:11:23,170 --> 00:11:25,200
这是我哥哥奥利弗
This is my brother Oliver.

223
00:11:25,210 --> 00:11:27,070
很高兴见到你  西娅的哥哥
Nice to meet you, Thea's brother.

224
00:11:27,070 --> 00:11:28,400
我打赌那座岛上的美食
I bet the food on that island is better

225
00:11:28,400 --> 00:11:29,910
肯定比这儿的东西好吃多了吧
than this stuff they're serving here, huh?

226
00:11:29,910 --> 00:11:31,960
那你就猜错了
You'd lose that bet.

227
00:11:32,460 --> 00:11:34,760
我们要去海湾走走  如果你想来的话
We're heading down to the bay to hang out if you want to come.

228
00:11:34,760 --> 00:11:38,780
谢了  不过下午我想和哥哥在一起
Thanks, but I'm spending the afternoon with my brother.

229
00:11:39,400 --> 00:11:41,010
那改天吧
Another time.

230
00:11:41,460 --> 00:11:42,990
回见
See ya.

231
00:11:47,690 --> 00:11:49,380
你是怎么认识这个肖恩的
How do you know that Shane guy?

232
00:11:49,380 --> 00:11:51,550
有时我们在一起抢个银行  吸个大麻
We rob banks and smoke crack together.

233
00:11:51,550 --> 00:11:54,350
很好笑  不过我觉得我不会对他有好感
That's funny, yeah. I have a feeling I'm not gonna be a fan.

234
00:11:54,350 --> 00:11:56,360
你还不了解他呢
You don't even know him.

235
00:11:57,050 --> 00:11:59,010
换个话题吧
Let's change the subject.

236
00:11:59,350 --> 00:12:00,660
好  你刚才要告诉我
Fine. You were gonna tell me

237
00:12:00,660 --> 00:12:04,020
今年没有圣诞派对的原因
why we're not having the annual Christmas party.

238
00:12:08,080 --> 00:12:11,440
你和爸爸出事的时候
When you and dad disappeared,

239
00:12:12,470 --> 00:12:14,890
圣诞节来了
by the time Christmas rolled around,

240
00:12:14,890 --> 00:12:16,780
没人想要庆祝节日
none of us felt much like celebrating,

241
00:12:16,780 --> 00:12:21,680
所以那年的圣诞就跳过去了
so we kind of skipped Christmas that year.

242
00:12:22,770 --> 00:12:24,380
之后年年如此
Every year.

243
00:12:25,520 --> 00:12:28,550
其实真的没有什么  所以
And it's really fine, so...

244
00:12:29,330 --> 00:12:33,310
不  不是的
No. No, it's really not.

245
00:12:38,360 --> 00:12:40,020
今年我们来庆祝圣诞
We're celebrating Christmas.

246
00:12:40,020 --> 00:12:42,020
我五年没有过圣诞节了  而西娅告诉我
I went five years without it, and then Thea tells me

247
00:12:42,020 --> 00:12:44,110
你们也没有  原因就在于我
that you guys didn't have it either and I'm the reason.

248
00:12:44,110 --> 00:12:46,940
所以现在可以因为我
So maybe now I can be the reason

249
00:12:46,940 --> 00:12:48,940
我们再次过圣诞
we have Christmas again.

250
00:12:50,040 --> 00:12:53,660
我可以办个奎恩圣诞派对
I thought I would throw the Queen Christmas party.

251
00:12:54,080 --> 00:12:55,570
你吗
You?

252
00:12:55,610 --> 00:12:59,520
我知道我不是一个够格的儿子
I know that I haven't been the son

253
00:12:59,760 --> 00:13:03,480
养子  或是哥哥
or the stepson or the brother that all of you deserve.

254
00:13:03,480 --> 00:13:05,380
尤其基于我最近的表现
Especially lately.

255
00:13:05,380 --> 00:13:08,750
但我觉得现在是个
But this feels like the right moment

256
00:13:08,750 --> 00:13:10,970
开始弥补我们所错过的时光的好时机
to start making up for lost time.

257
00:13:12,300 --> 00:13:13,980
你怎么看
What do you say?

258
00:13:14,880 --> 00:13:15,780
我完全赞同
I say yes.

259
00:13:15,780 --> 00:13:18,090
太好了  我会弄好所有的事
Yes! Ok. I will take care of everything.

260
00:13:18,090 --> 00:13:19,280
你们什么都不用做
You don't have to do anything.

261
00:13:19,280 --> 00:13:24,050
只要带着圣诞好心情  盛装出现就行了
Just show up, look fantastic, and bring some Christmas cheer, ok?

262
00:13:24,050 --> 00:13:25,470
好
Ok.

263
00:13:28,560 --> 00:13:29,890
好吧
Fine.

264
00:13:30,820 --> 00:13:32,640
你是个好人  奥利弗
You're a good man, Oliver.

265
00:13:36,730 --> 00:13:38,350
你是个好人
You're a good man.

266
00:13:38,890 --> 00:13:40,600
我能看出来
I can see it.

267
00:13:41,220 --> 00:13:45,530
在享有特权和养尊处优的外表下
Well, beneath the privileged upbringing and the wealthy veneer.

268
00:13:46,930 --> 00:13:49,290
我的人对你使用酷刑的时候我就看出来了
I saw it when my man tortured you

269
00:13:49,290 --> 00:13:51,400
你不会舍下你的朋友
and you wouldn't give up your friend.

270
00:13:52,120 --> 00:13:54,180
甚至都算不上一个朋友
Not even a friend, really.

271
00:13:54,180 --> 00:13:56,660
-就是一个你刚认识的人  -闭嘴
- Someone you just met. - Shut up.

272
00:13:56,660 --> 00:13:58,480
你对他有多少了解
What do you know him?

273
00:13:59,530 --> 00:14:01,490
我猜  一无所知
Nothing, I suspect.

274
00:14:01,650 --> 00:14:04,610
你知道这座岛的真面目吗
Do you even know what this island really is?

275
00:14:06,410 --> 00:14:10,430
这是一座监狱  我是说真的
It's a prison. I mean this literally.

276
00:14:10,450 --> 00:14:13,880
八年前  中国军队
Until 8 years ago, the Chinese military

277
00:14:13,890 --> 00:14:17,750
把这座岛变成了专门关押
operated this island as a penitentiary

278
00:14:17,750 --> 00:14:20,740
无法在大陆安全监禁的
for criminals deemed so dangerous,

279
00:14:20,740 --> 00:14:24,010
极具危险性的罪犯
they couldn't be safely incarcerated on the mainland.

280
00:14:24,010 --> 00:14:26,390
当军队停止这个计划时
When the military shut the program down,

281
00:14:26,400 --> 00:14:30,110
我的部队来到这里解决了所有的囚犯
my unit came in and disposed of all the inmates.

282
00:14:30,790 --> 00:14:32,780
但有两个人逃了出来
With the exception of two.

283
00:14:33,900 --> 00:14:36,800
你的朋友就是其中一个
Your friend was one of them.

284
00:14:39,660 --> 00:14:40,630
另外一个是谁
Who was the other?

285
00:14:40,630 --> 00:14:42,100
你见过他
You met him.

286
00:14:42,100 --> 00:14:44,420
他负责你的审讯
He presided over your interrogation.

287
00:14:44,420 --> 00:14:45,420
是他折磨的我
He tortured me.

288
00:14:45,430 --> 00:14:47,780
你有我需要的情报
You had information I needed.

289
00:14:47,780 --> 00:14:50,070
如果你是我  你会如何呢
What would you do in my position?

290
00:14:50,140 --> 00:14:51,860
要想抓住一个杀人魔
What would you do to capture the man

291
00:14:51,860 --> 00:14:54,910
你会怎么做呢
who slaughtered dozens of people?

292
00:15:01,570 --> 00:15:05,280
道格拉斯·米勒今天来见我  非常忧心
Douglas Miller came to see me today, quite concerned.

293
00:15:05,410 --> 00:15:07,550
他说你的丈夫询问过他
He said your husband interrogated him,

294
00:15:07,550 --> 00:15:11,420
但由他的提问可以看出
and his questions suggested a knowledge

295
00:15:11,430 --> 00:15:13,270
他应该还没有拿到名单
he shouldn't have of the list.

296
00:15:14,670 --> 00:15:15,810
让我跟他谈谈
Let me talk to him.

297
00:15:15,810 --> 00:15:19,320
我想我们已经过了谈谈那个阶段了吧  莫伊拉
I think we're past the point of conversation, Moira.

298
00:15:19,460 --> 00:15:21,380
一个月前你来找我  让我
A month ago you came to me and you told me

299
00:15:21,380 --> 00:15:24,170
不要碰你的家人  我照做了
to stay away from your family, and I did.

300
00:15:24,630 --> 00:15:27,380
但你的家人却不断靠近我
But your family isn't staying away from me.

301
00:15:28,050 --> 00:15:30,740
我应该有所行动了
Which means something must be done about it.

302
00:15:32,100 --> 00:15:33,280
你不同意吗
Don't you agree?

303
00:15:33,280 --> 00:15:34,800
是的  我同意
Yes, I do.

304
00:15:34,800 --> 00:15:36,100
我会处理这件事
And I'll handle it.

305
00:15:36,100 --> 00:15:37,860
我猜我想知道的是
I guess what I'm wondering is,

306
00:15:37,870 --> 00:15:41,290
是不是该我们的联盟出手的时候了
whether it's time for our associate to handle it.

307
00:15:44,730 --> 00:15:47,460
废话  当然了  我已经把钱还了
Hell, yeah, I returned the money.

308
00:15:47,520 --> 00:15:52,040
为了七亿美金可不值得胸前挨一支箭
$70 million isn't worth getting an arrow through the chest.

309
00:15:52,040 --> 00:15:55,610
你告诉他  如果有意见  他可以
And you can tell him, if he's got a problem with that, he can--

310
00:16:04,500 --> 00:16:07,540
长官  这是尼尔森·拉维奇
Commissioner, this is Nelson Ravich.

311
00:16:07,540 --> 00:16:09,180
兜帽男于本周前几天袭击了他
The hood hit him earlier this week.

312
00:16:09,180 --> 00:16:10,040
拉维奇遭袭之后不到五分钟
Ravich wired back the

313
00:16:10,040 --> 00:16:12,650
就把他骗的钱转交回去了
money he embezzled less than 5 minutes later.

314
00:16:21,200 --> 00:16:23,450
我们告知媒体这是兜帽男做的
We tell the press the hood did this.

315
00:16:23,490 --> 00:16:27,620
亨特杀人事件只是不足为奇的小事件
Hunt's murder is a page 10 story, at best.

316
00:16:27,620 --> 00:16:31,290
但拉维奇的死已让它上升到连环杀人事件
But Ravich makes this a serial murder case.

317
00:16:31,440 --> 00:16:33,870
我们不能让公众知道
We can't let the public get wind of the idea

318
00:16:33,870 --> 00:16:36,530
有两个这样难对付的凶手逍遥法外
that there are two of these nut jobs running around.

319
00:16:36,530 --> 00:16:38,280
你想让我放过一个连环杀手
You want me to ignore a serial killer.

320
00:16:38,280 --> 00:16:41,370
抓到其中一个疯子就好  我不管是哪个
Just catch one of these psychos. I don't care which one.

321
00:16:41,380 --> 00:16:44,900
这是你长官的直接命令
That is a direct order from your commanding officer.

322
00:16:47,030 --> 00:16:49,060
那就算了吧
Well, you can forget it, then.

323
00:16:51,610 --> 00:16:53,070
好吧
Fine.

324
00:16:53,070 --> 00:16:54,670
算了就算了
It's forgotten.

325
00:16:55,230 --> 00:16:57,560
你也不再负责本案了  警官
And you're off this case, Sergeant,

326
00:16:57,560 --> 00:16:59,570
即刻奏效
effective immediately.

327
00:17:28,730 --> 00:17:30,420
别想通过电话追踪到我
Don't bother trying to trace this back to me.

328
00:17:30,420 --> 00:17:31,990
你们破解不了这个加密信号的
You'll never make it through the encryption.

329
00:17:31,990 --> 00:17:35,970
在欧尼尔·亚当斯街角有个散热口
There's a heating vent on the corner of O'Neil and Adams.

330
00:17:36,110 --> 00:17:38,080
在那儿你会找到你想要的
You'll find what you want after there.

331
00:17:38,080 --> 00:17:41,070
设陷阱抓我是个错误  警探
It'd be a mistake to set a trap for me, detective.

332
00:17:41,070 --> 00:17:43,100
我把这里的一切都告诉你
I'm trading away just about everything I believe in here

333
00:17:43,100 --> 00:17:45,450
因为这是能抓到那混蛋的唯一方法
'cause it's the only way I've got to get this bastard.

334
00:17:45,450 --> 00:17:46,990
期限是圣诞节
You got till Christmas.

335
00:17:46,990 --> 00:17:49,370
那之后  无论有没有冒牌货
And then, copycat or not...

336
00:17:50,570 --> 00:17:52,550
我都会开始追捕你
I'm coming after you.

337
00:17:57,160 --> 00:18:00,380
奎恩工业股份有限公司
钢铁制造与焊接

338
00:18:04,620 --> 00:18:07,640
你朋友兰斯最后还是送了你圣诞节礼物
So your friend Lance gave you a Christmas present after all.

339
00:18:10,550 --> 00:18:14,140
特弗伦涂层钛合金刀片足以断骨
Teflon-coated titanium blade serrated to split the bone.

340
00:18:14,140 --> 00:18:17,290
箭柄是种特质聚合物
Shaft is some type of specialized polymer,

341
00:18:17,290 --> 00:18:19,420
比普通碳纤维更强劲
which is stronger than a typical carbon fiber.

342
00:18:19,420 --> 00:18:22,980
这个  这是专门定制的
This...This is a custom job.

343
00:18:22,980 --> 00:18:23,960
是在另一个弓箭手
So Lance gave in after

344
00:18:23,960 --> 00:18:25,440
扔下另一具尸体后  兰斯给你的
the other archer dropped another body.

345
00:18:25,440 --> 00:18:26,530
尼尔森·拉维奇
Nelson Ravich,

346
00:18:26,530 --> 00:18:28,340
是你划掉的
which is another name

347
00:18:28,360 --> 00:18:30,910
你父亲名单上的另一个名字
you crossed off your dad's list.

348
00:18:31,900 --> 00:18:34,600
那这人是不是想陷害你或引你出来
So is this guy trying to frame you or call you out?

349
00:18:35,950 --> 00:18:39,720
不管怎样  我都得找到他
Either way, I need to find him.

350
00:18:57,320 --> 00:18:58,200
你不会敲门吗
Don't you knock?

351
00:18:58,200 --> 00:19:01,100
费利西蒂  这是技术部门
Felicity, this is the I.T. Department.

352
00:19:01,290 --> 00:19:02,860
又不是女卫生间
It's not the ladies room.

353
00:19:02,860 --> 00:19:04,310
是啊
Right.

354
00:19:05,660 --> 00:19:06,750
我能帮你什么
What can I do for you?

355
00:19:06,750 --> 00:19:09,620
我朋友斯蒂夫很喜欢箭术
My buddy Steve is really into archery.

356
00:19:09,620 --> 00:19:12,660
很明显眼下这很流行
Apparently it's all the rage now.

357
00:19:12,660 --> 00:19:16,060
我也不懂为什么  在我看来这很荒谬
I don't know why. It's looks utterly ridiculous to me.

358
00:19:17,190 --> 00:19:19,410
下周末是斯蒂夫的生日
Anyway, it's Steve's birthday next weekend,

359
00:19:19,420 --> 00:19:21,350
我想给他买些箭
and I wanted to buy him some arrows.

360
00:19:21,350 --> 00:19:26,310
问题是  他用的是特制的箭
The thing is, he gets these special custom-made arrows,

361
00:19:26,310 --> 00:19:30,760
我不知道他在哪买的
and I have no idea where he gets them.

362
00:19:32,020 --> 00:19:35,320
我希望你可以查出这是哪来的
I was hoping you could find out where this came from.

363
00:19:37,220 --> 00:19:39,330
小心点
Careful.

364
00:19:46,370 --> 00:19:49,070
箭柄的合成材料是有专利的
The shaft's composite is patented.

365
00:19:55,580 --> 00:19:59,120
那个专利是萨迪特里斯公司注册的
And that patent is registered to a company called Sagittarius.

366
00:19:59,120 --> 00:20:01,950
-拉丁文里是弓箭手的意思  -真的吗
- That's Latin for the archer. - Really?

367
00:20:02,500 --> 00:20:04,740
你能找到这是
Could you find out where and when

368
00:20:04,740 --> 00:20:06,530
何时何地购买的吗
this was purchased?

369
00:20:10,760 --> 00:20:12,640
根据萨迪特里斯公司的记录
According to Sagittarius company records,

370
00:20:12,640 --> 00:20:16,880
这种箭是成批卖出的
that particular arrow was part of a bundle shipment.

371
00:20:17,610 --> 00:20:19,440
有200只
200 units.

372
00:20:20,180 --> 00:20:21,790
发到了
Sent...

373
00:20:23,340 --> 00:20:24,290
这个地址
to this address.

374
00:20:24,290 --> 00:20:25,790
费利西蒂
Felicity...

375
00:20:28,990 --> 00:20:30,770
你太棒了
you're remarkable.

376
00:20:31,120 --> 00:20:33,200
谢谢你这么说
Thank you for remarking on it.

377
00:20:35,010 --> 00:20:36,860
还有圣诞节快乐
And merry Christmas.

378
00:20:37,050 --> 00:20:38,600
我是犹太人
I'm Jewish.

379
00:20:41,070 --> 00:20:42,770
光明节快乐
Happy Hanukkah.

380
00:20:46,660 --> 00:20:50,390
星城警署的大量资料显示
According to the significant resources of the Starling City Police Department

381
00:20:50,400 --> 00:20:55,160
这个治安维护者的罪行正在扩大
it is clear that this Vigilante's cycle of violence has escalated.

382
00:20:55,160 --> 00:20:58,340
我呼吁市民密切关注此案
I'm asking our citizens to keep a close eye out

383
00:20:58,340 --> 00:21:01,280
并报告任何可疑事件
and to report anything suspicious.

384
00:21:01,280 --> 00:21:02,710
匿名热线已成立
A tip line has been set up,

385
00:21:02,710 --> 00:21:04,920
对于协助警方
and a reward will be offered

386
00:21:04,920 --> 00:21:07,140
抓捕凶手的人
to anyone who aids the authorities

387
00:21:07,150 --> 00:21:09,760
我们将给予奖励
in the capture of this madman.

388
00:21:10,670 --> 00:21:11,750
这不是他  对吗
It isn't him, is it?

389
00:21:11,750 --> 00:21:13,920
我们都在为城市的犯罪事件备受折磨
We are all frustrated with the crime plaguing our city.

390
00:21:13,920 --> 00:21:15,740
兜帽男并没有杀那些人
The man in the hood didn't kill those people.

391
00:21:17,740 --> 00:21:19,250
是你说他是个魔头的
You're the one who said he was a monster.

392
00:21:20,650 --> 00:21:22,230
那时他是为了保护我
He was protecting me.

393
00:21:23,130 --> 00:21:23,860
那不一样
It's different.

394
00:21:23,860 --> 00:21:26,890
这个所谓"兜帽男"
The apprehension of this so-called "Hood"

395
00:21:26,580 --> 00:21:29,640
{\pos(139,208)}星城警署高清频道

396
00:21:27,290 --> 00:21:29,810
在恐怖袭击我们的城市
that has been terrorizing our city.

397
00:21:31,020 --> 00:21:32,190
正如警署长官
As police commissioner...

398
00:21:32,190 --> 00:21:33,420
估计是乔安娜
It's probably Joanna.

399
00:21:34,410 --> 00:21:36,240
她说要来送些文件
She said she was going to come by with some files.

400
00:21:45,330 --> 00:21:46,500
圣诞节快乐  先生
Merry Christmas, Sir.

401
00:21:46,810 --> 00:21:47,870
你好吗
How are you?

402
00:21:47,870 --> 00:21:49,150
玩枪一门灵
Proficient with firearms.

403
00:21:50,990 --> 00:21:52,100
爸爸
Dad.

404
00:21:55,170 --> 00:21:57,510
我告诉过你我想和我爸过节了
I told you I wanted to spend the holidays with my dad.

405
00:21:57,510 --> 00:21:58,760
没错  因为莎拉
Right. Because of Sara.

406
00:21:58,760 --> 00:22:00,810
因为她的死让过节变得很痛苦
Because it makes the holidays a tough time.

407
00:22:01,950 --> 00:22:03,410
但是如果你和某个人在一起
But when you are with someone,

408
00:22:03,890 --> 00:22:05,270
就像我想和你在一起一样
as I want to be with you,

409
00:22:05,280 --> 00:22:06,490
那样的话就不是难熬的日子
then there aren't tough times.

410
00:22:06,490 --> 00:22:08,100
只是普通的日子而已
There's just times.

411
00:22:11,030 --> 00:22:12,360
你还受过去一些事的牵绊
Something is holding you back.

412
00:22:15,250 --> 00:22:18,280
奎恩家要举办圣诞派对
The Queens are having a last-minute Christmas party,

413
00:22:18,280 --> 00:22:20,690
我想让你当我的女伴
and I would like for you to be my plus one.

414
00:22:24,000 --> 00:22:28,230
我翻老照片的时候
I, um, was looking through some old photographs

415
00:22:28,230 --> 00:22:30,870
发现了这个
and...I found this.

416
00:22:32,200 --> 00:22:33,480
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.

417
00:22:40,750 --> 00:22:41,950
你跟这个人做朋友就已经够了
Bad enough you're friends with this guy,

418
00:22:41,950 --> 00:22:43,990
现在他这是算你的...什么
and now he's your...what?

419
00:22:44,870 --> 00:22:46,220
我也不知道他算什么
I don't know what he is.

420
00:22:46,390 --> 00:22:47,680
但是他说对了
But he's not wrong.

421
00:22:48,750 --> 00:22:50,270
有些事仍然牵绊着我
Something is holding me back.

422
00:22:51,500 --> 00:22:53,710
对  你就继续听他胡说吧
Right. Keep listening to that something.

423
00:22:54,890 --> 00:22:57,360
我尽量不干涉你的私生活  劳蕾尔
I try to stay out of your personal life, Laurel,

424
00:22:57,360 --> 00:22:58,440
我真不想干涉  但是梅林  奎恩这种人...
I really do, but these guys-- Merlyn, Queen--

425
00:22:58,450 --> 00:23:00,590
他们为人自私  以为可以为所欲为的
I mean, they're selfish. They think they can treat people

426
00:23:00,590 --> 00:23:01,960
对待别人
any way they damn please.

427
00:23:02,410 --> 00:23:03,760
是你  我  还有莎拉
It's you, me, and Sarah.

428
00:23:03,870 --> 00:23:04,990
什么
What?

429
00:24:51,670 --> 00:24:53,000
大厅装饰一新了
I see the halls are decked.

430
00:24:53,230 --> 00:24:54,310
你没事吧
You OK?

431
00:24:54,820 --> 00:24:55,920
我能应付
I'll manage.

432
00:24:56,070 --> 00:24:57,350
大家都还开心吧
Is everyone having a good time?

433
00:24:57,470 --> 00:24:58,950
你确定你要这样做吗  兄弟
You sure you want to do this, man?

434
00:24:59,420 --> 00:25:00,580
或许现在不是
Maybe now is not the best time

435
00:25:00,580 --> 00:25:02,080
当玛莎·斯图尔特的精灵的最好时机
for you to be Martha Stewart's elf.

436
00:25:02,240 --> 00:25:03,950
我的家人需要这个派对  狄格尔
My family needs this party, Diggle.

437
00:25:04,510 --> 00:25:05,890
也就是说我需要
Which means that I need it.

438
00:25:10,040 --> 00:25:12,490
嗨  老兄  西娅邀请我来的
Hey, dude. Thea invited me.

439
00:25:12,490 --> 00:25:13,760
希望你不会介意
I hope that's cool.

440
00:25:15,350 --> 00:25:16,590
这是给你母亲的
These are for your mom.

441
00:25:18,570 --> 00:25:19,820
真圆滑
Smooth.

442
00:25:21,460 --> 00:25:22,660
祝你好运  孩子
Good luck, kid.

443
00:25:27,310 --> 00:25:28,090
谢谢你能过来
Thank you for coming.

444
00:25:28,090 --> 00:25:29,190
奥利弗
Oliver.

445
00:25:30,040 --> 00:25:31,210
你们看上去很棒
You guys look great.

446
00:25:31,470 --> 00:25:32,410
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.

447
00:25:32,420 --> 00:25:33,490
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.

448
00:25:33,640 --> 00:25:34,970
我们拍张节日照吧
Let's get a holiday photo.

449
00:25:35,430 --> 00:25:37,920
我已经把圣诞贺卡寄出去了  奥利弗
I already sent out our Christmas cards, Oliver.

450
00:25:37,920 --> 00:25:39,910
妈  就拍一张我们四个人的纪念照
Mom, let's get a picture just for the 4 of us.

451
00:25:40,390 --> 00:25:41,500
当然
Of course.

452
00:25:45,210 --> 00:25:47,660
你好  奎恩夫人  这是给您的
Excuse me. Mrs. Queen? These are for you.

453
00:25:48,030 --> 00:25:49,420
谢谢
Well, thank you.

454
00:25:49,420 --> 00:25:51,630
我去把花放进水里
I'll--I'll go put this in water.

455
00:25:54,180 --> 00:25:55,380
一切都还好吗
Is everything all right?

456
00:25:55,850 --> 00:25:57,190
我们需要单独谈谈
You and I should talk alone.

457
00:26:03,480 --> 00:26:05,190
你们两个人之间没事吧
Everything OK between the two of you?

458
00:26:05,390 --> 00:26:07,460
没事  会解决的
Yeah. I'm sure it'll work itself out.

459
00:26:25,860 --> 00:26:28,110
真高兴你们两个人都能来
So glad that both of you could make it.

460
00:26:29,150 --> 00:26:30,990
-圣诞快乐  兄弟 -圣诞快乐
- Merry Christmas, man. - Merry Christmas.

461
00:26:33,470 --> 00:26:35,680
-圣诞快乐 -嗨
- Merry Christmas. - Hi.

462
00:26:37,950 --> 00:26:39,460
你们觉得这种奇怪的氛围
So how long do you guys think it'll be

463
00:26:39,460 --> 00:26:40,700
还要持续多久
till this isn't so weird?

464
00:26:40,960 --> 00:26:42,240
我们三个之间的这种
You know, the 3 of us.

465
00:26:42,240 --> 00:26:43,440
其实并不奇怪
It's not weird at all.

466
00:27:00,330 --> 00:27:01,750
你骗了我
You lied to me.

467
00:27:03,010 --> 00:27:04,620
你这是从何说起
An odd accusation coming from you.

468
00:27:05,890 --> 00:27:07,810
你回来的时候说  你不会
When you came home, you said you were through

469
00:27:07,810 --> 00:27:09,600
再调查罗伯特的死因了
investigating Robert's death.

470
00:27:10,160 --> 00:27:11,490
罗伯特是我的老朋友
Robert was my oldest friend.

471
00:27:13,480 --> 00:27:14,920
你以为我是那种
Do you take me for a man

472
00:27:14,930 --> 00:27:17,530
不为自己的挚友报仇的人吗
who wouldn't avenge his best friend's murder?

473
00:27:26,060 --> 00:27:27,460
我以为我会忘记这件事
I thought I could forget about it,

474
00:27:27,940 --> 00:27:29,410
回到正轨
go back to the way things were.

475
00:27:29,770 --> 00:27:31,770
但是你骗了我太多次了  莫伊拉
But you told me too many lies, Moira.

476
00:27:33,470 --> 00:27:35,010
你挪用公司资金
You embezzled money from the company.

477
00:27:35,920 --> 00:27:38,580
打捞"金牌奎恩"号沉船  为什么  莫伊拉
Salvaged the Queen's Gambit. Why, Moira?

478
00:27:39,910 --> 00:27:41,130
到底是为了什么
What was it all for?

479
00:27:42,770 --> 00:27:44,090
为了对付别人
For leverage.

480
00:27:44,760 --> 00:27:45,890
对付谁
Against whom?

481
00:27:46,940 --> 00:27:48,040
到底是谁
Against whom?

482
00:27:48,040 --> 00:27:49,620
你惹怒的那些人
People who you made very angry.

483
00:27:49,750 --> 00:27:51,340
那就让我帮你对抗他们
Well, then let me help you fight them.

484
00:27:51,340 --> 00:27:52,620
我不能对抗他们
I can't fight them.

485
00:27:52,990 --> 00:27:54,280
我也是他们的一员
I am them.

486
00:27:56,160 --> 00:27:59,400
我一直很努力地让自己相信我不是其中一员
I have tried so hard to convince myself that I'm not.

487
00:27:59,400 --> 00:28:00,580
一心去爱你...
And loving you...

488
00:28:04,820 --> 00:28:06,190
是你拯救了我
You were my salvation.

489
00:28:09,750 --> 00:28:10,810
莫伊拉
Moira.

490
00:28:11,220 --> 00:28:12,200
莫伊拉
Moira.

491
00:28:13,140 --> 00:28:14,220
不管你做过什么
Whatever you've done,

492
00:28:14,880 --> 00:28:16,290
不论他们是什么人
and whoever these people are,

493
00:28:18,350 --> 00:28:19,660
都不要再说谎了
the time for lies is over.

494
00:28:21,930 --> 00:28:24,140
你需要告诉我到底发生了什么
You need to tell me exactly what's going on.

495
00:28:27,480 --> 00:28:28,890
我们先去参加派对
Let's just get through the party...

496
00:28:31,200 --> 00:28:33,070
派对结束后我一定把一切都告诉你
and I promise I will tell you everything.

497
00:28:42,330 --> 00:28:44,450
汤米  我想跟奥利弗谈谈可以吗
Tommy, do you mind if I talk to Oliver for a minute?

498
00:28:44,920 --> 00:28:46,770
好  我去拿点喝的
Yeah, I'll go grab us a couple drinks.

499
00:28:47,140 --> 00:28:48,410
然后自己都喝掉
And drink them both.

500
00:28:51,250 --> 00:28:52,270
我知道你看到我和汤米在一起
I know it's probably not

501
00:28:52,270 --> 00:28:54,280
可能不好过
easy for you to see Tommy and I together.

502
00:28:54,340 --> 00:28:56,040
请柬上说要带女伴
Ah, the invitation said "Plus one",

503
00:28:56,740 --> 00:28:58,060
又没说不准带劳蕾尔
Not minus Laurel.

504
00:28:59,900 --> 00:29:02,020
我一直想和他重新开始生活
I've been wanting to move forward with him,

505
00:29:02,020 --> 00:29:03,560
但有些问题总是困扰着我
but something's been holding me back.

506
00:29:04,670 --> 00:29:06,000
我一直不停找借口
I keep making these excuses;

507
00:29:06,000 --> 00:29:08,080
我爸的原因
That it's my dad,

508
00:29:08,080 --> 00:29:10,430
工作的原因  直到我意识到
it's my work, when really...

509
00:29:12,790 --> 00:29:13,830
是因为你
it's you.

510
00:29:15,490 --> 00:29:16,700
但五年过去了
But for five years,

511
00:29:16,700 --> 00:29:18,020
我不再
I was emotionally...off,

512
00:29:20,560 --> 00:29:22,290
为此纠缠  因为你死了
off, because you had died.

513
00:29:25,290 --> 00:29:26,550
事实上
And the truth is,

514
00:29:27,730 --> 00:29:29,340
最让我没想到的那个人
the last person that I expected

515
00:29:29,340 --> 00:29:31,460
却让我又重新燃起
to make me feel again...

516
00:29:33,360 --> 00:29:34,360
对感情的希望
Has.

517
00:29:42,710 --> 00:29:43,780
我很高兴
I'm happy.

518
00:29:45,340 --> 00:29:46,630
为你们两个
For both of you.

519
00:29:48,850 --> 00:29:50,040
谢谢你
Thank you.

520
00:30:02,710 --> 00:30:04,330
西娅  有件事情想让你知道
Thea, it's something to tell you.

521
00:30:06,610 --> 00:30:07,680
奥利弗
Oliver!

522
00:30:09,960 --> 00:30:11,010
赶紧滚
Hit the road.

523
00:30:13,380 --> 00:30:14,630
你在干什么
What are you doing?

524
00:30:15,170 --> 00:30:17,090
有趣的是  我想问你同样的事
Funny, I was going to ask you the same thing,

525
00:30:17,090 --> 00:30:18,770
因为楼下是我特地为你准备的
Because there's a party going on downstairs

526
00:30:18,810 --> 00:30:20,410
派对
that I threw for you.

527
00:30:20,440 --> 00:30:22,770
我告诉过你  我不想要什么派对
I told you, I didn't want a party.

528
00:30:23,460 --> 00:30:24,790
可你不听
But you didn't care.

529
00:30:24,870 --> 00:30:27,260
因为你有假日综合症
Because you came down with the holiday blues.

530
00:30:28,220 --> 00:30:31,140
几个月来我都想让你对我敞开心扉
I've been trying to get you to open up for months.

531
00:30:31,670 --> 00:30:33,800
这个派对就是为了让我们回忆过往
All this party is doing is bringing back memories

532
00:30:33,800 --> 00:30:35,270
那些我一直试图忘记的过往
I've been trying to forget.

533
00:30:35,270 --> 00:30:36,250
西娅
Thea!

534
00:30:37,150 --> 00:30:39,080
你为什么想忘掉呢
Why would you want to forget?

535
00:30:40,310 --> 00:30:42,620
无论你这场派对有多精彩
No matter how fancy the party is you throw,

536
00:30:43,280 --> 00:30:46,330
都不可能还原我们破裂的家庭
things will never be the way they used to be in our family.

537
00:30:47,150 --> 00:30:48,440
永远也不会
Ever again.

538
00:30:50,510 --> 00:30:51,480
奥利弗
Oliver?

539
00:30:55,420 --> 00:30:56,440
又怎么了
What is it now?

540
00:30:58,950 --> 00:31:00,750
那个弓箭手开始行动了
The other Archer's moved to the next level.

541
00:31:00,820 --> 00:31:03,670
他挟持了人质  新闻刚刚转播
He's taken hostages. This just hit the news.

542
00:31:04,310 --> 00:31:06,490
节日快乐  星城
Happy holidays, Starling City.

543
00:31:08,370 --> 00:31:09,640
过去三个月
For the past three months,

544
00:31:09,640 --> 00:31:12,230
这座城市一直被不明势力围困
this city has been laid siege by a vigilante.

545
00:31:12,890 --> 00:31:15,720
警察却无法将之就法
But the police have been unable to bring him to justice

546
00:31:15,720 --> 00:31:18,370
他们辜负了身兼正义的使命
Because they lack the will to do what justice demands.

547
00:31:21,670 --> 00:31:23,310
每小时我都会以他的名义
I will kill one hostage...

548
00:31:24,210 --> 00:31:26,530
杀掉一个人质
every hour in the name of this vigilante

549
00:31:26,930 --> 00:31:30,080
直到他向相关机构自首为止
until he surrenders himself to my authority.

550
00:31:34,350 --> 00:31:35,420
警察在现场  奥利弗
Police are on the scene, Oliver.

551
00:31:35,420 --> 00:31:36,320
我认为你应该让他们去处理
I think you should let them handle this.

552
00:31:36,320 --> 00:31:38,890
那些人会因我而被杀  我必须去做个了结
Those people are there because of me. I have to end this.

553
00:31:38,890 --> 00:31:39,970
奥利弗  这个人
Oliver, this guy...

554
00:31:41,540 --> 00:31:42,910
这个人  非常危险
This guy, he's very dangerous.

555
00:31:42,910 --> 00:31:44,280
狄格  那个岛 比这个
Diggle, there wasn't anything on the island

556
00:31:44,280 --> 00:31:46,370
暴徒险恶多了
that wasn't twice as dangerous as this pretender,

557
00:31:46,370 --> 00:31:48,490
而我却在那活了五年
and I survived there for five years.

558
00:31:58,030 --> 00:31:59,090
通知你的人
Call your people.

559
00:31:59,110 --> 00:32:00,530
告诉他们把飞机带来
Tell them to bring the plane.

560
00:32:01,910 --> 00:32:03,070
没这个必要  姚飞
There's no need, Yao Fei.

561
00:32:03,200 --> 00:32:04,830
我的人很快就会出现的
My people will be here shortly.

562
00:32:06,610 --> 00:32:09,190
你不觉得你抓到我也太过容易了吗
Do you not think it convenient you captured me so easily?

563
00:32:11,570 --> 00:32:12,340
快走
Go!

564
00:32:12,340 --> 00:32:13,480
-什么  -快跑
- What?  - Run!

565
00:33:00,250 --> 00:33:01,630
星城由于人质事件
Starling City holds its breath

566
00:33:01,630 --> 00:33:03,500
陷入空前恐慌
as the hostage crisis unfolds.

567
00:33:03,720 --> 00:33:04,550
警察试图
Police have attempted to

568
00:33:04,550 --> 00:33:06,880
进入林中空地上的废弃建筑
enter the abandoned structure in the glades,

569
00:33:06,900 --> 00:33:09,990
却被爆炸装置挡住了去路
but found rigged explosives preventing them from doing so.

570
00:33:10,310 --> 00:33:12,010
目前  没有迹象表明
At the moment, there's been no sign

571
00:33:12,010 --> 00:33:14,840
守护者会在一小时内出现
of the vigilante as his one hour deadline nears.

572
00:33:21,990 --> 00:33:23,380
我看见三个爆炸装置
I count three thresholds,

573
00:33:23,600 --> 00:33:26,880
每条线都连着水银起爆器引发的塑胶炸药
each wired by mercury switches to semtex charges.

574
00:33:27,340 --> 00:33:30,220
你能排解一个装置作为突破口吗
Can you diffuse one for hrc to use as a breach point?

575
00:33:30,370 --> 00:33:31,200
那需要花一些时间
Well, that's going to take a while

576
00:33:31,200 --> 00:33:32,810
这样的话他就知道我们从哪进去了
And then he's going to know which way we're coming in.

577
00:33:32,810 --> 00:33:34,280
你有更好的主意吗  警官
You got a better idea, sergeant,

578
00:33:34,280 --> 00:33:35,710
现在是绝美的机会
Now would be a lovely time.

579
00:33:52,550 --> 00:33:53,420
他在哪
Where is he?

580
00:33:53,420 --> 00:33:54,190
我们不知道
We don't know.

581
00:33:54,190 --> 00:33:55,350
马上就没事了
It's going to be ok.

582
00:33:55,610 --> 00:33:56,710
跟着我
Follow me.

583
00:34:06,760 --> 00:34:07,830
快上楼顶
Get up on the roof.

584
00:34:09,900 --> 00:34:11,750
-你怎么办  -我来对付他  快走
- What about...  - I'll handle him. Move!

585
00:34:13,390 --> 00:34:14,260
人质
Hostages.

586
00:34:14,260 --> 00:34:15,720
屋顶上有五个人质
We've got five hostages on the roof.

587
00:34:15,720 --> 00:34:17,910
再说一遍  屋顶上有五个人质
Repeat, five hostages on the roof.

588
00:34:25,870 --> 00:34:26,940
你能来太好了
Thank you for coming.

589
00:34:27,750 --> 00:34:29,480
仓库一别后  我知道必须
After the warehouse, I knew I'd have to do

590
00:34:29,480 --> 00:34:31,470
做些极端的事吸引你的主意
something dramatic to get your attention.

591
00:34:31,830 --> 00:34:32,990
你到底想从我这里得到什么
What do you want with me?

592
00:34:33,100 --> 00:34:37,040
弓箭手想做的事  当然是想看看谁更快了
What any archer wants-- to see who's better.

593
00:35:25,600 --> 00:35:27,740
先是亨特  然后是拉维奇
First Hunt, then Ravich,

594
00:35:27,990 --> 00:35:29,260
现在该你了
and now you.

595
00:35:34,090 --> 00:35:35,400
我知道名单的事
I know about the list,

596
00:35:35,560 --> 00:35:38,120
以及名单的所有者希望你死
And the man who authored it wants you dead.

597
00:35:39,530 --> 00:35:40,800
他们叫你兜帽侠
They call you the hood.

598
00:35:41,060 --> 00:35:42,870
我来看看你的真实面目
Let's see what you look like without it.

599
00:36:14,520 --> 00:36:15,580
狄格
Dig.

600
00:36:17,730 --> 00:36:19,170
救命  救命
Help--help.

601
00:36:31,650 --> 00:36:33,790
放轻松  放轻松  放松就好
Hey, relax. Relax. Just relax.

602
00:36:33,790 --> 00:36:35,590
你安全了  现在在医院里
You're safe. You're in the hospital.

603
00:36:38,200 --> 00:36:39,110
发生了什么
What happened?

604
00:36:39,110 --> 00:36:40,500
我反追踪到你的信号
I back traced your signal.

605
00:36:40,500 --> 00:36:42,260
救起你  把你带到这儿
I cleaned you up and got you out of there.

606
00:36:42,260 --> 00:36:43,000
你现在有气胸
You've got a pneumothorax,

607
00:36:43,000 --> 00:36:44,730
三根肋骨骨折  还有点脑震荡
three broken ribs and a concussion,

608
00:36:44,730 --> 00:36:46,290
但医生说你会好起来的
but the doctor said you're going to be fine.

609
00:36:47,160 --> 00:36:49,140
-有些人来看望你了  -什么
- Some people are here to see you. - What?

610
00:36:53,550 --> 00:36:54,640
你还好吗
Are you all right?

611
00:36:54,740 --> 00:36:56,180
天啊  你看起来真憔悴
Oh, God, you look terrible.

612
00:36:56,550 --> 00:36:58,380
幸亏你当时戴了头盔
Well, thank God you were wearing your helmet.

613
00:36:58,640 --> 00:37:00,110
我告诉他们了  你骑摩托的时候
I told them how you were on a bike

614
00:37:00,110 --> 00:37:01,480
撞上前方一辆突然刹车的大卡车
and a semi pulled right in front of you.

615
00:37:03,520 --> 00:37:04,730
你为什么跑出去了呢
What were you even doing out?

616
00:37:04,730 --> 00:37:06,270
你连自己的派对都要逃脱
You bailed on your own party.

617
00:37:06,950 --> 00:37:08,070
看起来倒是没做错啊
It seemed like the right move.

618
00:37:08,070 --> 00:37:10,190
就像你说的
I mean, like you said,

619
00:37:10,190 --> 00:37:12,360
那不是最佳时机
It...wasn't the best timing.

620
00:37:14,910 --> 00:37:16,890
好吧  但我说那番话的时候
Ok, but when I was saying that,

621
00:37:17,980 --> 00:37:19,250
我其实是在发牢骚
that was me being a bitch.

622
00:37:19,690 --> 00:37:23,420
事实是我们每个人都不在最佳状态
Oh, the truth is, I don't think any of us were at our best.

623
00:37:23,630 --> 00:37:25,450
其实你是想办一个派对
The real truth is, you wanted to have

624
00:37:25,450 --> 00:37:27,110
来凝聚起我们这个家
a party to bring us closer together.

625
00:37:30,380 --> 00:37:31,470
现在我们一家都在这儿了
Here we are.

626
00:37:35,890 --> 00:37:37,900
我们让你好好休息一会儿
We're going to let you get some rest, hmm?

627
00:37:48,410 --> 00:37:49,440
话说
So...

628
00:37:50,450 --> 00:37:52,870
我们还是没能交换礼物
We never got to the exchanging presents part.

629
00:37:54,510 --> 00:37:56,250
我觉得我不配拿礼物了
I don't think I deserve a present.

630
00:37:56,920 --> 00:38:00,630
我知道自己最近对你很苛刻
Look, I know that I've been hard on you,

631
00:38:01,340 --> 00:38:05,140
因为你的行为举止和以前大不相同了
about being different from the way you were.

632
00:38:06,530 --> 00:38:07,660
但事实是
But the truth is,

633
00:38:07,660 --> 00:38:10,860
奥利  我也不再是
Ollie, I'm not the same person

634
00:38:10,860 --> 00:38:12,590
五年前的那个我了
I was five years ago, either.

635
00:38:13,710 --> 00:38:16,260
这么说或许我们可以接受
So maybe we can just accept each other.

636
00:38:18,760 --> 00:38:20,110
大家都不再是过去的模样
Not for who we were,

637
00:38:20,120 --> 00:38:21,320
重新去接受
but for the--

638
00:38:22,480 --> 00:38:24,010
现在的彼此了
for the people we are now.

639
00:38:25,350 --> 00:38:26,300
好的
Yeah.

640
00:38:32,060 --> 00:38:33,260
别作弊
No cheating.

641
00:38:33,260 --> 00:38:35,050
-好  -过来
- You're on. - Come here.

642
00:38:59,940 --> 00:39:02,230
谢谢  费利西蒂  很高兴你打电话来
Thank you, Felicity. It was good of you to call,

643
00:39:02,450 --> 00:39:03,780
但奥利弗会没事的
but Oliver's going to be fine.

644
00:39:04,070 --> 00:39:05,210
他的情况正在好转
He's already on the mend.

645
00:39:05,210 --> 00:39:07,160
好的  很高兴听到这消息
Good. I'm glad to hear this.

646
00:39:07,300 --> 00:39:08,690
我现在要进电梯了
I'm stepping into an elevator,

647
00:39:08,690 --> 00:39:10,640
可能会收不到信号
so I'll probably lose you.

648
00:39:10,680 --> 00:39:12,590
我一会儿再给你回电  再见
I'll call you straight back. Bye.

649
00:39:20,100 --> 00:39:21,850
-没事了  -他不会受伤吧
- It's done. - And he won't be harmed?

650
00:39:21,880 --> 00:39:23,800
他也不会知道你参与其中
Nor will he ever discover your involvement.

651
00:39:23,800 --> 00:39:24,850
我保证
You have my word.

652
00:39:24,850 --> 00:39:26,790
抱歉  我可没为此感到欣慰
Forgive me if I don't find that comforting.

653
00:39:26,810 --> 00:39:28,030
我警告过你  莫伊拉
You were warned, Moira.

654
00:39:29,900 --> 00:39:31,760
我告诉你要稳住沃尔特
I told you to get Walter under control,

655
00:39:31,760 --> 00:39:32,900
但你却做不到
and you couldn't.

656
00:39:33,020 --> 00:39:34,240
我只好出此下策
Steps had to be taken.

657
00:39:34,240 --> 00:39:36,850
对罗伯特被杀你也是这一番说辞
That's what you said to justify Robert's murder.

658
00:39:38,070 --> 00:39:40,000
你还不明白我为何不信任你
And you wonder why I don't trust you.

659
00:39:40,100 --> 00:39:42,030
一个绑架折磨自己儿子的女人
Quite a bid of judgment coming from the woman

660
00:39:42,030 --> 00:39:43,940
竟然还能如此振振有词
who had her son kidnapped and tortured.

661
00:39:43,940 --> 00:39:46,280
那是为了证明奥利弗对此一无所知
To prove to you that Oliver didn't know anything.

662
00:39:47,480 --> 00:39:49,060
这与现在又有什么关系
And what does it matter now?

663
00:39:49,920 --> 00:39:51,950
-木已成舟  -不  莫伊拉
- What's done is done. - No, Moira.

664
00:39:52,480 --> 00:39:55,380
这只是个开端  六个月内
It's just beginning. In six months,

665
00:39:55,380 --> 00:39:58,020
组织对这座城市的规划应该会
the organization's vision of what this city should be

666
00:39:58,060 --> 00:39:59,430
也势必会完成
will be complete.

667
00:40:00,120 --> 00:40:01,880
你心中一点良知都没有了吗
And you won't feel a thing then, will you?

668
00:40:03,980 --> 00:40:06,500
成千上万无辜的人将送命
Thousands of innocent people will be dead,

669
00:40:06,500 --> 00:40:07,760
你却毫不在意
and you'll feel nothing.

670
00:40:08,490 --> 00:40:09,600
非也
That's not true.

671
00:40:10,490 --> 00:40:12,190
有种成就感油然而生
I'll feel a sense of accomplishment.

672
00:40:14,660 --> 00:40:16,220
那时沃尔特也会回到你身边
And you'll have Walter back.

673
00:40:38,890 --> 00:40:39,910
你知道吗  狄格
You know, Dig,

674
00:40:40,580 --> 00:40:42,640
每当我出现在名单上的人面前时
when I confront somebody on the list,

675
00:40:44,450 --> 00:40:45,660
我告诉他们
I tell them

676
00:40:46,630 --> 00:40:48,210
他们辜负了这座城市
that they failed the city.

677
00:40:50,930 --> 00:40:53,120
可今晚  辜负了它的人是我
But tonight, it was me who failed.

678
00:40:53,680 --> 00:40:55,910
奥利弗  五名人质今晚能一家团圆
Oliver, five hostages are home tonight with their families

679
00:40:55,910 --> 00:40:57,140
共度佳节
enjoying the holidays.

680
00:40:59,920 --> 00:41:01,000
全是你的功劳
Because of you.

681
00:41:04,100 --> 00:41:05,550
那家伙  另外那个弓箭手
This guy, the other archer...

682
00:41:06,850 --> 00:41:07,960
他会遭到报应的
He'll get his.

683
00:41:09,060 --> 00:41:10,220
你会亲手惩罚他的
And you'll give it to him.

684
00:41:11,810 --> 00:41:13,270
现在可能面临着一个更严峻的问题
We might have a bigger problem.

685
00:41:16,430 --> 00:41:19,850
那个弓箭手告诉我有人拟此名单
The other archer told me that somebody compiled the list.

686
00:41:21,680 --> 00:41:22,950
我一直以为
I always assumed

687
00:41:23,840 --> 00:41:25,150
那个人是我父亲
it was my father.

688
00:41:29,300 --> 00:41:30,620
但如果不是呢
But what if it wasn't?

689
00:41:31,490 --> 00:41:32,600
什么意思
What do you mean?

690
00:41:34,220 --> 00:41:36,170
我认为参与这局棋的人不仅这些
I think there's someone else out there.

691
00:41:38,450 --> 00:41:40,440
还有比弓箭手危险得多的家伙
Someone who's more of a danger

692
00:41:40,610 --> 00:41:41,890
在等着我们
than the archer.

693
00:41:46,070 --> 00:41:49,160
我要打倒他
And I am going to take him down.

