1
00:02:05,000 --> 00:02:10,000
{\pos(190,270)}本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

3
00:02:10,100 --> 00:02:15,000
{\pos(190,278)}翻译：小黎   妄想的绒布熊   天朝直属   vivi   鱼小姐   luna_3

5
00:02:15,100 --> 00:02:20,000
{\pos(190,278)}初校：DJ   爱是李   十九罗汉   苹果

7
00:02:20,100 --> 00:02:25,000
{\pos(190,278)}时间轴：加森  搁浅   后期：冰河  监制：苹果

9
00:02:19,680 --> 00:02:24,580
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)绿   箭

10
00:02:19,680 --> 00:02:24,580
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)第一季 第三集

11
00:00:07,750 --> 00:00:09,770
我是奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.

12
00:00:09,960 --> 00:00:12,670
对家人来说  我是他们五年前消失深海
To my family, I am the brother and son

13
00:00:12,670 --> 00:00:16,770
现在重返家园的兄长  儿子
who just returned home after being lost at sea 5 years ago.

14
00:00:17,140 --> 00:00:18,950
他们不知道我此次归来有要务在身
They don't know I came back with a mission,

15
00:00:18,960 --> 00:00:21,590
要为我们的城市带来正义
to bring justice to our city,

16
00:00:21,610 --> 00:00:23,480
他们也将永远无从知晓
and they never can.

17
00:00:27,800 --> 00:00:31,560
我的目标都是危险而腐败的
The men and women I've targeted are dangerous, corrupt,

18
00:00:31,610 --> 00:00:33,670
社会毒瘤
a virulent cancer.

19
00:00:38,220 --> 00:00:40,030
比如詹姆斯·霍尔德
Cancers like James Holder,

20
00:00:39,990 --> 00:00:44,880
霍尔德集团
并不负责
火灾疏漏

21
00:00:40,680 --> 00:00:42,810
他的公司给住在林间的低收入家庭
whose corporation put defective smoke detectors

22
00:00:42,810 --> 00:00:45,610
安装破损的烟雾探测器
in low-income housing in the glades.

23
00:00:47,420 --> 00:00:51,670
太多火灾已经发生  太多葬礼已经举行
There have been many fires and too many funerals.

24
00:00:51,630 --> 00:00:53,130
{\pos(225,73)}詹姆斯·霍尔德

25
00:00:58,310 --> 00:01:00,490
但是这些毒瘤可以对抗和铲除
But cancers can be fought and conquered.

26
00:01:00,490 --> 00:01:02,870
一个手术师
All it takes is a surgeon...

27
00:01:04,710 --> 00:01:06,730
正确的手术工具  即可解决
and the right instrument.

28
00:01:13,600 --> 00:01:15,130
除了今天上午从法律团队那
Other than the bill I got handed

29
00:01:15,130 --> 00:01:16,440
拿回来的账单以外
this morning by my legal team,

30
00:01:16,440 --> 00:01:17,800
我感觉很不错
I'm feeling pretty good.

31
00:01:17,800 --> 00:01:19,880
还有  既然法律诉讼已成定局
Plus, now that this lawsuit's been settled,

32
00:01:19,880 --> 00:01:23,350
我们可以把精力集中于尤尼达克工业
we can focus our attention on Unidac Industries.

33
00:01:24,430 --> 00:01:25,850
好的
Ok.

34
00:01:25,850 --> 00:01:28,120
明天第一件事就去办公室找你
I'll see you in the office first thing.

35
00:01:35,920 --> 00:01:37,660
我屋里有武装的安保力量
I have armed security inside.

36
00:01:37,660 --> 00:01:39,160
我一叫他们就会出来
All I have to do is call out.

37
00:01:39,160 --> 00:01:40,610
叫吧
Go ahead.

38
00:01:40,610 --> 00:01:42,590
他们听不到的
They can't hear you.

39
00:01:45,120 --> 00:01:46,250
你他妈想要什么
What the hell do you want?

40
00:01:46,260 --> 00:01:48,990
那几场火灾中死了多少人
How many people died in those fires?

41
00:01:48,990 --> 00:01:50,720
多少人
How many?!

42
00:01:54,140 --> 00:01:56,210
法庭说你不欠受害者一丝一毫
The courts say you don't owe your victims anything.

43
00:01:56,210 --> 00:01:57,910
我不同意
I disagree.

44
00:01:58,460 --> 00:02:00,760
詹姆斯·霍尔德  你
James Holder... You--

45
00:02:51,150 --> 00:02:53,770
像詹姆斯·霍尔德这样的腐败之人
It's no surprise a man as corrupt as James Holder

46
00:02:53,770 --> 00:02:55,800
敌人众多并不奇怪
has more than one enemy.

47
00:02:55,050 --> 00:02:56,560
{\pos(193,76)}詹姆斯·霍尔德

48
00:03:11,090 --> 00:03:13,750
子弹  有毒
The bullet. Poison.

49
00:03:46,410 --> 00:03:48,000
你是谁
Who are you?

50
00:03:53,480 --> 00:03:55,360
你为什么用箭射我
Why did you shoot me?

51
00:03:55,980 --> 00:03:57,870
{\pos(195,242)}保护你

52
00:04:04,780 --> 00:04:05,750
{\pos(195,242)}喝  喝下去

53
00:04:28,170 --> 00:04:29,830
妈的
Damn.

54
00:04:42,910 --> 00:04:45,320
发生了什么  西娅没事吧
What happened? Thea ok?

55
00:04:45,390 --> 00:04:46,450
警察把她带回家
The cops brought her home.

56
00:04:46,450 --> 00:04:48,270
她和几个朋友昨晚闯入商店
Her and some of her friends broke into a store,

57
00:04:48,270 --> 00:04:50,500
试了几条裙子
tried on some dresses last night.

58
00:04:50,520 --> 00:04:53,980
呼气测醉仪警报亮得跟圣诞树一样
Lit up the breathalyzer like a christmas tree.

59
00:04:55,910 --> 00:04:57,400
您昨晚过得如何  先生
So how was your evening, sir?

60
00:04:57,400 --> 00:04:59,150
你是指晚饭时我说去洗手间
You mean after I said I had to go to the bathroom

61
00:04:59,150 --> 00:05:01,220
却再没有回来吗
at dinner and never came back?

62
00:05:02,090 --> 00:05:04,820
看来从现在开始你小便我也得看着了
I guess from now on I'll be watching you pee.

63
00:05:09,180 --> 00:05:12,030
谢谢你们  警官  我和妻子都很感谢
Thank you, officers. My wife and I appreciate it.

64
00:05:12,200 --> 00:05:13,690
我送你们出去
I'll see you out.

65
00:05:17,570 --> 00:05:19,520
上次是在大庭广众之下酩酊大醉
Last time it was public intoxication.

66
00:05:19,520 --> 00:05:21,100
这次是非法闯入店家
This time breaking and entering.

67
00:05:21,100 --> 00:05:24,410
天呐  我们在犯罪界可是节节攀升啊
My, how we are moving up in the criminal world.

68
00:05:24,410 --> 00:05:26,240
你付钱给那些店主时
You know, when you pay off the store owner,

69
00:05:26,240 --> 00:05:28,550
真应该看看他们卖的东西
you should check out the merchandise.

70
00:05:28,560 --> 00:05:30,160
他们有几件衣服可好看了
They got some pretty killer outfits.

71
00:05:30,160 --> 00:05:32,190
西娅  准备去上学吧
Thea, go get ready for school.

72
00:05:32,490 --> 00:05:35,910
我在考虑请天病假
Uh, you know, I was thinking of taking a sick day.

73
00:05:37,740 --> 00:05:40,850
好吧  那就好好睡一觉
Fine, then get some sleep.

74
00:05:45,350 --> 00:05:47,190
你脸色真难看
You look like crap.

75
00:05:48,780 --> 00:05:50,150
你让她旷课吗
You're letting her play hooky?

76
00:05:50,150 --> 00:05:51,680
当你妹妹如此表现时
When your sister gets like this,

77
00:05:51,680 --> 00:05:53,140
最好给她点空间
it's best to give her her space.

78
00:05:53,140 --> 00:05:55,080
她在测你底线
She's testing you.

79
00:05:55,080 --> 00:05:58,640
是的  她这招从谁那学的
Yes. Who'd she learn that from?

80
00:05:58,830 --> 00:06:00,250
妈妈
Mom.

81
00:06:01,870 --> 00:06:04,420
我这么大时  你和爸让我免受杀人惩罚
When I was her age, you and dad let me get away with murder.

82
00:06:04,430 --> 00:06:06,780
回首过去  我本可以少些私人空间
Looking back, I could have used less space

83
00:06:06,780 --> 00:06:08,600
多些父母教养
and more parenting.

84
00:06:17,310 --> 00:06:18,850
这说不通
It doesn't make sense.

85
00:06:18,850 --> 00:06:21,220
霍尔德符合侧写  富有的人渣
Holder fits the profile. Wealthy dirtbag.

86
00:06:21,220 --> 00:06:22,540
兜帽兄的最佳猎物
Red meat for the hood.

87
00:06:22,540 --> 00:06:23,970
我们找到的箭多于一支
And we recovered at least one arrow.

88
00:06:23,970 --> 00:06:25,890
只不过这次死因是
Yeah, only this time the cause of death

89
00:06:25,890 --> 00:06:27,130
子弹两次射穿心脏
is a double tap through the heart

90
00:06:27,130 --> 00:06:29,030
我们的嫌犯可从不用枪
and our perp doesn't use firearms.

91
00:06:29,030 --> 00:06:31,000
没准他终于发现比弓箭杀人
Maybe he's finally figured out there's easier ways

92
00:06:31,000 --> 00:06:33,360
更简单的方法了
to kill people than with a bow and arrow.

93
00:06:33,450 --> 00:06:36,860
就像你说过的  这家伙是半吊子
It's like you said, the guy's a whack-job.

94
00:06:56,980 --> 00:06:59,330
子弹上浸满毒液
The bullets were laced with curare,

95
00:06:59,330 --> 00:07:01,560
一种罕见而致命的毒药
a rare and deadly poison,

96
00:07:01,560 --> 00:07:03,730
这是杀人犯的独有的杀人手法
the killer's unique M.O.

97
00:07:05,630 --> 00:07:07,240
他的罪行遍及世界
He's killed all over the world--

98
00:07:07,240 --> 00:07:10,530
芝加哥  马尔科维亚  科托马耳他
Chicago, Markovia, Corto Maltese.

99
00:07:10,560 --> 00:07:13,280
国际刑警甚至给他取了个代号
Interpol even has a codename for him--

100
00:07:13,290 --> 00:07:14,780
死亡射手
Deadshot.

101
00:07:16,120 --> 00:07:18,180
我本想给詹姆斯·霍尔德一次机会
I was prepared to give James Holder a chance

102
00:07:18,180 --> 00:07:21,970
改正错误  但是这个死亡射手惨无人道
to right his wrongs, but this Deadshot has no morality,

103
00:07:22,120 --> 00:07:25,700
心无敬意  毫无准则
no honor, no code.

104
00:07:26,230 --> 00:07:27,710
他不为正义而杀人
He doesn't kill for justice,

105
00:07:27,710 --> 00:07:31,120
所以他就和我名单上的人一样危险
which makes him as dangerous as anyone on my list.

106
00:07:31,680 --> 00:07:35,200
事实上 这点让他变成最危险的人
In fact, it puts him right at the top.

107
00:07:43,120 --> 00:07:44,760
奎恩工业

108
00:07:47,170 --> 00:07:51,940
感觉如何  夜店好场所是不是
What do you think? Great spot for a nightclub or what?

109
00:07:51,940 --> 00:07:54,100
真好  但是我得告诉你  兄弟
Sweet. Though I got to tell you, man,

110
00:07:54,100 --> 00:07:55,620
你要是想给它起名叫奎恩神马的
if you're thinking about calling it Queens,

111
00:07:55,620 --> 00:07:57,150
我觉得你不会得到
I don't think you're gonna get the clientele

112
00:07:57,150 --> 00:07:58,540
你所期望的大批客源
that you were hoping for.

113
00:07:58,540 --> 00:07:59,730
那是私人办公室
Private office.

114
00:07:59,730 --> 00:08:02,550
我想是用来开一对一的私人会议吧
For the private one-on-one meetings, I would imagine.

115
00:08:02,550 --> 00:08:05,340
最好还是传统的二对一会议
Hopefully the occasional two-on-one meeting.

116
00:08:06,850 --> 00:08:09,240
哥们  你确定你要这么做吗
Man, are you sure you want to do this?

117
00:08:09,240 --> 00:08:11,050
你不像是有经验
It's not like you really have any experience

118
00:08:11,050 --> 00:08:14,930
经营  任何东西
in running a...well, running anything.

119
00:08:16,000 --> 00:08:18,110
要不明天晚上
How about tomorrow night the two of us,

120
00:08:18,110 --> 00:08:19,500
我们两个去别处借鉴下经验
We go and scope out the competition.

121
00:08:19,500 --> 00:08:21,320
市区开了家新的夜店
There's a new club opening downtown.

122
00:08:21,320 --> 00:08:23,930
叫作毒药  马克斯·福勒开的
It's called poison. Max fuller owns it.

123
00:08:24,050 --> 00:08:25,650
-马克斯·福勒吗  -嗯
- Max fuller? - Mm-hmm.

124
00:08:25,650 --> 00:08:26,970
我睡了他的未婚妻
I slept with his fiance.

125
00:08:26,970 --> 00:08:28,100
没错  是在婚礼前
Yeah, before the wedding.

126
00:08:28,100 --> 00:08:29,550
是在婚礼预演上
It was at the rehearsal dinner.

127
00:08:29,550 --> 00:08:32,000
婚礼预演严格来说就是在婚礼之前
The rehearsal dinner is technically before the wedding.

128
00:08:32,010 --> 00:08:33,620
不是吗
Right?

129
00:08:33,640 --> 00:08:36,300
再说了  谁会对遇难的人耿耿于怀呢
And besides, who stays mad at a castaway?

130
00:08:36,350 --> 00:08:38,360
啊该死  我得先走一步
Ah, damm it, I got to roll.

131
00:08:38,360 --> 00:08:40,050
晚些时候见  哥们
Anyway, I'll see you later, man.

132
00:08:40,050 --> 00:08:41,050
不错的地方
Good place.

133
00:08:41,050 --> 00:08:42,520
回见
See you.

134
00:08:45,380 --> 00:08:49,240
元芳  你怎么看
So... what do you think?

135
00:08:49,240 --> 00:08:51,830
我负责保护你的安全  不发表评论  先生
Well, I'm here to provide security, sir, not a commentary.

136
00:08:51,830 --> 00:08:53,540
别这样  狄格  帮个忙
Oh, come on, Dig, do me a favor.

137
00:08:53,540 --> 00:08:56,100
畅所欲言
Speak freely, please.

138
00:08:58,080 --> 00:09:00,730
这里是贫民窟  不是吗
Well, this is the glades, right?

139
00:09:00,730 --> 00:09:01,600
你的那些白人富友们
Your rich white friends

140
00:09:01,600 --> 00:09:03,440
肯定不会来这个街区的
wouldn't come to this neighborhood on a bet.

141
00:09:03,440 --> 00:09:05,890
我可是奥利弗·奎恩
I am Oliver Queen, right?

142
00:09:06,010 --> 00:09:08,930
如果我开了家夜店  队伍都得排上三小时
People would stand in line for 3 hours if I opened a club.

143
00:09:08,930 --> 00:09:10,770
但对这里的居民来说
And no one who actually lives in the glades

144
00:09:10,770 --> 00:09:12,370
没有任何好处
would see a penny of those cover charges.

145
00:09:12,370 --> 00:09:14,540
所以我们要把生意做好
So we make it a successful business,

146
00:09:14,540 --> 00:09:16,090
来改善这个街区
We gentrify the neighborhood.

147
00:09:16,090 --> 00:09:18,450
我在想我们什么时候能说到重点
I was wondering when we would get to that.

148
00:09:19,710 --> 00:09:23,260
半路杀出个白衣骑士  拯救被压迫者
The white knight swooping in to save the disenfranchised.

149
00:09:23,670 --> 00:09:27,120
全靠他只身一人  孤胆行侠
And all by his lonesome with no help from anybody.

150
00:09:28,710 --> 00:09:31,260
看来你觉得我不怎么样啊
You don't think very much of me, do you?

151
00:09:31,530 --> 00:09:33,390
不  先生  事实上我敬佩你
No, sir, actually, I have a very high regard

152
00:09:33,390 --> 00:09:35,860
有如此敏锐的感知
for how perceptive you are.

153
00:09:37,700 --> 00:09:39,220
先生
Sir.

154
00:09:49,080 --> 00:09:51,310
这家夜店将会隐藏好我的基地
The nightclub will conceal my base underneath

155
00:09:51,310 --> 00:09:55,250
为奥利弗·奎恩的无数个夜晚打好掩护
and provide an alibi for where Oliver Queen spends his nights.

156
00:09:57,840 --> 00:09:59,730
{\pos(169,141)}奥利弗·奎恩将在
贫民窟开张人气新店

157
00:10:01,660 --> 00:10:03,320
你有杰根斯那案子的取证资料吗
Do you have the depos on the Jergens case?

158
00:10:03,320 --> 00:10:05,440
有的  在这附近
Yeah, they're around here somewhere.

159
00:10:08,780 --> 00:10:10,660
我只是上网随便看看
I was just surfing the 'net.

160
00:10:10,660 --> 00:10:12,180
真的吗
Really?

161
00:10:12,810 --> 00:10:14,780
乔安娜  我已经放下他了
Joanna, I'm over him.

162
00:10:15,630 --> 00:10:17,590
然而你却不相信我
And you don't believe me.

163
00:10:17,590 --> 00:10:20,180
如果不是刚才看到你我会相信的
Well, I would have if I wouldn't have just caught you

164
00:10:20,180 --> 00:10:21,450
翻看他的新闻报道
Trolling for articles on him!

165
00:10:21,460 --> 00:10:23,360
-我没在翻看  -我想用不着我
- I wasn't trolling! - I don't want to have

166
00:10:23,360 --> 00:10:26,840
来提醒你他曾经背叛过你  劳蕾尔
to be the one to remind you that he cheated on you, Laurel.

167
00:10:26,840 --> 00:10:28,360
和你的妹妹偷腥
With your sister.

168
00:10:28,780 --> 00:10:30,540
多谢了你的自制能力
I appreciate your self control.

169
00:10:30,540 --> 00:10:33,240
你还停留在过去  我知道
You're stuck in the past. And the reason I know this

170
00:10:33,240 --> 00:10:35,740
是因为从那以后你唯一有的亲密关系
is the fact that the only physical relationship

171
00:10:35,740 --> 00:10:38,870
是和奥利弗的挚友
you've had since Oliver is with his best friend.

172
00:10:38,870 --> 00:10:39,840
是时候往前看了
It is time to move on.

173
00:10:39,840 --> 00:10:42,110
过去的都过去了
It is past time.

174
00:10:43,250 --> 00:10:44,280
我很忙的
I've been busy.

175
00:10:44,280 --> 00:10:45,780
我有很多活要干
I work a lot.

176
00:10:45,780 --> 00:10:47,190
好吧
Ok.

177
00:10:47,790 --> 00:10:48,710
就此打住
That's got to stop.

178
00:10:48,720 --> 00:10:50,290
今晚我们要出去
So we are going out tonight.

179
00:10:50,290 --> 00:10:52,100
我们要喝点小酒
And--and we are going to have some shots

180
00:10:52,100 --> 00:10:53,780
和陌生人跳舞
and we are going to dance with men that we don't know

181
00:10:53,780 --> 00:10:56,220
我们要一直玩到深夜
and we are going to stay out way too late.

182
00:10:59,140 --> 00:11:01,270
杰根斯的取证找到了
Jergens depos.

183
00:11:01,890 --> 00:11:04,460
我觉得我今晚去不了
I really don't think I can go out tonight.

184
00:11:04,880 --> 00:11:08,470
你觉得自己还有选择真的是太天真了
It is adorable that you actually think I'm giving you a choice.

185
00:11:16,170 --> 00:11:18,430
放学以后给我立马回家
I want you to come home right after school.

186
00:11:18,430 --> 00:11:20,950
不行  玛戈特和我说好要去逛街
Oh, can't. Margot and I are going to go to the mall.

187
00:11:20,950 --> 00:11:22,920
怎么  还要购物
What, more shopping?

188
00:11:23,420 --> 00:11:25,010
告诉玛戈特你去不了了
Tell Margot you'll have to cancel.

189
00:11:25,010 --> 00:11:27,690
你被禁足两周
You're grounded for two weeks.

190
00:11:28,470 --> 00:11:29,860
禁足
Grounded?

191
00:11:29,860 --> 00:11:31,690
我从来没被禁足过
I've never been grounded.

192
00:11:31,690 --> 00:11:34,440
那是因为你以前从来没偷过东西
Well, you've never committed larceny before.

193
00:11:35,220 --> 00:11:37,030
从什么时候你开始关心我了
Since when do you care?

194
00:11:37,030 --> 00:11:39,910
我一直在关心  我是你的妈妈
I've always cared. I'm your mother.

195
00:11:39,910 --> 00:11:42,640
我们过去五年关系保持得一直不错
Look, we've had a good thing going on the last five years.

196
00:11:42,640 --> 00:11:43,920
为什么现在要弄那么僵
Why mess with that now?

197
00:11:43,920 --> 00:11:45,830
不  我们贿赂了店主
No, we are paying off store owners

198
00:11:45,830 --> 00:11:46,790
让你不留案底
to keep your record clean,

199
00:11:46,790 --> 00:11:48,610
所以很明显  这样并不好
So clearly, it hasn't been working.

200
00:11:48,610 --> 00:11:50,740
所以你开始来教育我了
And you're going to teach me.

201
00:11:51,800 --> 00:11:53,690
是奥利弗让你这么做的
It's Oliver, isn't it?

202
00:11:53,700 --> 00:11:56,280
他的伪善已经影响了你
His judgmental hypocrisy is rubbing off on you.

203
00:11:56,280 --> 00:11:59,460
不  我不需要奥利弗来教我怎么教育你
No, I don't need oliver to teach me how to parent you.

204
00:11:59,460 --> 00:12:00,800
你4点前必须到家
You'll be home by 4:00.

205
00:12:00,800 --> 00:12:02,290
不然怎么样
Or what?

206
00:12:02,290 --> 00:12:04,360
你打算叫警察来抓我吗
You're going to call the cops on me?

207
00:12:05,490 --> 00:12:07,270
替我和他们问个好
Tell them I say hi.

208
00:13:16,990 --> 00:13:19,280
霍尔德凶案的弹道分析出来了
Got ballistics back on the Holder murder.

209
00:13:19,370 --> 00:13:22,530
他们取出了他身上两枚7.62毫米的子弹
They pulled two 7.62 millimeter bullets out of him.

210
00:13:22,530 --> 00:13:24,620
根据伤口的大小和形状
According to the stippling and size of the entry wound,

211
00:13:24,620 --> 00:13:25,880
凶手估计是在
they estimate the shots were fired

212
00:13:25,880 --> 00:13:28,440
大约一百码以外射击的
From approximately a hundred yards away.

213
00:13:28,680 --> 00:13:30,500
一百码吗
A hundred yards?

214
00:13:30,500 --> 00:13:32,310
兜帽男从另一栋楼上射杀了他
What, so the hood shoots him from another building,

215
00:13:32,310 --> 00:13:34,210
特意跑去他那儿  放倒保安
goes over to his place, he takes out his security,

216
00:13:34,210 --> 00:13:35,560
然后射了几只箭
and then he fires off a few arrows?

217
00:13:35,560 --> 00:13:37,260
据药检显示
And according to his tox screen,

218
00:13:37,260 --> 00:13:39,270
他的血液里含有高浓度的
his blood contained high concentrations

219
00:13:39,270 --> 00:13:41,080
南美箭毒树毒液
of strychnos toxifera.

220
00:13:41,080 --> 00:13:42,350
-什么  -箭毒
- What? - Curare.

221
00:13:42,350 --> 00:13:43,250
是种毒药
It's a kind of poison.

222
00:13:43,260 --> 00:13:45,520
好的  我们现在从弓箭转向了
Oh. Ok, so now we switch from arrows

223
00:13:45,520 --> 00:13:47,900
狙击手的子弹和毒药
to sniper bullets and poison.

224
00:13:48,150 --> 00:13:49,430
我不相信
I'm not buying it.

225
00:13:49,430 --> 00:13:51,610
我们在现场还发现了箭
We still found arrows on the scene.

226
00:13:51,610 --> 00:13:54,000
这是兜帽男出现过的确凿证据
Solid evidence the hood was there.

227
00:13:54,250 --> 00:13:55,510
你去哪
Where you going?

228
00:13:55,510 --> 00:13:57,820
我自己去找证据
I'm going to get my own evidence.

229
00:14:11,560 --> 00:14:14,300
7.62毫米
7.62 millimeter rounds.

230
00:14:14,300 --> 00:14:16,810
通过资金路径追查到了兄弟会
The money trail leads back to the Bratva--

231
00:14:16,820 --> 00:14:18,670
俄罗斯黑手党
the Russian mob.

232
00:14:18,920 --> 00:14:22,250
终于  好运来了
Finally... some good luck.

233
00:15:08,230 --> 00:15:11,050
{\pos(195,242)}我来找阿列克谢·列昂诺夫

234
00:15:12,700 --> 00:15:14,810
{\pos(195,242)}这里没人叫那个名字

235
00:15:15,790 --> 00:15:17,590
{\pos(192,242)}不在你的车库里

236
00:15:21,920 --> 00:15:23,640
{\pos(195,242)}在地下室里

237
00:15:33,140 --> 00:15:34,170
{\pos(195,242)}我是兄弟会的

238
00:15:35,970 --> 00:15:38,920
{\pos(195,242)}我要见阿列克谢·列昂诺夫

239
00:15:45,070 --> 00:15:47,040
很高兴见到你
Pleased to meet you.

240
00:15:52,010 --> 00:15:53,830
我道歉
I apologize.

241
00:15:53,830 --> 00:15:56,480
我们对于队长
We meant no disrespect

242
00:15:56,480 --> 00:15:58,290
没有不敬的意思
to a captain.

243
00:15:59,350 --> 00:16:02,830
特别还是个美国人
Particularly an American one.

244
00:16:05,570 --> 00:16:07,100
所以
So...

245
00:16:07,100 --> 00:16:09,560
我能帮你什么
How can I be of assistance?

246
00:16:09,850 --> 00:16:11,790
我在物色一名杀手
I'm in the market for a hired gun.

247
00:16:11,790 --> 00:16:13,850
组织之前用过的
Someone the organization's used before.

248
00:16:13,850 --> 00:16:18,210
他的标志是使用带有箭毒的7.62毫米口径手枪
His calling card is a 7.62 millimeter gun laced with curare.

249
00:16:18,510 --> 00:16:20,940
我不认识用这玩意的人
I know no man who uses such tools.

250
00:16:20,940 --> 00:16:22,730
但是你能查到
But you can find out who does.

251
00:16:22,730 --> 00:16:25,420
首先  为了彼此的健康干杯
First, we will drink to each other's health,

252
00:16:25,420 --> 00:16:29,540
然后我会调查你要找的家伙的身份
then I will look into the identity of this man you seek.

253
00:16:33,940 --> 00:16:37,850
我也会确认你是不是兄弟会的队长
I will also confirm that you are really Bratva captain.

254
00:16:38,020 --> 00:16:39,560
如果不是的
Should this not be the case,

255
00:16:39,560 --> 00:16:41,720
我会让我的修理工
I will send my mechanic here

256
00:16:41,720 --> 00:16:44,670
找到你  然后杀了你和你的家人
to find you and kill you and your family.

257
00:16:52,520 --> 00:16:53,730
卡尔·拉斯姆森今晚
Carl Rasmussen was found

258
00:16:53,730 --> 00:16:56,210
早些时候被发现被人枪杀于自己的家中
shot to death in his home earlier this evening.

259
00:16:56,210 --> 00:16:57,930
警方不会对拉斯姆森先生的死
The police will not comment if there's a connection

260
00:16:57,930 --> 00:16:59,600
和数天之前
between Mr. Rasmussen's death

261
00:16:59,600 --> 00:17:02,100
詹姆斯·霍尔德的案子是否有关发表评论
and the murder of James Holder a few nights ago.

262
00:17:02,100 --> 00:17:05,360
拉斯姆森先生还有一个妻子和三个孩子
Mr. Rasmussen leaves behind a wife and three children.

263
00:17:25,350 --> 00:17:27,070
这是巨大的损失
It's a great loss.

264
00:17:27,070 --> 00:17:28,420
卡尔是位巨人
Carl was a titan.

265
00:17:28,420 --> 00:17:32,700
准备买下尤尼达克工业全部财产的巨人
A titan who was looking to buy out a company called Unidac Industries?

266
00:17:32,700 --> 00:17:35,680
工业有点用词不当
Well, industries are something of a misnomer.

267
00:17:35,790 --> 00:17:37,490
UI最近的活动
UI's recent activity was

268
00:17:37,490 --> 00:17:39,350
实际上是在寻找新能源
actually looking into alternative energy.

269
00:17:39,350 --> 00:17:41,340
我认为我的搭档想说明的是
I think the point my partner is trying to make

270
00:17:41,340 --> 00:17:42,480
卡尔·拉斯姆森已经是
is that Carl Rasmussen was

271
00:17:42,480 --> 00:17:44,960
这周死掉的第二位竞标人
the second bidder this week to lose his life.

272
00:17:44,960 --> 00:17:46,800
你是在暗示些什么吗  警探
Are you implying something, detective?

273
00:17:46,800 --> 00:17:48,010
只不过是你丈夫
Well, only that your husband's

274
00:17:48,010 --> 00:17:49,730
想要买下尤尼达克工业
looking into buying Unidac Industries

275
00:17:49,730 --> 00:17:52,490
然后竞争者就纷纷挂掉了
and the competition seems to be dropping like flies.

276
00:17:52,490 --> 00:17:54,500
我肯定你的影射
And I'm sure your veiled accusation

277
00:17:54,500 --> 00:17:58,070
和你对我家人的感情一点关系都没有吧
has nothing to do with how you feel about my family?

278
00:17:58,240 --> 00:18:00,840
尤尼达克正在接受破产管理  警探
Unidac's in receivership, detective.

279
00:18:00,850 --> 00:18:03,270
所有权服从于清算拍卖
Ownership is subject to a liquidation auction,

280
00:18:03,270 --> 00:18:04,420
那就意味着
so that means there are

281
00:18:04,420 --> 00:18:06,110
有很多的潜在买家
many prospective buyers.

282
00:18:06,110 --> 00:18:08,940
拍卖就在明天  所以
And the auction's tomorrow, so...

283
00:18:08,940 --> 00:18:11,030
如果我要除去竞争者
if I was taking out the competition,

284
00:18:11,030 --> 00:18:14,350
我还需要在这么短的时间里杀掉一大波人
I have a lot of killing to do in a very short amount of time.

285
00:18:15,110 --> 00:18:17,890
我们只是在调查有兴趣的买家
We're just making the rounds with the interested buyers.

286
00:18:17,890 --> 00:18:19,250
让他们小心一点
Let them know to be careful.

287
00:18:19,250 --> 00:18:22,060
当然  兰斯警探会关心
Oh, yes. And I'm overwhelmed

288
00:18:22,060 --> 00:18:25,170
我们的安全  真是令我受宠若惊
that Detective Lance is concerned for our safety.

289
00:18:25,910 --> 00:18:27,070
那么
Well...

290
00:18:27,080 --> 00:18:29,360
谢谢你的关心  先生
Thank you for your concern, gentlemen.

291
00:18:29,360 --> 00:18:31,820
我们的安全顾问  狄格尔先生
Our security consultant, Mr. Diggle,

292
00:18:31,820 --> 00:18:34,670
会采取必要的预防措施
is taking all the necessary precautions.

293
00:18:35,490 --> 00:18:36,970
是的
Yeah.

294
00:18:37,390 --> 00:18:38,900
好的
Right.

295
00:18:39,370 --> 00:18:42,190
如果需要我们
Well, if you need us,

296
00:18:42,990 --> 00:18:45,320
一通报警电话就行了
we're just a 911 call away.

297
00:18:53,760 --> 00:18:56,460
天啊  今晚肯定会很赞
Oh, my, this is going to be killer.

298
00:18:56,460 --> 00:18:59,240
-只要马克思没看到我  -我同意
- If Max never sees me here... - I agree.

299
00:18:59,240 --> 00:19:00,440
如果你要经营企业
Ah, if you want to run a business,

300
00:19:00,440 --> 00:19:02,340
就得承担一些风险
you've got to take a few risks.

301
00:19:02,340 --> 00:19:04,070
名单上没有你
I don't see your name on the list.

302
00:19:04,080 --> 00:19:06,040
奎恩先生
Mr. Queen.

303
00:19:09,270 --> 00:19:12,180
我这辈子从没见过这个家伙
I have never seen this guy before in my life.

304
00:19:30,030 --> 00:19:32,970
你出来找乐子是不是违反了某种法律啊
Doesn't you going out and having fun violate some kind of law,

305
00:19:32,970 --> 00:19:36,040
比如那些刻在石碑上的玩意
you know, like the ones that are carved on a stone tablet?

306
00:19:36,040 --> 00:19:37,960
-好好笑  汤米  -谢了
- That's cute, Tommy. - Thanks.

307
00:19:37,960 --> 00:19:40,370
你们俩这是又出来猎艳了吧
I can see you two are up to your old hunting patterns.

308
00:19:40,370 --> 00:19:41,580
只不过看看我这五年
Just seeing what passes for fun

309
00:19:41,580 --> 00:19:44,110
错过了星城什么有趣的东西
in Starling City after five years.

310
00:19:44,780 --> 00:19:45,940
我确定你会发现
Well, I'm sure you'll find

311
00:19:45,940 --> 00:19:47,880
没了你之后一切都不一样了
that it just hasn't been the same without you.

312
00:19:47,880 --> 00:19:49,790
老哥
Big brother!

313
00:19:49,950 --> 00:19:52,340
我现在太晕了
Oh! I am so wasted right now.

314
00:19:52,340 --> 00:19:55,240
这里有两个你
There is-- there is two of you.

315
00:19:56,930 --> 00:19:58,550
我以为你被禁足了
I thought you were grounded.

316
00:19:58,550 --> 00:20:02,010
是啊  多亏了你  谢了啊
I am. And thank you-- thank you for that, by the way.

317
00:20:04,450 --> 00:20:05,710
你该回家了
You're done for the night.

318
00:20:05,710 --> 00:20:07,250
你能怎样
Oh, what are you going to do?

319
00:20:07,250 --> 00:20:09,410
-告诉妈妈  -西娅
- Tell mom? - Thea!

320
00:20:10,810 --> 00:20:13,900
你不该跟这些人混在一起
You are hanging with the wrong people.

321
00:20:13,910 --> 00:20:16,430
你不也一样吗
You're one to talk.

322
00:20:16,650 --> 00:20:20,020
你对你这些所谓的朋友了解多少
How much do you know about your own so-called friends over here?

323
00:20:20,030 --> 00:20:21,930
西娅  或许你该
Oh, Thea, maybe you should--

324
00:20:21,930 --> 00:20:25,390
汤米  我觉得你的好兄弟有权知道
Tommy...I think your bff has a right to know.

325
00:20:25,390 --> 00:20:27,650
西娅  我们走
Thea, let's go.

326
00:20:27,650 --> 00:20:29,600
我猜他们从未告诉你
Well, I guess they never told you

327
00:20:29,600 --> 00:20:32,610
你不在的时候他们俩有多甜蜜
that they've been screwing while you were gone.

328
00:20:41,100 --> 00:20:43,240
-兄弟  -汤米
- Look, man, I-- - Tommy...

329
00:20:44,840 --> 00:20:46,360
没关系
It's ok.

330
00:20:49,220 --> 00:20:52,260
你和我  我们回去
You and me, we're done for the night.

331
00:20:52,260 --> 00:20:55,010
别碰我
Take your hands off of me.

332
00:20:55,780 --> 00:20:57,550
你不是我的父亲
You're not my father.

333
00:20:57,550 --> 00:20:59,810
你也快算不上是我的哥哥了
And you're barely my brother.

334
00:21:06,080 --> 00:21:07,410
看啊
Look at this.

335
00:21:07,670 --> 00:21:09,200
奥利弗·奎恩
Oliver Queen.

336
00:21:11,620 --> 00:21:12,880
马克斯·福勒
Max Fuller.

337
00:21:13,830 --> 00:21:15,140
你好吗
How you been?

338
00:21:16,020 --> 00:21:17,230
听说你被淹死很开心
Happy you drowned.

339
00:21:20,860 --> 00:21:22,020
嘿  马克斯
Hey, Max--

340
00:21:25,800 --> 00:21:27,050
扶他起来
Get him up!

341
00:21:27,630 --> 00:21:28,970
让他走  让他走
Hey, let him go, let him go!

342
00:21:29,550 --> 00:21:31,390
我说了  让他走
Hey, I said let him go!

343
00:21:32,160 --> 00:21:33,830
我告诉过你  他肯定会发飙的
Told you he was going to be pissed.

344
00:21:33,830 --> 00:21:35,670
走开  梅林  这事跟你没关系
Back off, Merlyn. This isn't your problem.

345
00:21:35,670 --> 00:21:36,900
你们想对他动手
You want to get to him?

346
00:21:37,110 --> 00:21:38,360
得先过经过我
You've got to go through me.

347
00:21:39,450 --> 00:21:41,310
他们要对我动手了
Wow, they are probably going to get through me.

348
00:21:54,910 --> 00:21:56,330
够了吗  马克斯
So is this over, Max?

349
00:21:56,470 --> 00:21:58,690
还是你要让你的小跟班们来对付我
Or are you going to have your boys pound on me next?

350
00:22:03,190 --> 00:22:05,060
你们三个这辈子都别想进来了
You three consider yourselves banned for life.

351
00:22:06,470 --> 00:22:07,890
滚出我的地盘
Get the hell out of my place!

352
00:22:08,880 --> 00:22:10,410
反正你的店也弱爆了
Your club sucks anyway.

353
00:22:12,050 --> 00:22:12,720
你们没事吧
You guys ok?

354
00:22:12,720 --> 00:22:14,100
你在哪儿学的这一手
Where'd you learn to do that?

355
00:22:14,100 --> 00:22:15,360
警察老爸  记得吗
Cop dad, remember?

356
00:22:15,740 --> 00:22:17,490
他逼我去上自我防御课
He made me take self defense classes.

357
00:22:19,800 --> 00:22:20,890
劳蕾尔
Laurel.

358
00:22:22,250 --> 00:22:23,420
西娅说的那些
What Thea said...

359
00:22:24,360 --> 00:22:26,400
奥利弗  汤米和我不需要你的祝福
Oliver, Tommy and I don't need your blessing,

360
00:22:28,250 --> 00:22:29,660
我也不需要你的原谅
and I don't need your forgiveness.

361
00:24:00,540 --> 00:24:02,380
你们先坐
Why don't you guys take a seat

362
00:24:02,650 --> 00:24:03,940
我去拿点吃的
and I will grab a couple of burgers

363
00:24:03,940 --> 00:24:05,530
还有敷脸的冰块
and some ice for those faces.

364
00:24:05,960 --> 00:24:06,870
那女孩挺可爱啊
The girl's pretty cute.

365
00:24:06,870 --> 00:24:07,970
她是我哥哥的妻子
That's my sister in law.

366
00:24:07,970 --> 00:24:10,440
我保证不跟她说话  也不乱瞄
Who I will never speak to or... look at.

367
00:24:11,470 --> 00:24:12,970
永远不  我得去拿瓶啤酒
Ever. Gonna grab a beer...

368
00:24:13,900 --> 00:24:15,410
她没带婚戒
She's not wearing a wedding ring.

369
00:24:15,720 --> 00:24:17,020
一个从未谋面的哥哥吗
Brother out of the picture?

370
00:24:19,300 --> 00:24:20,590
可以这么说
Yeah, you could say that.

371
00:24:25,370 --> 00:24:26,380
你好吗
How are you?

372
00:24:27,050 --> 00:24:29,450
看到你领养了两个白人男孩  真不错
So sweet of you to adopt two white boys.

373
00:24:29,540 --> 00:24:30,970
他们需要一个好的道德模范
They need a good role model.

374
00:24:31,370 --> 00:24:32,990
那是我的主顾奥利弗·奎恩
That's my client Oliver Queen.

375
00:24:34,240 --> 00:24:36,180
看起来你对他保护得很周全啊
Looks like you're doing a bang up job protecting him.

376
00:24:39,050 --> 00:24:40,500
兄弟
Look, man...

377
00:24:42,150 --> 00:24:43,270
关于劳蕾尔
About Laurel.

378
00:24:44,670 --> 00:24:45,990
我正打算要告诉你
I was going to tell you.

379
00:24:46,390 --> 00:24:49,550
我想找一个好的方式
I was just trying to figure out the right way.

380
00:24:49,630 --> 00:24:51,790
告诉一个人在他失踪  下落不明之后
To tell somebody that you slept with their girlfriend

381
00:24:51,790 --> 00:24:54,470
你睡了他的女朋友
after they went missing and were then presumed dead.

382
00:24:57,100 --> 00:24:58,710
难道没有卖这种祝福卡片的吗
What, there's no greeting card for that?

383
00:25:01,350 --> 00:25:02,350
听着
Look...

384
00:25:02,480 --> 00:25:03,770
我不该这样
It was wrong.

385
00:25:05,010 --> 00:25:06,700
-我很抱歉  -汤米
- And I'm sorry. - Tommy.

386
00:25:09,650 --> 00:25:10,870
我那时死了
I was dead.

387
00:25:10,870 --> 00:25:12,760
不  兄弟  你和劳蕾尔在一起
No, man, you were with Laurel.

388
00:25:13,870 --> 00:25:15,990
不管你是真的死了  还是
And whether you were dead, or as it turns out,

389
00:25:15,990 --> 00:25:18,380
在一个荒岛上存活下来
alive on a deserted island,

390
00:25:18,960 --> 00:25:20,320
你都是我的朋友
You are my friend.

391
00:25:21,210 --> 00:25:23,470
我和劳蕾尔在一起
And me being with Laurel violated that friendship

392
00:25:23,470 --> 00:25:25,020
从多个层面伤害了我们的友谊
in about 50 different ways.

393
00:25:25,020 --> 00:25:26,060
谢谢
Thank you.

394
00:25:27,720 --> 00:25:28,990
但是没关系
But it's ok.

395
00:25:30,580 --> 00:25:32,390
这次又有多危险
How dangerous is this gig, anyway?

396
00:25:32,520 --> 00:25:34,180
小菜一碟  卡拉  不用担心
It's a cakewalk, Carla, don't worry.

397
00:25:35,090 --> 00:25:36,150
太晚了
Too late.

398
00:25:36,570 --> 00:25:37,990
你忘了你哥哥是
Or have you forgotten this job

399
00:25:38,000 --> 00:25:39,290
因为这份工作死掉的吗
got your brother killed?

400
00:25:40,640 --> 00:25:42,100
因为  狄格  我没忘
Because, Dig, I haven't.

401
00:25:43,070 --> 00:25:44,110
我忘不了
I can't.

402
00:25:49,000 --> 00:25:51,600
这件事你真的很淡定  我
You are being really chill about this. I--

403
00:25:55,220 --> 00:25:56,170
你好
Hello?

404
00:26:01,420 --> 00:26:03,430
是个俄国超模打给我的
It's a russian model calling me.

405
00:26:05,260 --> 00:26:07,120
我们  我可以单独待一分钟吗
Can we... can I have a minute, please?

406
00:26:07,470 --> 00:26:09,830
我知道你为什么这么淡定了
I can see now why you were able to be so chill.

407
00:26:10,560 --> 00:26:11,650
好好享受
Enjoy.

408
00:26:13,590 --> 00:26:14,760
我猜对了吗
So I checked out?

409
00:26:14,760 --> 00:26:17,930
没错  他的名字是弗洛伊德·罗通
You did. His name is Floyd Lawton.

410
00:26:17,930 --> 00:26:20,440
我有他最近住过的地址
I have address. Where he stayed last time,

411
00:26:20,440 --> 00:26:22,290
他还在星城里
he was in starling city.

412
00:26:22,300 --> 00:26:23,380
就这些
But that is all.

413
00:26:23,380 --> 00:26:26,010
但愿他是个不爱搬家的人  说吧
Let's hope he's a creature of habit. Go.

414
00:26:26,050 --> 00:26:28,250
1700号  百老汇街
1700 Broadway,

415
00:26:28,250 --> 00:26:30,110
帕珀旅馆  52号房间
Papp motel, room 52.

416
00:26:30,360 --> 00:26:32,420
你不会把我们扯进去吧
You'll leave us out of this, yes?

417
00:26:33,320 --> 00:26:36,740
如果你没有被罗通先生杀掉的话
Assuming Mr. Lawton doesn't kill you first.

418
00:27:52,400 --> 00:27:54,280
是费利西蒂·斯莫克吗
Ahem. Felicity Smoke?

419
00:27:55,670 --> 00:27:57,900
你好  我是奥利弗·奎恩
Hi. I'm Oliver Queen.

420
00:27:58,630 --> 00:27:59,690
当然
Of course.

421
00:28:00,480 --> 00:28:02,530
我知道你是谁  你是奎恩先生
I know who you are, you're Mr. Queen.

422
00:28:02,550 --> 00:28:04,320
不  奎恩先生是我父亲
No, Mr. Queen was my father.

423
00:28:04,320 --> 00:28:06,750
没错  可他死了  我是说溺水身亡了
Right, but he's dead. I mean, he drowned.

424
00:28:07,190 --> 00:28:08,420
可你还活着  所以
But you didn't, which means

425
00:28:08,420 --> 00:28:10,660
才能下楼到IT部来
you could come down to the I.T. Department

426
00:28:10,680 --> 00:28:12,630
听我喋喋不休地说话
and listen to me babble.

427
00:28:13,590 --> 00:28:14,730
但马上就说完了
Which will end.

428
00:28:15,150 --> 00:28:17,850
倒数3...2...1
In 3...2...1.

429
00:28:18,200 --> 00:28:19,660
我电脑出了点问题
I'm having some trouble with my computer

430
00:28:19,660 --> 00:28:21,880
他们让我来找你
and they told me that you were the person to come and see.

431
00:28:23,970 --> 00:28:26,360
当时我在咖啡店上网
I was at my coffee shop surfing the web

432
00:28:26,360 --> 00:28:27,870
不小心把拿铁洒在上头了
and I spilt a latte on it.

433
00:28:27,990 --> 00:28:29,230
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.

434
00:28:29,630 --> 00:28:31,940
这看起来像是子弹孔
'Cause these look like bullet holes.

435
00:28:31,950 --> 00:28:33,820
我去的那家咖啡店附近治安挺糟
My coffee shop is in a bad neighborhood.

436
00:28:37,510 --> 00:28:40,210
如果你能想办法修好
If there is anything that you can salvage from it,

437
00:28:41,010 --> 00:28:42,530
我将感激不尽
I would really appreciate it.

438
00:28:45,200 --> 00:28:46,210
好吧
Mm-hmm.

439
00:28:55,150 --> 00:28:56,990
不错嘛  你在这儿
Oh. Well, good, you're here.

440
00:28:57,540 --> 00:28:59,650
我被软禁在家  记得吗
I'm under house arrest, remember.

441
00:29:00,120 --> 00:29:02,830
你想穿CK还是这件扎克·珀森
Do you want to wear the Calvin Klein or the Zac Posen?

442
00:29:04,540 --> 00:29:05,960
晚餐的时候
For dinner?

443
00:29:06,610 --> 00:29:08,220
我就打算穿睡衣
I was just going to wear pajamas.

444
00:29:08,490 --> 00:29:10,150
是出席沃尔特的股份拍卖会时的衣服
To Walter's stock auction.

445
00:29:11,200 --> 00:29:12,640
我倒宁愿禁足在家
I think I rather be grounded.

446
00:29:12,670 --> 00:29:14,120
不  你的出席至关重要
No, it's important that you come.

447
00:29:14,600 --> 00:29:15,860
对谁至关重要
Important to whom?

448
00:29:17,890 --> 00:29:19,050
对我
To me.

449
00:29:24,660 --> 00:29:26,360
好吧  听我说
All right, listen to me.

450
00:29:31,480 --> 00:29:32,570
你四岁的时候
When you were four years old,

451
00:29:32,570 --> 00:29:34,240
有天带了只猫回家
you came home one day with a cat.

452
00:29:35,550 --> 00:29:37,310
那是只流浪猫  不仅身上脏
It was a stray, it was filthy,

453
00:29:38,020 --> 00:29:39,190
脾气也很坏
and it was mean.

454
00:29:39,420 --> 00:29:40,840
但你就站在那儿  宣布
But you stood there and you declared

455
00:29:40,850 --> 00:29:42,470
它以后要和我们一起住
that it was coming to live with us.

456
00:29:43,490 --> 00:29:45,390
你父亲从办公室回来
Your father came home from the office

457
00:29:45,390 --> 00:29:46,700
看到眼前的那一幕
and he saw what was going on,

458
00:29:46,700 --> 00:29:49,950
就让你坐下  解释说
and he sat you down and he explained to you

459
00:29:49,960 --> 00:29:53,000
那只猫其实是只老虎
that the cat was in fact a tiger

460
00:29:53,150 --> 00:29:54,770
我们得把它送回家
and that we needed to get it home.

461
00:29:55,530 --> 00:29:56,760
不知为何
And somehow...

462
00:29:59,090 --> 00:30:00,510
你竟然明白了
you understood.

463
00:30:01,860 --> 00:30:04,600
罗伯特总是轻而易举就能说通你
Robert was always so good at getting through to you.

464
00:30:04,610 --> 00:30:07,190
我  我一直很嫉妒这一点  我...
I--I was always so jealous of that. I--

465
00:30:13,450 --> 00:30:14,830
你从来没提过他
You never talk about him.

466
00:30:17,550 --> 00:30:18,590
爸爸
Dad.

467
00:30:20,760 --> 00:30:23,090
这是你这么多年来第一次提到他
That's the first time you've talked about him in years.

468
00:30:27,130 --> 00:30:29,450
我想我和你都养成了一些坏习惯
Well, I think you and I have gotten into some bad habits.

469
00:30:30,560 --> 00:30:32,880
最近发生了许多变化  西娅
There's been a lot that has changed recently, Thea,

470
00:30:32,880 --> 00:30:35,410
我想也许这也能改变
and I think that maybe this can change, too.

471
00:30:52,490 --> 00:30:53,790
这看起来像是副工程图
It looks like blueprints.

472
00:30:53,940 --> 00:30:55,160
你知道是什么的工程图吗
Do you know what of?

473
00:30:55,970 --> 00:30:58,140
-交易所大厦  -没听说过
- The Exchange Building. - Never heard of it.

474
00:30:58,410 --> 00:31:00,890
尤尼达克工业计划举行拍卖会的地方
It's where the Unidac Industry's auction is scheduled to take place.

475
00:31:02,670 --> 00:31:04,890
我记得你说过这是你的电脑
I thought you said that was your laptop.

476
00:31:04,890 --> 00:31:05,810
对
Yes.

477
00:31:06,530 --> 00:31:08,750
先声明  我可不想卷入
Look, I don't want to get in the middle

478
00:31:08,750 --> 00:31:11,210
莎士比亚式的家庭闹剧之中
of some Shakespearian family drama thing.

479
00:31:12,430 --> 00:31:13,370
什么
What?

480
00:31:13,370 --> 00:31:14,880
斯蒂尔先生娶了你母亲
Mr. Steele's marrying your mom.

481
00:31:16,170 --> 00:31:17,560
克劳迪斯  格特鲁德
Claudius, Gertrude...

482
00:31:16,110 --> 00:31:18,980
{\an8}哈姆雷特王子的叔叔克劳迪斯
弑兄娶嫂夺得王位

483
00:31:18,390 --> 00:31:18,980
哈姆雷特
Hamlet?

484
00:31:18,980 --> 00:31:21,260
我在曾经退学的四间学校里
I didn't study Shakespeare at any of the four schools

485
00:31:21,260 --> 00:31:22,440
都没学过莎士比亚
that I dropped out of.

486
00:31:24,150 --> 00:31:26,660
斯蒂尔先生想买下尤尼达克工业
Mr. Steele is trying to buy Unidac Industries.

487
00:31:27,350 --> 00:31:28,870
而你却刚好拿到了与他的某个
And you've got a company laptop

488
00:31:28,870 --> 00:31:31,520
竞争对手相关的公司笔记本电脑
associated with one of the guys he's competing against.

489
00:31:31,650 --> 00:31:33,720
-弗洛伊德·罗通  -不
- Floyd Lawton. - No.

490
00:31:34,870 --> 00:31:36,190
沃伦·帕特尔
Warren Patel.

491
00:31:38,560 --> 00:31:39,880
谁是弗洛伊德·罗通
Who's Floyd Lawton?

492
00:31:40,280 --> 00:31:44,910
显然  他是帕特尔先生的手下
He is an employee of Mr. Patel, evidently.

493
00:31:48,350 --> 00:31:49,130
交易所大厦由三座
The Exchange Building

494
00:31:49,130 --> 00:31:52,180
布下眼线的塔楼所环绕
is surrounded by 3 towers with eye lines into the building.

495
00:31:53,320 --> 00:31:54,790
几乎从任何角度都能
Lawton could get a kill shot off

496
00:31:54,790 --> 00:31:56,170
给罗通致命一击
from virtually anywhere.

497
00:31:58,550 --> 00:31:59,980
可我不能顾及整个区域
But I can't cover the area.

498
00:31:59,980 --> 00:32:02,300
保护不到死亡射手的所有目标
I can't protect all of deadshot's targets.

499
00:32:03,160 --> 00:32:04,510
我一个人办不到
I can't do this alone.

500
00:32:10,340 --> 00:32:13,790
-你这狗娘养的  -探长  安静点
- Ah, you son of a bitch! - Detective, quiet!

501
00:32:13,790 --> 00:32:14,480
你小子胆大了
You've got a pair on you,

502
00:32:14,480 --> 00:32:16,190
敢跑到警局门前动手
pulling this right outside the police station!

503
00:32:16,190 --> 00:32:17,910
弗洛伊德·罗通就是那个要对
Floyd Lawton's the one targeting the buyers

504
00:32:17,910 --> 00:32:19,750
尤尼达克工业感兴趣的买家下手的家伙
interested in Unidac Industries.

505
00:32:19,750 --> 00:32:21,610
国际刑警把他称作"死亡射手"
Interpol calls him "Deadshot"

506
00:32:21,610 --> 00:32:22,810
因为他弹无虚发
because he never misses.

507
00:32:22,810 --> 00:32:25,390
我走之后你可以仔细调查一番
You can look this up after I go.

508
00:32:25,390 --> 00:32:28,060
是  然后就不对你紧追不放了  是吗
Yeah, and stop chasing you, I suppose?

509
00:32:28,590 --> 00:32:30,230
沃伦·帕特尔雇了罗通
Warren Patel hired Lawton.

510
00:32:30,600 --> 00:32:32,180
我还不确定谁是他们的目标
I can't be sure who they're targeting,

511
00:32:32,180 --> 00:32:33,240
也有可能是所有买家
it might be all the buyers,

512
00:32:33,240 --> 00:32:35,980
那么大的地方我保护不了所有人
And I can't protect them in a space that big.

513
00:32:37,310 --> 00:32:38,560
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.

514
00:32:39,320 --> 00:32:40,330
是吗
Yeah?

515
00:32:40,330 --> 00:32:41,650
专业的帮助
Professional help.

516
00:32:42,360 --> 00:32:44,240
罗通的子弹都喂了毒
Lawton laces his bullets with curare.

517
00:32:44,630 --> 00:32:46,050
叫你的伙计都穿上防弹衣
Tell your men to wear Kevlar.

518
00:32:46,210 --> 00:32:47,310
我会叫他们朝你开枪
I'll tell them to shoot you--

519
00:33:10,230 --> 00:33:13,000
这是个不错的活动嘛
Well, it's quite a turn out, huh?

520
00:33:13,000 --> 00:33:14,930
事实上是个不错的机会
Well, it's quite an opportunity, actually.

521
00:33:15,210 --> 00:33:18,050
可不管拍卖结果如何
But regardless of the outcome of the auction,

522
00:33:18,390 --> 00:33:19,410
我都是个赢家
I'm already a winner

523
00:33:19,410 --> 00:33:21,070
因为我身旁有两位最美的女士
because I have the two most beautiful women

524
00:33:21,070 --> 00:33:22,540
-陪在我身边  -两个
- At my side tonight.  - Two?

525
00:33:29,190 --> 00:33:30,470
谢谢你能来  西娅
Thanks for coming, Thea.

526
00:33:31,790 --> 00:33:33,830
这对于你妈妈和我都是一种宽慰
It means a lot to your mother. And me.

527
00:33:37,400 --> 00:33:40,360
斯蒂尔先生  拍卖将于五分钟后开始
Mr. Steele, the auction will be opening in 5 minutes.

528
00:33:40,450 --> 00:33:41,890
请准备就绪
Please make sure your bid is ready.

529
00:33:41,890 --> 00:33:43,380
谢谢你  吉娜
Thank you, Gina.

530
00:33:43,380 --> 00:33:44,650
我们走吧
Shall we?

531
00:33:48,040 --> 00:33:50,930
沃伦·帕特尔  你能跟我走一趟吗  先生
Warren Patel. I'm going to need you to come with me, sir.

532
00:33:53,220 --> 00:33:55,130
第一小组准备就绪  第二小组  收到了吗
Unit one, all clear. Unit two, you copy?

533
00:33:55,160 --> 00:33:56,650
我们正在监视帕特尔
We have Patel in custody.

534
00:33:56,650 --> 00:33:57,770
依然没有劳顿的踪影
Still, no sign of Lawton.

535
00:33:58,100 --> 00:33:58,980
第三小组
Unit three?

536
00:33:59,050 --> 00:34:01,800
我在西北方向  一切正常
I'm at the northwest perimeter. All clear.

537
00:34:01,900 --> 00:34:02,510
第四小组
Unit four?

538
00:34:02,520 --> 00:34:04,030
停车场已准备就绪
Parking structure is clear.

539
00:34:04,030 --> 00:34:05,560
第五小组  现在是什么情况
Unit five, what's your status?

540
00:34:05,680 --> 00:34:08,350
这是第五小组  一切正常
This is unit five. All clear.

541
00:34:16,580 --> 00:34:18,910
原来你在这里
Oh, what a shock.

542
00:34:19,730 --> 00:34:21,280
这可是周五
It is friday night.

543
00:34:22,090 --> 00:34:23,330
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?

544
00:34:23,730 --> 00:34:26,260
我是一名律师而这里是法院
Well, I am an attorney and this is a courthouse,

545
00:34:26,300 --> 00:34:29,440
我想该是我问 你在这里做什么
So I think the better question is, what are you doing here?

546
00:34:30,060 --> 00:34:32,220
我想跟你谈谈昨晚的事情
I wanted to talk to you about last night.

547
00:34:33,070 --> 00:34:34,770
你是指我救你一命的事
You mean how I saved your asses?

548
00:34:35,130 --> 00:34:35,830
不客气
You're welcome.

549
00:34:35,830 --> 00:34:38,510
首先  我们永远
Ok, first of all, we shall never,

550
00:34:38,550 --> 00:34:40,280
永远也不要再提起那件事
ever speak of that ever again.

551
00:34:40,280 --> 00:34:44,060
其次  你应该知道我想说什么
And secondly, I think you know that I meant the other thing.

552
00:34:44,940 --> 00:34:46,260
我不屑于听你的话
I don't care to talk about that.

553
00:34:46,270 --> 00:34:47,440
我和奥利弗谈过了
I spoke to Oliver.

554
00:34:48,450 --> 00:34:50,120
他对此事异常冷静
He was surprisingly cool.

555
00:34:54,080 --> 00:34:55,300
那是因为他知道
That's because he knew.

556
00:34:57,110 --> 00:34:59,100
你看见西娅告诉他时他的表情了吗
Did you see his face when Thea told him?

557
00:35:00,410 --> 00:35:02,020
汤米  他连眼睛都没眨
Tommy, he didn't even blink.

558
00:35:02,740 --> 00:35:04,060
相信我  他之前就知道
Trust me, he knew.

559
00:35:04,100 --> 00:35:05,580
那为什么他什么也没有说
Then why didn't he say anything?

560
00:35:05,580 --> 00:35:06,660
不知道
I don't know.

561
00:35:07,870 --> 00:35:10,370
可能因为他觉得没什么资格说我吧
Maybe because he knows he doesn't have any right to judge me.

562
00:35:12,960 --> 00:35:14,470
尽管这样  还是有一线希望
There's a silver lining, though.

563
00:35:15,110 --> 00:35:16,460
既然大家
Now that the whole truth

564
00:35:16,470 --> 00:35:18,210
都已坦白
and nothing but is out,

565
00:35:19,060 --> 00:35:20,940
我们之间还有可能吗
is there a chance now for you and me?

566
00:35:27,650 --> 00:35:28,880
你说你不认为
You said you didn't think

567
00:35:28,910 --> 00:35:30,800
我是那种专一的男人
that I was a one girl type of guy.

568
00:35:31,400 --> 00:35:32,660
我要证明你是错的
I'm going to prove you wrong.

569
00:35:34,930 --> 00:35:36,050
所以来跟我约会
By dating me.

570
00:35:36,100 --> 00:35:37,460
所以我要变得更优秀
By being better.

571
00:35:38,360 --> 00:35:40,060
变成配得上你的男人
By being someone that you deserve

572
00:35:40,620 --> 00:35:42,250
变成你愿意以身相许的男人
and that you want to be with.

573
00:35:43,890 --> 00:35:44,950
好吧
Well...

574
00:35:45,380 --> 00:35:48,130
这个男人我肯定有兴趣认识认识
That's certainly a guy I'd be interested in meeting.

575
00:35:50,730 --> 00:35:51,790
太好了
Good.

576
00:35:52,120 --> 00:35:53,910
那我们现在就开始吧
Now how about we start,

577
00:35:53,910 --> 00:35:55,230
把你从这里接走
by getting you the heck out of here.

578
00:35:55,230 --> 00:35:56,930
来吧  这可是周五晚上
Come on, it is friday night.

579
00:35:57,800 --> 00:35:58,450
走吧
Come on.

580
00:35:58,450 --> 00:35:59,730
-好吧  -太好了
- Fine.  - Good.

581
00:36:04,840 --> 00:36:06,660
你还真是人模狗样啊
Well, don't you scrub up nice?

582
00:36:06,760 --> 00:36:08,180
我是来这里支持我的家人
Here to support my family.

583
00:36:08,290 --> 00:36:09,960
是啊  我也是  谁能帮帮我
Yeah, me, too, god help me.

584
00:36:10,710 --> 00:36:11,720
谢谢你
Thank you.

585
00:36:18,210 --> 00:36:20,330
狄格  警戒起来了吗
Dig. Got your eyes open?

586
00:36:20,900 --> 00:36:21,950
这正是我来这的原因  先生
That's what I'm here for, sir.

587
00:36:21,950 --> 00:36:23,760
你完全没必要问这种问题
That and answering patronizing questions.

588
00:36:24,000 --> 00:36:25,350
这个家伙拖得太久了
This guy's out of time.

589
00:36:25,350 --> 00:36:26,080
如果他想干什么
If he's going to do something,

590
00:36:26,080 --> 00:36:27,790
一定会赶在拍卖会之前
it's going to happen before the auction.

591
00:36:28,810 --> 00:36:29,710
什么意思  先生
Sir?

592
00:36:32,130 --> 00:36:33,590
我是从广播里听到的
I heard the story on the radio.

593
00:36:34,260 --> 00:36:35,560
奥利弗
Oliver.

594
00:36:36,140 --> 00:36:38,450
你能来简直是太好了
So pleased you were able to attend. Hmm.

595
00:36:38,770 --> 00:36:39,520
沃尔特  刚刚警察说
Walter, the police said

596
00:36:39,520 --> 00:36:41,500
有些投标人已经被谋杀了
that some of the unidac bidders were murdered.

597
00:36:42,170 --> 00:36:44,210
我想我们应该更小心些了
I just think that we should be a little bit more careful.

598
00:36:44,910 --> 00:36:46,320
我妈妈已经失去了一个丈夫
My mother's already lost a husband.

599
00:36:46,320 --> 00:36:49,300
如果莫伊拉能理解你的感受的话
Well, if Moira shared your concern,

600
00:36:49,310 --> 00:36:50,240
她就不会来
she wouldn't have come.

601
00:36:50,300 --> 00:36:52,710
更不会把你的妹妹也带来
And she definitely wouldn't have brought your sister.

602
00:37:16,720 --> 00:37:18,710
奥利弗  你能来简直是太好了
Oliver, what a wonderful surprise.

603
00:37:19,700 --> 00:37:21,420
你现在必须得把她们都带出去
I need you to get them out of here right now.

604
00:37:36,850 --> 00:37:38,600
你没事吧  你受伤了吗
Are you ok? Are you hurt?

605
00:37:38,600 --> 00:37:40,310
不  我很好  沃尔特在哪儿
No, I'm fine! Where is Walter?

606
00:37:40,310 --> 00:37:43,040
快走  快走  沃尔特没事
Go, go, go, go! Walter's fine.

607
00:37:43,040 --> 00:37:44,310
先生  我得掩护你离开这里
Sir, I have to get you out of here.

608
00:37:44,310 --> 00:37:44,940
不  先带她们走
No, them!

609
00:37:45,130 --> 00:37:46,070
她们
Them.

610
00:37:46,810 --> 00:37:48,730
快走  走  我去找他  我去找他
Go, go, I'll find him, ma'am, I'll find him.

611
00:39:11,250 --> 00:39:12,450
把你的枪放下
Drop your guns.

612
00:39:13,840 --> 00:39:15,620
我很欣赏你的工作
I admire your work.

613
00:39:16,790 --> 00:39:19,830
不过你不怎么看好我的专业手法吧
Guess you won't be extending me any professional courtesy.

614
00:39:19,830 --> 00:39:21,620
我们不是一路人
We're not in the same line of work.

615
00:39:22,580 --> 00:39:23,980
你的工作就是谋杀
Your profession is murder.

616
00:39:24,200 --> 00:39:25,650
你也杀过人
You've taken lives.

617
00:39:26,620 --> 00:39:27,880
那是为了帮助别人
For the good of others.

618
00:39:29,220 --> 00:39:30,490
你却是为了自己
You're out for yourself.

619
00:40:16,040 --> 00:40:17,170
{\pos(191,240)}白痴

620
00:40:17,520 --> 00:40:20,180
{\pos(191,222)}一个人留在这里太危险

621
00:40:28,130 --> 00:40:30,270
{\pos(191,240)}他们会杀掉你

622
00:41:50,000 --> 00:41:51,240
你好
Hey.

