1
00:01:45,000 --> 00:01:50,000
{\pos(70,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

2
00:01:45,000 --> 00:01:50,000
{\pos(70,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

3
00:01:45,000 --> 00:01:50,000
{\pos(60,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

4
00:01:45,000 --> 00:01:50,000
{\pos(86,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

5
00:01:45,000 --> 00:01:50,000
{\pos(100,254)}人人影视
YYeTs.com

6
00:01:45,000 --> 00:01:50,000
{\pos(101,267)}原创翻译  双语字幕

8
00:01:45,000 --> 00:01:50,000
{\pos(240,267)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com

9
00:01:50,100 --> 00:01:55,000
{\pos(190,278)}翻译：呆蓝   宅女之后   喵喵阿飘   vivi的夏天   天朝直属

11
00:01:55,100 --> 00:02:00,000
{\pos(190,278)}翻译：小榴莲   Luna_3   初校：苹果果   爱是李   宅女之后   glorydai 

13
00:02:00,100 --> 00:02:05,000
{\pos(190,278)}时间轴：呆森   仓鼠sama   搁浅   后期：冰河   监制：苹果

15
00:09:28,750 --> 00:09:33,700
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)绿   箭

16
00:09:28,750 --> 00:09:33,700
t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)第一季 第十一集

17
00:00:00,840 --> 00:00:03,210
我的名字叫奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.

18
00:00:03,210 --> 00:00:05,460
五年里  我被困孤岛
For five years, I was stranded on an island

19
00:00:05,460 --> 00:00:07,740
只有一个目标
with only one goal--

20
00:00:08,120 --> 00:00:09,250
生存
To survive.

21
00:00:09,260 --> 00:00:11,210
奥利弗·奎恩还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.

22
00:00:11,210 --> 00:00:13,770
现在我要完成父亲的遗愿
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish--

23
00:00:13,770 --> 00:00:15,640
用他留给我的名单
to use the list of names he left me

24
00:00:15,640 --> 00:00:19,140
扳倒那些荼毒城市的人
and bring down those who are poisoning my city.

25
00:00:19,850 --> 00:00:23,080
要做这些   我必须伪装成另一个人
To do this, I must become someone else.

26
00:00:23,540 --> 00:00:27,050
我必须成为另一个存在
I must become something else.

27
00:00:27,160 --> 00:00:28,830
《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously on "Arrow"...

28
00:00:28,830 --> 00:00:31,250
你让我不要碰你的家人  我照做了
You told me to stay away from your family and I did.

29
00:00:31,250 --> 00:00:32,950
但你的家人却不断靠近我
But your family isn't staying away from me.

30
00:00:32,950 --> 00:00:34,850
我应该有所行动了
Which means something must be done about it.

31
00:00:34,850 --> 00:00:37,540
我在哪儿能找到照片中这个人
Where can I find the man in this picture?

32
00:00:37,540 --> 00:00:40,170
你不觉得你抓到我也太过容易了吗
Do you not think it convenient you captured me so easily?

33
00:00:40,170 --> 00:00:41,350
快跑
Run!

34
00:00:52,040 --> 00:00:54,730
你知道这座岛的真面目吗
Do you even know what this island really is?

35
00:00:54,730 --> 00:00:56,340
这是一座监狱
It's a prison.

36
00:00:56,600 --> 00:00:59,000
如果你是我  你会如何呢
What would you do in my position?

37
00:01:17,300 --> 00:01:18,590
该有法律规定
Ought to be a law.

38
00:01:18,590 --> 00:01:20,730
但没有
Well, there's not.

39
00:01:31,640 --> 00:01:33,390
小心
Watch it!

40
00:01:39,460 --> 00:01:43,060
倒车  离开这里
Back up! Get out of here!

41
00:02:18,360 --> 00:02:20,080
塔希提绿还是午夜黑
Tahitian green or midnight black--

42
00:02:20,080 --> 00:02:20,850
你觉得哪个好
What do you think?

43
00:02:20,850 --> 00:02:23,180
我觉得你整周都在暗示  西娅
I think that you've been dropping hints all week, Thea,

44
00:02:23,180 --> 00:02:25,090
但妈妈还是不会给你买辆车作为生日礼物
and mom still isn't buying you a car for your birthday.

45
00:02:25,090 --> 00:02:26,720
你说的真是再清楚不过了
I could not have said it better myself.

46
00:02:26,720 --> 00:02:29,070
奥利弗18岁生日时收到了汽车
Oliver got a car when he turned 18.

47
00:02:29,070 --> 00:02:31,430
但我可以倒出车道
Yeah, but I could back it out of the driveway

48
00:02:31,430 --> 00:02:32,270
而不会撞上树
without hitting a tree.

49
00:02:32,270 --> 00:02:33,640
对  但我还记得
That's true. But I do remember you

50
00:02:33,640 --> 00:02:35,870
你把你爸的玛莎拉蒂弄掉漆了
taking the paint off the side of your dad's Maserati.

51
00:02:35,870 --> 00:02:37,760
派对策划人还等着呢
Yeah, the party planner's waiting.

52
00:02:37,770 --> 00:02:39,890
不好意思  我得先走了
Sorry to run off like this.

53
00:02:39,980 --> 00:02:42,260
我们不是要买辆敞篷车吗
Don't we have a convertible to go buy?

54
00:02:42,270 --> 00:02:44,500
-祝你好运  -好
- Good luck. - Yes.

55
00:02:44,550 --> 00:02:46,060
她感觉怎么样
How's she holding up?

56
00:02:46,080 --> 00:02:48,500
她没事啦
Oh, she's ok.

57
00:02:48,640 --> 00:02:50,930
西娅觉得她有点太好了
Thea thinks she's actually a little bit too ok.

58
00:02:50,930 --> 00:02:51,640
什么意思
What do you mean?

59
00:02:51,640 --> 00:02:54,230
就是  举止怪异
Just... behaving erratically.

60
00:02:54,230 --> 00:02:56,240
前一分钟还心情低落  一会儿又管理公司了
Shut-in one minute, running the company the next.

61
00:02:56,240 --> 00:02:59,640
她的丈夫失踪了  音讯全无
Well, her husband is missing and presumed who-knows-what.

62
00:02:59,640 --> 00:03:01,580
如果谁有理由举止怪异
If anyone had an excuse to be erratic,

63
00:03:01,580 --> 00:03:02,840
那就是你妈妈
it's your mom.

64
00:03:02,840 --> 00:03:05,100
我也是这么和西娅说的
That's what I told Thea.

65
00:03:05,140 --> 00:03:07,690
警署对这次抢劫案的评论
The department has got the same comment about this heist

66
00:03:06,660 --> 00:03:10,880
{\pos(176,195)}装甲车被劫

67
00:03:07,690 --> 00:03:10,630
和另外两次一样  不予置评
as it did the other two. No comment.

68
00:03:10,630 --> 00:03:12,940
星城警署可能不愿意公开发表意见
The SCPD may not be willing to go on the record,

69
00:03:12,940 --> 00:03:16,260
但在这段独家短片里  交通摄像头拍下了抢劫全程
but traffic cameras got the entire heist in this exclusive.

70
00:03:16,260 --> 00:03:20,110
凌晨一点后  三名戴面罩的歹徒发射了一枚导弹
Shortly after 1 am, three mask robbers approached the armored vehicle

71
00:03:20,120 --> 00:03:21,620
然后接近装甲车
after a launching what appears to be...

72
00:03:20,200 --> 00:03:23,130
{\pos(176,195)}装甲车被劫

73
00:03:21,620 --> 00:03:23,220
所以才得把钱存到海外啊
That's why you keep all your money offshore.

74
00:03:23,220 --> 00:03:24,580
走向下车的保安
towards the guards outside.

75
00:03:24,580 --> 00:03:26,820
有一名保安当场死亡
One of the guard was pronounced dead on the scene,

76
00:03:26,820 --> 00:03:27,710
{\pos(176,195)}装甲车被劫

77
00:03:26,850 --> 00:03:29,180
另一名保安在被送往星城总院途中死亡
while the other died on the road.

78
00:03:29,420 --> 00:03:31,970
歹徒的身份尚未查明
Their identities have not yet been released.

79
00:03:31,650 --> 00:03:33,300
{\an8}奎恩工业股份有限公司
钢铁制造与焊接

80
00:03:34,510 --> 00:03:35,750
这么多人在上面工作
With all the guys working up top,

81
00:03:35,750 --> 00:03:39,050
你也许得考虑给你的弓箭洞穴
you might want to think about a side entrance for your, uh,

82
00:03:39,480 --> 00:03:41,140
开个侧门
arrowcave.

83
00:03:41,690 --> 00:03:44,880
开一个吧  南方小道
Just put one in. South alleyway.

84
00:03:45,510 --> 00:03:47,310
我有点东西想给你看
Something I want to show you.

85
00:03:47,310 --> 00:03:48,580
你终于开始网上约会
Finally getting into online dating

86
00:03:48,580 --> 00:03:50,220
需要我帮你写简介
and you need help with your profile.

87
00:03:50,220 --> 00:03:53,500
不完全是  但我确实想见一个人
Not exactly. But there is somebody I'd like to meet.

88
00:03:54,480 --> 00:03:55,250
我看过了
Yeah, I read about it.

89
00:03:55,250 --> 00:03:57,710
这是本月以来第三次卡车被劫
This is the third truck to be hit this month.

90
00:03:58,000 --> 00:04:00,150
我在早间新闻里看到了
I saw it on the news this morning.

91
00:04:00,250 --> 00:04:02,940
我不知道为什么看起来这么眼熟
I couldn't figure out why it seemed so familiar.

92
00:04:03,070 --> 00:04:04,780
然后我想到这个
Then I remembered this.

93
00:04:04,780 --> 00:04:05,930
坎大哈  09年
Kandahar, '09,

94
00:04:05,930 --> 00:04:08,610
那时海军陆战队摧毁了塔利班的运输装甲车
when the Marines took out a Taliban transport vehicle.

95
00:04:08,500 --> 00:04:13,480
{\an8}装甲车被劫

96
00:04:08,610 --> 00:04:11,970
两辆车这么像是有原因的
Yeah. Well, there's a reason why it looks so similar.

97
00:04:11,970 --> 00:04:12,850
这些人用的是
These guys are running the

98
00:04:12,860 --> 00:04:14,550
同样的群集技术  你从哪找到的
same swarming technique. Where'd you find this?

99
00:04:14,550 --> 00:04:15,730
我在调查一个人
I was researching someone.

100
00:04:15,730 --> 00:04:17,960
一个为私人安全公司效力的保镖
Bodyguard who works for a private security firm.

101
00:04:17,960 --> 00:04:21,390
黑鹰小队保护集团  他叫泰德·盖纳
Blackhawk Squad Protection Group. His name is Ted Gaynor.

102
00:04:18,250 --> 00:04:19,540
{\an8}黑鹰小队保护集团

103
00:04:22,490 --> 00:04:24,310
奥利弗  我第一次去阿富汗时
Oliver, Ted Gaynor was my commanding officer

104
00:04:24,310 --> 00:04:26,450
泰德·盖纳是我的指挥官
on my first tour in Afghanistan.

105
00:04:29,880 --> 00:04:32,970
狄格  我很抱歉
Dig...I'm sorry.

106
00:04:36,150 --> 00:04:38,340
但盖纳在名单上
But Gaynor's on the list.

107
00:04:38,620 --> 00:04:39,440
盖纳还差几万美元
Gaynor's a few hundred

108
00:04:39,440 --> 00:04:41,030
才能上你的名单吧
thousand dollars short of making your list.

109
00:04:41,030 --> 00:04:43,010
我从没说过名单上的都是有钱人吧
Well, I never said it was just one-percenters, did I?

110
00:04:43,010 --> 00:04:45,810
奥利弗  他救过我的命
Oliver, this guy saved my life.

111
00:04:45,960 --> 00:04:48,390
还因此获得勋章
Received a commendation for it.

112
00:04:48,670 --> 00:04:51,130
我不管你的名单上写什么  他不是恶人
I don't care what your book says. He's not a stick-up man.

113
00:04:51,130 --> 00:04:53,030
你很久没见过他了吧  狄格尔
You haven't known him in a long time, Diggle.

114
00:04:53,030 --> 00:04:55,830
我们回国后一直都保持联系
We both kept in contact with each other since we got stateside.

115
00:04:55,830 --> 00:04:58,930
半年前他还想让我在"黑鹰"里工作
6 months ago he even offered me a job at Blackhawk.

116
00:04:58,940 --> 00:05:00,980
相信我  我比你了解他
Now, trust me, you don't know this man like I do.

117
00:05:00,980 --> 00:05:03,080
但我知道他在阿富汗训练的项目是
I know in Afghanistan his training specialty

118
00:05:03,080 --> 00:05:05,300
M-32手榴弹发射器
was M-32 multiple grenade launchers,

119
00:05:05,300 --> 00:05:07,540
正是这些抢劫中使用的武器
the exact same weapon used in these heists

120
00:05:07,540 --> 00:05:09,450
这不是在什么当地运动商店
and not exactly something that you find

121
00:05:09,450 --> 00:05:11,670
能买到的东西
at your local sporting goods store.

122
00:05:11,670 --> 00:05:13,110
两个月前  我们发现
Two months ago, we found out

123
00:05:13,110 --> 00:05:14,810
这根本不是你爸爸的本子
this wasn't even your father's book,

124
00:05:14,820 --> 00:05:17,090
这是上次袭击你的弓箭手写的
that it was written by whoever hired the other archer.

125
00:05:17,090 --> 00:05:18,330
难道这还不足以让你怀疑
Doesn't that kind of beg the question

126
00:05:18,330 --> 00:05:19,530
这个名单或许有问题吗
what else you could be wrong about?

127
00:05:19,530 --> 00:05:21,140
我可能会出错
I could be wrong.

128
00:05:21,610 --> 00:05:22,730
但这份名单不会错
But the list isn't.

129
00:05:22,730 --> 00:05:25,660
我今晚得去和盖纳先生好好聊一聊
Now, I'm gonna have a pointed conversation

130
00:05:25,660 --> 00:05:29,130
我们看看他有什么解释
with Mr. Gaynor tonight. We'll see what he has to say about it.

131
00:05:30,630 --> 00:05:33,360
这星期你不如休息吧
I understand if you want to take the week off.

132
00:05:33,770 --> 00:05:35,400
好吧  谢谢
Well, thank you.

133
00:05:35,400 --> 00:05:36,940
{\an8}黑鹰小队保护集团

134
00:05:37,140 --> 00:05:38,590
长官
Sir.

135
00:06:36,510 --> 00:06:39,170
哎呀  讲中文啦

136
00:06:40,020 --> 00:06:42,640
每天都吃一样的粥
Different day, same slop.

137
00:06:43,550 --> 00:06:44,950
你新来的吗
You new?

138
00:06:45,030 --> 00:06:46,380
是的
Yeah.

139
00:06:46,870 --> 00:06:48,850
别担心  我花了一年
Don't worry. It took me a year

140
00:06:48,850 --> 00:06:50,950
才熟悉这个岛的地形
to find my way around the island.

141
00:06:54,590 --> 00:06:57,610
我的任务是去押送一个囚犯
I'm supposed to be transporting a prisoner.

142
00:06:57,820 --> 00:07:00,100
一个戴着绿色兜帽的中国人
A Chinese guy who wears a green hood.

143
00:07:00,220 --> 00:07:02,630
好像是他们在东边营地抓到的吧
Sounds like the guy they took to the east camp.

144
00:07:02,630 --> 00:07:05,570
我正要往那边走  我送你一程吧
I'm heading over that way. Come on. You can hitch a ride.

145
00:07:05,810 --> 00:07:07,380
走吧  快来
Let's go. Come on.

146
00:07:17,720 --> 00:07:19,640
等下  等下
Hold up! Hold up!

147
00:07:20,020 --> 00:07:22,100
一  二
One, two.

148
00:07:35,120 --> 00:07:36,770
{\an8}奎恩工业股份有限公司
钢铁制造与焊接

149
00:07:37,240 --> 00:07:40,270
那边的墙还需要刷一点纹理上去
That wall over there still has to be taped and textured.

150
00:07:40,280 --> 00:07:42,410
等到他们铺好瓷砖
I need you to to grout the hallway floor

151
00:07:42,420 --> 00:07:45,680
你就去走廊地板灌浆
as soon as they are done with the tile install.

152
00:07:44,950 --> 00:07:45,970
{\an8}爸爸来电

153
00:07:45,680 --> 00:07:47,330
好了
All right.

154
00:07:48,600 --> 00:07:50,320
-怎么了  -汤米  是我
- Yeah? - Hey, tommy.

155
00:07:50,320 --> 00:07:51,890
我现在很忙
I am really busy.

156
00:07:51,900 --> 00:07:54,250
汤米  我知道我们的关系
Tommy, I know things have been, well,

157
00:07:54,250 --> 00:07:55,890
从那时就很紧张...
strained between us since...

158
00:07:55,890 --> 00:07:58,490
从你冻结我的基金和说我是败家子那时吗
Since you cut me off and told me that I was a loser?

159
00:07:58,490 --> 00:08:01,150
我也是恨铁不成钢啊
I was just trying to jolt you into adulthood.

160
00:08:01,550 --> 00:08:03,900
看看你的成长  你有第一份工作了
And look at you now. You've got your first job.

161
00:08:04,230 --> 00:08:06,170
严厉教育还是起作用了
My tough love worked.

162
00:08:06,350 --> 00:08:08,420
你想怎么  爸爸
What do you want, dad?

163
00:08:09,140 --> 00:08:11,890
我就想跟我的儿子吃顿饭
Nothing more than to share a meal with my son.

164
00:08:12,420 --> 00:08:13,890
明天晚上吃饭可以吗
Dinner tomorrow night?

165
00:08:13,890 --> 00:08:15,140
我跟劳蕾尔有约了
Laurel and I have plans.

166
00:08:15,140 --> 00:08:16,810
带她一起来
Bring her along. I think it's time

167
00:08:16,810 --> 00:08:18,490
是时候多了解一下她了
I got to know her a little better.

168
00:08:18,490 --> 00:08:19,880
汤米
Tommy...

169
00:08:21,500 --> 00:08:24,070
我说过很过分的话
I've said some pretty hurtful things,

170
00:08:24,070 --> 00:08:25,800
我很后悔
and I regret them.

171
00:08:25,970 --> 00:08:27,660
但你还是我的儿子
But you're still my son.

172
00:08:27,660 --> 00:08:30,410
我还是希望
And I still want what I've always wanted.

173
00:08:32,610 --> 00:08:34,330
我们能亲近点
For us to be close.

174
00:08:36,530 --> 00:08:39,040
我问下劳蕾尔的想法  待会给你回复
Let me check with Laurel and I'll get back to you.

175
00:08:40,790 --> 00:08:42,100
黑鹰小队保护集团

176
00:09:15,100 --> 00:09:16,960
泰德·盖纳  我们得好好聊聊了
Ted Gaynor, we're gonna have a conversation.

177
00:09:16,960 --> 00:09:19,550
你要是敢动一下或者拿枪出来
You make a move, go for a gun, anything,

178
00:09:19,550 --> 00:09:22,230
你就不会有好果子吃
things will end badly for you.

179
00:09:22,630 --> 00:09:24,910
把弓放下来
Put the bow down.

180
00:09:55,080 --> 00:09:56,710
没事了
It's all clear.

181
00:09:56,760 --> 00:09:57,360
你还好吧
You ok?

182
00:10:01,270 --> 00:10:02,920
我还得跟老板请示一下
Well, I gotta talk to my boss,

183
00:10:02,920 --> 00:10:06,030
不过...  看你刚才的表现
but after... what I just saw,

184
00:10:06,030 --> 00:10:08,380
我敢打包票说你有工作了
I'd say you're as good as hired.

185
00:10:08,380 --> 00:10:10,580
这面试真的太带感了  泰德
Hell of a job interview, Ted.

186
00:10:10,940 --> 00:10:14,080
治安维持者通常会找有钱的混蛋
Usually the vigilante only goes after rich schmucks.

187
00:10:14,080 --> 00:10:16,510
为什么这次会为你破例呢
Any reason why he would change his M.O. For you?

188
00:10:19,530 --> 00:10:21,750
你认识我很长时间了  约翰
You've known me a long time, John.

189
00:10:22,320 --> 00:10:24,000
你怎么想的呢
What do you think?

190
00:10:28,440 --> 00:10:30,340
他可能搞错了吧
That he made a mistake.

191
00:10:31,600 --> 00:10:33,320
找错人了
Got the wrong guy.

192
00:10:38,130 --> 00:10:40,040
我可能会射到你  我可能会杀死你
I could've shot you. I could've killed you.

193
00:10:40,040 --> 00:10:41,580
你到底在想什么
What the hell were you thinking?!

194
00:10:41,580 --> 00:10:43,590
我不会让你无凭无证就诬陷一个清白之人
I'm not gonna let you William Tell an innocent man.

195
00:10:43,590 --> 00:10:44,920
盖纳不是清白的  狄格尔
Gaynor isn't innocent, Diggle.

196
00:10:44,920 --> 00:10:45,780
你会这样看他
You seem to think that

197
00:10:45,780 --> 00:10:47,330
还不是因为那破本子
mainly because of what's in you're damn book,

198
00:10:47,330 --> 00:10:49,060
你宁愿相信那本破本子也不相信我
which you apparently trust more than you trust me.

199
00:10:49,070 --> 00:10:51,090
我相信我的父亲
I trust my father.

200
00:10:51,210 --> 00:10:54,100
他向我解释说  名单上涉及的所有人
And he explained to me that every name on that list

201
00:10:54,100 --> 00:10:55,600
都该受到惩罚
has a reason to be there.

202
00:10:55,600 --> 00:10:57,480
我以为你从你爸爸的尸体上拿到的书
I thought you took that book off your father's dead body.

203
00:10:57,480 --> 00:10:59,450
他要怎么跟你唠叨这些
How can he have been so chatty?

204
00:11:01,520 --> 00:11:03,960
几年前  我找到了他留给我的讯息
A few years ago, I found a message he left me

205
00:11:03,960 --> 00:11:05,490
解释了这份名单
explaining the list.

206
00:11:05,490 --> 00:11:06,960
奥利弗  这怎么可能
Oliver, how is that possible?

207
00:11:06,960 --> 00:11:08,280
你流落在一个荒岛上
You were on a deserted island.

208
00:11:08,280 --> 00:11:11,200
我又没说我在荒岛上找到的
I didn't say that I found it on the island.

209
00:11:12,830 --> 00:11:14,580
狄格尔  过去四个月
Diggle, for the past 4 months,

210
00:11:14,580 --> 00:11:18,010
我说谎  隐瞒  伤害
I have lied to, hurt, and hid things

211
00:11:18,010 --> 00:11:20,120
所有我在意的人
from all the people that I care about.

212
00:11:20,130 --> 00:11:23,330
你真的觉得我会在毫无把握的情况下
Do you really think that I would do all of this

213
00:11:23,330 --> 00:11:25,660
出手吗
if I wasn't sure?

214
00:11:30,930 --> 00:11:33,630
奥利弗  盖纳要我加入黑鹰
Oliver, listen. Gaynor got me into Blackhawk,

215
00:11:33,630 --> 00:11:35,700
我会证明他是无辜的
and I'm gonna prove he's innocent.

216
00:11:37,540 --> 00:11:38,990
那如果他有罪呢
And if he isn't?

217
00:11:39,070 --> 00:11:41,460
如果他不是  我会亲手将他绳之以法
If he's not, I'll be the one to take him down myself.

218
00:11:41,460 --> 00:11:43,090
这是你欠我的
You owe me that.

219
00:11:45,440 --> 00:11:47,450
至少欠我这些
You owe me at least that.

220
00:11:54,620 --> 00:11:56,910
你驻扎在这附近吗
Were you stationed by the perimeter?

221
00:11:56,910 --> 00:11:59,240
-是  -你报道了吗
- Yes. - And your report?

222
00:11:59,240 --> 00:12:02,020
一切顺利  长官  没问题
Uh, everything's good, sir. No trouble.

223
00:12:02,020 --> 00:12:04,500
你在这儿驻扎多久了
How long have you been stationed here?

224
00:12:05,070 --> 00:12:06,690
我刚来  长官
Just arrived, sir.

225
00:12:06,690 --> 00:12:09,200
你看起来的确像个菜鸟
Yes, you do seem rather green.

226
00:12:11,090 --> 00:12:12,720
不过我不记得最近有潜艇
Although I don't recall the submarine

227
00:12:12,720 --> 00:12:15,650
送一批新兵过来
bringing in a phalanx of new troops lately.

228
00:12:18,490 --> 00:12:20,420
潜艇
Submarine?

229
00:12:20,420 --> 00:12:23,880
我还以为大家都是乘飞机上岛的
I thought everybody came into the island on the plane.

230
00:12:25,450 --> 00:12:27,100
确实如此
Indeed they do.

231
00:12:33,110 --> 00:12:35,560
我感觉你把全城的裙子都试过一遍了
I think you've tried on every dress in the city.

232
00:12:35,560 --> 00:12:37,030
我觉得很值得
It's so gonna be worth it.

233
00:12:37,030 --> 00:12:39,040
我的朋友们一定会很吃惊
My friends are gonna freak.

234
00:12:39,040 --> 00:12:42,120
如果你爸爸还活着  他也会很吃惊
Yes, well, if your father were still alive, he'd freak, too.

235
00:12:42,120 --> 00:12:44,460
不过吃惊的角度不太一样
Though in an entirely different way.

236
00:12:44,460 --> 00:12:46,200
就像当时他看到我
Like when he saw what I was wearing

237
00:12:46,200 --> 00:12:47,650
第一次搭异性舞伴时的穿着
to my first boy-girl dance.

238
00:12:47,650 --> 00:12:50,030
你搭的可怜的小男孩
That poor boy you went with.

239
00:12:50,030 --> 00:12:52,460
罗伯特把他吓得够呛
Oh, Robert scared him to death.

240
00:12:52,460 --> 00:12:54,180
爸爸以前常说
You know, dad used to say

241
00:12:54,180 --> 00:12:57,630
他最伤心的一天  就是我的18岁生日
his saddest day would be when I turned 18.

242
00:12:58,670 --> 00:13:02,490
现在他不在了  我才是那个伤心的人
Now he's gone and I'm the one that's sad.

243
00:13:07,070 --> 00:13:08,450
抱歉
Sorry.

244
00:13:09,210 --> 00:13:11,730
{\an8}马尔科姆来电

245
00:13:10,320 --> 00:13:12,260
我得接这个电话
I need to take this.

246
00:13:13,790 --> 00:13:15,130
喂
Hello.

247
00:13:16,470 --> 00:13:19,340
我明白  但我现在正和我女儿在一起
Yes, I understand, but I'm with my daughter.

248
00:13:22,480 --> 00:13:24,780
好  我会去的
All right. I'll be there.

249
00:13:28,010 --> 00:13:30,270
你不是说今天一整天都陪我的吗
I thought you said we were gonna spend the whole day together.

250
00:13:30,270 --> 00:13:31,680
我知道
I know.

251
00:13:31,840 --> 00:13:33,460
但是
But, uh,

252
00:13:33,830 --> 00:13:36,580
监察部需要我签署文件
Compliance needs to file the 8k

253
00:13:36,580 --> 00:13:39,160
因为我暂代沃尔特在公司的职位
connected to my assuming Walter's position in the company

254
00:13:39,160 --> 00:13:41,120
他们可不能等
and they can't wait.

255
00:13:42,980 --> 00:13:44,440
抱歉
I'm sorry.

256
00:13:46,380 --> 00:13:48,110
你还好吗
Is everything ok?

257
00:13:48,380 --> 00:13:49,990
你看起来很焦虑
You look worried.

258
00:13:50,240 --> 00:13:52,320
不是焦虑  只是...
Not worried, just...

259
00:13:54,490 --> 00:13:56,210
我爸爸打来电话
my father called.

260
00:13:59,610 --> 00:14:00,650
怎么了
And how did that go?

261
00:14:00,650 --> 00:14:03,430
他邀请我们今晚一起吃饭
He invited us to dinner for tonight.

262
00:14:05,490 --> 00:14:07,440
很明显他想修补一下父子关系
Apparently he wants to mend some fences,

263
00:14:07,440 --> 00:14:10,320
但多亏了他  我连根篱笆都买不起
but thanks to him, I can't afford a fence,

264
00:14:10,320 --> 00:14:12,410
所以我只能假设他有别的事情
so I can only assume he's got some other agenda.

265
00:14:12,410 --> 00:14:14,460
只有一种方法可以知道他的目的
Well, there's only one way to find out.

266
00:14:14,460 --> 00:14:18,760
或许他是要向我们伸出橄榄枝
Maybe he really is trying to extend an ove branch.

267
00:14:20,640 --> 00:14:23,880
你总是把人往好的方面想
You really do look for the best in people, don't you?

268
00:14:24,120 --> 00:14:25,710
算你走运
Lucky for you.

269
00:14:33,680 --> 00:14:36,300
抱歉今天打扰你享受天伦之乐了
I'm sorry to have to pull you away from your family like that.

270
00:14:36,300 --> 00:14:37,440
你想怎么样  马尔科姆
What do you want, Malcolm?

271
00:14:37,440 --> 00:14:40,760
我们和你朋友卡尔·巴拉德有些矛盾
We have a problem with your friend Carl Ballard.

272
00:14:40,760 --> 00:14:43,280
他试图收购空地
He's trying to gentrify the glades.

273
00:14:44,650 --> 00:14:46,430
卡尔知道那不是计划的一部分
Carl knows that's not part of the plan.

274
00:14:46,440 --> 00:14:48,890
所以你要去让他停手
Which is why you're gonna shut him down.

275
00:14:49,200 --> 00:14:51,520
你是他的朋友  他会听你的话的
You're his friend. He'll listen to you.

276
00:14:53,150 --> 00:14:54,670
如果你要我去处理卡尔
If you want me to help you with Carl,

277
00:14:54,670 --> 00:14:56,810
我要一些回报
I want something in return.

278
00:14:57,600 --> 00:15:01,400
证明沃尔特还活着
Proof Walter's still alive.

279
00:15:02,480 --> 00:15:03,890
我的话还不够吗
My word isn't enough?

280
00:15:05,230 --> 00:15:06,510
有句话说得好
What's that saying--

281
00:15:06,510 --> 00:15:08,620
"信任也需要核实"
"Trust but verify"?

282
00:15:12,520 --> 00:15:13,960
人生箴言
Words to live by.

283
00:15:25,310 --> 00:15:28,410
两天后  我还在汽车排气口掏
Two days later, I am still digging regurgitated tacos

284
00:15:28,410 --> 00:15:29,520
令人反胃的玉米面豆卷
out of the car vents

285
00:15:29,520 --> 00:15:32,190
他居然问我为什么不开空调
and he asks me why I won't turn on the A/C.

286
00:15:33,050 --> 00:15:34,320
好吧  你赢了
All right, you win.

287
00:15:34,320 --> 00:15:36,140
保镖女王可没那么差
Bodyguarding queen was never that bad.

288
00:15:36,140 --> 00:15:38,790
为国效力六年  我唯一有资格的
6 years serving my country, the only thing I'm qualified for

289
00:15:38,790 --> 00:15:40,600
就是给娇生惯养的富家子当保姆
is babysitting spoiled brats.

290
00:15:40,600 --> 00:15:42,270
泰德  他们并不都是如此的
Well, Ted, they're not all like that.

291
00:15:42,270 --> 00:15:45,970
我还没遇到过一个能在乡下呆一天的
I haven't met one yet that would survive a single day in country.

292
00:15:46,010 --> 00:15:48,540
有时我会想  我到底是做什么的
Sometimes it makes me wonder what I was doing over there.

293
00:15:48,570 --> 00:15:50,190
招牌菜
Specialty of the house.

294
00:15:50,700 --> 00:15:51,370
谢谢你  卡莉
Thank you, Carly.

295
00:15:51,370 --> 00:15:53,010
我的那份呢
Where is my cake?

296
00:15:53,010 --> 00:15:54,710
没有你的  受够了你一直抱怨
No. Tired of listening to you complain

297
00:15:54,720 --> 00:15:56,360
干洗店让你的西装缩水
about the dry cleaners shrinking your suit.

298
00:15:56,370 --> 00:15:57,470
没错
Oh, yeah.

299
00:16:02,940 --> 00:16:04,220
她喜欢你
She likes you.

300
00:16:04,420 --> 00:16:06,250
她是我的嫂子  泰德
She's my sister-in-law, Ted.

301
00:16:06,380 --> 00:16:07,600
不再是了
Not anymore.

302
00:16:08,450 --> 00:16:10,170
你哥哥已经不在了  约翰
Your brother's gone, John.

303
00:16:10,670 --> 00:16:12,160
但你还在
But you are here.

304
00:16:15,630 --> 00:16:18,020
车在外面  要载客人去
Car's waiting outside. Got a client to drop off

305
00:16:18,020 --> 00:16:19,830
切金艺术馆的开幕典礼
at the Chaykin art gallery opening.

306
00:16:20,110 --> 00:16:21,580
约翰  你还记得保罗·诺克斯吗
John, you remember Paul Knox?

307
00:16:21,580 --> 00:16:24,030
他曾经在阿富汗工作过
He was a couple of ranks under us back in the 'Stan.

308
00:16:27,160 --> 00:16:28,540
很高兴能和你一起工作
Good to be working with you.

309
00:16:32,960 --> 00:16:34,180
我在外面等你
I'll be outside.

310
00:16:38,620 --> 00:16:40,270
我不知道诺克斯在黑鹰工作
I didn't know Knox worked at Blackhawk.

311
00:16:40,280 --> 00:16:43,290
上过月他休假回来  他们雇佣了他
They recruited him when his tour ended last month.

312
00:16:44,660 --> 00:16:46,270
人是会改变的  约翰
People change, John.

313
00:16:47,360 --> 00:16:49,620
而且每个人都有机会来证明这一点
And everyone deserves a chance to prove it.

314
00:17:07,720 --> 00:17:09,600
敲门不能光在嘴上说
Knocking is not just a suggestion.

315
00:17:09,600 --> 00:17:11,240
我需要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.

316
00:17:11,340 --> 00:17:13,150
西娅  我不会告诉你
Thea, I'm not telling you

317
00:17:13,150 --> 00:17:14,950
妈要送你的礼物是不是辆车
if mom's getting you a car.

318
00:17:15,250 --> 00:17:17,360
不是那件事
It's not about that.

319
00:17:18,230 --> 00:17:20,320
你记不记得上周我问你
Remember last week when I asked you

320
00:17:20,320 --> 00:17:22,300
是不是觉得妈很奇怪
if you thought mom was acting weird?

321
00:17:22,300 --> 00:17:23,370
记得
Yeah.

322
00:17:23,550 --> 00:17:25,310
我知道为什么了
Well, I found out why.

323
00:17:26,070 --> 00:17:28,650
她和汤米的爸爸在一起了
She's hooking up with Tommy's dad.

324
00:17:29,740 --> 00:17:30,790
太离谱了
That's insane.

325
00:17:30,790 --> 00:17:33,080
我看到他们在一起了
I just saw them together.

326
00:17:33,560 --> 00:17:35,860
他们又旧情复燃了
It's happening all over again.

327
00:17:35,870 --> 00:17:37,450
你在说什么
What are you talking about?

328
00:17:42,450 --> 00:17:47,500
在你和爸爸登上金牌号的几个月前
A couple of months before you and dad left on the "Gambit,"

329
00:17:48,080 --> 00:17:50,010
他们就经常在吵架
mom and dad were arguing a lot.

330
00:17:50,010 --> 00:17:50,820
吵什么
About what?

331
00:17:50,820 --> 00:17:51,900
不知道
I don't know.

332
00:17:52,170 --> 00:17:54,220
但她当时就经常和
But she was having a lot of these...

333
00:17:54,970 --> 00:17:57,840
梅林先生吃午餐
lunch meetings with Mr. Merlyn.

334
00:17:57,840 --> 00:18:01,150
现在沃尔特也走了  妈妈就和梅林先生
And now Walter's gone, too, and mom and Mr. Merlyn

335
00:18:01,150 --> 00:18:03,390
重修旧好了  真恶心
are back at it. It's gross.

336
00:18:04,140 --> 00:18:06,930
妈妈永远都不会背着爸爸出轨的
Mom never would have cheated on dad.

337
00:18:07,260 --> 00:18:09,050
她也不会对沃尔特不忠
She's not cheating on Walter.

338
00:18:11,250 --> 00:18:12,350
你不愿意相信
You don't want to believe it,

339
00:18:12,350 --> 00:18:15,840
是因为妈在你心中拥有完美的形象
because you have this perfect image of mom in your head.

340
00:18:16,630 --> 00:18:19,620
但那个不是真的她  奥利
That's not who she is, Ollie.

341
00:18:19,770 --> 00:18:21,260
她不仅说谎
She's a liar

342
00:18:21,330 --> 00:18:22,910
还是个背叛者
and a cheater.

343
00:18:24,520 --> 00:18:26,890
你真的完全不了解她
And you really don't know her at all.

344
00:18:43,050 --> 00:18:45,260
她以为我和马尔科姆有外遇
She thinks Malcolm and I are having an affair?

345
00:18:45,260 --> 00:18:47,340
爸爸还在的时候就这么想了
And that it started back when dad was still alive.

346
00:18:47,340 --> 00:18:48,560
她为什么会这么想
Why would she think that?

347
00:18:48,560 --> 00:18:50,250
她说你和爸爸一直在争吵
She says you and dad were fighting.

348
00:18:52,380 --> 00:18:53,490
妈妈
Mom...

349
00:18:53,680 --> 00:18:55,060
这不是你该担心的事  亲爱的
It's not your concern, sweetheart.

350
00:18:55,070 --> 00:18:56,840
西娅的话让我担心
Thea made it my concern.

351
00:19:01,230 --> 00:19:02,650
到底怎么回事
What was going on?

352
00:19:09,680 --> 00:19:15,840
罗伯特曾多次出轨
Robert was unfaithful to me repeatedly.

353
00:19:17,620 --> 00:19:20,740
退一步讲  这让我们的婚姻很难维持
It made our marriage difficult, to say the least.

354
00:19:22,640 --> 00:19:23,750
抱歉  奥利弗  但你的父亲
I'm sorry, Oliver, but your father

355
00:19:23,750 --> 00:19:26,180
不是那个你一直想的那个人
wasn't always the man you thought he was.

356
00:19:26,810 --> 00:19:29,170
我知道他在你心中有多完美
I know you thought he walked on water,

357
00:19:29,260 --> 00:19:31,890
但你知道吗  我就想让你这样记住他
but, you see, that how I wanted you to remember him--

358
00:19:31,960 --> 00:19:33,910
一个爱你们的好男人
As a good man who loved you.

359
00:19:33,950 --> 00:19:36,370
我也是希望西娅能这样记住他的
That's how I want Thea to remember him.

360
00:19:36,370 --> 00:19:38,990
所以答应我保守这个秘密
So promise me you'll keep it a secret.

361
00:19:41,710 --> 00:19:42,810
当然
Of course.

362
00:19:47,010 --> 00:19:47,700
妈妈
Mom.

363
00:19:47,700 --> 00:19:48,750
怎么了
Yes?

364
00:19:49,400 --> 00:19:51,650
为什么西娅觉得你和梅林先生
Why would Thea think that you and Mr. Merlyn

365
00:19:51,650 --> 00:19:53,270
还在一起
are still sneaking around?

366
00:19:54,220 --> 00:19:55,970
我也不晓得
Well, I can't imagine.

367
00:19:58,800 --> 00:20:00,530
你最近见过他吗
Have you seen him lately?

368
00:20:01,870 --> 00:20:02,860
奥利弗
Oliver...

369
00:20:05,050 --> 00:20:08,660
他担任梅林环球集团的总裁已经很多年了
He's been the CEO of Merlyn Global Group for years.

370
00:20:08,670 --> 00:20:12,250
而我经营奎恩联合企业只有数周
I've been running Queen Consolidated mere weeks.

371
00:20:12,250 --> 00:20:16,030
没错  我是偶尔要向他请教
Yes, I occasionally go and ask for advice.

372
00:20:19,290 --> 00:20:21,370
对我的审讯结束了吗
Is my interrogation over?

373
00:20:40,460 --> 00:20:42,800
这里就是我们
See, this is where we, uh,

374
00:20:42,800 --> 00:20:45,670
关押有逃跑企图囚犯的地方
detain prisoners prone to running off

375
00:20:46,090 --> 00:20:47,990
在我解决他们之前
before I've finished with them.

376
00:20:59,630 --> 00:21:01,820
就像你一样的犯人  奎恩先生
Prisoners like you, Mr. Queen.

377
00:21:08,440 --> 00:21:10,180
有一年的圣诞
At Christmas one year,

378
00:21:11,140 --> 00:21:12,790
汤米想要一只小狗
Tommy wanted a puppy.

379
00:21:13,070 --> 00:21:14,930
他想给它起名叫亚瑟
He wanted to name it Arthur,

380
00:21:14,930 --> 00:21:18,250
亚瑟就是亚瑟王  因为他是梅林
As in King Arthur, because he's a Merlyn.

381
00:21:15,300 --> 00:21:17,960
{\an8}梅林和亚瑟王是挚友

382
00:21:19,270 --> 00:21:21,480
你以前真是超级可爱
Well, you used to be so incredibly adorable.

383
00:21:21,480 --> 00:21:22,620
我现在也是
I still am.

384
00:21:23,250 --> 00:21:24,990
我太太应该会很喜欢你  劳拉
My wife would have liked you, Laurel.

385
00:21:27,010 --> 00:21:28,400
我真希望我能认识她
I wish I would have known her.

386
00:21:28,400 --> 00:21:30,810
她在我和汤米成为朋友前就去世了
She passed away before Tommy and I became friends.

387
00:21:30,820 --> 00:21:33,870
她是被杀害的  劳拉  可以直说的
She was killed, Laurel. There's no need to be polite about it.

388
00:21:34,390 --> 00:21:36,850
你今天还挺高兴的  是吧  爸爸
You're just a ray of sunshine today, aren't you, dad?

389
00:21:36,930 --> 00:21:39,610
请原谅我  谈起我妻子会让我
Please forgive me. Talking about my wife has a tendency

390
00:21:39,610 --> 00:21:41,490
有些伤感
to make me a little bit maudlin.

391
00:21:49,570 --> 00:21:51,870
我还以为我不用再做
And here I was beginning to think my days of being

392
00:21:51,870 --> 00:21:54,450
奥利弗·奎恩的私人电脑极客了
Oliver Queen's personal computer geek were coming to an end.

393
00:21:51,870 --> 00:21:54,450
{\an8}极客：智力超群，善于钻研

394
00:21:54,450 --> 00:21:55,840
那就是你对我表达思念的方式吗
Is that your way of saying you miss me?

395
00:21:55,840 --> 00:21:59,250
不  但你要是那么想  就算是吧
No. But if it works for you, go with it.

396
00:21:59,620 --> 00:22:01,730
我的一个朋友在玩寻宝游戏
Heh. So a friend of mine is running a scavenger hunt,

397
00:22:01,740 --> 00:22:05,670
最后等着他的是一箱82年拉菲罗斯柴尔德
and there's a case of Lafite Rothschild 1982 waiting at the end.

398
00:22:05,670 --> 00:22:06,980
我爱死红葡萄酒了
Oh...I love red wine.

399
00:22:06,980 --> 00:22:08,670
但是想找到它
But in order to find it,

400
00:22:08,710 --> 00:22:10,630
我得先过了这一关
I first need to get through this.

401
00:22:13,130 --> 00:22:14,560
安全卡
Hmm. Security fob.

402
00:22:25,060 --> 00:22:26,490
有私人密码保护
It's PIN protected.

403
00:22:26,560 --> 00:22:28,600
质询响应回溯到一家名叫
Challenge response goes back to a company called

404
00:22:28,600 --> 00:22:30,650
黑鹰小队保护集团的公司
Blackhawk Squad Protection Group.

405
00:22:30,650 --> 00:22:32,870
我朋友的保镖给他办理的
Yeah, my friend had his bodyguard set it up for him.

406
00:22:32,870 --> 00:22:35,540
但是我个人认为这是骗人玩的  管他呢
Personally, however, I think it's cheating. But whatever.

407
00:22:35,970 --> 00:22:39,330
这是军用级别的加密安全协议
This is a military-grade cryptographic security protocol.

408
00:22:39,600 --> 00:22:42,200
你朋友真的能惹上这样的事
Your friend really went to all this trouble?

409
00:22:42,200 --> 00:22:44,350
阔佬都很难取悦
The idle rich are hard to entertain.

410
00:22:44,720 --> 00:22:46,030
听着
Listen...

411
00:22:46,330 --> 00:22:50,290
你破解掉这个  其中一瓶葡萄酒就归你了
You get through it and one of those bottles of wine is yours.

412
00:23:02,900 --> 00:23:05,870
我很开心  梅林先生  谢谢你
This been lovely, Mr. Merlyn. Thank you.

413
00:23:05,870 --> 00:23:07,580
感谢你和我一起用餐
Thank you for joining me.

414
00:23:07,580 --> 00:23:10,480
能加深对你的了解真的非常好
It's been wonderful getting to know you better.

415
00:23:10,940 --> 00:23:11,710
希望汤米不介意
And if Tommy doesn't mind

416
00:23:11,710 --> 00:23:14,000
我在这高兴的氛围下谈点业务
me mixing a little business with pleasure,

417
00:23:14,010 --> 00:23:16,850
我需要你在这上面签名
I could use your signature on these.

418
00:23:29,200 --> 00:23:31,080
你要关闭妈妈的免费诊所
You want to shut down mom's free clinic?

419
00:23:31,080 --> 00:23:32,580
不再是她的了  汤米
It's not hers anymore, Tommy.

420
00:23:32,580 --> 00:23:35,230
那个诊所对妈妈来说意义重大
That clinic meant everything to mom.

421
00:23:35,230 --> 00:23:37,080
你那时才8岁  我认为你并不清楚
You were 8 years old. I don't think you were in a position

422
00:23:37,080 --> 00:23:39,400
什么对你妈妈来说是重要的
to know what was important to your mother.

423
00:23:39,450 --> 00:23:40,610
我只需要你的签名
I just need your signature--

424
00:23:40,610 --> 00:23:41,710
停
Stop.

425
00:23:42,360 --> 00:23:43,380
这顿饭
This dinner

426
00:23:44,180 --> 00:23:46,180
根本不是为了认识劳蕾尔
was never about getting to know Laurel.

427
00:23:46,190 --> 00:23:47,680
而是为了这个
It was about this.

428
00:23:59,270 --> 00:24:01,550
你一点也没变也不会改变
You haven't changed and you never will.

429
00:24:02,450 --> 00:24:04,990
也该看清这点了
It's about time that I learned that

430
00:24:04,990 --> 00:24:07,590
我不会再让你让我失望了
and stopped letting you disappoint me.

431
00:24:08,760 --> 00:24:09,880
我们走
We're leaving.

432
00:24:14,030 --> 00:24:16,400
这个诊所是他母亲的
This clinic was his mother's.

433
00:24:16,400 --> 00:24:17,320
是的
Yes.

434
00:24:17,320 --> 00:24:19,370
他母亲给他上了一堂课  也是我一直想告诉他的
And his mother taught him a lesson I've been trying to,

435
00:24:19,380 --> 00:24:22,420
世界是苛刻无情的
that the world is a harsh and unforgiving place.

436
00:24:22,420 --> 00:24:24,500
她是什么时候教他那个的
And when did she teach him that?

437
00:24:28,040 --> 00:24:30,010
在她头上中了一枪
When she was lying dead in the street

438
00:24:30,180 --> 00:24:31,940
横尸街头的时候
with a bullet in her head.

439
00:24:34,670 --> 00:24:35,760
晚安
Good night.

440
00:24:40,720 --> 00:24:43,700
管理使得事物平稳运行  很不错
Management keeps things running smooth, which is nice.

441
00:24:44,070 --> 00:24:46,830
比提枪上战场好多了  对吧
Better than going to war with the army you got, right?

442
00:24:47,000 --> 00:24:47,990
的确
Indeed.

443
00:24:48,010 --> 00:24:49,420
的确
Indeed.

444
00:24:50,520 --> 00:24:53,150
泰德  诺克斯是因为你才去黑鹰工作的吗
So, Ted, are you the reason Knox is working for Blackhawk?

445
00:24:53,660 --> 00:24:56,470
我知道你不喜欢他
Look, I know you don't like the guy.

446
00:24:56,540 --> 00:24:58,080
我也不怎么待见他
I wasn't his biggest fan, either,

447
00:24:58,080 --> 00:25:02,440
但这年头工作都不好找啊
but jobs are hard to come by for everybody these days.

448
00:25:02,470 --> 00:25:04,040
咱们这样的人
And guys like us,

449
00:25:04,530 --> 00:25:05,260
所有人都认为
when all anyone thinks

450
00:25:05,270 --> 00:25:07,750
你最会做的就是朝人开枪
you're qualified for is shooting at people--

451
00:25:07,750 --> 00:25:09,910
要是我没给诺克斯这份工作
If I hadn't gotten Knox this job,

452
00:25:10,060 --> 00:25:12,270
他很有可能就去抢酒馆
chances are he'd be out knocking over liquor stores

453
00:25:12,270 --> 00:25:13,950
或者抢银行了
or robbing banks.

454
00:25:21,690 --> 00:25:22,500
你发现了什么
What did you get?

455
00:25:22,510 --> 00:25:25,110
我觉得你朋友的保镖给了他错的安全卡
I think your friend's bodyguard gave him the wrong security fob.

456
00:25:25,120 --> 00:25:25,700
这怎么说
Why is that?

457
00:25:25,700 --> 00:25:28,550
我进入黑鹰的认证系统之后
Well, once I got past Blackhawk's authentication system,

458
00:25:28,550 --> 00:25:31,390
没看见任何有关寻宝游戏的信息
there wasn't anything about a scavenger hunt.

459
00:25:31,800 --> 00:25:33,800
只有目录和...
Just a directory and...

460
00:25:34,020 --> 00:25:35,610
我觉得你无意间
Well, I think you stumbled onto,

461
00:25:35,610 --> 00:25:39,070
或者是让我无意间发现了非法的事情
or got me to stumble onto something pretty illegal.

462
00:25:39,070 --> 00:25:40,040
定义非法
Define illegal.

463
00:25:40,040 --> 00:25:43,080
用枪榴弹发射器和催泪瓦斯
Oh, you know. Robbing an armored car

464
00:25:43,080 --> 00:25:44,900
抢劫装甲车
with grenade launchers and tear gas.

465
00:25:44,900 --> 00:25:46,200
-什么  -黑鹰里有人
- What? - Someone at Blackhawk

466
00:25:46,210 --> 00:25:48,860
用他们的系统窃取这座城市七个主要的
was using their system to store detailed routes and schedules

467
00:25:48,860 --> 00:25:51,590
装甲车运送公司的详细路线和时间表
for each of the city's 7 major armored car carriers,

468
00:25:51,600 --> 00:25:53,350
包括已经被袭击的三个
including the 3 that have already been hit.

469
00:25:53,350 --> 00:25:54,690
奎恩先生  我认为
Mr. Queen, I think

470
00:25:54,690 --> 00:25:56,550
应该把这个消息告知警方
we should provide this information to the police.

471
00:25:56,560 --> 00:25:58,720
有了这个  他们应该可以推测出下一次抢劫
With it, they should be able to predict the next heist.

472
00:25:58,720 --> 00:26:00,130
等等  费利西蒂
Hold on. Felicity,

473
00:26:00,240 --> 00:26:02,050
我不希望你因为我朋友的事遇上麻烦
I don't want you to get in trouble with my friend,

474
00:26:02,050 --> 00:26:04,500
帮我个忙  把那个目录传给我
so do me a favor. Forward that directory on to me

475
00:26:04,510 --> 00:26:06,880
我会亲自去通知警方
and I'll get it to the police personally.

476
00:26:07,070 --> 00:26:08,120
谢谢你
Thank you.

477
00:26:10,660 --> 00:26:12,450
看来没有葡萄酒了
So, no wine, then?

478
00:27:01,360 --> 00:27:02,130
布莱克
Blake.

479
00:27:02,130 --> 00:27:03,510
布莱克  撑住  伙计
Blake. C'mon, man. C'mon.

480
00:27:11,890 --> 00:27:13,060
布莱克受伤了
Blake is hit.

481
00:27:13,060 --> 00:27:14,140
他受伤了
He's hit!

482
00:27:16,670 --> 00:27:18,950
我们走  快走
Let's go! Let's go!

483
00:27:42,900 --> 00:27:45,520
天呐  看啊
Aah! Oh, god, check it out!

484
00:27:45,520 --> 00:27:48,370
惊喜吧
You must be so surprised.

485
00:27:48,370 --> 00:27:51,120
这里的一切都太棒了
Oh, isn't everything absolutely perfect?

486
00:27:51,160 --> 00:27:53,560
可惜爸爸不在
Except for dad's not here.

487
00:27:54,120 --> 00:27:55,390
如果他在场
If dad were here,

488
00:27:55,390 --> 00:27:57,070
会说你看起来美极了
he'd say you look beautiful.

489
00:27:59,950 --> 00:28:02,080
失陪一下
Oh! Excuse me a sec.

490
00:28:08,480 --> 00:28:11,680
我听说兜帽男今晚阻止了装甲车抢劫
I heard the hood foiled an armored car heist this evening.

491
00:28:11,750 --> 00:28:13,300
发射火箭炮的不是盖纳
Gaynor wasn't running the rocket launcher.

492
00:28:13,300 --> 00:28:15,690
我知道  事发时我跟他在一起
I know. I was with him the whole time it was going down.

493
00:28:16,250 --> 00:28:17,590
看来你是对的
It looks like you were right.

494
00:28:18,140 --> 00:28:19,970
如果黑鹰里有谁涉案
Listen, if someone at Blackhawk is involved,

495
00:28:19,970 --> 00:28:21,350
我能肯定是诺克斯
I'd put my money on Knox.

496
00:28:21,350 --> 00:28:22,980
抢劫发生前他刚走
He started right before the heists began,

497
00:28:22,980 --> 00:28:24,530
他还受过军事训练
and he has military training.

498
00:28:24,570 --> 00:28:26,320
我打伤了一个
Ok. I injured one.

499
00:28:26,340 --> 00:28:28,970
他们逃到货车上的时候他流了好多血
He was bleeding pretty badly when they made off in their van.

500
00:28:29,200 --> 00:28:32,330
如果哪辆货车上有诺克斯的血
Ok, so if any of Knox's blood is in one of the motor pool vans,

501
00:28:32,330 --> 00:28:34,030
-就可以肯定是他  -我跟你一起去
- we'll know for sure. - I'm going with you.

502
00:28:34,030 --> 00:28:35,660
不不  你留下开派对
No, no, no, listen. You have this party.

503
00:28:35,660 --> 00:28:37,460
我说过我来处理这事
And I told you I would handle this.

504
00:28:37,570 --> 00:28:40,020
如果有什么事  打个电话就行
If there's any problems, you're just a phone call away.

505
00:28:42,710 --> 00:28:43,870
小心行事
Head on a swivel.

506
00:28:45,080 --> 00:28:46,680
我就是干这行的  老兄
That's the way I was born, man.

507
00:28:52,740 --> 00:28:53,700
生日快乐
Happy birthday!

508
00:28:53,700 --> 00:28:55,190
我会想你的
I'll miss you!

509
00:28:55,190 --> 00:28:57,080
我们给你准备了一份特别的生日礼物
We have a special birthday gift for you.

510
00:28:57,080 --> 00:28:59,970
它叫"迷魂"  会让你飘飘欲仙
It's called Vertigo. It's supposed to make you feel all floaty.

511
00:28:59,970 --> 00:29:02,240
如果我妈发现了
Uh, if my mom caught me with this,

512
00:29:02,240 --> 00:29:04,110
我就活不过今晚了
I wouldn't make it to 19.

513
00:29:04,110 --> 00:29:05,580
我去楼上把它放好
I'm gonna go put it upstairs,

514
00:29:05,580 --> 00:29:07,690
一会儿就回来
and then I'll be right back down.

515
00:29:17,320 --> 00:29:19,960
莫伊拉  给你看个东西
Moira, I have a little something for you.

516
00:29:20,700 --> 00:29:21,760
沃尔特
Walter...

517
00:29:23,290 --> 00:29:24,860
我做到了你要求的事
I did as you asked.

518
00:29:24,860 --> 00:29:27,350
现在轮到你做我要求的事了
Now it's your turn to do as I asked.

519
00:29:27,350 --> 00:29:28,850
我会搞定的
I'll take care of it.

520
00:29:29,860 --> 00:29:31,040
谢谢你  莫伊拉
Thank you, Moira

521
00:29:36,460 --> 00:29:37,740
在我的派对上
At my party.

522
00:29:38,230 --> 00:29:39,780
在我面前这样吗
Right here in front of me?

523
00:29:39,780 --> 00:29:41,350
不  西娅  你不明白
No, Thea, you don't understand.

524
00:29:41,350 --> 00:29:43,620
沃尔特才失踪了两个月
Walter hasn't been gone two months

525
00:29:43,620 --> 00:29:45,330
你就背着他乱搞
and you're already cheating on him.

526
00:29:45,330 --> 00:29:46,760
就像当年对爸爸一样
Just like you did on dad.

527
00:29:46,770 --> 00:29:48,610
西娅  我没有出轨
Thea, I never cheated.

528
00:29:48,610 --> 00:29:51,130
我不会相信你说的话
Like I would believe anything you say.

529
00:29:52,180 --> 00:29:56,530
不  我希望当年在游艇上的人是你
No. I wish it had been you that was on that boat.

530
00:30:19,180 --> 00:30:20,530
{\an8}黑鹰小队保护集团

531
00:30:22,180 --> 00:30:22,880
{\an8}黑鹰小队保护集团

532
00:30:57,410 --> 00:30:58,870
我就知道你会来
I had a feeling you'd show up.

533
00:31:00,690 --> 00:31:02,070
是吗  为什么  诺克斯
Yeah? Why is that, Knox?

534
00:31:02,750 --> 00:31:04,080
盖纳雇了你之后
Right after Gaynor got you hired,

535
00:31:04,090 --> 00:31:05,290
就有人黑了我们的系统
someone hacked our system.

536
00:31:05,290 --> 00:31:07,160
这之前没人能通过我们的防火墙
First person to ever make it through our firewall.

537
00:31:07,510 --> 00:31:08,860
你想说说这是怎么做到的吗
You want to tell me how you did it?

538
00:31:10,220 --> 00:31:11,380
不太清楚
I'm not really sure.

539
00:31:11,710 --> 00:31:13,590
他觉得你不会这么合作
He didn't think you'd be very cooperative.

540
00:31:13,590 --> 00:31:14,450
谁
Who?

541
00:31:20,810 --> 00:31:21,940
约翰
Hey, John.

542
00:31:29,680 --> 00:31:30,790
泰德  你也有份吗
Ted, you're part of this?

543
00:31:31,560 --> 00:31:32,680
不  不是有份
No, not part of.

544
00:31:33,710 --> 00:31:36,020
我的人  我的任务
My men. My mission.

545
00:31:37,280 --> 00:31:38,220
任务
Mission?

546
00:31:39,410 --> 00:31:40,840
这里又不是阿富汗
This isn't Afghanistan.

547
00:31:40,960 --> 00:31:42,540
我知道
Oh, don't I know that.

548
00:31:43,480 --> 00:31:45,770
在那里我们有几百万美金的
Over there we were trusted with millions of dollars

549
00:31:45,770 --> 00:31:47,320
武器和人力
in weapons and personnel.

550
00:31:48,710 --> 00:31:50,030
那时我们是征服者
We were conquerors.

551
00:31:51,340 --> 00:31:54,170
现在我们是拿着电击棒的小保姆
Now we're nannies with tasers.

552
00:31:56,970 --> 00:31:59,470
所以你们就能去偷
So that gives you the right to steal,

553
00:32:00,880 --> 00:32:02,380
去杀害无辜百姓吗
to kill innocent civilians?

554
00:32:02,380 --> 00:32:04,000
我不会说服你相信我是对的
I'm not gonna convince you I'm right.

555
00:32:05,130 --> 00:32:06,960
我会说服你加入我们团队
I am gonna convince you to join the team.

556
00:32:07,360 --> 00:32:09,050
现在我知道你疯了
Yeah, now I know you're crazy.

557
00:32:09,880 --> 00:32:11,790
今晚早些时候本来是我们最后一次行动
Earlier tonight was supposed to be our last score,

558
00:32:11,790 --> 00:32:13,760
但因为兜帽男  黄了
but because of the hood guy, we struck out.

559
00:32:15,020 --> 00:32:17,490
现在我们少了一个人
Now we're down a man.

560
00:32:18,850 --> 00:32:20,640
好消息是你有能力补上他的位置
Good thing you're qualified to take his place.

561
00:32:22,070 --> 00:32:23,210
泰德  我觉得你说服人的能力
Ted, I think your convincing

562
00:32:23,210 --> 00:32:25,100
有待提高啊
is gonna have to be a lot more convincing.

563
00:32:27,640 --> 00:32:28,730
收到
Copy that.

564
00:32:29,300 --> 00:32:30,300
卡瓦诺
Cavanaugh.

565
00:32:34,330 --> 00:32:35,330
卡莉
Carly.

566
00:32:37,080 --> 00:32:38,430
你这个贱人
You son of a bitch.

567
00:32:39,070 --> 00:32:39,750
不
No!

568
00:32:39,760 --> 00:32:41,590
别  别  等等
Don't! Don't! Wait!

569
00:32:41,660 --> 00:32:43,340
-别  -诺克斯
- Don't. - Knox.

570
00:32:48,570 --> 00:32:50,390
你们今晚都要死  约翰
You both can die tonight, John.

571
00:32:51,730 --> 00:32:53,530
除非我们同坐一条船
Or once we do this, we're on a plane

572
00:32:53,530 --> 00:32:55,180
她就能回去陪你侄子
and she can go home to your nephew.

573
00:32:55,880 --> 00:32:57,140
由你决定
It's your call.

574
00:33:36,220 --> 00:33:37,360
我们走
Come on, let's go.

575
00:33:38,390 --> 00:33:40,180
你不该那么做的  狄格
Well, you shouldn't have done that, Dig.

576
00:33:40,570 --> 00:33:42,910
现在你得眼睁睁看着我们杀死你的女友
Now you gotta watch us kill your pretty little girlfriend.

577
00:33:42,920 --> 00:33:44,560
不  求你了
No! Please don't!

578
00:33:44,560 --> 00:33:46,200
伙计们  你们忘了一件事
You're forgetting one thing, guys.

579
00:33:46,400 --> 00:33:47,910
是吗  什么事
Oh, yeah, what's that?

580
00:33:48,260 --> 00:33:49,930
我才是拿着手榴弹的人
I'm the one with the grenade.

581
00:33:52,460 --> 00:33:53,760
卡莉  快离开这
Carly, get out of there!

582
00:34:35,630 --> 00:34:36,640
不许动
Freeze!

583
00:34:41,120 --> 00:34:42,300
放下武器  泰德
Drop it, Ted,

584
00:34:42,710 --> 00:34:43,860
不然  我发誓我会
or I swear...

585
00:34:44,680 --> 00:34:47,560
不要  装腔作势
Don't...posture.

586
00:34:49,280 --> 00:34:50,850
你不会这么做的
You're not gonna do it.

587
00:34:52,590 --> 00:34:53,720
你不能
You can't.

588
00:34:54,870 --> 00:34:56,340
从你的眼睛就能看出来
I can see it in your eyes.

589
00:35:13,930 --> 00:35:14,930
你来晚了
You're late.

590
00:35:16,090 --> 00:35:17,450
你知道我要来
You knew I was coming?

591
00:35:21,350 --> 00:35:22,910
下次在别人身上装窃听器
Next time you plant a bug on someone,

592
00:35:22,910 --> 00:35:24,370
就不要让对方察觉
be more subtle about it.

593
00:35:26,540 --> 00:35:28,160
尽管我希望你能相信我
I wish you trusted me, though.

594
00:35:28,160 --> 00:35:29,550
我相信你  狄格尔
I trust you, Diggle.

595
00:35:31,530 --> 00:35:34,540
但他们不会
But them, never.

596
00:35:39,640 --> 00:35:40,820
你该走了
You should get out of here.

597
00:35:46,810 --> 00:35:47,830
约翰
John!

598
00:35:56,510 --> 00:35:58,630
卡莉  你还好吗
Carly. You ok?

599
00:35:59,830 --> 00:36:02,380
我们是警察  放下武器
This is the police! Drop your weapon!

600
00:36:41,650 --> 00:36:43,010
西娅
Oh, Thea.

601
00:36:43,890 --> 00:36:44,480
你还好吗
Are you ok?

602
00:36:44,480 --> 00:36:46,350
是的  我没事
Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.

603
00:36:47,100 --> 00:36:49,260
只是有点头痛
I'm just headachy, really.

604
00:36:50,060 --> 00:36:51,880
我的车  它  它是
The car--is--is it--

605
00:36:52,320 --> 00:36:54,300
西娅  别管车了
Thea, the car isn't important right now.

606
00:36:56,300 --> 00:36:57,980
你知道发生了什么吗  亲爱的
Do you remember what happened, sweetheart?

607
00:37:00,090 --> 00:37:01,550
我不想看到你
You go away.

608
00:37:03,820 --> 00:37:06,110
西娅  别这样
Thea, please.

609
00:37:06,110 --> 00:37:08,270
我说了我没事
I said I'm fine.

610
00:37:23,250 --> 00:37:25,270
你爸现在开始给我打电话了
Your father's even beginning to call me now.

611
00:37:25,280 --> 00:37:26,740
不要浪费时间
Don't waste your minutes.

612
00:37:30,100 --> 00:37:32,620
你父亲虽然是个混蛋  但他还是你父亲
Your father is a jerk, but he's still your father.

613
00:37:40,090 --> 00:37:41,900
我想他只是想
I think in his own way,

614
00:37:43,680 --> 00:37:46,530
他以为这么做可以保护你
I think he sees himself as protecting you somehow.

615
00:37:47,030 --> 00:37:50,030
是啊  他利用我过世母亲给自己辩护
Yeah. He is really good at using my dead mother

616
00:37:50,030 --> 00:37:51,900
这招很绝啊
for an excuse for being a jerk.

617
00:37:52,990 --> 00:37:54,490
你从没提起过你的母亲
You never talk about your mother.

618
00:37:56,780 --> 00:37:58,700
我那时才八岁  我记不清
I was only 8 and I don't remember much

619
00:37:58,700 --> 00:38:00,120
发生的事情
about what happened.

620
00:38:02,370 --> 00:38:03,590
但在那之后
But after...

621
00:38:04,920 --> 00:38:08,380
我父亲将我完全拒之门外
my father completely shut me out.

622
00:38:14,680 --> 00:38:15,950
然后自己走掉了
And then he went away.

623
00:38:18,460 --> 00:38:22,130
他走了有一两年
He was gone for maybe a year or two.

624
00:38:23,080 --> 00:38:27,070
我那时才八岁他竟离开了我
I was 8 and he left me.

625
00:38:27,110 --> 00:38:28,970
我看清了他的真面目
That is who my father is.

626
00:38:31,680 --> 00:38:33,360
他只考虑自己
He only cares about himself.

627
00:38:51,890 --> 00:38:53,190
警察没有难为你吧
Cops give you a hard time?

628
00:38:53,190 --> 00:38:54,470
没有  我跟他们解释
Nah. I explained to them to

629
00:38:54,470 --> 00:38:56,130
我和盖纳只是共同服役的伙伴
me and Gaynor were old war buddies.

630
00:38:56,140 --> 00:38:57,630
他企图拉我入伙
He tried to rope me in...

631
00:39:00,300 --> 00:39:01,630
被我拒绝后  他就绑架了卡莉
When I refused, he kidnapped Carly,

632
00:39:01,630 --> 00:39:03,190
我所做的一切都是被胁迫的
everything else happened under duress.

633
00:39:10,130 --> 00:39:11,470
我搞砸了  奥利弗
I screwed up, Oliver.

634
00:39:14,170 --> 00:39:16,470
很显然盖纳已不是我想象中的人了
Obviously Gaynor wasn't who I thought he was.

635
00:39:18,920 --> 00:39:20,110
我错了
I was wrong.

636
00:39:21,080 --> 00:39:22,470
是啊  但
Yeah, but...

637
00:39:23,690 --> 00:39:25,040
但你也有对的时候
You were right, too.

638
00:39:28,960 --> 00:39:29,950
当你跟我说
When you told me that I

639
00:39:29,950 --> 00:39:31,800
我宁愿信任那名单也不愿信任你
trusted the list more than I trusted you...

640
00:39:33,950 --> 00:39:37,050
狄格尔  事实上  当我从那孤岛回来后
Diggle, the truth is, after what happened to me on the island...

641
00:39:41,410 --> 00:39:45,860
我很难再去信任...任何事情
It's difficult for me to trust...anything.

642
00:39:48,640 --> 00:39:49,740
但你却可以
But you do.

643
00:39:52,330 --> 00:39:54,770
这也是我为什么选你当我的搭档
And that reminded me why I chose you as my partner.

644
00:39:57,040 --> 00:39:58,960
因为你总是看到人性最好的一面
It's because you see the best in people.

645
00:40:25,840 --> 00:40:28,040
{\an8}泰德·盖纳

646
00:40:34,940 --> 00:40:36,260
我也学到了一些东西
I learned something, too.

647
00:40:38,130 --> 00:40:39,610
要不是你告诉我  我永远也不想了解
Until you tell me, I'll never want to know

648
00:40:39,610 --> 00:40:41,340
名单上的其他人
what other names are in this book.

649
00:40:52,470 --> 00:40:54,520
她向我保证了她没有欺骗沃尔特
She promised me she's not cheating on Walter.

650
00:40:54,520 --> 00:40:57,100
难道我会相信那女人说的话吗
Like I would trust anything that woman says.

651
00:40:57,100 --> 00:40:59,230
奎恩小姐  西娅·奎恩
Miss Queen! Thea Queen?

652
00:40:59,580 --> 00:41:00,580
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?

653
00:41:00,580 --> 00:41:02,050
我们接到你医生的电话
We received a call from your doctor.

654
00:41:02,050 --> 00:41:03,540
在这起交通事故中
In the event of a vehicular accident,

655
00:41:03,540 --> 00:41:04,900
他们需要报告
They're required to report to result

656
00:41:04,910 --> 00:41:06,210
驾驶人毒性分析的结果
of the driver's tox screen.

657
00:41:06,210 --> 00:41:09,170
我们发现奎恩小姐吸食了一种叫"迷魂"的毒品
Miss Queen tested positive for a narcotic called Vertigo.

658
00:41:10,630 --> 00:41:12,590
这不是贫民窟那卖的毒品吗
The drug they're using in the glades?

659
00:41:12,750 --> 00:41:13,930
西娅·奎恩在吸食毒品后驾车
Thea Queen, you're under arrest

660
00:41:13,930 --> 00:41:16,200
你现已被捕
for driving under the influence of narcotics.

661
00:41:25,310 --> 00:41:26,570
你知道为什么我的人
Do you know why my men

662
00:41:26,570 --> 00:41:28,250
都要戴面罩吗  奎恩先生
wear balaclavas, Mr. Queen?

663
00:41:30,630 --> 00:41:33,100
因为它盖住了除了眼睛之外的部分
Because it masks everything but the eyes.

664
00:41:33,880 --> 00:41:37,060
通过一个人的眼睛就能发现真相
In a man's eyes, one can always find the truth.

665
00:41:39,030 --> 00:41:41,470
你不惜冒险去救你的朋友
You risked everything to save your friend.

666
00:41:42,290 --> 00:41:44,010
即使我已经提醒你这个人不可靠
Someone I warned you about,

667
00:41:45,170 --> 00:41:46,630
你却仍然相信他
yet you trusted him.

668
00:41:47,750 --> 00:41:50,140
但你的信任摆错了位置
But that trust was misplaced.

