1
00:00:54,150 --> 00:00:58,690
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

2
00:00:58,690 --> 00:01:04,050
翻译：冰蓝   鱼小姐   爱卿遛小鸟   不要叫我马维斯

3
00:01:55,900 --> 00:01:59,850
翻译：喵喵阿飘   luna_3   妄想的绒布熊

4
00:02:01,350 --> 00:02:06,350
时间轴：仓鼠sama  暮暮

5
00:02:06,350 --> 00:02:11,690
校对：陈小圈   喵喵阿飘   不要叫我马维斯

6
00:02:18,570 --> 00:02:23,570
后期：zzzyusa  总监：苹果果来拜年

7
00:00:00,680 --> 00:00:02,910
我的名字叫奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.

8
00:00:02,910 --> 00:00:06,610
五年里  我被困孤岛  只有一个目标
For 5 years I was stranded on an island with only one goal--

9
00:00:07,860 --> 00:00:08,850
生存
Survive.

10
00:00:08,850 --> 00:00:10,860
奥利弗·奎恩还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.

11
00:00:09,320 --> 00:00:10,560
{\pos(193,207)}最新新闻  失踪亿万富翁重现人间

12
00:00:10,620 --> 00:00:11,950
{\an8}年度报告

13
00:00:10,860 --> 00:00:13,400
现在我要完成父亲的遗愿
Now I will fulfill my father's dying wish--

14
00:00:13,400 --> 00:00:15,310
用他留给我的名单
to use the list of names he left me

15
00:00:15,310 --> 00:00:18,230
扳倒那些荼毒城市的人
and bring down those who are poisoning my city.

16
00:00:18,870 --> 00:00:21,620
要做这些   我必须伪装成另一个人
To do this, I must become someone else.

17
00:00:22,030 --> 00:00:25,330
我必须成为另一个存在
I must become something else.

18
00:00:25,330 --> 00:00:26,800
《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously on "Arrow"...

19
00:00:26,800 --> 00:00:27,730
斯莱德·威尔逊
Slade Wilson.

20
00:00:27,730 --> 00:00:30,020
十公里外有个机场
There's an airfield 10 clicks from here.

21
00:00:30,110 --> 00:00:31,500
那是离开这座岛的关键
It's key off this island.

22
00:00:31,500 --> 00:00:32,660
我觉得是姚飞让你来
I think Yao Fei sent you

23
00:00:32,660 --> 00:00:35,150
因为他知道我一个人不可能成功
because he knows I cannot take the airstrip alone.

24
00:00:35,410 --> 00:00:37,950
-你窃听了我妈妈  -你得听听
- You bugged my mother? - Just listen.

25
00:00:38,750 --> 00:00:40,700
我已经明确地告诉他
I made it clear to him persuasively

26
00:00:40,700 --> 00:00:43,140
他的计划会危及我们事业的发展
that his plans endangered the undertaking.

27
00:00:43,140 --> 00:00:44,070
你打算怎么做
What are you going to do?

28
00:00:44,070 --> 00:00:46,170
我得换种方式和我妈谈谈
I need to have another chat with my mom.

29
00:00:48,890 --> 00:00:51,860
这周之前必须完成那两家公司的合并
And I'll need the Unidac merger finalized by the end of the week.

30
00:00:51,860 --> 00:00:54,050
我们时间有限
We're on something of a clock here.

31
00:01:06,460 --> 00:01:07,700
莫伊拉·奎恩
Moira Queen,

32
00:01:08,260 --> 00:01:10,510
你辜负了这座城市
you have failed this city.

33
00:01:15,700 --> 00:01:17,430
站着别动
Stand still!

34
00:01:18,400 --> 00:01:19,730
求你别杀我
Please don't kill me.

35
00:01:20,710 --> 00:01:23,360
你是否知道你丈夫失踪的内情
Do you know anything about your husband's disappearance?

36
00:01:23,360 --> 00:01:26,020
-什么  -沃尔特·斯蒂尔还活着吗
- What?! - Is Walter Steele still alive?!

37
00:01:26,250 --> 00:01:28,280
我不知道我丈夫在哪里
I don't know where my husband is.

38
00:01:28,280 --> 00:01:29,340
我发誓
I swear.

39
00:01:30,250 --> 00:01:32,840
你知道事业的情况吗
Do you know anything about the undertaking?

40
00:01:32,840 --> 00:01:34,890
我说了不许动
I said don't move!

41
00:01:34,890 --> 00:01:36,350
我是一名母亲
I'm--I'm a mother.

42
00:01:37,280 --> 00:01:39,160
我有个儿子  奥利弗
I have a son--Oliver.

43
00:01:39,160 --> 00:01:42,000
还有个女儿  她叫西娅
A daughter, her name is Thea.

44
00:01:42,100 --> 00:01:45,470
她还只是个少女  求你别让我和他们生死诀别
She's just a teenager. Please don't take me from my children.

45
00:01:46,350 --> 00:01:47,860
他们已经失去了父亲
They lost their father.

46
00:01:48,420 --> 00:01:50,120
不能再失去我了
They can't lose me, too.

47
00:01:51,540 --> 00:01:54,250
求你了  不管你是谁  求你了
Please, whoever you are, please.

48
00:01:54,980 --> 00:01:55,900
好吧
Ok.

49
00:01:59,860 --> 00:02:01,340
我不会伤害你
I'm not going to hurt you.

50
00:02:11,690 --> 00:02:13,700
我是莫伊拉·奎恩  在39层楼
This is Moira Queen, I'm on the 39th floor,

51
00:02:13,700 --> 00:02:14,890
我需要帮助
I need help.

52
00:02:15,220 --> 00:02:16,810
有人闯入了
There's an intruder.

53
00:02:17,620 --> 00:02:18,560
快点
Please!

54
00:02:49,710 --> 00:02:51,670
我不会伤害你  费利西蒂
I'm not going to hurt you, Felicity.

55
00:02:51,670 --> 00:02:52,760
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?

56
00:02:54,190 --> 00:02:55,570
因为你也知道我的名字
Because you know my name.

57
00:02:58,200 --> 00:02:59,780
奥利弗
Oliver, oh...

58
00:03:01,980 --> 00:03:04,550
我突然明白了你的一切
Everything about you just became so unbelievably clear.

59
00:03:05,530 --> 00:03:06,410
你在流血
You're bleeding.

60
00:03:06,410 --> 00:03:07,860
不需要你告诉我
I don't need to be told that.

61
00:03:07,860 --> 00:03:08,860
你得去医院
You need a hospital.

62
00:03:08,930 --> 00:03:11,780
送我去我爸爸在贫民区的老工厂
My--My father's old factory, in the glades.

63
00:03:11,780 --> 00:03:14,070
不  你需要医生  不是炼钢工人
No, you-- you need a doctor, not a steelworker.

64
00:03:14,070 --> 00:03:16,540
费利西蒂  你得向我保证
Felicity...You have to promise me

65
00:03:16,540 --> 00:03:19,360
你要送我去我爸爸的工厂里
that you are going to take me to my father's factory

66
00:03:19,360 --> 00:03:20,630
不去别的地方
and nowhere else.

67
00:03:21,180 --> 00:03:22,610
我保证
Yeah, promise.

68
00:03:25,540 --> 00:03:28,160
我有种直觉  保险公司不会管血痕的事
Something tells me blood stains are not covered under my lease.

69
00:03:29,980 --> 00:03:32,010
警方目前不愿作出评论
So far the police are unwilling to comment,

70
00:03:32,010 --> 00:03:33,930
但未经证实的目击者报告
but unsubstantiated eyewitness reports

71
00:03:33,930 --> 00:03:37,530
表明星城的治安维持者于今晚早些时候
claims that the starling city vigilante attacked Mrs. Queen

72
00:03:35,620 --> 00:03:41,270
{\an8}袭击奎恩联合企业

73
00:03:37,530 --> 00:03:39,390
在奎恩女士的办公室袭击了她
in her office earlier tonight.

74
00:03:39,430 --> 00:03:41,020
在这场袭击中  她并未受伤
She was unharmed in the assault.

75
00:03:41,020 --> 00:03:41,930
打扰了
Excuse me.

76
00:03:42,710 --> 00:03:45,230
能帮帮我吗  他真的很沉
Can you help me? He's really heavy!

77
00:03:54,220 --> 00:03:55,680
该死
Oh, damn it.

78
00:03:55,790 --> 00:03:57,250
刚好错开颈动脉
He just missed a carotid.

79
00:03:57,460 --> 00:03:59,280
这是二区伤口  按住这里
It's a zone two wound. Press there.

80
00:03:59,850 --> 00:04:01,390
我该送他去医院的
I should have taken him to a hospital.

81
00:04:01,540 --> 00:04:04,280
不  费利西蒂  他要你送他过来
No, Felicity, that's why he asked you to bring him here.

82
00:04:04,370 --> 00:04:05,130
是因为他知道警方
Because he knew the police

83
00:04:05,130 --> 00:04:07,460
会好奇他是如何受的伤
would want to know how and why he got the wound.

84
00:04:07,460 --> 00:04:08,570
我觉得这是
I'm guessing how and why

85
00:04:08,570 --> 00:04:11,030
奥利弗·奎恩最不喜欢的问题
are Oliver Queen's least favorite questions.

86
00:04:11,220 --> 00:04:15,150
他还不喜欢时间和地点的问题
Yeah, well, there's also when and where, he's not too fond of.

87
00:04:15,850 --> 00:04:17,750
如果我们不能送他去医院
So if we can't bring him to the hospital...

88
00:04:17,750 --> 00:04:20,810
我们把这里当成医院
We bring the hospital to him.

89
00:04:21,360 --> 00:04:21,930
这是
Is that...

90
00:04:21,930 --> 00:04:24,840
对  他的血  他贮备了  以防万一
Yeah. His blood. He stored it for a rainy day.

91
00:04:24,840 --> 00:04:27,540
现在正是紧急关头
And I say right now, it's pouring.

92
00:04:27,730 --> 00:04:29,020
我来  你去那边
I got it. Over there.

93
00:04:29,470 --> 00:04:30,570
你知道自己在干什么吗
Do you know what you're doing?

94
00:04:30,830 --> 00:04:33,650
对  我在军队接受过医疗训练
Yeah, I had some medical training in the army.

95
00:04:34,190 --> 00:04:35,450
希望足够应付
I just hope it's enough.

96
00:04:37,240 --> 00:04:39,510
还记得小时候玩过的手术游戏吗
Remember playing "operation" when you were a kid?

97
00:04:39,740 --> 00:04:40,630
是的
Yes.

98
00:04:42,380 --> 00:04:43,810
但它从来没让我想吐过
And it never made me want to throw up.

99
00:04:43,810 --> 00:04:46,420
费利西蒂  相信我  他会没事的
Hey, Felicity, listen, trust me. He'll be fine.

100
00:04:46,420 --> 00:04:48,260
他经历过比这更糟的情况
He's been through a lot worse than this.

101
00:04:55,200 --> 00:04:56,180
该死的
Ah, damn.

102
00:05:07,140 --> 00:05:09,530
你这六个月是怎么活下来的
How did you survive here for six months?

103
00:05:10,060 --> 00:05:12,070
我听说女童军之间斗得更厉害
I know girl scouts who have more fight in them.

104
00:05:12,070 --> 00:05:14,150
沦落到和女童军争斗了  斯莱德
Fighting girl scouts now, Slade, huh?

105
00:05:15,690 --> 00:05:16,740
搞什么鬼
What the hell?!

106
00:05:16,740 --> 00:05:20,700
听着  小子  供给机还有十天就到了
Listen, kid. We have ten days until the supply plane lands.

107
00:05:20,880 --> 00:05:23,870
这十天要把你训练成至少半个士兵
Ten days to turn you into at least half a soldier.

108
00:05:23,920 --> 00:05:26,140
所以请严肃一点
So start taking it seriously.

109
00:05:32,390 --> 00:05:34,400
这到底有什么意义
What is the point of this?!

110
00:05:34,480 --> 00:05:36,010
士兵们才不拿竹子呢
These soldiers don't carry bamboo!

111
00:05:36,010 --> 00:05:38,530
他们拿枪  如果他们有人
They have guns! So what am I supposed to do

112
00:05:38,530 --> 00:05:40,800
拿枪指着我  我该怎么办
if one of them jams a gun in my face, huh?

113
00:05:40,820 --> 00:05:42,510
用我的竹棒威胁他们吗
Threaten them with my stick?!

114
00:05:44,240 --> 00:05:45,780
用这个指着我
Jam this in my face.

115
00:05:48,260 --> 00:05:49,190
快
Do it.

116
00:05:59,960 --> 00:06:02,220
我投降  我投降
I give up. I give up.

117
00:06:04,760 --> 00:06:06,820
绝对不能向这些家伙投降
There is no giving up to these guys!

118
00:06:06,820 --> 00:06:09,710
不许哭  不许收买他们
No crying, or buying your way out of it!

119
00:06:10,580 --> 00:06:12,290
你有两个选择
You have two choices--

120
00:06:13,530 --> 00:06:16,090
逃或者死
escape, or die.

121
00:06:16,520 --> 00:06:17,740
选吧
So choose.

122
00:06:19,100 --> 00:06:20,060
逃
Escape.

123
00:06:21,860 --> 00:06:23,250
那就让我教你
Then let me show you

124
00:06:23,660 --> 00:06:25,150
怎么活下来
how not to die.

125
00:06:35,680 --> 00:06:37,140
炼狱
Lian Yu.

126
00:06:37,540 --> 00:06:39,120
是这座岛的名字  我懂
It's the name of the island, I know.

127
00:06:39,670 --> 00:06:41,500
汉语意为试炼地狱
It's mandarin for "Purgatory."

128
00:06:41,500 --> 00:06:43,430
是吗  很好
It is? Wonderful.

129
00:06:44,830 --> 00:06:46,140
那是着陆带吗
Is that the air strip?

130
00:06:46,450 --> 00:06:49,640
美国情报科学学会拍下这个岛的卫星照片
A.S.I.S. took satellite images of the whole island.

131
00:06:49,720 --> 00:06:51,240
这是法尔斯的主营
This is Fyers' main camp,

132
00:06:51,240 --> 00:06:53,100
我就是在那儿被困近一年
where I was held for almost a year.

133
00:06:53,630 --> 00:06:55,420
你认为姚飞现在也会在那儿吗
Do--do you think that's where Yao Fei is now?

134
00:06:55,420 --> 00:06:57,200
那样的话我们能给他带个口信
'Cause we could get a message to him.

135
00:06:57,200 --> 00:06:58,720
告诉他我们找到离开这个岛的方法了
We can tell him we found a way off the island.

136
00:06:58,720 --> 00:06:59,970
别管他
Forget about him.

137
00:07:01,350 --> 00:07:03,410
这是着陆带
This is the airstrip.

138
00:07:03,730 --> 00:07:05,780
这些红外图像显示
And these infrared images show

139
00:07:05,780 --> 00:07:07,440
这周围全天都有
there are at last ten soldiers guarding

140
00:07:07,440 --> 00:07:09,060
至少十名士兵守卫
the perimeter at any given time.

141
00:07:09,060 --> 00:07:10,370
对你来说敌人太多了
Too many of 'em for you?

142
00:07:10,480 --> 00:07:11,400
不
No.

143
00:07:12,230 --> 00:07:14,800
困扰我的是在这塔上的家伙
My problem is the guy here in the tower.

144
00:07:14,880 --> 00:07:17,870
这是PATC  移动空管塔
It's a PATC. A portable air traffic control tower.

145
00:07:17,870 --> 00:07:20,670
美国政府建造来解决灾区需要
The U.S. Government set up these for disaster zones,

146
00:07:20,670 --> 00:07:22,520
比如受海啸袭击后的泰国
like Thailand after the tsunami.

147
00:07:23,740 --> 00:07:25,040
那么问题在哪儿呢
So what's the problem?

148
00:07:25,390 --> 00:07:27,040
这是防弹玻璃
The glass is bulletproof.

149
00:07:27,310 --> 00:07:30,030
我无法用狙击枪干掉塔里的守卫
I can't take out the tower guard with my sniper rifle.

150
00:07:30,310 --> 00:07:31,500
如果他发现了可疑情况
And if he suspects anything's wrong,

151
00:07:31,500 --> 00:07:33,960
就会通知法尔斯  我们的行动就得取消
he'll radio Fyers and we're cancelled.

152
00:07:35,970 --> 00:07:37,830
你负责把他弄出来
It'll be up to you to take him out.

153
00:07:38,070 --> 00:07:39,580
靠近他  干掉他
Up close and personal.

154
00:07:40,460 --> 00:07:41,900
你准备好了吗
Are you ready for that?

155
00:07:42,510 --> 00:07:44,200
你认为呢
Do you think I'm ready?

156
00:07:45,390 --> 00:07:48,700
我在想  每三个月才有一架供给机
What I think is there's only one supply plane every 3 months.

157
00:07:49,130 --> 00:07:52,020
我们明天得离开  要不然也活不下去了
We leave tomorrow, or we die soon afterwards.

158
00:07:53,420 --> 00:07:54,500
我选择离开
I pick leaving.

159
00:07:56,500 --> 00:07:59,620
去睡一会儿  我们六点行动
So get some sleep. We leave at 0600.

160
00:08:08,530 --> 00:08:09,490
别担心
Don't worry.

161
00:08:10,160 --> 00:08:12,280
你很快就能回到女朋友身边了
You'll be back with your girlfriend soon enough.

162
00:08:37,270 --> 00:08:38,290
早上好
Morning.

163
00:08:41,810 --> 00:08:43,370
请别恨我
Please don't hate me.

164
00:08:44,560 --> 00:08:46,030
为什么我要恨你
Why would I hate you?

165
00:08:47,180 --> 00:08:49,140
背着你和莎拉在一起
For cheating on you with Sarah.

166
00:08:53,430 --> 00:08:54,790
痛吗  奥利
Did it hurt, Ollie?

167
00:08:55,020 --> 00:08:56,260
什么痛
Did what hurt?

168
00:08:56,400 --> 00:08:57,480
他们杀你的时候
When they killed you?

169
00:09:00,630 --> 00:09:01,900
快起来
Rise and shine.

170
00:09:20,190 --> 00:09:21,170
来吧
Come on.

171
00:09:21,910 --> 00:09:23,120
我们要走了
We're moving out.

172
00:09:55,380 --> 00:09:56,450
安全
All clear.

173
00:09:57,510 --> 00:10:00,670
我们能休息一会儿吗
Hey, can we, um, can we rest for a second?

174
00:10:01,210 --> 00:10:02,950
你到飞机上有的是时间休息
You can rest on the plane.

175
00:10:03,430 --> 00:10:06,920
天啊  真期待飞机上的电影
Gosh, well, really looking forward to that in-flight movie.

176
00:10:09,480 --> 00:10:11,510
-天啊  -别动
- Oh, god. - Don't move.

177
00:10:12,190 --> 00:10:13,420
是地雷吗
Is it a mine?

178
00:10:22,870 --> 00:10:23,400
对
Yeah.

179
00:10:23,400 --> 00:10:25,250
这些士兵还在岛上布了地雷
The soldiers mine the island?

180
00:10:25,290 --> 00:10:26,650
不  可能是日本人埋的
No, it's probably Japanese,

181
00:10:26,650 --> 00:10:28,400
二战时候留下的
left over from World War II.

182
00:10:29,080 --> 00:10:30,280
还没失效
Still active.

183
00:10:30,280 --> 00:10:31,270
真是惊人
Impressive.

184
00:10:31,630 --> 00:10:32,750
你能拆除吗
Can you disarm it?

185
00:10:35,140 --> 00:10:36,430
在不炸死你的情况下吗
Without disarming you?

186
00:10:40,330 --> 00:10:41,300
士兵来了
Soldiers.

187
00:10:52,970 --> 00:10:54,160
他们只能看见你
They can only see you.

188
00:10:54,160 --> 00:10:55,820
等等  别走
Wait! Stop!

189
00:11:08,550 --> 00:11:10,170
你离开营地这么远干什么
What are you doing so far from camp?

190
00:11:10,170 --> 00:11:11,850
我和队伍分散了
I got separated from my unit.

191
00:11:12,690 --> 00:11:13,720
跟我们走吧
Come with us.

192
00:11:15,290 --> 00:11:16,550
不行
I-- I can't.

193
00:11:16,610 --> 00:11:19,860
今天可真倒霉
I'm kind of having a bad day, you know?

194
00:11:34,000 --> 00:11:35,020
别动
Be still.

195
00:11:43,280 --> 00:11:44,260
谢了
Thanks.

196
00:11:54,920 --> 00:11:55,830
姚飞
Yao Fei.

197
00:11:55,830 --> 00:11:57,550
进来  请坐
Come in. Sit.

198
00:12:01,000 --> 00:12:02,410
第一次见你
Now the first time

199
00:12:02,720 --> 00:12:05,030
拿着这支弓时
I saw you with this contraption...

200
00:12:07,120 --> 00:12:09,350
还觉得特别可笑
I thought you looked utterly ridiculous.

201
00:12:11,400 --> 00:12:12,550
直到你用它打败了
That is, until you took out

202
00:12:12,550 --> 00:12:14,850
我最棒的三名手下
three of my best men with it.

203
00:12:15,290 --> 00:12:19,270
明天补给飞机会送25支复合弓过来
25 compound bows will be arriving on tomorrow's supply plane.

204
00:12:20,840 --> 00:12:23,970
我想让你训练我部分手下学会用弓
I'd like you to train a few of my men on how to use them.

205
00:12:25,400 --> 00:12:28,760
要掌握箭术可能得花上好几年
Archery can take years to master.

206
00:12:29,000 --> 00:12:31,640
你这位老师可是专家
Well, I trust you'll be a proficient instructor.

207
00:12:33,700 --> 00:12:34,700
没其他事了
That'll be all.

208
00:12:43,250 --> 00:12:44,270
我希望你能坚定
I hope you are steadfast

209
00:12:44,270 --> 00:12:46,800
对我们的承诺  姚飞
in your commitment to our cause, Yao Fei.

210
00:12:47,440 --> 00:12:48,650
为了她
For her sake.

211
00:12:48,650 --> 00:12:49,610
我会的
I am.

212
00:12:57,390 --> 00:12:59,060
看来你从没做过童子军
Obviously you were never a boy scout.

213
00:12:59,060 --> 00:13:01,440
是吗  为什么这么说
Yeah? What tipped you off?

214
00:13:03,090 --> 00:13:04,170
得抓紧时间了
We better hurry.

215
00:13:04,640 --> 00:13:06,390
晚上会有狼
The wolves come out at night.

216
00:13:07,940 --> 00:13:09,150
这里有狼
There are wolves here?

217
00:13:09,620 --> 00:13:11,650
对啊  当然有
Right. Of course there are.

218
00:13:11,650 --> 00:13:14,620
没有狼还怎么算是世上最糟的地方
Because what would the worst place on earth be without wolves.

219
00:13:15,280 --> 00:13:17,680
只有火能防止它们靠近
The only thing that will keep them out is fire.

220
00:13:17,680 --> 00:13:19,700
很欢迎你来帮忙
Well, you know, you're welcome to help.

221
00:13:27,600 --> 00:13:28,700
不是吧
Seriously?

222
00:13:30,240 --> 00:13:32,330
我钻了两个小时
I've been working on this for two hours.

223
00:13:32,560 --> 00:13:34,710
我知道  我看了两个小时
I know. I was watching you.

224
00:13:35,040 --> 00:13:37,680
谢谢你娱乐大众
Thank you for the entertainment.

225
00:13:47,910 --> 00:13:50,560
你要把照片看穿了
You're going to wear that thing out just by looking at it.

226
00:13:52,280 --> 00:13:53,150
别担心
Don't worry.

227
00:13:53,580 --> 00:13:56,120
你回家时她会载歌载舞欢迎的
She'll be waiting for flowers when you get back.

228
00:13:57,250 --> 00:13:58,210
表示怀疑
I doubt it.

229
00:13:59,110 --> 00:14:01,110
还记得我跟你说过  我沉船漂来这岛上的吗
Remember how I told you I was shipwrecked here?

230
00:14:02,240 --> 00:14:04,760
沉船时她妹妹跟我在一起
Her sister was with me when the boat went down.

231
00:14:04,770 --> 00:14:07,630
真有意思  我从没想过你是个坏男孩
That's funny. I never took you as being the bad boy.

232
00:14:07,870 --> 00:14:09,540
你看起来好像没这个胆
You seem to lack the spine.

233
00:14:10,100 --> 00:14:11,570
所以我必须得回家
That's why I've got to get home.

234
00:14:13,080 --> 00:14:14,280
弥补这一切
To make this right.

235
00:14:14,320 --> 00:14:17,040
你睡了女朋友的妹妹
If you think you can sleep with your girlfriend's sister

236
00:14:17,440 --> 00:14:19,210
还觉得能弥补的话
and still make it right...

237
00:14:19,840 --> 00:14:22,970
你真是比我想的还要蠢  听我的
you're dumber than I thought. And believe me what I tell you

238
00:14:23,040 --> 00:14:24,420
好好跟她道个歉
that is saying something.

239
00:14:24,420 --> 00:14:26,730
你给我的印象也不是那种
Yeah, well, you don't really strike me as the type of guy

240
00:14:26,730 --> 00:14:29,020
肯接受道歉的人
who accepts apologies, so...

241
00:14:29,720 --> 00:14:32,560
每个人都是自私的
Well, everybody is in this life for themselves.

242
00:14:32,960 --> 00:14:35,180
在澳大利亚的间谍学校学到的
Learn that at Australian spy school?

243
00:14:35,630 --> 00:14:38,260
不  在这里学到的
No. I learned that here.

244
00:14:39,050 --> 00:14:41,360
还记得我说过以前有个搭档吗
Do you remember I told you that I had a partner?

245
00:14:41,730 --> 00:14:42,640
记得
Yeah.

246
00:14:43,230 --> 00:14:45,070
还记得那个折磨你的人吗
Do you remember the guy who tortured you?

247
00:14:50,250 --> 00:14:53,360
那个变态是你搭档
That freak show was your partner?!

248
00:14:53,360 --> 00:14:55,030
他叫比利·温特格林
His name's Billy Wintergreen.

249
00:14:55,030 --> 00:14:56,550
好吧
Oh. Ok.

250
00:14:56,550 --> 00:14:58,620
我们的任务是救出姚飞
Our mission was to exfiltrate Yao Fei

251
00:14:58,620 --> 00:15:01,660
查明法尔斯那帮人为什么对他这么感兴趣
and to find out why Fyers and his men were so interested in him.

252
00:15:01,890 --> 00:15:03,140
但我们的飞机在半空中被击落
But our bird got shot out of the sky

253
00:15:03,140 --> 00:15:05,000
当时离他们的基地还远着呢
before we even saw the airstrip.

254
00:15:05,180 --> 00:15:06,520
我就是在那找到你的
That's where I found you.

255
00:15:09,030 --> 00:15:10,380
法尔斯把我们抓起来时
When Fyers took us prisoner,

256
00:15:10,380 --> 00:15:12,700
问我们要不要向他们投诚
he asked if we would join him and his men.

257
00:15:12,860 --> 00:15:15,460
比利答应了
Billy accepted Fyers' invitation.

258
00:15:17,220 --> 00:15:18,370
我拒绝了
I declined.

259
00:15:18,850 --> 00:15:22,270
他是我儿子乔的教父
He was the godfather to my son Joe.

260
00:15:23,580 --> 00:15:26,440
却想都没想
And yet, he turned his back on me

261
00:15:26,850 --> 00:15:29,120
就背叛了我
without even thinking twice about it.

262
00:15:30,200 --> 00:15:34,110
每个人都是自私的
Everybody is in this life for themselves!

263
00:15:50,900 --> 00:15:53,240
要是你让他通知营地  我们就完了
If you let him radio camp, we're done.

264
00:15:55,990 --> 00:15:58,520
-那其他人呢  -你担心这一个
- What about the others? - You worry about your one.

265
00:15:58,580 --> 00:16:00,240
其余十个交给我
I'll worry about my ten.

266
00:16:24,550 --> 00:16:25,500
干得好
Good job.

267
00:16:26,070 --> 00:16:27,020
应该吧
I think.

268
00:16:27,210 --> 00:16:27,840
他心率加快了
His heart rate's elevated,

269
00:16:27,840 --> 00:16:29,660
不过已经不出血了
but at least the bleeding stopped.

270
00:16:30,340 --> 00:16:31,450
谢谢帮忙
Thanks for your help.

271
00:16:31,870 --> 00:16:32,860
你很镇静
You kept your head on.

272
00:16:32,860 --> 00:16:35,380
我一直在想  要是看到我老板受了枪伤
Well, I always wondered how I'd react

273
00:16:35,380 --> 00:16:38,190
倒在我车里流血不止  我会怎么做
if I found my boss shot and bleeding inside my car.

274
00:16:39,070 --> 00:16:40,250
我帮忙可不是因为他是我老板
Not that I helped because he's my boss.

275
00:16:40,250 --> 00:16:42,100
换做是谁受了枪伤在我车里流血
I'd help anyone who was shot

276
00:16:42,100 --> 00:16:44,880
我都会帮忙的
and bleeding in my car.

277
00:16:46,360 --> 00:16:48,690
你一定很震惊吧
I was thinking all of this would be more of a shock.

278
00:16:50,000 --> 00:16:51,790
还是你觉得这一天迟早会到来
What do you say you called this all along?

279
00:16:51,830 --> 00:16:53,760
我可什么都没说
I'm not saying anything.

280
00:16:54,680 --> 00:16:57,330
不过奥利弗给了我一台都是弹孔的笔记本电脑
Except Oliver brought me a laptop riddled with bullet holes,

281
00:16:57,330 --> 00:16:59,070
让我调查黑箭
Had me trace a black arrow,

282
00:16:59,360 --> 00:17:02,500
和一个涉嫌抢劫装甲车的公司
and research a company involved in armored car heists.

283
00:17:02,760 --> 00:17:05,760
我是一介女流  但也没无知到那种地步
I may be blonde, but I'm not that blonde.

284
00:17:05,930 --> 00:17:08,570
奥利弗是不怎么擅长编故事
Yeah, Oliver's not too great with the cover stories.

285
00:17:08,850 --> 00:17:10,130
你也是
Neither are you.

286
00:17:10,460 --> 00:17:11,450
你们俩还跟我扯说是
The two of you with that whole

287
00:17:11,450 --> 00:17:14,600
缓解宿醉的能量饮料  拜托
energy drink hangover cure? Please.

288
00:17:15,390 --> 00:17:17,120
说起来  里面装的到底是什么
What was really in that vial, anyway?

289
00:17:18,720 --> 00:17:20,700
-"迷魂"  -我就知道
- Vertigo. - I knew it!

290
00:17:21,090 --> 00:17:22,580
虽然我不知道那是"迷魂"
I mean, I didn't know it was Vertigo for sure,

291
00:17:22,580 --> 00:17:23,550
但我知道
but I definitely knew

292
00:17:23,550 --> 00:17:25,220
那肯定不是用来缓解宿醉的
it wasn't something that could cure a hangover.

293
00:17:25,220 --> 00:17:27,620
我们要分析出它的成分  拿下"伯爵"
Yeah, we needed it analyzed so we could take down the Count.

294
00:17:29,870 --> 00:17:31,210
就凭你和奥利弗两人之力
That was you and Oliver?

295
00:17:31,250 --> 00:17:32,540
还有你  费利西蒂
And you, Felicity.

296
00:17:33,630 --> 00:17:35,340
没有你  我们永远不可能找到他的老窝
Without you, we never would have found him.

297
00:17:37,560 --> 00:17:38,740
但是为什么是我呢
But why come to me?

298
00:17:43,060 --> 00:17:45,060
可能他也不好意思承认
Hard as it probably is for him to admit,

299
00:17:45,480 --> 00:17:47,510
即使是奥利弗  有时候也需要援手
even Oliver needs help sometimes.

300
00:18:39,700 --> 00:18:40,680
该死
Damn!

301
00:19:41,730 --> 00:19:42,570
怎么回事
What's happening?!

302
00:19:42,570 --> 00:19:44,050
有个标有劳拉西泮的注射器
There's a syringe labeled Ativan.

303
00:19:44,050 --> 00:19:45,560
能阻止癫痫  去拿
It should stop the seizure. Go.

304
00:19:47,310 --> 00:19:48,560
心跳停止了
His heart stopped.

305
00:19:49,340 --> 00:19:50,460
我去打911
I'm calling 9-1-1.

306
00:19:50,540 --> 00:19:52,570
不  等一下  不能打
No. Wait, you can't.

307
00:19:54,050 --> 00:19:55,430
你知道这些东西要怎么用吗
You know how to use one of those?

308
00:19:55,820 --> 00:19:58,870
马上就能知道了
We are about to find out.

309
00:20:01,040 --> 00:20:02,040
你没事先招呼
You didn't say clear!

310
00:20:01,040 --> 00:20:02,040
{\an8}电击前说clear  
确定周围没有人碰到被电击的人

311
00:20:04,000 --> 00:20:05,060
我听到电荷声了
I heard the charge.

312
00:20:05,140 --> 00:20:06,250
好现象
That's good news.

313
00:20:06,860 --> 00:20:07,620
为什么
How's that?

314
00:20:07,620 --> 00:20:08,370
说明可能不是机器的问题
It means it might not be the machine,

315
00:20:08,370 --> 00:20:09,650
而是接线的问题
it could be the wiring.

316
00:20:10,820 --> 00:20:12,460
快点  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!

317
00:20:12,460 --> 00:20:13,330
再来一次
Try again.

318
00:20:14,580 --> 00:20:15,470
准备
Clear.

319
00:20:31,500 --> 00:20:32,590
你到底做了什么
What the hell did you do?

320
00:20:34,310 --> 00:20:36,220
我从七岁起就开始组装电脑
I've been building computers since I was seven.

321
00:20:37,120 --> 00:20:38,330
接线可是大学问
Wires are wires.

322
00:20:38,500 --> 00:20:39,460
现在要做什么
What do we do now?

323
00:20:40,350 --> 00:20:42,420
祈祷我们自己没吓出心脏病
Pray we don't have a heart attack ourselves.

324
00:20:58,120 --> 00:20:59,300
就这么一件事
One job to do,

325
00:20:59,650 --> 00:21:01,520
你都能给我搞砸了
and you manage to screw up even then.

326
00:21:08,010 --> 00:21:10,000
我要去确认一切没有问题
I'm going to go make sure that everything is clear.

327
00:21:10,140 --> 00:21:11,510
你待在这  锁好门
Stay here, keep the door locked.

328
00:21:11,510 --> 00:21:13,550
除了我  别让任何人进来
Do not let anybody in except for me.

329
00:21:13,630 --> 00:21:14,870
-明白了吗  -明白
- You got that? - Yeah.

330
00:21:17,270 --> 00:21:19,170
拿着这个
Here. Keep this.

331
00:21:20,380 --> 00:21:22,390
别失手把自己打死了
And try not to shoot yourself by mistake.

332
00:21:58,550 --> 00:21:59,490
喂
Hello?

333
00:22:03,030 --> 00:22:04,280
喂
Hello?

334
00:22:09,020 --> 00:22:10,400
有人在听吗
Is anybody there?

335
00:22:15,020 --> 00:22:16,360
你疯了吗
Have you lost your mind?

336
00:22:16,670 --> 00:22:18,540
他们很可能对电话实行着监控
They might be monitoring the calls.

337
00:22:19,770 --> 00:22:23,230
指挥塔  这里是天鹰801F
Island tower, this is Skyhawk 801 foxtrot,

338
00:22:23,230 --> 00:22:26,110
我们在小岛东南方向700公里处
we are 700 kilometers southeast of your position.

339
00:22:26,110 --> 00:22:28,460
预计抵达时间为三小时二十分钟  完毕
Eta, three hours, 22 minutes, over.

340
00:22:32,020 --> 00:22:35,690
这里是指挥塔  天鹰801F
Island tower, Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot.

341
00:22:35,690 --> 00:22:36,780
收到
Acknowledged.

342
00:22:40,780 --> 00:22:43,690
天鹰801F
Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot.

343
00:22:43,690 --> 00:22:44,730
收到
Acknowledged.

344
00:22:45,500 --> 00:22:48,760
世间万物
Of all creatures that breathe and move upon the earth

345
00:22:51,410 --> 00:22:52,350
这是什么
What is it?

346
00:22:52,500 --> 00:22:53,910
这是暗号
It's a challenge code.

347
00:22:53,910 --> 00:22:56,010
他们在查明正身
They're trying to verify our identity.

348
00:22:58,550 --> 00:23:01,270
天鹰801F
Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot.

349
00:23:01,740 --> 00:23:02,940
请重复
Please repeat.

350
00:23:03,540 --> 00:23:06,550
世间万物
Of all creatures that breathe and move upon the earth.

351
00:23:08,090 --> 00:23:09,370
-等等  -怎么了
- Wait. - What?

352
00:23:09,370 --> 00:23:12,230
我知道这个  我知道
Wait, I know this. I know this.

353
00:23:12,230 --> 00:23:15,700
他们挑了我大学时候读过的一本书
They picked the one book that I read in college.

354
00:23:15,700 --> 00:23:17,160
你他妈到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?

355
00:23:17,160 --> 00:23:19,600
《奥德赛》[古希腊著名史诗]里面的话
A quote, from "The Odyssey".

356
00:23:22,520 --> 00:23:26,920
世间万物
Of all creatures that breathe and move upon the earth,

357
00:23:26,920 --> 00:23:29,400
唯...唯人
Nothing--nothing is born

358
00:23:29,630 --> 00:23:31,110
本懦
that is weaker than man.

359
00:23:32,200 --> 00:23:34,040
你确定吗  万一错了
Are you sure about this? Because if you're wrong,

360
00:23:34,040 --> 00:23:35,730
飞机会调头回去的
this plane will turn around.

361
00:23:35,730 --> 00:23:38,190
确定  我确定
Yes, yes. I'm positive.

362
00:23:38,380 --> 00:23:40,530
唯人
Nothing is born

363
00:23:41,070 --> 00:23:42,500
本懦
that is weaker than man.

364
00:23:42,920 --> 00:23:43,910
就这么说
Say it.

365
00:23:46,000 --> 00:23:47,820
等等  等等  等等
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait.

366
00:23:47,820 --> 00:23:49,600
对不起  对不起  对不起
Sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.

367
00:23:50,420 --> 00:23:51,420
是"性"
Bred.

368
00:23:51,830 --> 00:23:53,150
不是"本"  是"性"
Not born, bred.

369
00:23:53,150 --> 00:23:56,010
唯人性懦
Nothing is bred that is weaker than man.

370
00:23:56,090 --> 00:23:57,120
是这个
That's it.

371
00:23:58,760 --> 00:24:01,380
唯人性懦
Nothing is bred that is weaker than man.

372
00:24:03,760 --> 00:24:05,550
收到  稍后见
Roger that. See you in a few hours.

373
00:24:05,550 --> 00:24:06,170
完毕
Out.

374
00:24:08,470 --> 00:24:09,350
《奥德赛》
"The Odyssey".

375
00:24:09,350 --> 00:24:12,860
没错  讲的是一个人
Yeah! It's, uh, well, it's a story about a guy

376
00:24:12,860 --> 00:24:14,670
回家的历险故事
who's trying to get home, so.

377
00:24:16,620 --> 00:24:17,670
在兰施图尔空军基地
Well, after a few days

378
00:24:17,680 --> 00:24:18,910
待几天之后
at Landstuhl Air Base,

379
00:24:19,840 --> 00:24:21,000
你就能回家了
you'll be on your way home.

380
00:24:21,910 --> 00:24:23,640
但听起来你不和我一起走
But you sound like you're not coming with me.

381
00:24:24,140 --> 00:24:25,220
我会和你一起走
I'll be coming with you.

382
00:24:25,870 --> 00:24:28,460
等我先空袭这里之后
After I radio in an airstrike on this location.

383
00:24:29,760 --> 00:24:33,160
我要送法尔斯和他的手下们下地狱
I'm going to send Fyers and all his men straight back to hell.

384
00:24:42,570 --> 00:24:43,200
等等
Wait.

385
00:24:44,920 --> 00:24:46,600
你不能炸了这座岛
You can't blow up the island.

386
00:24:47,720 --> 00:24:49,490
姚飞还在这里
Yao Fei is still out there.

387
00:24:49,830 --> 00:24:51,990
-他的死活不关我的事  -真的吗
- He is not my concern. - Really?

388
00:24:52,000 --> 00:24:53,680
你来这不就是为了他吗
He's the only reason you came here.

389
00:24:53,680 --> 00:24:55,700
你的任务就是救他
Rescuing him was your mission!

390
00:24:55,700 --> 00:24:57,220
那么  任务有变
Well, the mission has changed.

391
00:24:57,220 --> 00:24:59,150
爱德华·法尔斯是一个佣兵
Edward Fyers is a mercenary

392
00:24:59,150 --> 00:25:01,180
他不会无缘无故来这里的
and he is not on this island by mistake.

393
00:25:01,180 --> 00:25:02,970
他盯上了我们两个
He has plans for me and you

394
00:25:02,970 --> 00:25:04,260
姚飞会帮他
that involve Yao Fei.

395
00:25:04,530 --> 00:25:06,640
不管他想做什么  我必须阻止
And whatever they are, they must end.

396
00:25:09,400 --> 00:25:10,730
姚飞救了我的命
Yao Fei saved my life.

397
00:25:12,650 --> 00:25:14,470
这是你欠的债
That is your debt to repay,

398
00:25:14,620 --> 00:25:15,800
不是我
not mine.

399
00:25:20,800 --> 00:25:22,020
你去哪
Where are you going?!

400
00:25:26,140 --> 00:25:27,100
一直以来
All my life,

401
00:25:28,570 --> 00:25:30,550
我只考虑我自己
all that I've ever thought about is myself.

402
00:25:31,400 --> 00:25:33,440
我把家人的爱当作理所当然
I took my family for granted.

403
00:25:33,550 --> 00:25:35,440
我背叛了我爱的人
I betrayed people that I loved.

404
00:25:38,460 --> 00:25:40,680
但我不会再做这种人了
And I'm not going to be that person anymore.

405
00:25:44,310 --> 00:25:46,920
我不能眼睁睁让姚飞死
I can't leave Yao Fei here to die.

406
00:25:49,210 --> 00:25:50,080
我不会
I won't.

407
00:25:51,870 --> 00:25:53,690
飞机还有三个小时起飞
The plane leaves in three hours.

408
00:25:53,820 --> 00:25:55,850
如果到时你和你的朋友还没来
If you and your friend are not on it,

409
00:25:55,910 --> 00:25:58,000
我就丢下你们自己走
I am going to leave without you.

410
00:26:08,800 --> 00:26:10,390
如果我不能及时回来
If I don't make it back in time,

411
00:26:11,810 --> 00:26:13,200
而你离开了
and you get out of here...

412
00:26:16,320 --> 00:26:17,810
我希望你替我打个电话回家
I want you to call my family.

413
00:26:20,290 --> 00:26:21,360
打给我家人
Call my family.

414
00:26:24,010 --> 00:26:24,950
好  孩子
Sure, kid.

415
00:26:53,130 --> 00:26:54,710
他又心脏骤停了
He's going into cardiac arrest again.

416
00:26:54,790 --> 00:26:55,510
不
No.

417
00:26:55,980 --> 00:26:58,310
是导线松了
Ah. The leads just came loose.

418
00:27:01,350 --> 00:27:03,910
他从屋顶跳下来我都没这么担心
It's less stressful when he's jumping off rooftops.

419
00:27:09,440 --> 00:27:11,970
很多人中了这把弓发出的箭
This bow has put arrows in quite a few people.

420
00:27:14,790 --> 00:27:15,950
是的  都是坏人
Yeah, bad people.

421
00:27:17,090 --> 00:27:18,190
你不觉得困扰吗
That doesn't bother you?

422
00:27:20,550 --> 00:27:21,290
因为...
Because...

423
00:27:22,680 --> 00:27:24,130
我没有恶意
and I mean this in a good way,

424
00:27:24,810 --> 00:27:26,880
只是你看起来像是会受到困扰
you seem like the kind of guy it would bother.

425
00:27:30,910 --> 00:27:32,000
我在阿富汗的时候
When I was in Afghanistan,

426
00:27:32,000 --> 00:27:35,790
我的部队的任务是保护一个本地军阀
my unit was tasked with protecting this local war lord.

427
00:27:37,570 --> 00:27:38,920
葛雷姆·卡迪尔
Gholem Qadir.

428
00:27:39,480 --> 00:27:41,630
卡迪尔没有人性  贩卖鸦片
Qadir was less than human, sold opium.

429
00:27:42,080 --> 00:27:43,110
贩卖儿童
Sold children.

430
00:27:44,510 --> 00:27:45,310
有一天
One day,

431
00:27:45,310 --> 00:27:47,160
我们随他去摩苏尔
we were accompanying him to Mosul

432
00:27:48,020 --> 00:27:50,730
我的车队遇到叛乱分子伏击
when my convoy was ambushed by insurgents.

433
00:27:50,860 --> 00:27:51,880
我们的火力压过他们
We had them outgunned.

434
00:27:51,880 --> 00:27:53,820
交火时间不超过一分钟
Fire fight didn't last more than a minute.

435
00:27:54,070 --> 00:27:55,310
当硝烟散去
When the smoke cleared,

436
00:27:55,480 --> 00:27:56,920
我去他们的位置查看
I moved in on their position.

437
00:27:59,830 --> 00:28:01,950
他们都死了  我知道我杀的是哪个
They were all dead. I knew which one I had killed.

438
00:28:04,400 --> 00:28:05,480
当我摘下他的头巾
When I pulled off his keffiyeh,

439
00:28:05,480 --> 00:28:07,660
我看到他只是一个孩子  最多不过18岁
I could see it was just a kid, no more than 18.

440
00:28:09,180 --> 00:28:10,330
我一枪射穿了他的喉咙
Shot him in the throat.

441
00:28:13,180 --> 00:28:14,380
我为了保护一个人渣
I killed this kid to protect

442
00:28:14,380 --> 00:28:16,420
杀了这个孩子
this human piece of garbage,

443
00:28:16,420 --> 00:28:17,960
我就问自己  我还是好人吗
and I thought, am I still good?

444
00:28:20,150 --> 00:28:21,340
我还是个好人吗
Am I still a good man?

445
00:28:25,580 --> 00:28:26,770
和奥利弗共事
Doing this with Oliver;

446
00:28:28,190 --> 00:28:29,800
我们做的事  让我在很久之后
Doing what we do, I feel good again

447
00:28:29,800 --> 00:28:31,360
第一次又觉得自己是好人
for the first time in a long time.

448
00:28:33,790 --> 00:28:37,030
这么多附带的伤害  值得吗
And that's worth all the collateral damage?

449
00:28:37,090 --> 00:28:38,920
如果你指的是有人丧命  我没杀过任何人
I haven't killed anyone, if that's what you're asking.

450
00:28:39,520 --> 00:28:40,500
但他杀过
But he has.

451
00:28:43,380 --> 00:28:44,450
很遗憾
Unfortunately,

452
00:28:45,150 --> 00:28:47,460
打仗总会产生伤亡的
there are always casualties when you're fighting a war.

453
00:29:36,140 --> 00:29:36,910
你是怎么...
How did you...

454
00:29:36,910 --> 00:29:39,100
跟我走  我们边走边解释
Come on, let's go. I'll explain on the way.

455
00:29:39,100 --> 00:29:41,090
傻孩子  你不该回这里来
Stupid boy. You should never have come back here!

456
00:29:41,090 --> 00:29:44,330
我找到了斯莱德·威尔逊  他有办法离岛
I found Slade Wilson and he has a way off the island,

457
00:29:44,440 --> 00:29:46,150
我们得马上走
but we have to go right now.

458
00:29:46,570 --> 00:29:47,110
不  不
No. No!

459
00:29:47,270 --> 00:29:49,600
什么  为什么不
What? What do you mean, no?

460
00:29:49,900 --> 00:29:50,750
这是我们的机会
This is our chance.

461
00:29:50,750 --> 00:29:52,770
你到底为了什么
What--what reason could you possibly have

462
00:29:52,770 --> 00:29:53,650
非要留在这里
for staying here?!

463
00:29:53,660 --> 00:29:56,840
不是什么  是为了一个人
Not what. Who.

464
00:30:03,000 --> 00:30:05,290
奎恩先生  我想您错过了
Ah, Mr. Queen, I think it's past time

465
00:30:05,290 --> 00:30:08,160
离开这个岛的机会  永远地错过了
you left this island. Permanently.

466
00:30:20,420 --> 00:30:23,810
指挥塔  这里是天鹰801F
Island tower, Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot.

467
00:30:23,820 --> 00:30:25,920
我们正停在两千英尺外  完毕
We are 2,000 feet and holding, over.

468
00:30:27,040 --> 00:30:29,550
天鹰801F
Skyhawk 801 Foxtrot.

469
00:30:29,800 --> 00:30:31,200
这里是指挥塔
This is island tower.

470
00:30:32,100 --> 00:30:33,310
可以着陆了
You're clear to land.

471
00:30:34,160 --> 00:30:34,980
收到
Roger that.

472
00:30:45,740 --> 00:30:48,000
我非常好奇
Simply to satisfy my own curiosity,

473
00:30:48,000 --> 00:30:49,550
你为什么还活着
why aren't you already dead?

474
00:30:50,390 --> 00:30:52,280
我明明看见姚飞把你掐死了
I saw Yao Fei choke you to death.

475
00:30:52,280 --> 00:30:54,110
我猜他只是外强中干而已
I guess he's not as strong as he looks.

476
00:30:56,630 --> 00:30:58,080
可你还是回来找他
Still, you return for him.

477
00:30:59,100 --> 00:31:00,760
所以你要么是个蠢货
So you're either a fool,

478
00:31:01,300 --> 00:31:03,830
要么就真把自己当成英雄了
or is it possible you now think yourself a hero?

479
00:31:04,730 --> 00:31:06,680
-我不是英雄  -当然不是
- I'm not a hero.  - Of course not.

480
00:31:07,060 --> 00:31:08,410
若是无人可救
It's not possible to be a hero

481
00:31:08,410 --> 00:31:10,040
想做英雄也是白搭
when there's nobody worthy of saving.

482
00:31:13,670 --> 00:31:14,780
这就是你想要的
Is this what you want?

483
00:31:15,540 --> 00:31:17,060
你想让我跟他再打一架
Did you want me to fight him again?!

484
00:31:17,290 --> 00:31:18,490
不  奎恩先生
Oh, no, Mr. Queen.

485
00:31:19,250 --> 00:31:20,460
你一直搞错了
That's where you're mistaken.

486
00:31:21,340 --> 00:31:22,790
这不是比赛
This is not a match.

487
00:31:23,790 --> 00:31:24,920
是处决
It's an execution.

488
00:31:26,300 --> 00:31:26,970
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.

489
00:31:37,380 --> 00:31:38,850
你是温特格林  对吗
It's Wintergreen, right?

490
00:31:39,660 --> 00:31:40,830
比利·温特格林
Bill Wintergreen?

491
00:31:47,880 --> 00:31:49,130
我知道你的所有事情
I know all about you.

492
00:31:49,720 --> 00:31:51,900
我知道你为澳大利亚政府工作
I know you work for the Australian government.

493
00:31:52,300 --> 00:31:54,600
曾为你的国家效忠
And that you used to fight for your country.

494
00:31:54,750 --> 00:31:56,530
你曾有过信仰
You used to stand for something!

495
00:32:11,680 --> 00:32:14,240
无论他给你多少钱  我以三倍价格雇你
Whatever he's paying you, I'll triple it.

496
00:32:21,400 --> 00:32:22,870
他们有多少人
How many of them are there?!

497
00:32:35,020 --> 00:32:37,500
斯莱德  回来受死吗
Slade. Come back to die?

498
00:32:49,620 --> 00:32:51,610
有那么容易背叛我吗  比利
Was it so easy to betray me, Billy?

499
00:33:13,000 --> 00:33:13,840
知道吗  比利
You know, Billy...

500
00:33:17,150 --> 00:33:19,080
你的脚上功夫一向不错
you always had a good kick.

501
00:34:04,700 --> 00:34:06,220
我们的飞机来了
There goes our ride.

502
00:34:22,850 --> 00:34:23,980
厉害
I'm impressed.

503
00:34:24,830 --> 00:34:25,950
你居然没吐
You didn't puke.

504
00:34:26,030 --> 00:34:27,060
我忍住了
I swallowed it.

505
00:34:28,140 --> 00:34:29,250
你可以把我松开了
You can untie me now.

506
00:34:33,360 --> 00:34:35,490
你为什么非让我把你绑起来
Why'd you want me to tie you up in the first place?

507
00:34:36,410 --> 00:34:38,330
忍受剧痛的人很不稳定
A man in pain is unreliable.

508
00:34:38,850 --> 00:34:40,390
我怕我会杀了你
I was afraid I might kill you.

509
00:34:43,370 --> 00:34:44,090
谢谢
Thanks.

510
00:34:48,170 --> 00:34:48,890
怎么了
What?

511
00:34:49,880 --> 00:34:51,410
我被困在岛上而
I'm trapped on an island and

512
00:34:51,640 --> 00:34:53,980
唯一的朋友是一个叫威尔逊的人  就这样
my only friend is named Wilson. So.

513
00:34:58,230 --> 00:34:58,970
现在怎么办
What now?

514
00:34:59,100 --> 00:35:01,760
希望这次行动可以拖住法尔斯
We hope my fireworks show set Fyers back,

515
00:35:01,760 --> 00:35:03,880
也许足以让那些雇佣他的人
maybe enough for those who hired him in the first place

516
00:35:03,880 --> 00:35:04,860
取消行动
to call things off.

517
00:35:04,860 --> 00:35:05,800
雇他
Hired him?

518
00:35:06,780 --> 00:35:09,480
法尔斯是个外国雇佣兵  只为钱干活
Well, Fyers is a merc. He follows the money.

519
00:35:10,080 --> 00:35:12,370
所以在岛上他受雇于其他人
So he's on this island under someone's employ.

520
00:35:13,400 --> 00:35:15,270
-那我们怎么做  -我们得确保
- Then what do we do?  - We have to make sure

521
00:35:15,270 --> 00:35:17,860
不会死在这个荒芜的岛上
that neither of us dies on this godforsaken island.

522
00:35:17,860 --> 00:35:20,140
你之前不是说如果我们没搭上飞机
I thought you said if we didn't get on the plane...

523
00:35:21,760 --> 00:35:22,910
我们就逃不出去了
we weren't going to make it.

524
00:35:24,560 --> 00:35:26,210
只能说  之前我训练的那个蠢孩子
Well, that dumb kid that I trained,

525
00:35:26,590 --> 00:35:27,910
永远做不到
he would never have made it.

526
00:35:28,460 --> 00:35:29,200
你
You?

527
00:35:34,740 --> 00:35:36,210
还是有机会的
You might just have a chance.

528
00:35:38,870 --> 00:35:40,150
是的  我是法尔斯
Yep, it's Fyers.

529
00:35:40,440 --> 00:35:42,910
卫星显示岛上有多处爆炸
Satellites showed multiple heat blooms on the island.

530
00:35:42,910 --> 00:35:44,000
到底发生了什么
What the hell is happening there?

531
00:35:44,000 --> 00:35:46,810
-情况有点复杂  -因为斯莱德·威尔逊
- There was a complication.  - Slade Wilson?

532
00:35:46,810 --> 00:35:47,970
我正在处理
I'm handling it.

533
00:35:47,970 --> 00:35:50,060
好好处理  我付出了那么多
Well, handle it better. I've worked too hard

534
00:35:50,060 --> 00:35:52,740
也计划了很久  不允许在好事将近之时
and planned for too long to have complications arise

535
00:35:52,740 --> 00:35:53,430
出现任何差错
so close to the end.

536
00:35:53,430 --> 00:35:55,030
我向你保证  不会再发生任何事
I assure you, it won't happen again.

537
00:35:55,180 --> 00:35:56,410
姚飞怎么样了
What about Yao Fei?

538
00:35:56,470 --> 00:35:58,190
已经确保他会合作了
I've ensured his cooperation.

539
00:35:58,410 --> 00:36:01,350
好  我付给你这么多钱  法尔斯
Good. Paid you a lot of money, Fyers.

540
00:36:01,350 --> 00:36:03,760
希望物有所值
I expect a return on my investment.

541
00:36:05,720 --> 00:36:06,800
你要见我
You sent for me.

542
00:36:06,800 --> 00:36:08,050
我是一个守信用的人
I'm a man of my word.

543
00:36:09,140 --> 00:36:11,920
今天你把那小子交给我们  做得很好
You made the right call today, turning in your young castaway.

544
00:36:12,130 --> 00:36:15,090
凭这一点  我允许你见她五分钟
And for that, I'll grant you five minutes.

545
00:36:21,440 --> 00:36:23,740
莎朵  莎朵
Shado? Shado!

546
00:36:24,160 --> 00:36:24,920
莎朵
Shado!

547
00:36:26,540 --> 00:36:27,210
{\an2}爸

548
00:36:27,910 --> 00:36:28,540
{\an2}爸

549
00:36:29,160 --> 00:36:30,090
{\an2}对不起

550
00:36:31,610 --> 00:36:32,690
{\an2}真的对不起

551
00:36:34,290 --> 00:36:35,870
{\an2}爸爸  发生了什么事

552
00:36:37,950 --> 00:36:39,600
{\an2}很快会结束

553
00:37:05,240 --> 00:37:06,350
看来我没死
I guess I didn't die.

554
00:37:08,490 --> 00:37:09,220
再一次
Again.

555
00:37:11,160 --> 00:37:11,850
太棒了
Cool.

556
00:37:20,920 --> 00:37:21,700
不是很糟
It's not bad.

557
00:37:22,750 --> 00:37:24,450
我要怎么解释这一次呢
So how am I going to explain this one?

558
00:37:25,330 --> 00:37:26,400
枪走火
Hickey gone wrong?

559
00:37:28,170 --> 00:37:28,860
警方收集到一个
The police collected a

560
00:37:28,860 --> 00:37:30,930
你在奎恩联合企业留下的血样
sample of your blood at Queen Consolidated.

561
00:37:31,350 --> 00:37:34,230
我刚黑进了罪证鉴定室并且摧毁了样本
I just hacked the crime lab and ordered the sample destroyed.

562
00:37:34,230 --> 00:37:35,260
{\an8}终止申请已生效

563
00:37:39,520 --> 00:37:41,480
我希望你不介意
I hope it's all right.

564
00:37:42,270 --> 00:37:44,180
你的系统看上去像是八十年代的
Your system looked like it was from the eighties,

565
00:37:44,180 --> 00:37:45,820
还不包括八十年代的优点
and not the good part of the eighties,

566
00:37:45,820 --> 00:37:49,070
像麦当娜或者是护腿之类的
like Madonna and, well, legwarmers.

567
00:37:49,130 --> 00:37:50,230
这可是个大工程
It's a lot of work.

568
00:37:51,860 --> 00:37:54,050
所以说你加入我们了吗
Does that mean you're in?

569
00:37:54,050 --> 00:37:56,240
是指我是否加入你们的事业吗
You mean in as in I'm going to join your crusade?

570
00:37:56,250 --> 00:37:59,420
实际上  你已经算是我们的荣誉队员了
Well, you're practically an honorary member of the team already.

571
00:37:59,570 --> 00:38:00,810
狄格尔也是这么说的
Hmm. So Mr. Diggle said.

572
00:38:03,720 --> 00:38:04,360
不
No.

573
00:38:04,590 --> 00:38:06,230
那你为什么升级我的系统
Then why'd you upgrade my system?

574
00:38:06,230 --> 00:38:07,820
第一  看到弄得这么烂的系统
First, because seeing a network

575
00:38:07,820 --> 00:38:11,170
从灵魂深处伤害了我
that poorly set up hurts me. In my soul.

576
00:38:11,170 --> 00:38:14,580
第二  我想找到沃尔特
And second... I want to find Walter.

577
00:38:16,090 --> 00:38:17,040
我的继父
My stepfather.

578
00:38:17,780 --> 00:38:18,820
他对我很好
He was nice to me.

579
00:38:20,220 --> 00:38:22,340
狄格尔先生告诉我你用来打击罪犯的
And Mr. Diggle told me that the notebook you use

580
00:38:22,340 --> 00:38:25,320
笔记本与让沃尔特失踪的是同一本
to fight crime is the same notebook that got Walter abducted.

581
00:38:26,550 --> 00:38:28,560
我会帮你救他  但仅此而已
I'll help you rescue him, but that's it.

582
00:38:30,030 --> 00:38:33,340
之后我还是回到我无聊的IT女生活
Then I want to go back to my boring life of being an I.T. girl.

583
00:38:35,500 --> 00:38:36,690
这就是我的想法
That's my offer.

584
00:38:38,230 --> 00:38:38,950
好
Ok.

585
00:38:41,950 --> 00:38:43,420
还有我很想知道
So I've been meaning to ask...

586
00:38:45,080 --> 00:38:46,180
这儿有没有厕所
Is there a bathroom?

587
00:38:46,180 --> 00:38:47,650
到这以后我已经憋了很久了
'Cause I've had to pee since I got here.

588
00:38:48,330 --> 00:38:50,010
上楼左转
It's upstairs to the left.

589
00:38:50,010 --> 00:38:51,670
-好极了  -费利西蒂
- Great. - Felicity.

590
00:38:59,080 --> 00:38:59,840
谢谢
Thank you.

591
00:39:00,450 --> 00:39:01,080
不客气
Yeah.

592
00:39:11,060 --> 00:39:13,490
奥利弗  我知道你不想伤害她
Oliver, I know you don't want to hurt this girl

593
00:39:13,820 --> 00:39:14,520
你告诉她真相
and you didn't have any

594
00:39:14,520 --> 00:39:16,140
也是无可奈何
choice in telling her who you really were,

595
00:39:16,140 --> 00:39:17,590
但我们是在把她
but we're asking her to

596
00:39:17,590 --> 00:39:19,270
牵扯到很危险的事情中去
get involved in some pretty dangerous stuff.

597
00:39:19,280 --> 00:39:20,990
-我们能保护她  -怎么保护
- We can protect her. - How?

598
00:39:22,260 --> 00:39:24,060
你母亲向你开枪了  奥利弗
Your mother just shot you, Oliver.

599
00:39:24,060 --> 00:39:25,230
你连自己的安全都无法保证
You can't even keep yourself safe.

600
00:39:25,230 --> 00:39:28,060
她受到了惊吓  她是在保护自己
She was scared. She was defending herself.

601
00:39:28,060 --> 00:39:29,780
或者  她是在隐瞒什么东西
Or, she was hiding something.

602
00:39:29,780 --> 00:39:31,500
比如说她涉及
Like maybe her involvement

603
00:39:31,500 --> 00:39:33,470
沃尔特的失踪  甚至更糟
in Walter's disappearance, or worse.

604
00:39:33,470 --> 00:39:34,480
狄格尔  我们不一定知道
Diggle, we don't always know

605
00:39:34,480 --> 00:39:36,570
每个人处事的风格
why people do what they do.

606
00:39:38,420 --> 00:39:39,300
但我知道的是
But what I do know

607
00:39:39,300 --> 00:39:41,080
当我站在她办公室里
is that when I was standing in her office

608
00:39:41,080 --> 00:39:43,250
举着弓瞄着她心脏的时候
with an arrow aimed at her heart,

609
00:39:43,250 --> 00:39:50,210
她求我看在我和西娅的份上饶了她
she begged me to spare her, all on behalf of me and Thea.

610
00:39:50,730 --> 00:39:53,340
我收拾过很多坏人
Now, I've taken down a lot of bad people.

611
00:39:53,620 --> 00:39:55,460
没有一个提到他们的孩子  狄格
None of them brought up their kids, Dig.

612
00:39:55,630 --> 00:39:57,980
奥利弗  她有名单
Oliver, she had the list.

613
00:39:57,980 --> 00:40:00,330
或许她不是那个幕后黑手
Now she may not be in charge of whatever "It" is,

614
00:40:00,700 --> 00:40:02,050
但肯定和她脱不了干系
but she's definitely involved.

615
00:40:02,050 --> 00:40:03,040
脱不了什么干系
Involved in what?!

616
00:40:04,400 --> 00:40:06,420
我们都不知道幕后是什么
We don't even know what "It" is,

617
00:40:06,420 --> 00:40:07,620
在我们弄明白之前
and until we do,

618
00:40:07,630 --> 00:40:09,360
全都和她无关
she is off limits!

619
00:40:12,360 --> 00:40:13,550
听懂了吗
Am I clear?

620
00:40:26,560 --> 00:40:27,460
奥利弗  你这么说
But Oliver, are you saying

621
00:40:27,460 --> 00:40:29,860
是真的相信她是无辜的
this because you truly believe she's innocent?

622
00:40:30,840 --> 00:40:32,290
还是只是因为你不愿面对
Or because you don't want to face

623
00:40:32,290 --> 00:40:33,500
你母亲可能有罪的事实
the fact that your mother might be guilty?

624
00:40:50,990 --> 00:40:51,700
大约6尺1[1米89左右]
6'1,

625
00:40:53,050 --> 00:40:54,560
嗓音低沉
and a deep voice.

626
00:40:55,780 --> 00:40:56,580
发生什么了
What's going on?

627
00:40:56,900 --> 00:40:58,110
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?

628
00:40:58,260 --> 00:40:59,580
我打了你一晚的电话
I've been calling you all night.

629
00:40:59,580 --> 00:41:01,480
我在店里  那儿没信号
I was at the club. I get zero reception in there.

630
00:41:01,480 --> 00:41:03,810
或许你该改建个矿井
Maybe it's time you invest in a land mine.

631
00:41:03,810 --> 00:41:06,060
-西娅  -你母亲昨晚受到袭击
- Thea. - Your mother was attacked last night.

632
00:41:06,460 --> 00:41:07,950
-是治安维持者干的  -什么
- By the vigilante. - What?!

633
00:41:07,950 --> 00:41:09,860
他到我办公室来了
He came after me at the office.

634
00:41:09,860 --> 00:41:11,340
他伤着你了吗  你还好吗
Did he hurt you? Are you ok?

635
00:41:11,340 --> 00:41:12,340
事实上  是她伤了他
Actually, she hurt him.

636
00:41:12,690 --> 00:41:15,140
她用藏在办公室里的枪正面射伤了他
She shot him point blank with a gun hidden in her office.

637
00:41:15,140 --> 00:41:16,590
那对你们的调查应该有所帮助
That should help with your investigation.

638
00:41:16,590 --> 00:41:18,370
你们有找到任何证据
Did you get any evidence,

639
00:41:18,370 --> 00:41:20,510
比如血样  或者
like a blood sample, or...

640
00:41:21,640 --> 00:41:23,960
鉴证室里发生了小意外
There was a screw-up at the lab.

641
00:41:24,520 --> 00:41:25,570
太糟了
That's too bad.

642
00:41:28,640 --> 00:41:29,570
我们再联系
We'll be in touch.

643
00:41:30,990 --> 00:41:32,200
-谢谢  -不用
- Thank you. - Yes.

644
00:41:38,380 --> 00:41:39,400
宝贝
Oh, sweetheart.

645
00:41:39,850 --> 00:41:40,730
我害怕极了
I was so scared.

646
00:41:40,730 --> 00:41:42,220
你没事我就放心了
I'm just glad you're ok.

647
00:41:43,380 --> 00:41:44,630
我以为他会杀了我
I thought he was going to kill me.

648
00:41:49,650 --> 00:41:50,730
我向你保证
I promise you,

649
00:41:52,170 --> 00:41:53,940
他绝不会再来找你麻烦了
he's never going to bother you again.

