1
00:00:08,295 --> 00:00:10,396


2
00:00:14,295 --> 00:00:16,096


3
00:00:18,595 --> 00:00:20,596


4
00:00:23,395 --> 00:00:25,196


5
00:00:27,495 --> 00:00:29,596


6
00:00:29,945 --> 00:00:31,796


7
00:00:32,095 --> 00:00:34,396


8
00:00:34,945 --> 00:00:36,946


9
00:00:38,695 --> 00:00:40,846


10
00:00:05,913 --> 00:00:07,046
# The war was lost #

11
00:00:07,281 --> 00:00:09,415
# The treaty signed #

12
00:00:09,683 --> 00:00:11,550
# I was not caught #

13
00:00:11,785 --> 00:00:13,886
# I crossed the line #

14
00:00:14,120 --> 00:00:16,054
# I was not caught #

15
00:00:16,289 --> 00:00:18,090
# Though many tried #

16
00:00:18,358 --> 00:00:20,426
# I live among you #

17
00:00:20,694 --> 00:00:22,695
# Well disguised #

18
00:00:22,929 --> 00:00:24,930
# Never mind #

19
00:00:25,131 --> 00:00:26,964
# Never mind #

20
00:00:27,266 --> 00:00:31,503
# I live the life I left behind #

21
00:00:31,804 --> 00:00:34,171
# There's truth that lives #

22
00:00:34,440 --> 00:00:36,107
# And truth that dies #

23
00:00:36,442 --> 00:00:40,478
# I don't know which, so never mind #

24
00:00:42,882 --> 00:00:44,915
# I could not kill #

25
00:00:45,149 --> 00:00:47,117
# The way you kill #

26
00:00:47,385 --> 00:00:49,185
# I could not hate #

27
00:00:49,454 --> 00:00:51,655
# I tried, I failed #

28
00:00:51,923 --> 00:00:53,490
# You turned me in #

29
00:00:53,758 --> 00:00:55,926
# At least you tried #

30
00:00:56,294 --> 00:01:00,496
# You side with them whom you despise #

31
00:01:00,898 --> 00:01:04,300
# This was your heart, this swarm of flies #

32
00:01:04,601 --> 00:01:06,201
# This was once your mouth #

33
00:01:06,470 --> 00:01:09,271
# This bowl of lies #

34
00:01:09,506 --> 00:01:11,474
# You serve them well #

35
00:01:11,742 --> 00:01:13,810
# I'm not surprised #

36
00:01:14,077 --> 00:01:16,045
# You're of their kin #

37
00:01:16,313 --> 00:01:18,513
# You're of their kind #

38
00:01:18,748 --> 00:01:20,649
# Never mind #

39
00:01:20,850 --> 00:01:22,417
# Never mind #

40
00:01:22,752 --> 00:01:26,488
# I had to leave my life behind #

41
00:01:26,756 --> 00:01:28,657
# The story's told #

42
00:01:28,925 --> 00:01:31,526
# With facts and lies #

43
00:01:31,861 --> 00:01:35,763
# You own the world, so never mind #

44
00:01:25,998 --> 00:01:28,883


45
00:01:41,502 --> 00:01:44,504
You want milk? Sugar?

46
00:01:44,673 --> 00:01:46,740
Black.

47
00:02:14,734 --> 00:02:17,235
You bang down my door for a staring contest?

48
00:02:17,436 --> 00:02:20,505
A long time ago,

49
00:02:20,873 --> 00:02:23,341
you gave me a man's name on a piece of paper.

50
00:02:24,777 --> 00:02:25,810
I did.

51
00:02:26,078 --> 00:02:27,511
Because you knew what I'd do.

52
00:02:27,746 --> 00:02:30,547
I knew what I'd do.

53
00:02:30,782 --> 00:02:32,750
I didn't know you at all.

54
00:02:33,051 --> 00:02:36,420
Who was he to you, that man?

55
00:02:36,621 --> 00:02:39,090
Me? Nobody.

56
00:02:39,357 --> 00:02:41,692
Some greaser crankhead.

57
00:02:41,893 --> 00:02:43,927
Info come to me,

58
00:02:44,128 --> 00:02:45,795
I pass it on.

59
00:02:46,197 --> 00:02:49,398
Because why not get blackmail on a Sheriff's Deputy?

60
00:02:49,633 --> 00:02:51,467
That didn't hurt.

61
00:02:51,769 --> 00:02:54,403
But I have a sense of justice.

62
00:02:54,605 --> 00:02:56,039
You know that.

63
00:02:56,373 --> 00:02:57,974
That's why this was so surprising.

64
00:03:02,045 --> 00:03:04,412
That name on the piece of paper,

65
00:03:04,614 --> 00:03:06,281
whoever he was...

66
00:03:08,284 --> 00:03:10,753
he wasn't the man who hurt my wife.

67
00:03:12,555 --> 00:03:13,889
How's that?

68
00:03:14,157 --> 00:03:18,126
They caught the guy last month.

69
00:03:18,293 --> 00:03:20,828
DNA.

70
00:03:21,096 --> 00:03:23,231
I didn't know about it.

71
00:03:23,498 --> 00:03:25,599
I thought the info was solid.

72
00:03:28,570 --> 00:03:30,404
So none of this is a new development.

73
00:03:30,672 --> 00:03:32,907
You've never been in control.

74
00:03:34,608 --> 00:03:37,177
We gonna fight, Raymond?

75
00:03:37,444 --> 00:03:40,113
I would have been different.

76
00:03:40,447 --> 00:03:42,916
Of all the lies people tell themselves,

77
00:03:43,184 --> 00:03:45,085
I bet that's the most common.

78
00:03:45,286 --> 00:03:46,586
I could have.

79
00:03:46,788 --> 00:03:51,456
You fucked me.

80
00:03:51,758 --> 00:03:53,325
I sold my soul for nothing.

81
00:03:55,195 --> 00:03:57,496
If you were selling, it wasn't me buying.

82
00:03:57,798 --> 00:03:59,098
You wanted your hooks in a cop,

83
00:03:59,432 --> 00:04:01,733
so you used my wife's fucking tragedy

84
00:04:02,002 --> 00:04:03,869
to get me to kill somebody.

85
00:04:04,171 --> 00:04:06,405
I didn't get you to do anything.

86
00:04:06,639 --> 00:04:08,572
I gave you a name

87
00:04:08,841 --> 00:04:10,374
and you made your choice.

88
00:04:10,709 --> 00:04:12,476
And that choice was in you before your wife

89
00:04:12,778 --> 00:04:14,145
or any of this other stuff.

90
00:04:14,446 --> 00:04:17,182
It was always there... waiting.

91
00:04:19,051 --> 00:04:20,251
And didn't you use that man

92
00:04:20,619 --> 00:04:23,121
to be what you were always waiting to become?

93
00:04:24,723 --> 00:04:28,192
This thing, your wife...

94
00:04:28,459 --> 00:04:30,961
those are just excuses.

95
00:04:31,296 --> 00:04:33,030
You think you were Superman previous?

96
00:04:33,298 --> 00:04:38,501
And, hey, own it.

97
00:04:38,803 --> 00:04:41,604
You think I'd have done less?

98
00:04:42,005 --> 00:04:45,407
If that's the kind of thing that keeps you out of heaven,

99
00:04:45,642 --> 00:04:47,509
I don't want to go.

100
00:04:50,680 --> 00:04:54,550
Who gave you the name?

101
00:04:56,019 --> 00:04:58,321
Guy one of my guys knew, as I remember.

102
00:05:00,823 --> 00:05:02,924
Told me your story.

103
00:05:03,259 --> 00:05:05,460
Gave up the crankhead talking up the rape.

104
00:05:05,862 --> 00:05:08,930
I never heard of the dude until then. Or you.

105
00:05:10,900 --> 00:05:14,535
He was scum, I know that.

106
00:05:16,905 --> 00:05:19,106
I never even asked him anything.

107
00:05:21,109 --> 00:05:23,510
That guy, I just...

108
00:05:26,781 --> 00:05:28,615
You want out?

109
00:05:30,218 --> 00:05:32,119
You're free.

110
00:05:33,720 --> 00:05:35,855
You ain't had the nerve for this for a while.

111
00:05:43,130 --> 00:05:46,065
I don't want a shoot-out in my fucking kitchen, Raymond.

112
00:05:46,367 --> 00:05:49,635
And I don't want to see you die.

113
00:05:49,903 --> 00:05:52,938
By me or one of my other guys.

114
00:05:56,575 --> 00:05:58,676
I didn't set you up.

115
00:05:58,978 --> 00:06:01,313
And I ain't your suicide ticket.

116
00:06:12,557 --> 00:06:14,458
State lands start at the forest.

117
00:06:14,793 --> 00:06:18,262
Mostly we watch for fires and weed farms.

118
00:06:18,630 --> 00:06:21,032
Some of these shacks have been here since the '30s.

119
00:06:21,433 --> 00:06:23,700
Scene looks weeks old. Could be a lot more.

120
00:06:23,968 --> 00:06:25,468
Place is totally contaminated.

121
00:06:25,903 --> 00:06:27,971
We'll process, but we might not get anything else.

122
00:06:28,306 --> 00:06:29,905
- You have anything now?  - The blood is female.

123
00:06:29,974 --> 00:06:32,175
Dead gonorrhea biophages.

124
00:06:32,576 --> 00:06:34,610
All right, I want a grid search and a cadaver dog.

125
00:06:39,917 --> 00:06:42,484
Jesus Christ. You don't have enough to do?

126
00:06:42,785 --> 00:06:44,586
Give this to Sonoma Sheriff's.

127
00:06:51,361 --> 00:06:53,562
Blake's been running girls

128
00:06:53,863 --> 00:06:55,664
behind your back outside the clubs.

129
00:06:55,966 --> 00:06:58,532
That's not a tremendous surprise.

130
00:06:58,800 --> 00:07:00,268
Ambition fucked him up.

131
00:07:00,535 --> 00:07:02,036
No, it's bigger than you think.

132
00:07:02,371 --> 00:07:05,573
He's got a special stable with Chessani's kid.

133
00:07:05,807 --> 00:07:08,709
Eastern Bloc girls.

134
00:07:09,111 --> 00:07:11,946
Surgery at the Pitlor Clinic, make 'em top gear.

135
00:07:12,281 --> 00:07:15,949
He'll fill me in on it. Don't worry.

136
00:07:16,284 --> 00:07:18,418
You know about these parties they throw?

137
00:07:18,619 --> 00:07:20,520
Rich men.

138
00:07:20,788 --> 00:07:23,690
Politicians, developers.

139
00:07:25,159 --> 00:07:27,560
Caspere was going to these things.

140
00:07:27,795 --> 00:07:30,497
Deals get done.

141
00:07:30,798 --> 00:07:32,931
I need you to give up the man

142
00:07:33,200 --> 00:07:35,634
who tipped you to my rapist.

143
00:07:37,237 --> 00:07:40,339
Give me some time. I'll look him up.

144
00:07:40,573 --> 00:07:42,808
You sure you got time?

145
00:07:44,677 --> 00:07:46,979
On the ropes ain't the same thing as bleeding out.

146
00:07:47,180 --> 00:07:49,147
You know that.

147
00:07:49,515 --> 00:07:52,417
I'm back in the corridor and we're legit.

148
00:07:52,718 --> 00:07:55,920
This past shit you're worked up on,

149
00:07:56,155 --> 00:07:58,256
it can go away.

150
00:08:01,060 --> 00:08:03,461
State's following up, too.

151
00:08:03,662 --> 00:08:05,463
On the DL.

152
00:08:05,764 --> 00:08:07,631
Want my help looking for the girl

153
00:08:07,999 --> 00:08:10,367
who pawned the shit that sent us to the shoot-out.

154
00:08:10,568 --> 00:08:14,271
Irina Rulfo.

155
00:08:16,207 --> 00:08:19,076
We're looking for her, too.

156
00:08:21,046 --> 00:08:24,914
I'm gonna put my other hand up now.

157
00:08:25,215 --> 00:08:27,083
Don't you fucking shoot me, Raymond.

158
00:08:53,443 --> 00:08:56,111
You help me find that hard drive,

159
00:08:56,446 --> 00:08:59,713
I'll give you the man who put you wrong.

160
00:08:59,981 --> 00:09:01,582
Who wants the hard drive?

161
00:09:01,783 --> 00:09:03,817
Corporate guy.

162
00:09:06,888 --> 00:09:09,056
Could be a lot of sensitive footage on that thing.

163
00:09:16,797 --> 00:09:18,931
Where you going now?

164
00:09:20,301 --> 00:09:23,169
To see about killing a man.

165
00:09:23,504 --> 00:09:25,738
You sit back down with a gun on me again...

166
00:09:29,110 --> 00:09:31,110
don't let me see you coming.

167
00:09:34,481 --> 00:09:36,281
I'd like to avoid that, Frank.

168
00:09:37,683 --> 00:09:39,618
Good.

169
00:09:42,388 --> 00:09:44,323
You might be one of the last friends I got.

170
00:09:46,226 --> 00:09:48,226
Wouldn't that be fucked up?

171
00:10:22,592 --> 00:10:25,027
This is part of it. Vinci, Caspere,

172
00:10:25,362 --> 00:10:26,828
those parties we've been talking about.

173
00:10:27,063 --> 00:10:28,864
The missing girl, Vera,

174
00:10:29,232 --> 00:10:31,099
she made her last phone call from that lodge a mile back.

175
00:10:31,401 --> 00:10:33,469
Caspere's GPS put him right here.

176
00:10:33,870 --> 00:10:35,671
Now we've got a scene where a girl's been butchered.

177
00:10:35,938 --> 00:10:37,239
I'm interested in collusions.

178
00:10:37,740 --> 00:10:39,740
And maybe those parties are where your collusions get sealed.

179
00:10:40,075 --> 00:10:41,976
This is important. Somebody died here.

180
00:10:42,278 --> 00:10:43,378
Somebody dies every second of the day

181
00:10:43,779 --> 00:10:45,580
and they're not all lucky enough to do it in California.

182
00:10:45,881 --> 00:10:48,049
Uh, ladies, I've been briefed.

183
00:10:48,384 --> 00:10:49,917
I think we've got this now, you don't mind.

184
00:10:50,286 --> 00:10:53,087
This connects to a state's missing persons case, hm?

185
00:10:53,422 --> 00:10:54,922
And we'll be happy to share our findings.

186
00:10:56,757 --> 00:10:59,092
You know of any parties get thrown up here?

187
00:10:59,394 --> 00:11:01,795
A lodge a mile back, off the road?

188
00:11:02,263 --> 00:11:05,699
No, can't say we have. It's private property and not state forest.

189
00:11:05,966 --> 00:11:07,467
Sold it off a few years back.

190
00:11:07,768 --> 00:11:09,203
No noise in the forest? Commotion?

191
00:11:09,537 --> 00:11:12,639
This is my scene, Miss Davis.

192
00:11:12,907 --> 00:11:15,374
So get to it, Sheriff.

193
00:11:22,949 --> 00:11:24,750
Work the girls and the parties.

194
00:11:24,984 --> 00:11:26,385
You work the diamonds.

195
00:11:26,753 --> 00:11:28,821
Figure out where they came from originally.

196
00:11:29,155 --> 00:11:30,488
Maybe we can finger whoever took them.

197
00:11:30,656 --> 00:11:32,524
Velcoro?

198
00:11:32,791 --> 00:11:35,427
He's on the Rulfo girl.

199
00:12:28,611 --> 00:12:29,444
What?

200
00:12:34,284 --> 00:12:36,285
I thought I killed you.

201
00:12:38,487 --> 00:12:40,655
11 years ago.

202
00:12:40,855 --> 00:12:43,190
Thereabouts.

203
00:12:44,393 --> 00:12:46,093
Maybe I still will.

204
00:12:46,295 --> 00:12:48,329
That right?

205
00:12:48,563 --> 00:12:51,165
Who'd you really kill?

206
00:12:51,466 --> 00:12:53,834
There was a woman,

207
00:12:54,035 --> 00:12:56,670
29 years old.

208
00:12:56,870 --> 00:12:58,705
September 2004.

209
00:12:58,906 --> 00:13:01,240
An attorney.

210
00:13:01,475 --> 00:13:03,576
Dark brown hair.

211
00:13:03,911 --> 00:13:06,879
Underground parking garage downtown.

212
00:13:09,249 --> 00:13:11,150
Yeah, you remember.

213
00:13:12,485 --> 00:13:14,019
They're saying I did a lot of things.

214
00:13:14,253 --> 00:13:16,855
Got a brain condition.

215
00:13:18,558 --> 00:13:20,392
I forget things.

216
00:13:22,562 --> 00:13:25,364
I feel like I should have my lawyer here.

217
00:13:25,598 --> 00:13:27,299
How'd you get in to see me?

218
00:13:27,534 --> 00:13:29,701
She was my wife.

219
00:13:31,670 --> 00:13:33,538
I used to be a cop.

220
00:13:36,074 --> 00:13:39,544
You have no idea what you cost me.

221
00:13:39,945 --> 00:13:42,046
Hey, look, man, I ain't talking to you whatever this is about.

222
00:13:42,348 --> 00:13:43,715
You heard what this is about!

223
00:13:44,015 --> 00:13:47,351
I needed to look in your eyes.

224
00:13:50,020 --> 00:13:52,088
It was you.

225
00:13:53,691 --> 00:13:56,125
You don't even look like him, either.

226
00:13:56,293 --> 00:13:58,328
Who?

227
00:13:58,696 --> 00:14:01,197
My eyes look same as yours, you ask me.

228
00:14:01,432 --> 00:14:03,466
They're gonna burn you.

229
00:14:03,734 --> 00:14:04,800
That remains to be seen.

230
00:14:05,068 --> 00:14:07,536
You better hope they do.

231
00:14:07,804 --> 00:14:09,972
Key on my eyes, dipshit.

232
00:14:10,240 --> 00:14:12,140
See if I'm whistling Dixie.

233
00:14:12,409 --> 00:14:14,377
If they don't give you life,

234
00:14:14,711 --> 00:14:16,612
I will have every inch of your flesh

235
00:14:16,980 --> 00:14:19,982
removed with a cheese grater starting with your prick.

236
00:14:20,283 --> 00:14:22,917
I'll cut off your nose and your lips.

237
00:14:23,118 --> 00:14:24,919
Your nuts, too.

238
00:14:25,220 --> 00:14:27,989
And I'll make sure you live.

239
00:14:28,257 --> 00:14:30,492
Hell, they give you life,

240
00:14:30,760 --> 00:14:32,293
I might do it anyway.

241
00:14:32,495 --> 00:14:35,129
Like I said.

242
00:14:37,399 --> 00:14:40,534
Hey. Hey, who are you?

243
00:14:40,802 --> 00:14:42,269
You got the wrong dude.

244
00:14:42,570 --> 00:14:43,937
I don't even know you, man.

245
00:14:44,138 --> 00:14:46,573
You know me.

246
00:14:46,841 --> 00:14:49,676
You just didn't know you did.

247
00:14:56,983 --> 00:15:00,453
When you said blue diamonds, I remembered something.

248
00:15:00,654 --> 00:15:02,655
'92, the riots.

249
00:15:02,989 --> 00:15:05,291
Bad time to be in the insurance business.

250
00:15:05,592 --> 00:15:06,992
This could be the same stones.

251
00:15:07,327 --> 00:15:09,261
Two and a half million in blue diamonds,

252
00:15:09,630 --> 00:15:12,096
Peruzzi-cut. That's what you got, I think.

253
00:15:12,432 --> 00:15:15,199
Sable Fine Jewelers in Hollywood.

254
00:15:15,501 --> 00:15:18,603
There was a robbery April 30, 1992.

255
00:15:21,441 --> 00:15:23,475
You got to understand what it was like back then.

256
00:15:23,709 --> 00:15:27,245
Fires starting everywhere.

257
00:15:27,513 --> 00:15:29,379
Snipers taking potshots at cops.

258
00:15:29,614 --> 00:15:32,015
Tanks in the street.

259
00:15:32,350 --> 00:15:35,118
"Fuck the police" coming out of every...

260
00:15:37,522 --> 00:15:39,856
A lot of our guys just up and quit.

261
00:15:41,326 --> 00:15:43,594
The Sable Fine Jewelers robbery,

262
00:15:43,962 --> 00:15:46,596
that's two and a half million in blue diamonds.

263
00:15:46,964 --> 00:15:49,766
Yeah, I was the one you talked to on the phone.

264
00:15:50,133 --> 00:15:53,503
Double homicide, husband and wife proprietors.

265
00:15:53,737 --> 00:15:55,572
Woman was pregnant.

266
00:15:57,341 --> 00:16:00,677
Margaret Osterman. I remember her name.

267
00:16:02,712 --> 00:16:04,913
Report doesn't list a suspect,

268
00:16:05,181 --> 00:16:06,482
zero people of interest.

269
00:16:06,749 --> 00:16:08,517
- Yeah, well...  - Nothing.

270
00:16:08,885 --> 00:16:11,119
Place was looted right after the actual robberies,

271
00:16:11,387 --> 00:16:13,722
so no crime scene integrity.

272
00:16:16,726 --> 00:16:18,861
Wasn't no looters, either.

273
00:16:22,097 --> 00:16:24,431
Security tape was missing.

274
00:16:24,733 --> 00:16:27,234
Those two people were executed.

275
00:16:27,536 --> 00:16:28,769
They knew what they were doing.

276
00:16:29,004 --> 00:16:30,738
Tactical, like.

277
00:16:33,341 --> 00:16:35,242
Then those poor kids.

278
00:16:37,411 --> 00:16:39,278
Leonard and Laura.

279
00:16:41,448 --> 00:16:43,884
They witnessed it or something, right?

280
00:16:47,588 --> 00:16:49,255
Christ.

281
00:16:51,458 --> 00:16:53,726
You had to show me this?

282
00:17:01,434 --> 00:17:06,438
They were hiding in one of the display cabinets.

283
00:17:06,773 --> 00:17:09,274
Had to stay like that for a long time.

284
00:17:11,911 --> 00:17:15,779
Hiding with their parents lying there like...

285
00:17:21,787 --> 00:17:23,487
I had quadruple my normal caseload.

286
00:17:23,789 --> 00:17:25,924
Riots overwhelmed the system.

287
00:17:26,224 --> 00:17:27,958
Something didn't close fast,

288
00:17:28,092 --> 00:17:30,994
you moved on.

289
00:17:31,295 --> 00:17:33,664
Kids couldn't offer up anything?

290
00:17:36,400 --> 00:17:38,401
They could barely talk.

291
00:17:39,503 --> 00:17:42,072
Girl was maybe four.

292
00:17:42,306 --> 00:17:44,274
Boy a little older.

293
00:17:45,776 --> 00:17:47,743
Men wore masks.

294
00:17:51,481 --> 00:17:53,348
That's about it.

295
00:17:55,619 --> 00:17:57,653
Ended up in the foster system.

296
00:18:01,991 --> 00:18:03,825
You got kids?

297
00:18:06,261 --> 00:18:08,329
One on the way.

298
00:18:10,933 --> 00:18:13,367
Oh, God.

299
00:18:13,636 --> 00:18:16,771
Those kids fucked me up.

300
00:18:17,139 --> 00:18:19,573
Coming from where they did, going into the system.

301
00:18:20,875 --> 00:18:23,343
All that and the city burning to the fucking ground.

302
00:18:34,388 --> 00:18:36,589
Be at the Kali Klub in Ventura

303
00:18:36,857 --> 00:18:38,457
next Saturday at 6:00 PM.

304
00:18:38,826 --> 00:18:40,893
Say you're me. Say you're there to see Bogdan.

305
00:18:41,294 --> 00:18:43,663
And you've got to dress like you're worth $2,000 a night.

306
00:18:44,031 --> 00:18:45,865
You're gonna need somebody's help with that.

307
00:18:46,033 --> 00:18:47,600
Ha.

308
00:18:48,035 --> 00:18:51,437
This bus is gonna take you up to wherever the party is, I heard.

309
00:18:51,872 --> 00:18:54,673
And they're not gonna let you take in a purse or a phone or anything.

310
00:18:55,008 --> 00:18:57,375
They're gonna make you turn all that stuff in.

311
00:18:59,378 --> 00:19:01,880
Okay.

312
00:19:04,416 --> 00:19:06,451
You're gonna be around a lot of guys

313
00:19:06,719 --> 00:19:08,520
that expect easy sex.

314
00:19:08,855 --> 00:19:10,554
What are you gonna do about that?

315
00:19:10,856 --> 00:19:13,590
I'll figure it out.

316
00:19:16,695 --> 00:19:18,663
If those webcam guys were bad,

317
00:19:18,897 --> 00:19:20,297
this is way worse.

318
00:19:20,532 --> 00:19:21,598
Thena, I'm police.

319
00:19:21,900 --> 00:19:23,367
I know how to take care of myself.

320
00:19:23,702 --> 00:19:27,937
They're not gonna let you take in a knife or anything.

321
00:19:28,338 --> 00:19:31,774
They're gonna pat you down and make you strip.

322
00:19:33,443 --> 00:19:35,045
That's what I heard.

323
00:19:38,949 --> 00:19:41,484
That all I need to know?

324
00:19:42,887 --> 00:19:44,953
I made that for you.

325
00:19:47,423 --> 00:19:50,325
I was thinking about a woman drowning on dry land.

326
00:19:50,593 --> 00:19:53,062
Well, I don't really get art.

327
00:19:55,531 --> 00:19:58,466
I just don't understand why you work so hard to be alone.

328
00:20:01,937 --> 00:20:04,238
I find it really doesn't take that much work.

329
00:20:04,573 --> 00:20:07,742
I've been here for 10 minutes and you're just

330
00:20:08,077 --> 00:20:10,344
playing with knives just to keep me away.

331
00:20:10,645 --> 00:20:13,714
I was working out when you knocked.

332
00:20:22,056 --> 00:20:23,590
Okay.

333
00:20:23,891 --> 00:20:26,826
Anything else about this party?

334
00:20:28,262 --> 00:20:30,197
Just that...

335
00:20:30,431 --> 00:20:32,599
whatever you plan,

336
00:20:32,934 --> 00:20:35,300
you get on that bus, and it's fuck or run.

337
00:20:40,941 --> 00:20:44,343
It's hard, I won't lie.

338
00:20:44,644 --> 00:20:46,345
He filled this house up, you know?

339
00:20:46,479 --> 00:20:50,415
He loved you both as much as any man I ever knew.

340
00:20:50,784 --> 00:20:53,918
He never wanted anything, but it was for his family.

341
00:20:56,488 --> 00:20:58,456
It's ridiculous, I know.

342
00:21:04,596 --> 00:21:06,931
This isn't consolation.

343
00:21:08,367 --> 00:21:09,800
This was his, Joyce.

344
00:21:15,373 --> 00:21:17,374
That Blake guy's not outside, right?

345
00:21:17,541 --> 00:21:20,343
Right now?

346
00:21:20,511 --> 00:21:22,146
No.

347
00:21:22,346 --> 00:21:24,581
You know Blake?

348
00:21:24,883 --> 00:21:27,716
He turned up here right after the funeral.

349
00:21:27,985 --> 00:21:30,619
Asked how I was doing.

350
00:21:30,954 --> 00:21:33,022
Condolences and all that bullshit.

351
00:21:36,126 --> 00:21:37,926
And when he got through the bullshit?

352
00:21:39,362 --> 00:21:42,598
Asked if Stan had shared anything with me,

353
00:21:42,965 --> 00:21:45,267
might help him figure out who killed him.

354
00:21:45,567 --> 00:21:47,402
Had Stan said anything like that?

355
00:21:47,636 --> 00:21:49,470
No.

356
00:21:49,806 --> 00:21:52,640
I mean, he wasn't running things for you

357
00:21:52,909 --> 00:21:54,509
like that Blake guy, right?

358
00:21:59,015 --> 00:22:01,849
That's just skillsets.

359
00:22:02,050 --> 00:22:03,851
I loved Stan.

360
00:22:10,358 --> 00:22:12,226
Mikey doesn't know what to do.

361
00:22:14,595 --> 00:22:18,497
Stan was a great father.

362
00:22:18,765 --> 00:22:22,401
Not like a lot of... of them.

363
00:22:22,736 --> 00:22:26,206
I think about my little boy not having...

364
00:22:32,913 --> 00:22:34,346
- I'm sorry.  - It's okay.

365
00:22:42,222 --> 00:22:44,957
- I'm sorry.  - It's okay, Joyce.

366
00:22:58,270 --> 00:23:00,604
And this is a stealth bomber.

367
00:23:02,440 --> 00:23:04,942
Yeah.

368
00:23:05,210 --> 00:23:07,944
It can carry 80 smart bombs.

369
00:23:08,212 --> 00:23:10,480
Means they never miss.

370
00:23:15,920 --> 00:23:17,053
It's called "The Spirit."

371
00:23:20,557 --> 00:23:22,825
You...

372
00:23:23,227 --> 00:23:25,627
maybe you're not that interested in this stuff anymore, huh?

373
00:23:25,828 --> 00:23:27,229
That's okay.

374
00:23:27,430 --> 00:23:29,164
It kills people.

375
00:23:34,771 --> 00:23:36,571
Yeah.

376
00:23:43,812 --> 00:23:46,881


377
00:23:43,812 --> 00:23:46,881
Maybe some TV, then? You want to watch anything? I DVR'd the Cardinals.

378
00:23:47,182 --> 00:23:49,117
We could watch "Friends." It's always on.

379
00:23:49,484 --> 00:23:51,953
"Friends"? That show that's like 20 years old?

380
00:23:52,288 --> 00:23:54,188
I had an old girlfriend that used to watch it.

381
00:23:59,127 --> 00:24:01,628
What-all you scribbling over there?

382
00:24:01,996 --> 00:24:04,531
There some high drama happening I don't see?

383
00:24:04,832 --> 00:24:06,666
Please limit our interaction.

384
00:24:06,968 --> 00:24:08,969
I have a mandate to observe.

385
00:24:18,312 --> 00:24:21,180
By all means, buddy, find "Friends."

386
00:24:32,225 --> 00:24:34,159
Your dad teach you that?

387
00:24:37,263 --> 00:24:40,031
My old man never had time for sports.

388
00:24:44,403 --> 00:24:46,104
You want to sit for a second?

389
00:25:00,085 --> 00:25:02,652
Your father...

390
00:25:02,920 --> 00:25:06,423
was a good, good man.

391
00:25:09,026 --> 00:25:10,793
He was one of the best.

392
00:25:10,961 --> 00:25:12,895
I know that.

393
00:25:13,230 --> 00:25:15,898
Everybody doesn't need to keep saying.

394
00:25:18,802 --> 00:25:21,570
Things are gonna be hard for a while,

395
00:25:21,805 --> 00:25:24,072
but you'll come out.

396
00:25:24,307 --> 00:25:26,808
'Cause you got him in you.

397
00:25:27,043 --> 00:25:30,212
His fight is in you.

398
00:25:32,115 --> 00:25:33,748
Sometimes...

399
00:25:37,053 --> 00:25:41,588
sometimes a thing happens, splits your life.

400
00:25:41,890 --> 00:25:45,559
There's a before and after.

401
00:25:45,894 --> 00:25:49,096
I got like five of them at this point.

402
00:25:49,331 --> 00:25:53,401
And this is your first.

403
00:25:55,404 --> 00:25:57,138
But if you use it right...

404
00:25:57,339 --> 00:26:00,273
the bad thing...

405
00:26:00,508 --> 00:26:02,409
you use it right and...

406
00:26:05,446 --> 00:26:07,680
it makes you better.

407
00:26:08,815 --> 00:26:11,017
Stronger.

408
00:26:11,352 --> 00:26:13,653
It gives you something most people don't have.

409
00:26:17,090 --> 00:26:20,792
Bad as this is, wrong as it is...

410
00:26:22,195 --> 00:26:23,795
this hurt...

411
00:26:25,765 --> 00:26:27,999
it can make you a better man.

412
00:26:31,104 --> 00:26:32,803
That's what pain does.

413
00:26:34,839 --> 00:26:37,341
It shows you what was on the inside.

414
00:26:39,811 --> 00:26:41,479
And inside of you...

415
00:26:43,515 --> 00:26:45,349
is pure gold.

416
00:26:46,818 --> 00:26:48,386
And I know that.

417
00:26:48,653 --> 00:26:50,887
Your father knew that, too.

418
00:26:52,790 --> 00:26:55,559
Pure, solid gold.

419
00:26:55,793 --> 00:26:57,726
That's what you got.

420
00:27:17,814 --> 00:27:20,082
You enjoy this?

421
00:27:20,317 --> 00:27:21,683
You like your job?

422
00:27:22,051 --> 00:27:24,752
Please refrain from interacting with me, Mr. Velcoro.

423
00:27:32,060 --> 00:27:34,695
Hey, your mom, she...

424
00:27:34,997 --> 00:27:37,865
she mention anything changing?

425
00:27:38,200 --> 00:27:40,834
She said I might not be seeing you as much.

426
00:27:41,068 --> 00:27:42,169
You okay with that?

427
00:27:42,370 --> 00:27:45,239
I guess not.

428
00:27:50,445 --> 00:27:52,346
Look, things, if they change...

429
00:27:54,282 --> 00:27:56,416
they might...

430
00:27:57,684 --> 00:28:00,253
they might tell you things about you

431
00:28:00,454 --> 00:28:03,623
and about me.

432
00:28:03,923 --> 00:28:05,858
And the things they say, whatever they...

433
00:28:08,128 --> 00:28:10,163
whatever they say, whatever stories you hear,

434
00:28:10,464 --> 00:28:13,432
I am your father, you are my son.

435
00:28:16,369 --> 00:28:17,869
I will always love you.

436
00:28:21,807 --> 00:28:23,441
Okay.

437
00:29:03,914 --> 00:29:05,480
# one, two, three, four... #

438
00:29:18,127 --> 00:29:20,429
# well, if you don't like it #

439
00:29:20,763 --> 00:29:23,231
# go ahead, find yourself a saint #

440
00:29:23,532 --> 00:29:26,133
# go ahead now, try to find a boy #

441
00:29:26,468 --> 00:29:29,036
# who's gonna be what I ain't #

442
00:29:29,338 --> 00:29:30,904
# now what you need is #

443
00:29:31,273 --> 00:29:35,543
# a plastic doll with a fresh coat of paint #

444
00:29:35,877 --> 00:29:39,079
# who's gonna sift through the madness #

445
00:29:39,380 --> 00:29:41,548
# and always acts so quaint #

446
00:29:41,849 --> 00:29:44,451
# I said, yeah, yeah, yeah... #

447
00:29:45,886 --> 00:29:47,887
# well, with your new friend #

448
00:29:48,188 --> 00:29:50,857
# you're really making a scene #

449
00:29:51,191 --> 00:29:54,227
# and I see you bouncing around... #

450
00:30:49,346 --> 00:30:50,713
What happened tonight, Ray?

451
00:30:51,047 --> 00:30:52,415
I mean, you send him home early,

452
00:30:52,683 --> 00:30:54,383
you think that helps?

453
00:30:58,555 --> 00:30:59,922
I, uh...

454
00:31:00,123 --> 00:31:02,057
I want to...

455
00:31:02,359 --> 00:31:05,460
I want to make a deal with you.

456
00:31:07,896 --> 00:31:10,465
- I'm hanging up.  - Wait, please wait.

457
00:31:12,301 --> 00:31:14,803
Just don't go.

458
00:31:14,970 --> 00:31:17,472
You win.

459
00:31:19,442 --> 00:31:22,343
I'm not trying to win, Ray.

460
00:31:22,777 --> 00:31:25,078
I really think at this point we should leave it to the lawyers.

461
00:31:25,279 --> 00:31:27,815
Just listen.

462
00:31:27,982 --> 00:31:30,451
Don't...

463
00:31:30,719 --> 00:31:33,153
I won't contest custody.

464
00:31:33,321 --> 00:31:34,921
Okay?

465
00:31:36,791 --> 00:31:39,158
He's yours.

466
00:31:39,460 --> 00:31:41,694
I know he'll be happy with you and...

467
00:31:41,895 --> 00:31:44,464
and Richard.

468
00:31:46,233 --> 00:31:47,933
Are you serious?

469
00:31:48,168 --> 00:31:51,103
You're drunk again.

470
00:31:51,304 --> 00:31:53,873
No, listen.

471
00:31:54,174 --> 00:31:57,676
Just forget the paternity thing.

472
00:31:57,910 --> 00:31:59,344
Don't tell him.

473
00:32:01,914 --> 00:32:05,417
Don't ever tell him what happened or...

474
00:32:05,651 --> 00:32:08,920
or where he comes from.

475
00:32:09,188 --> 00:32:11,155
He shouldn't have to know.

476
00:32:11,323 --> 00:32:13,424
Just...

477
00:32:13,759 --> 00:32:16,326
just let him believe I'm his father...

478
00:32:18,663 --> 00:32:19,797
and I'll go away.

479
00:32:20,098 --> 00:32:23,534
It's for... it's for me, Ray.

480
00:32:23,769 --> 00:32:25,669
I have to know.

481
00:32:27,272 --> 00:32:29,806
Please...?

482
00:32:30,941 --> 00:32:33,209
Please.

483
00:32:33,444 --> 00:32:35,912
Never tell him

484
00:32:36,146 --> 00:32:39,181
and I'll stay away.

485
00:32:39,450 --> 00:32:41,284
I won't contest a thing.

486
00:32:45,355 --> 00:32:47,389
I'll never see him again.

487
00:32:50,493 --> 00:32:52,027
Sweetheart...

488
00:32:52,228 --> 00:32:54,763
Just say yes.

489
00:32:55,064 --> 00:32:58,166
Please? Please. Just... just say yes.

490
00:33:00,670 --> 00:33:02,671
And I'll leave your lives forever.

491
00:33:05,474 --> 00:33:07,408
Okay.

492
00:33:07,709 --> 00:33:11,045
Yes, Ray, I will... I will do that.

493
00:33:11,246 --> 00:33:14,315
You swear to me.

494
00:33:15,517 --> 00:33:17,384
I swear.

495
00:33:17,653 --> 00:33:20,954
Thank you. Thank you.

496
00:33:21,155 --> 00:33:22,889
Thank you.

497
00:33:35,336 --> 00:33:37,236
The name is Irina Rulfo.

498
00:33:37,537 --> 00:33:39,371
Sometime girl to one of your guys

499
00:33:39,739 --> 00:33:43,141
got taken in that shoot-out here a while back.

500
00:33:43,376 --> 00:33:46,078
You're Santa Muerte.

501
00:33:46,279 --> 00:33:48,046
You know her?

502
00:33:48,281 --> 00:33:50,015
It's not like that.

503
00:33:50,283 --> 00:33:52,150
It's not a gang like you thinking.

504
00:33:52,452 --> 00:33:54,252
Whatever the fuck. It's a book club.

505
00:33:54,553 --> 00:33:56,387
You were Ledo Amarillo's boy.

506
00:33:56,689 --> 00:33:58,990
Moving that cheap Mexican brown.

507
00:33:59,257 --> 00:34:00,725
Where could I find Irina?

508
00:34:28,052 --> 00:34:29,552
There's other appendages,

509
00:34:29,786 --> 00:34:31,086
won't heal up that easy.

510
00:34:31,388 --> 00:34:34,423
Motherfucker! I don't know.

511
00:34:34,658 --> 00:34:37,159
Where would I look?

512
00:34:44,835 --> 00:34:47,301
Where's them wetback hoochies hole up?

513
00:34:47,503 --> 00:34:49,538
Where's she stay?

514
00:34:57,479 --> 00:34:58,780
A flat G...

515
00:34:59,015 --> 00:35:01,149
or the next nail...

516
00:35:01,417 --> 00:35:03,417
goes through your eye.

517
00:35:05,687 --> 00:35:08,789
They got a place, El Monte.

518
00:35:16,497 --> 00:35:18,198
This is gonna hurt.

519
00:35:29,276 --> 00:35:32,144
Diamonds came from an unsolved robbery during the '92 riots.

520
00:35:32,446 --> 00:35:34,380
Jewelry store, double homicide.

521
00:35:39,619 --> 00:35:40,953
Ahem. No suspects.

522
00:35:45,892 --> 00:35:47,826
You make headway on the Rulfo girl?

523
00:35:56,568 --> 00:35:58,202
You sure you want to work this party?

524
00:36:01,073 --> 00:36:04,174
I don't want to bring this to Davis till we have something.

525
00:36:04,542 --> 00:36:07,578
Type of men at these things... I mean, who knows?

526
00:36:10,582 --> 00:36:12,482
It's your ass is what he means.

527
00:36:14,351 --> 00:36:15,819
Yeah.

528
00:36:16,186 --> 00:36:19,555
We've got your back. We'll double-tail the bus.

529
00:36:19,890 --> 00:36:21,891
I can't bring a phone in or anything else.

530
00:36:23,427 --> 00:36:25,495
Transponder.

531
00:36:27,098 --> 00:36:28,931
You stick that somewhere.

532
00:36:31,167 --> 00:36:33,368
Like in your shoe.

533
00:36:39,943 --> 00:36:42,577
We'll follow.

534
00:36:42,912 --> 00:36:45,246
We'll set up a perimeter around the place.

535
00:36:45,547 --> 00:36:48,282
And if I have to, I'll get in.

536
00:36:53,889 --> 00:36:55,456
Only try not to stab anyone.

537
00:36:55,691 --> 00:36:58,259
Unless you have to.

538
00:37:00,896 --> 00:37:02,328
What's your name again?

539
00:37:02,530 --> 00:37:04,931
Athena.

540
00:37:05,199 --> 00:37:07,500
- Freelance. - Mm-hmm.

541
00:37:07,802 --> 00:37:10,270
You're a little older than you said,

542
00:37:10,538 --> 00:37:12,338
but you got something.

543
00:37:12,573 --> 00:37:15,008
Okay, on the bus.

544
00:37:15,209 --> 00:37:17,377
Good, arms.

545
00:37:21,948 --> 00:37:22,982
Okay, go.

546
00:37:31,091 --> 00:37:33,659
Let's go.

547
00:37:33,960 --> 00:37:37,328
Okay, let's see it. Let's go.

548
00:37:37,496 --> 00:37:40,098
Come on.

549
00:37:40,265 --> 00:37:41,900
Good.

550
00:37:44,970 --> 00:37:47,438
You get back tomorrow.

551
00:37:47,740 --> 00:37:49,240
Do not be arguing, bitch.

552
00:37:50,743 --> 00:37:52,443
There.

553
00:39:08,048 --> 00:39:10,116
You come here to talk some more?

554
00:39:12,552 --> 00:39:13,753
Didn't know this was your place.

555
00:39:16,123 --> 00:39:17,757
That's one off the bucket list...

556
00:39:18,091 --> 00:39:20,859
Mexican standoff with actual Mexicans.

557
00:39:27,433 --> 00:39:29,001
She's on the bus ahead of us.

558
00:39:29,368 --> 00:39:32,437
- You can catch up now.  - Copy that.

559
00:39:32,738 --> 00:39:34,939
We'll take my car once they land.

560
00:39:44,817 --> 00:39:48,252
A guy, Ledo Amarillo,

561
00:39:48,620 --> 00:39:51,155
got blown up by the cops a couple months back.

562
00:39:51,423 --> 00:39:54,157
Came to that 'cause his lady

563
00:39:54,391 --> 00:39:56,559
sold some hot items.

564
00:39:56,794 --> 00:39:59,395
I'm looking for her.

565
00:39:59,596 --> 00:40:00,663
That's it.

566
00:40:00,965 --> 00:40:04,434
Sounds like you want to make a deal.

567
00:40:04,768 --> 00:40:07,037
But you told us you don't need partners.

568
00:40:07,305 --> 00:40:10,772
Her name is Irina Rulfo.

569
00:40:12,475 --> 00:40:14,844
Amarillo used to pimp her out.

570
00:40:16,947 --> 00:40:19,381
I just want to talk to her.

571
00:40:19,615 --> 00:40:21,917
You know where she is,

572
00:40:22,185 --> 00:40:25,020
or you can put me in touch,

573
00:40:25,288 --> 00:40:27,188
we can talk about deals.

574
00:40:29,424 --> 00:40:31,592
Well, we no longer need to make a deal.

575
00:40:36,999 --> 00:40:39,500
I got two protected clubs.

576
00:40:39,701 --> 00:40:42,770
If you help,

577
00:40:43,104 --> 00:40:45,839
you can push your stuff through there

578
00:40:46,040 --> 00:40:48,075
three nights a week

579
00:40:48,276 --> 00:40:50,710
for a year.

580
00:40:51,012 --> 00:40:54,547
End of the year, we renegotiate.

581
00:40:55,984 --> 00:40:58,818
Based on mutual performance.

582
00:40:59,120 --> 00:41:00,652
Why do you need this girl,

583
00:41:00,888 --> 00:41:03,256
if we can locate her?

584
00:41:03,556 --> 00:41:05,691
I want her to answer some questions.

585
00:41:05,993 --> 00:41:08,961
This guy her man ripped off,

586
00:41:09,296 --> 00:41:12,198
he was in possession of something.

587
00:41:20,172 --> 00:41:23,241
First year, I don't take a percentage.

588
00:41:24,977 --> 00:41:26,744
You keep what you make.

589
00:41:26,913 --> 00:41:28,880
100%.

590
00:41:29,181 --> 00:41:31,849
We'll get her to call you... maybe.

591
00:41:35,921 --> 00:41:38,155
It's a start.

592
00:41:40,825 --> 00:41:42,993
But we need to meet

593
00:41:43,194 --> 00:41:45,362
face-to-face

594
00:41:45,563 --> 00:41:47,164
at some point.

595
00:42:48,990 --> 00:42:51,091
Um, what... what is that?

596
00:42:51,425 --> 00:42:54,060
Like, pure Molly. It's pretty great.

597
00:42:54,395 --> 00:42:57,063
- Keep you in good mood.  - Mm-hmm.

598
00:43:00,733 --> 00:43:02,401
Open.

599
00:43:28,127 --> 00:43:29,427
All right, I want eyes on her.

600
00:43:29,628 --> 00:43:31,695
Copy. Moving.

601
00:43:53,483 --> 00:43:54,783
Enjoy yourselves, gentlemen.

602
00:44:25,980 --> 00:44:28,715
Phone call, boss. It's a girl.

603
00:44:28,916 --> 00:44:31,552
Sounds Spanish.

604
00:44:33,555 --> 00:44:35,789
- Frank Semyon. - My name is Irina.

605
00:44:36,157 --> 00:44:39,526
- You wanna talk to me?  - Yes. Yes, Irina.

606
00:44:39,727 --> 00:44:43,429
Can we meet?

607
00:44:43,863 --> 00:44:45,998
I'd like to talk to you about Ledo and what happened to him.

608
00:44:46,266 --> 00:44:48,767
I can pay you for your time.

609
00:44:49,035 --> 00:44:52,671
No, we talk on phone.

610
00:44:53,073 --> 00:44:55,908
Police said you pawned things from Ben Caspere's house.

611
00:44:56,210 --> 00:44:58,577
That's how they got your man Ledo.

612
00:44:58,877 --> 00:45:00,612
How did you get that stuff?

613
00:45:00,879 --> 00:45:02,914
Ledo really kill Caspere?

614
00:45:03,216 --> 00:45:05,183
A man gave them to me.

615
00:45:05,551 --> 00:45:08,553
Paid me $500 plus whatever I got to pawn them.

616
00:45:08,787 --> 00:45:11,523
Can you describe him?

617
00:45:11,790 --> 00:45:14,892
Thin, white. He was a cop.

618
00:45:15,127 --> 00:45:17,027
Didn't wear a uniform.

619
00:45:17,295 --> 00:45:18,496
How do you know he was a cop?

620
00:45:18,863 --> 00:45:21,932
I know a cop. Think I've seen him before.

621
00:45:22,200 --> 00:45:23,434
He's like a jefe.

622
00:45:23,768 --> 00:45:26,570
Meet with me, I'll show you some pictures.

623
00:45:26,771 --> 00:45:28,239
You pick him out.

624
00:45:28,573 --> 00:45:30,407
I ain't talking to no more white men.

625
00:45:30,708 --> 00:45:32,509
They make me call, I call.

626
00:45:34,044 --> 00:45:36,045
You can get your people to come with you.

627
00:45:36,313 --> 00:45:38,948
No tricks. You'll be safe.

628
00:45:39,316 --> 00:45:42,084
And I'll give you a thousand to point the man out.

629
00:45:43,754 --> 00:45:45,921
Si. Okay.

630
00:47:04,363 --> 00:47:06,197
As promised, you've seen her.

631
00:47:08,800 --> 00:47:13,037
We take Thursday, Friday, Saturday night at the clubs.

632
00:47:13,205 --> 00:47:14,871
No fee.

633
00:47:16,574 --> 00:47:18,408
Like you said.

634
00:47:18,676 --> 00:47:20,611
Next year we renegotiate.

635
00:47:20,811 --> 00:47:23,813
Like you said.

636
00:47:24,081 --> 00:47:26,750
Why the fuck did you do this?

637
00:47:26,984 --> 00:47:29,419
Why hurt the girl?

638
00:47:29,687 --> 00:47:30,920
The fuck is wrong with you?

639
00:47:33,590 --> 00:47:35,991
You heard her.

640
00:47:36,260 --> 00:47:37,760
Bitch was working for cops.

641
00:47:54,943 --> 00:47:57,145
Frank...?

642
00:48:01,116 --> 00:48:03,084
Yeah.

643
00:49:20,791 --> 00:49:22,425
Fuck. Shit.

644
00:49:22,693 --> 00:49:24,427
I've been watching you, miss.

645
00:49:24,695 --> 00:49:26,162
You know, I said to myself,

646
00:49:26,430 --> 00:49:28,431
now there is a real woman.

647
00:49:28,699 --> 00:49:30,466
Not like these little girls.

648
00:49:30,800 --> 00:49:32,901
Oh, they try to make like they understand,

649
00:49:33,169 --> 00:49:35,704
but it's just empty eyes.

650
00:49:38,608 --> 00:49:42,110
You see, for me, it's just as much about the dialogue.

651
00:49:44,881 --> 00:49:46,382
I could talk to you all day about the oil business,

652
00:49:46,716 --> 00:49:48,983
but I'm sure you'd like to do something else.

653
00:50:39,932 --> 00:50:42,534
$12 million doesn't fit in a briefcase.

654
00:50:42,868 --> 00:50:44,368
The exchange will be secure.

655
00:50:44,703 --> 00:50:46,604
We can enter the money into the system

656
00:50:46,939 --> 00:50:49,340
as marketing costs, investment overlay.

657
00:50:49,575 --> 00:50:51,008
Like you did with Semyon?

658
00:50:52,511 --> 00:50:54,045
That was between him and Caspere.

659
00:50:55,680 --> 00:50:57,614
And your people's investments

660
00:50:57,916 --> 00:51:00,150
are worth considerably more to us.

661
00:51:00,418 --> 00:51:02,553
Now, please, enjoy the evening.

662
00:51:02,921 --> 00:51:06,389
Full moon is the best time to ratify alliances.

663
00:51:32,214 --> 00:51:35,049
A nation's strength is determined by two things...

664
00:51:37,119 --> 00:51:40,288
Its energy resources...

665
00:51:40,556 --> 00:51:42,791
and its capacity for war.

666
00:51:46,928 --> 00:51:48,963
Oh, yes, here we are.

667
00:51:52,166 --> 00:51:54,368
You care to watch for a while?

668
00:51:54,669 --> 00:51:57,237
I do so enjoy the natural state.

669
00:52:00,308 --> 00:52:03,243
You're the prettiest little girl I ever seen.

670
00:52:06,647 --> 00:52:09,649
I heard there's a unicorn in those woods.

671
00:52:13,587 --> 00:52:15,154
You want to help me look for it?

672
00:52:20,627 --> 00:52:22,594
Why don't you partake

673
00:52:22,862 --> 00:52:24,329
and I'll join you momentarily?

674
00:52:24,631 --> 00:52:26,832
Excuse, please.

675
00:52:27,099 --> 00:52:30,936
I... bathroom. I return.

676
00:52:31,203 --> 00:52:34,439
You come right back here, now.

677
00:52:34,774 --> 00:52:36,942
Don't make me have to find you, miss.

678
00:52:39,310 --> 00:52:41,245
Splash of water.

679
00:52:41,446 --> 00:52:43,280
Perfume.

680
00:54:31,283 --> 00:54:32,984
Fuck.

681
00:54:46,965 --> 00:54:49,199
Some of them taste better than others.

682
00:54:58,375 --> 00:54:59,208
Vera?

683
00:55:04,481 --> 00:55:07,016
Vera. Vera Machiado?

684
00:55:07,217 --> 00:55:08,818
Oh, my God.

685
00:55:10,953 --> 00:55:12,954
I'm a friend of your sister Dani's.

686
00:55:13,222 --> 00:55:14,522
We got to get you out of here.

687
00:55:14,791 --> 00:55:16,424
- No. No...  - Come on.

688
00:55:16,659 --> 00:55:18,560
Come on. Get up.

689
00:55:18,728 --> 00:55:20,862
Come on.

690
00:55:35,043 --> 00:55:37,144
Now, I know I said don't make me have to come and find you,

691
00:55:37,378 --> 00:55:39,346
but...

692
00:55:44,586 --> 00:55:46,552
Fucking whore.

693
00:56:10,777 --> 00:56:13,011
Fuck you do?

694
00:56:29,795 --> 00:56:31,729
Oh, God. Take her. Take her, take her.

695
00:56:31,930 --> 00:56:34,565
Go, go, go, go.

696
00:56:35,700 --> 00:56:37,934
Move.

697
00:56:38,269 --> 00:56:40,237
- Who is she?  - My missing person.

698
00:56:40,537 --> 00:56:42,372
Take her.

699
00:56:42,640 --> 00:56:43,974
Velcoro's getting the car. Go.

700
00:56:44,142 --> 00:56:45,909
Fuck.

701
00:56:48,212 --> 00:56:50,380
Okay, you got to run. You got to run.

702
00:56:50,581 --> 00:56:52,548
Go, go, go.

703
00:56:52,750 --> 00:56:54,250
Hey!

704
00:57:02,592 --> 00:57:05,127
Fuck. Come on...!

705
00:57:07,931 --> 00:57:08,831
Look. That's him.

706
00:57:13,568 --> 00:57:15,436
Get down! Get down!

707
00:57:17,072 --> 00:57:19,674
Go.

708
00:57:23,846 --> 00:57:25,613
Kill the lights.

709
00:57:25,981 --> 00:57:28,448
- Who's the girl?  - Bezzerides's missing person.

710
00:57:31,281 --> 00:57:32,448
I got this stuff.

711
00:57:36,291 --> 00:57:38,225
Some kind of deal going down.

712
00:57:38,526 --> 00:57:40,127
Same land area as we were talking.

713
00:57:40,361 --> 00:57:41,995
Fuck. What happened?

714
00:57:42,330 --> 00:57:43,996
They gave me something. I don't know.

715
00:57:45,632 --> 00:57:47,300
I think I killed someone.

716
00:57:50,637 --> 00:57:52,371
Oh, Jesus.

717
00:57:52,605 --> 00:57:54,707
Those motherfuckers.

718
00:58:05,551 --> 00:58:07,219
These contracts...

719
00:58:08,787 --> 00:58:10,822
signatures all over them.

720
00:58:39,549 --> 00:58:41,918
# when you're a storm #

721
00:58:42,186 --> 00:58:45,388
# you're so emotional #

722
00:58:45,655 --> 00:58:48,691
# moody and controlled #

723
00:58:48,926 --> 00:58:52,627
# sly and involved #

724
00:58:52,896 --> 00:58:55,797
# if you're all right #

725
00:58:56,099 --> 00:58:58,901
# you come to me in times #

726
00:58:59,168 --> 00:59:02,470
# you make me realize #

727
00:59:02,738 --> 00:59:05,974
# I'm not the kindest guy #

728
00:59:06,276 --> 00:59:09,076
# but I give, give, give, give #

729
00:59:13,048 --> 00:59:16,417
# I give what I can give #

730
00:59:19,388 --> 00:59:22,623
# so just give, give, give, give #

731
00:59:26,693 --> 00:59:30,297
# give me what you have, dear #

