1
00:00:08,295 --> 00:00:10,396


2
00:00:14,295 --> 00:00:16,096


3
00:00:18,595 --> 00:00:20,596


4
00:00:23,395 --> 00:00:25,196


5
00:00:27,495 --> 00:00:29,596


6
00:00:29,945 --> 00:00:31,796


7
00:00:32,095 --> 00:00:34,396


8
00:00:34,945 --> 00:00:36,946


9
00:00:38,695 --> 00:00:40,846


10
00:00:43,395 --> 00:00:45,096


11
00:00:47,495 --> 00:00:49,596


12
00:00:56,295 --> 00:00:58,296


13
00:00:05,205 --> 00:00:07,123
# The war was lost #

14
00:00:07,124 --> 00:00:09,418
# The treaty signed #

15
00:00:09,460 --> 00:00:11,587
# I was not caught #

16
00:00:11,629 --> 00:00:13,880
# I crossed the line #

17
00:00:13,881 --> 00:00:15,882
# I was not caught #

18
00:00:15,883 --> 00:00:18,218
# Though many tried #

19
00:00:18,260 --> 00:00:20,386
# I live among you #

20
00:00:20,387 --> 00:00:22,722
# Well disguised #

21
00:00:22,723 --> 00:00:24,724
# I had to leave #

22
00:00:24,725 --> 00:00:27,143
# My life behind #

23
00:00:27,144 --> 00:00:29,438
# I dug some graves #

24
00:00:29,480 --> 00:00:31,564
# You'll never find #

25
00:00:31,565 --> 00:00:33,984
# The story's told #

26
00:00:34,026 --> 00:00:36,152
# With facts and lies #

27
00:00:36,153 --> 00:00:38,322
# I have a name #

28
00:00:38,364 --> 00:00:40,532
# But never mind #

29
00:00:40,574 --> 00:00:42,825
# Never mind #

30
00:00:42,826 --> 00:00:44,911
# Never mind #

31
00:00:44,912 --> 00:00:48,707
# The war was lost, the treaty signed #

32
00:00:48,749 --> 00:00:53,920
# There's truth that lives and truth that dies #

33
00:00:53,921 --> 00:00:58,092
# I don't know which, so never mind #

34
00:01:00,344 --> 00:01:05,014
# I could not kill the way you kill #

35
00:01:05,015 --> 00:01:07,141
# I could not hate #

36
00:01:07,142 --> 00:01:09,435
# I tried, I failed #

37
00:01:09,436 --> 00:01:11,605
# You turned me in #

38
00:01:11,647 --> 00:01:13,816
# At least you tried #

39
00:01:13,857 --> 00:01:18,611
# You side with them whom you despise #

40
00:01:18,612 --> 00:01:21,948
# This was your heart, this swarm of flies #

41
00:01:21,949 --> 00:01:27,203
# This was once your mouth, this bowl of lies #

42
00:01:27,204 --> 00:01:31,667
# You served them well, I'm not surprised #

43
00:01:31,709 --> 00:01:33,793
# You're of their kin #

44
00:01:33,794 --> 00:01:36,130
# You're of their kind #

45
00:01:25,998 --> 00:01:28,883


46
00:02:28,098 --> 00:02:30,434
I feel so fucked up.

47
00:02:30,517 --> 00:02:32,603
My head's so fucked up.

48
00:02:34,188 --> 00:02:36,106
You want me to roll a joint?

49
00:02:36,190 --> 00:02:38,775
Oh, those fucking fucks.

50
00:02:40,194 --> 00:02:42,195
Holloway was there.

51
00:02:42,196 --> 00:02:44,114
Fucking Geldof.

52
00:02:44,198 --> 00:02:47,201
The fucking AG was shaking hands with the...

53
00:02:50,704 --> 00:02:53,290
That piece of shit tried to choke me out.

54
00:02:59,963 --> 00:03:02,382
He put his hands on the wrong...

55
00:03:07,721 --> 00:03:10,307
I've been waiting my whole life for that.

56
00:03:14,728 --> 00:03:17,314
I think I even...

57
00:03:19,149 --> 00:03:21,235
went looking.

58
00:03:23,153 --> 00:03:25,405
That's my whole life.

59
00:03:27,240 --> 00:03:30,869
And when I ran out of the woods and they found me...

60
00:03:31,536 --> 00:03:32,871
The woods?

61
00:03:33,246 --> 00:03:35,082
What?

62
00:03:36,917 --> 00:03:39,086
What?

63
00:03:40,420 --> 00:03:42,047
You said...

64
00:03:42,089 --> 00:03:44,424
Oh, God.

65
00:04:11,284 --> 00:04:13,787
Hey, look, I don't think...

66
00:04:16,373 --> 00:04:19,959
This wouldn't help you.

67
00:04:19,960 --> 00:04:21,962
It might.

68
00:04:23,547 --> 00:04:25,799
It usually does.

69
00:04:28,635 --> 00:04:30,303
All right.

70
00:04:36,810 --> 00:04:40,563
Oh, it's the drugs. It's the drugs.

71
00:04:40,564 --> 00:04:42,314
I'm fucked up.

72
00:04:45,485 --> 00:04:47,571
You're too far out of my league anyway.

73
00:04:51,241 --> 00:04:53,452
I'm gonna check out the other two.

74
00:04:55,078 --> 00:04:58,415
You and the girl, you should stay here through tomorrow.

75
00:04:58,457 --> 00:05:01,543
You know, we can see what the damage is

76
00:05:01,585 --> 00:05:03,503
and report all this to Davis.

77
00:05:03,504 --> 00:05:05,922
Yeah.

78
00:05:07,299 --> 00:05:09,384
You can call your sister.

79
00:05:14,347 --> 00:05:17,098
Addenda to corporate charters for holding companies,

80
00:05:17,099 --> 00:05:20,103
shares dispersed to new owners... Eagle Iron LLC.

81
00:05:20,145 --> 00:05:24,190
President Osip Agranov.

82
00:05:24,191 --> 00:05:25,859
Electralux Entertainment.

83
00:05:25,860 --> 00:05:29,779
President Anthony Chessani.

84
00:05:33,658 --> 00:05:36,453
It shows the holding company's assets.

85
00:05:41,708 --> 00:05:44,793
These are all land parcels in that corridor.

86
00:05:44,794 --> 00:05:47,047
Valley poisoned by mine runoff.

87
00:05:50,967 --> 00:05:54,428
There was some kind of buy/sell deal upon death.

88
00:05:54,429 --> 00:05:57,305
I mean, they just repurchased Caspere's shares for pennies

89
00:05:57,306 --> 00:05:58,475
and redistributed them.

90
00:05:58,516 --> 00:06:00,142
Motive.

91
00:06:00,143 --> 00:06:01,478
Well, it's something.

92
00:06:22,249 --> 00:06:24,042
Everything all right?

93
00:06:25,043 --> 00:06:27,337
Yeah. Yeah.

94
00:06:28,588 --> 00:06:30,548
It's just my fiancee.

95
00:06:48,108 --> 00:06:49,858
Okay, what's next?

96
00:06:49,859 --> 00:06:52,695
I got to, uh...

97
00:06:52,696 --> 00:06:54,614
I got to check in at home.

98
00:07:09,963 --> 00:07:12,381
We should drop this on Davis.

99
00:07:12,382 --> 00:07:15,467
You want to hold the fort?

100
00:07:15,468 --> 00:07:17,470
Question her when she comes up.

101
00:07:18,388 --> 00:07:20,140
Yeah.

102
00:07:23,476 --> 00:07:27,397
You think they could make me for that security guard?

103
00:07:28,982 --> 00:07:30,400
Would they?

104
00:07:31,735 --> 00:07:33,570
I don't know.

105
00:07:57,093 --> 00:07:59,262
I hoped you'd make it home.

106
00:08:00,346 --> 00:08:02,724
But I guess here is good enough.

107
00:08:02,766 --> 00:08:05,560
Took a couple kicks last night.

108
00:08:05,602 --> 00:08:07,562
Can you talk about it?

109
00:08:07,604 --> 00:08:10,565
There'll be some new people operating at the clubs

110
00:08:10,566 --> 00:08:12,858
for a while, a few days a week.

111
00:08:12,859 --> 00:08:14,819
What people?

112
00:08:14,861 --> 00:08:18,156
Mexicans. Something else to solve.

113
00:08:18,198 --> 00:08:20,823
In the midst of being gangbanged by forces unseen,

114
00:08:20,824 --> 00:08:22,575
I figure I'd drill a new orifice,

115
00:08:22,576 --> 00:08:24,871
go on and fuck myself for a change.

116
00:08:26,289 --> 00:08:28,664
Frank, what can you pull together?

117
00:08:28,665 --> 00:08:29,709
Liquid right now?

118
00:08:29,710 --> 00:08:33,129
Maybe 200K. Three tops.

119
00:08:35,381 --> 00:08:37,884
We could just walk away from the table.

120
00:08:37,885 --> 00:08:41,429
That's 45 years of my life.

121
00:08:41,471 --> 00:08:43,473
You see me managing an Applebee's?

122
00:08:43,474 --> 00:08:46,267
I worked at one once.

123
00:08:46,309 --> 00:08:48,561
They give you a shift meal.

124
00:08:55,401 --> 00:08:57,737
I'll handle the deliveries at Lux.

125
00:09:00,823 --> 00:09:03,159
Mrs. Semyon. You look lovely this morning.

126
00:09:03,160 --> 00:09:05,828
Ray, dashing as ever.

127
00:09:07,497 --> 00:09:09,290
Keep it holstered.

128
00:09:26,140 --> 00:09:29,352
Aw. A little bit of a strange night.

129
00:09:34,148 --> 00:09:36,442
You should just tell me what's going on, Paul.

130
00:09:36,484 --> 00:09:39,111
The men on the phone scared me.

131
00:09:39,112 --> 00:09:41,947
He said, "Ask Paul about the pictures."

132
00:09:41,948 --> 00:09:43,283
That's all he said.

133
00:09:43,324 --> 00:09:46,118
He hung up.

134
00:09:46,119 --> 00:09:47,453
What is this about?

135
00:09:47,495 --> 00:09:49,955
Tell me or I'm not going.

136
00:09:49,956 --> 00:09:53,625
It was that case. I was undercover.

137
00:09:53,626 --> 00:09:56,296
I just want you to be safe for a couple days.

138
00:09:58,631 --> 00:10:00,717
We are having a baby.

139
00:10:02,051 --> 00:10:04,470
This will all be cleared up by then.

140
00:10:06,139 --> 00:10:08,473
Why did you get with me, Paul?

141
00:10:08,474 --> 00:10:10,977
Why did you even ask me out?

142
00:10:16,232 --> 00:10:19,068
I'm just trying to be a good man.

143
00:10:21,237 --> 00:10:23,740
Well, you don't try right.

144
00:10:30,371 --> 00:10:34,291
What happened?

145
00:10:34,292 --> 00:10:36,711
It was bad in there.

146
00:10:38,129 --> 00:10:39,963
If they think I was you,

147
00:10:39,964 --> 00:10:43,009
you need to disappear for a little while.

148
00:10:44,260 --> 00:10:45,635
What?

149
00:10:45,636 --> 00:10:47,971
How am I supposed to disappear?

150
00:10:47,972 --> 00:10:49,807
I'll give you some money.

151
00:10:51,309 --> 00:10:53,935
Go up north. Oregon, maybe.

152
00:10:53,936 --> 00:10:55,812
Dad knows some people.

153
00:10:55,813 --> 00:10:58,065
He should go, too, just...

154
00:10:58,066 --> 00:10:59,399
just to be safe.

155
00:10:59,400 --> 00:11:01,067
For how long?

156
00:11:01,068 --> 00:11:02,778
I... I'm seeing someone

157
00:11:02,779 --> 00:11:05,322
and I'm starting school in the fall.

158
00:11:05,323 --> 00:11:07,991
We just need to put this case down.

159
00:11:07,992 --> 00:11:10,410
And then you're okay.

160
00:11:10,411 --> 00:11:13,038
But you gotta go. Both of you.

161
00:11:13,039 --> 00:11:15,207
Now, like today.

162
00:11:15,208 --> 00:11:18,002
You get somebody to put some of your things together for you.

163
00:11:18,003 --> 00:11:21,004
You don't go back home.

164
00:11:21,005 --> 00:11:23,507
What did you do?

165
00:11:23,508 --> 00:11:25,551
I saved a girl.

166
00:11:27,512 --> 00:11:30,472
She's in the next room

167
00:11:30,473 --> 00:11:33,850
coming off of whatever they had her on.

168
00:11:33,851 --> 00:11:35,728
Did they give you something?

169
00:11:40,608 --> 00:11:43,777
Did you go all the way in?

170
00:11:43,778 --> 00:11:45,613
Inside the party?

171
00:11:46,572 --> 00:11:48,032
Yeah.

172
00:11:50,576 --> 00:11:51,786
Did you?

173
00:12:13,057 --> 00:12:16,476
I don't see how you can expect us to stay here.

174
00:12:16,477 --> 00:12:19,186
Paul, if something this wrong is going on,

175
00:12:19,187 --> 00:12:20,521
maybe you should go to your bosses.

176
00:12:20,522 --> 00:12:21,897
Tell them you need out.

177
00:12:21,898 --> 00:12:23,691
It's more complicated than that.

178
00:12:23,692 --> 00:12:25,570
The less you know, the better.

179
00:12:25,571 --> 00:12:28,405
I can't go to the bosses, not yet.

180
00:12:28,406 --> 00:12:31,158
This op I did, it might be nothing.

181
00:12:32,952 --> 00:12:34,827
But I just want you both to be safe

182
00:12:34,828 --> 00:12:37,081
if my cover was blown, that's it.

183
00:12:37,082 --> 00:12:38,790
Two, three nights tops.

184
00:12:38,791 --> 00:12:41,584
And what are we supposed to do?

185
00:12:41,585 --> 00:12:43,753
Room service.

186
00:12:43,754 --> 00:12:49,718
Don't answer the door or the phone if it isn't me.

187
00:12:49,719 --> 00:12:53,764
And, you know, just relax.

188
00:12:58,144 --> 00:12:59,395
Okay.

189
00:13:08,070 --> 00:13:10,363
You bring someone up,

190
00:13:10,364 --> 00:13:13,658
invest time and emotion,

191
00:13:13,659 --> 00:13:15,618
personal attachment,

192
00:13:15,619 --> 00:13:18,747
and hope for what?

193
00:13:18,748 --> 00:13:20,040
Parity.

194
00:13:20,041 --> 00:13:21,999
Well, this is way bigger than Blake.

195
00:13:22,000 --> 00:13:23,834
You got probable future governor

196
00:13:23,835 --> 00:13:26,253
and current Attorney General Geldof there.

197
00:13:26,254 --> 00:13:28,380
And that guy from Catalast, McCandless,

198
00:13:28,381 --> 00:13:30,466
- he closed the deal.  - What deal?

199
00:13:30,467 --> 00:13:33,427
We got these documents from one of Catalast's holding companies,

200
00:13:33,428 --> 00:13:36,472
transferred ownership of assets, land in that rail corridor.

201
00:13:36,473 --> 00:13:38,766
Now, they sold Caspere's shares in two other companies.

202
00:13:38,767 --> 00:13:42,063
One of them's owned by the mayor's kid, Tony Chessani.

203
00:13:42,064 --> 00:13:44,440
Him? Kid's a twist.

204
00:13:44,482 --> 00:13:47,232
I fixed a hit and run for him once... motherfucker.

205
00:13:47,233 --> 00:13:49,612
Well, the other company's owned by this older cat.

206
00:13:49,613 --> 00:13:51,321
He was at the party.

207
00:13:51,322 --> 00:13:54,658
I saw him at the warehouse where they dropped the girls last week.

208
00:13:54,659 --> 00:13:56,952
Looked European.

209
00:13:56,994 --> 00:14:00,330
Papers said his name was...

210
00:14:00,331 --> 00:14:03,667
Osip Agranov.

211
00:14:05,961 --> 00:14:08,129
He's Russian Israeli.

212
00:14:08,130 --> 00:14:10,633
Blake was listed as the holding company's treasurer.

213
00:14:10,634 --> 00:14:13,802
So to me, it looked like your man helped Tony

214
00:14:13,803 --> 00:14:16,472
and this other guy fuck you out of Caspere's shares.

215
00:14:16,473 --> 00:14:19,891
It could be they killed Caspere for them.

216
00:14:19,892 --> 00:14:23,019
My old chief Holloway, he was there, too.

217
00:14:23,020 --> 00:14:27,232
The girl, Irina Rulfo,

218
00:14:27,233 --> 00:14:30,027
she's had a cop gave her Caspere's stash.

219
00:14:30,028 --> 00:14:32,529
Paid her to pawn it.

220
00:14:32,530 --> 00:14:33,823
She said he was white.

221
00:14:33,824 --> 00:14:35,490
You found Irina?

222
00:14:35,491 --> 00:14:37,493
Sort of.

223
00:14:39,036 --> 00:14:41,330
She's gone.

224
00:14:48,546 --> 00:14:51,214
You got a name for me?

225
00:14:51,215 --> 00:14:53,592
The man who put you on my wife's attacker?

226
00:14:55,261 --> 00:14:58,638
I'll have it for you by the end of the day.

227
00:14:58,639 --> 00:15:00,557
Word of honor.

228
00:15:00,558 --> 00:15:04,144
I guess I'll continue with the belief it wasn't you.

229
00:15:08,232 --> 00:15:10,775
Ray...

230
00:15:10,776 --> 00:15:13,611
go ahead and show yourself out just now.

231
00:15:13,612 --> 00:15:16,239
I need a few minutes alone,

232
00:15:16,240 --> 00:15:18,992
process the ins and outs of all this.

233
00:15:18,993 --> 00:15:21,035
Sure.

234
00:15:21,036 --> 00:15:22,955
I gotta go anyways.

235
00:15:36,218 --> 00:15:37,802
Woodrugh, Velcoro.

236
00:15:37,803 --> 00:15:41,054
The Rulfo girl said a policeman paid her to pawn Caspere's stuff.

237
00:15:41,055 --> 00:15:43,640
Look in LAPD service records, all right.

238
00:15:43,641 --> 00:15:45,436
Find out where Holloway was in '92

239
00:15:45,437 --> 00:15:47,604
and who else was in his squad.

240
00:15:47,605 --> 00:15:49,146
Davis is meeting me this afternoon.

241
00:15:49,147 --> 00:15:51,775
I want her to see those signatures in person.

242
00:15:51,776 --> 00:15:54,402
Your sister put me onto you.

243
00:15:54,403 --> 00:15:56,363
Said you were missing.

244
00:15:59,742 --> 00:16:03,787
And then this was delivered to her.

245
00:16:03,829 --> 00:16:06,457
Contents of a mailbox you kept.

246
00:16:06,498 --> 00:16:08,500
I need you to look at this stuff.

247
00:16:09,501 --> 00:16:11,503
These pictures.

248
00:16:17,926 --> 00:16:20,304
Oh, shit, man.

249
00:16:20,346 --> 00:16:22,348
Forgot I kept that box.

250
00:16:24,516 --> 00:16:26,601
Right.

251
00:16:26,602 --> 00:16:29,396
Yeah, Tascha must have sent these.

252
00:16:29,438 --> 00:16:30,981
Tascha?

253
00:16:31,023 --> 00:16:32,523
You know Ben Caspere?

254
00:16:32,524 --> 00:16:35,277
He had a girl he introduced as Tascha.

255
00:16:37,446 --> 00:16:39,823
Yeah.

256
00:16:39,865 --> 00:16:44,411
I met Ben at the Panticapaem Institute

257
00:16:44,453 --> 00:16:46,497
when I was a maid.

258
00:16:46,538 --> 00:16:47,831
He was the one.

259
00:16:47,873 --> 00:16:51,668
He hooked me up on the circuit.

260
00:16:51,710 --> 00:16:56,090
Tascha... God... was his, like, favorite.

261
00:16:56,131 --> 00:16:58,092
She's Hungarian.

262
00:16:58,133 --> 00:17:01,219
But she had these plans.

263
00:17:01,220 --> 00:17:05,099
Photos of these parties. I warned her.

264
00:17:05,140 --> 00:17:07,935
Fuck, maybe she sent these as backup.

265
00:17:07,976 --> 00:17:11,394
Bitch tried to involve me in that shit.

266
00:17:11,395 --> 00:17:13,065
She tried to blackmail them.

267
00:17:13,066 --> 00:17:15,275
I warned her.

268
00:17:15,317 --> 00:17:16,819
Dudes like this don't play.

269
00:17:16,820 --> 00:17:19,487
All right, what about these diamonds?

270
00:17:19,488 --> 00:17:21,365
They mean anything to you?

271
00:17:21,406 --> 00:17:23,157
Those must be...

272
00:17:23,158 --> 00:17:27,830
Yeah, she had said once that Caspere had shown her these diamonds.

273
00:17:27,871 --> 00:17:30,581
Said they were special like.

274
00:17:30,582 --> 00:17:32,084
What happened to Tascha?

275
00:17:36,338 --> 00:17:40,676
Wherever we were, it was someplace up north.

276
00:17:42,928 --> 00:17:45,263
They found a camera.

277
00:17:45,264 --> 00:17:48,391
So I think there was a cabin

278
00:17:48,392 --> 00:17:50,561
out back.

279
00:17:50,602 --> 00:17:53,814
It was Tony C and their guys.

280
00:17:53,856 --> 00:17:55,691
They took her into the woods.

281
00:17:55,732 --> 00:17:58,569
- Will you testify?  - Fuck, no.

282
00:17:59,736 --> 00:18:01,738
I was hammered anyway.

283
00:18:01,780 --> 00:18:04,531
You know what? Thinking about it, I don't know what I've seen.

284
00:18:04,532 --> 00:18:06,368
Is that when you tried to get out?

285
00:18:06,369 --> 00:18:09,538
I never tried to get out.

286
00:18:10,789 --> 00:18:12,206
Girl fucked up.

287
00:18:12,207 --> 00:18:14,543
All you gotta do is follow the rules.

288
00:18:14,585 --> 00:18:16,336
I didn't want to get out.

289
00:18:16,378 --> 00:18:18,045
You feel me?

290
00:18:18,046 --> 00:18:20,632
I was never missing.

291
00:18:21,758 --> 00:18:23,218
You didn't look like you wanted to be

292
00:18:23,219 --> 00:18:25,470
where you were when I found you.

293
00:18:25,512 --> 00:18:28,765
I took too much Molly on top of champagne.

294
00:18:28,807 --> 00:18:35,105
So what? It happens.

295
00:18:35,147 --> 00:18:37,149
All right, so...

296
00:18:39,401 --> 00:18:40,985
who's the other girl?

297
00:18:40,986 --> 00:18:42,778
Her name is Laura, maybe.

298
00:18:42,779 --> 00:18:45,238
I ain't seen her in like five, six months.

299
00:18:45,239 --> 00:18:47,200
Maybe they took her out to the cabin?

300
00:18:47,201 --> 00:18:50,745
No, she wasn't dumb like Tascha.

301
00:18:50,746 --> 00:18:53,165
Look, can I just get a ride?

302
00:18:53,206 --> 00:18:55,082
Or call somebody?

303
00:18:55,083 --> 00:18:56,918
Your sister's on her way.

304
00:18:56,960 --> 00:18:59,962
What the fuck?

305
00:18:59,963 --> 00:19:01,880
You don't think my sister's fucked up?

306
00:19:01,881 --> 00:19:05,550
The way she waits hand and foot on that panty-sniffing motherfucker?

307
00:19:05,551 --> 00:19:07,137
Better than being strung out.

308
00:19:07,138 --> 00:19:10,098
Yo, I have a place.

309
00:19:10,140 --> 00:19:12,059
I got nice things.

310
00:19:12,100 --> 00:19:15,770
I had a good thing with Tony and his people.

311
00:19:15,771 --> 00:19:17,979
Maybe... and this is just a thought,

312
00:19:17,980 --> 00:19:21,276
maybe you were put on Earth for more than fucking.

313
00:19:23,362 --> 00:19:25,906
Everything is fucking.

314
00:19:46,051 --> 00:19:48,470
Oh, thank God.

315
00:19:50,305 --> 00:19:53,140
No, stop. I am not going with you.

316
00:19:53,141 --> 00:19:55,016
Fuck your pervertido husband.

317
00:19:55,017 --> 00:19:58,144
- He's different now.  - You need to lay low, Vera.

318
00:19:58,145 --> 00:20:01,481
Stay with your sister. I'll let you know when it's safe.

319
00:20:01,482 --> 00:20:03,068
Till then, you're in danger.

320
00:20:03,110 --> 00:20:06,279
You fucking putas. You put me in danger.

321
00:20:06,321 --> 00:20:08,822
And I'm the only one who can get you out.

322
00:20:08,823 --> 00:20:12,242
You reach out to those men, I'll let them know you talked to a cop

323
00:20:12,243 --> 00:20:14,329
and they'll paint a cabin with you.

324
00:20:25,059 --> 00:20:27,303


325
00:20:27,759 --> 00:20:30,303
You motherfuckers.

326
00:20:42,402 --> 00:20:45,279


327
00:20:45,402 --> 00:20:47,279
Holy fuck.

328
00:20:51,869 --> 00:20:53,037


329
00:20:53,869 --> 00:20:55,537
Shit.

330
00:21:04,880 --> 00:21:06,840
Late today.

331
00:21:06,882 --> 00:21:08,466
Had to get Ivar covering the pit.

332
00:21:08,508 --> 00:21:12,345
Sorry, boss. I was taking care of some stuff.

333
00:21:12,387 --> 00:21:15,891
The girls had a little private thing last night.

334
00:21:17,142 --> 00:21:19,269
15 Gs.

335
00:21:19,311 --> 00:21:21,395
- Yours.  - Holy cow.

336
00:21:21,396 --> 00:21:24,815
You must be what they call a natural-born pimp.

337
00:21:24,816 --> 00:21:29,112
Me, I always saw a difference between a whore and a pimp.

338
00:21:29,154 --> 00:21:32,991
A whore can still have integrity.

339
00:21:34,075 --> 00:21:36,494
You want to move me up, let me know.

340
00:21:36,495 --> 00:21:38,830
That's the thing, right?

341
00:21:40,040 --> 00:21:41,917
There's nothing to move you up to.

342
00:21:41,958 --> 00:21:45,085
Is there?

343
00:21:45,086 --> 00:21:49,925
I mean, all my shit's been taken down to the street.

344
00:21:52,677 --> 00:21:54,596
You'll get it back, boss.

345
00:21:54,638 --> 00:21:57,432
Everybody knows you will.

346
00:21:58,600 --> 00:22:01,185
Stan was following you.

347
00:22:01,186 --> 00:22:03,271
And he wasn't the subtlest guy in the world,

348
00:22:03,272 --> 00:22:06,441
so I'm guessing that you spotted the tail.

349
00:22:06,483 --> 00:22:09,319
Hey, look, boss, I don't know...

350
00:22:09,361 --> 00:22:11,779
What did he see you doing

351
00:22:11,780 --> 00:22:14,991
caused you to punch his ticket like that?

352
00:22:15,033 --> 00:22:19,286
You took his eyes. Why?

353
00:22:19,287 --> 00:22:21,331
To make it look connected to Caspere?

354
00:22:23,541 --> 00:22:26,086
Truth is your only play right now,

355
00:22:26,127 --> 00:22:28,629
because you fucked up

356
00:22:28,630 --> 00:22:31,298
letting yourself be alone

357
00:22:31,299 --> 00:22:33,967
in this room with me.

358
00:22:33,968 --> 00:22:37,764
Look, Frank, there's been a mistake somewhere.

359
00:22:37,806 --> 00:22:39,849
You're arrogant.

360
00:22:39,891 --> 00:22:42,143
Or else you never would have walked in here.

361
00:23:18,430 --> 00:23:21,015
Have I got a fucking story for you.

362
00:23:23,268 --> 00:23:25,270
Hell.

363
00:23:46,291 --> 00:23:49,209
Please...

364
00:23:49,210 --> 00:23:51,671
Please. Frank, please.

365
00:23:51,713 --> 00:23:53,881
- I can...  - You can what?

366
00:23:53,882 --> 00:23:56,843
Talk? Osip?

367
00:23:56,885 --> 00:23:58,511
His crew?

368
00:23:58,553 --> 00:24:01,305
Caspere? Stan?

369
00:24:01,306 --> 00:24:04,348
Osip's people, they've been running Eastern Bloc girls

370
00:24:04,349 --> 00:24:07,351
through Southern California for over a year, Frank.

371
00:24:07,352 --> 00:24:09,395
Osip's been moving to take your spot

372
00:24:09,396 --> 00:24:11,316
ever since your meeting in Paris.

373
00:24:11,317 --> 00:24:14,360
With your help, huh?

374
00:24:14,402 --> 00:24:15,945
They reached out.

375
00:24:15,987 --> 00:24:19,238
All these moves you were making, you'd have done the same.

376
00:24:19,239 --> 00:24:21,991
You think they give a shit about handshakes?

377
00:24:21,992 --> 00:24:24,746
You never should have brought this to Osip.

378
00:24:29,084 --> 00:24:32,420
Fuck.

379
00:24:37,842 --> 00:24:40,470
You kill Caspere? Or did Osip?

380
00:24:40,511 --> 00:24:43,387
No, no. Nobody knows who that was, man. Nobody.

381
00:24:43,388 --> 00:24:44,889
So where's the money I gave him?

382
00:24:44,890 --> 00:24:47,558
Caspere was always gonna fuck you, Frank.

383
00:24:47,559 --> 00:24:49,187
Osip was backing the play.

384
00:24:49,188 --> 00:24:51,271
Osip and Tony Chessani,

385
00:24:51,272 --> 00:24:54,608
they're absorbing Caspere's action?

386
00:24:54,609 --> 00:24:57,985
- Why'd you kill Stan?  - He saw me meeting Osip and his guy.

387
00:24:57,986 --> 00:25:00,949
He wanted a payoff, Frank. He tried blackmailing me.

388
00:25:00,950 --> 00:25:04,243
- Bullshit.  - What the fuck? It's bullshit.

389
00:25:04,285 --> 00:25:06,452
You got all these big plans, land deals.

390
00:25:06,453 --> 00:25:08,873
Where was that supposed to leave us?

391
00:25:08,874 --> 00:25:12,502
You taught me, "Make your own opportunities."

392
00:25:12,543 --> 00:25:16,463
That guy way back, Velcoro's wife,

393
00:25:16,464 --> 00:25:18,299
who was that guy you gave up?

394
00:25:18,300 --> 00:25:20,801
What? Velcoro? Frank, what...

395
00:25:20,802 --> 00:25:24,847
He didn't hurt Ray's wife. Who was he?

396
00:25:24,889 --> 00:25:27,100
This fucking meth head.

397
00:25:27,141 --> 00:25:30,852
He said I ripped him off. He was gonna come after me.

398
00:25:30,853 --> 00:25:33,147
I heard about this deputy's wife.

399
00:25:33,148 --> 00:25:35,649
I saw a chance to step up for you,

400
00:25:35,650 --> 00:25:37,901
get noticed.

401
00:25:37,902 --> 00:25:40,070
Look me in the eyes.

402
00:25:40,071 --> 00:25:41,906
I want to watch your lights go out.

403
00:25:46,744 --> 00:25:50,498
I can get money back. I know where there's money.

404
00:25:57,422 --> 00:25:59,756
Osip and Catalast,

405
00:25:59,757 --> 00:26:02,009
there's a big cash exchange tomorrow night up in Ojai.

406
00:26:02,010 --> 00:26:04,678
McCandless's place. Crystal Ranch.

407
00:26:04,679 --> 00:26:08,433
Osip's turning over 12 million for Caspere's shares.

408
00:26:08,474 --> 00:26:10,016
12 million, Frank.

409
00:26:10,017 --> 00:26:11,561
Who's gonna be there?

410
00:26:11,602 --> 00:26:13,353
I don't know for sure.

411
00:26:13,354 --> 00:26:16,983
It's a handoff. Security.

412
00:26:17,024 --> 00:26:19,527
Osip, he'll be there.

413
00:26:22,363 --> 00:26:25,700
All right. Get yourself together.

414
00:26:29,620 --> 00:26:32,038
Anything else you can tell me?

415
00:26:32,039 --> 00:26:33,624
Anything?

416
00:26:35,209 --> 00:26:37,044
Might help.

417
00:26:46,971 --> 00:26:49,723
They're taking it all, Frank.

418
00:26:49,724 --> 00:26:52,893
Osip's people bought the liens on the clubs.

419
00:26:52,894 --> 00:26:54,477
My people won't go along with that.

420
00:26:54,478 --> 00:26:56,647
You don't have any people, Frank, that's what I'm saying.

421
00:26:56,689 --> 00:26:59,525
Nails, they never approached him.

422
00:26:59,567 --> 00:27:01,569
But anybody else, they already bought.

423
00:27:01,570 --> 00:27:04,447
Ivar.

424
00:27:04,488 --> 00:27:06,157
Anything else?

425
00:27:07,241 --> 00:27:08,784
Look,

426
00:27:08,826 --> 00:27:11,954
they don't know you got me now.

427
00:27:11,996 --> 00:27:15,916
I can work on the inside for you, man.

428
00:27:15,917 --> 00:27:17,584
Triple-cross.

429
00:27:17,585 --> 00:27:19,462
Do this for me instead.

430
00:27:19,503 --> 00:27:22,256
I can...

431
00:27:25,509 --> 00:27:27,261
Remember where I found you?

432
00:27:27,262 --> 00:27:29,805
Pushing Baby Aspirin to club kids.

433
00:27:31,098 --> 00:27:32,850
Johnny Mank wanted to cap you in the alley.

434
00:27:32,892 --> 00:27:36,479
I said, "Nah, there's potential here."

435
00:27:38,856 --> 00:27:41,692
Now you just shit my carpet.

436
00:28:17,478 --> 00:28:20,356
Can't remember anything? Something I can use?

437
00:28:22,608 --> 00:28:24,527
Well, I grouped them as hedonists.

438
00:28:24,528 --> 00:28:28,321
And they seemed very close in a secretive way.

439
00:28:28,322 --> 00:28:32,618
And they did not stay long. We had no real relationship.

440
00:28:32,827 --> 00:28:35,078
You seem pretty friendly here.

441
00:28:35,079 --> 00:28:38,415
Well, at the time everyone was a pilgrim.

442
00:28:38,416 --> 00:28:42,084
You understand? Everyone was passing in their separate journeys.

443
00:28:42,085 --> 00:28:44,255
And not all looking for the same thing.

444
00:28:44,256 --> 00:28:47,048
Some exploit openness and freedom.

445
00:28:47,049 --> 00:28:50,176
It was a shadow of our best intentions.

446
00:28:50,177 --> 00:28:53,179
But people came and went, faces lost.

447
00:28:53,180 --> 00:28:55,641
I regret so much of that time.

448
00:29:05,025 --> 00:29:09,530
I remembered his face finally.

449
00:29:12,408 --> 00:29:14,910
The man who took me away.

450
00:29:16,537 --> 00:29:19,123
You always said you couldn't remember anything.

451
00:29:21,208 --> 00:29:23,377
People came and went.

452
00:29:25,880 --> 00:29:28,048
But there was a man...

453
00:29:29,383 --> 00:29:31,343
and I remember his face.

454
00:29:34,221 --> 00:29:38,683
And I think I always remembered it.

455
00:29:38,684 --> 00:29:41,186
We couldn't sleep.

456
00:29:41,187 --> 00:29:43,647
I wandered the forest for four days.

457
00:29:43,648 --> 00:29:46,149
Can't see it, those four days,

458
00:29:46,150 --> 00:29:50,528
but I remembered his face.

459
00:29:50,529 --> 00:29:52,907
I wish I could... if I could just give you back...

460
00:29:54,158 --> 00:29:56,785
my father... you see, my father, he was...

461
00:29:58,078 --> 00:29:59,872
He was a harsh man. He was strict.

462
00:29:59,873 --> 00:30:02,041
I wasn't going to be like him.

463
00:30:03,709 --> 00:30:06,419
Oh, god.

464
00:30:06,420 --> 00:30:08,880
God damn everything.

465
00:30:08,881 --> 00:30:11,342
That's what I say.

466
00:30:18,432 --> 00:30:20,184
Are you gonna turn yourself in?

467
00:30:20,185 --> 00:30:22,852
No.

468
00:30:22,853 --> 00:30:24,938
I can't.

469
00:30:24,939 --> 00:30:27,024
But I can fix it.

470
00:30:28,609 --> 00:30:30,945
I wish your life had been easier.

471
00:30:35,783 --> 00:30:39,036
You didn't ask me if I did it.

472
00:30:39,078 --> 00:30:40,536
It doesn't matter.

473
00:30:40,537 --> 00:30:43,207
You're the most innocent person I've ever known.

474
00:31:04,428 --> 00:31:06,763
Thank you. I won't forget this.

475
00:31:06,764 --> 00:31:10,016
The APB on you, they're watching your house.

476
00:31:10,017 --> 00:31:12,269
I should have trusted you with more of this.

477
00:31:12,270 --> 00:31:14,771
I think with that harassment,

478
00:31:14,772 --> 00:31:16,607
I could have stepped up more.

479
00:31:16,649 --> 00:31:18,442
- Helped you out. - It's all right.

480
00:31:18,443 --> 00:31:20,443
I was jealous.

481
00:31:20,444 --> 00:31:22,112
I'll say it.

482
00:31:22,113 --> 00:31:24,115
I should have stopped thinking of you that way

483
00:31:24,116 --> 00:31:25,615
or switched partners.

484
00:31:25,616 --> 00:31:28,619
No, I fucked up there.

485
00:31:28,661 --> 00:31:30,787
You didn't.

486
00:31:30,788 --> 00:31:33,624
I think I...

487
00:31:33,666 --> 00:31:36,961
I think I might be unfair to people sometimes.

488
00:31:41,716 --> 00:31:43,717
Stay safe.

489
00:31:43,718 --> 00:31:45,886
And stay alive.

490
00:31:51,892 --> 00:31:55,437
Please be careful. Please get out of this.

491
00:31:55,438 --> 00:31:57,064
I will.

492
00:32:07,992 --> 00:32:09,742
Follow them to Eugene.

493
00:32:09,743 --> 00:32:12,995
They're gonna exit. Better if you don't know where.

494
00:32:12,996 --> 00:32:16,248
- And watch for tails more than anything. - Copy that.

495
00:32:16,249 --> 00:32:19,962
Had to toss my phone, so I'll call you on a burner, check in.

496
00:32:19,963 --> 00:32:21,754
Thank you for this.

497
00:32:21,755 --> 00:32:23,591
Again.

498
00:32:23,632 --> 00:32:25,176
Fuck you, Bezzerides.

499
00:32:40,733 --> 00:32:43,151
Got three in one day.

500
00:32:43,152 --> 00:32:45,069
Bet that's a record.

501
00:33:06,342 --> 00:33:08,176
Delegate nothing.

502
00:33:08,177 --> 00:33:10,261
It's worse than we thought.

503
00:33:10,262 --> 00:33:13,724
We've been in a secret war here the last six months or so.

504
00:33:13,725 --> 00:33:15,391
Everybody's bought.

505
00:33:15,392 --> 00:33:17,268
Ivar?

506
00:33:17,269 --> 00:33:19,103
Don't tip, either.

507
00:33:19,104 --> 00:33:22,440
Better they think we're in the dark.

508
00:33:22,441 --> 00:33:24,943
Jordan just walked in.

509
00:33:24,944 --> 00:33:27,028
I'll catch her.

510
00:33:27,029 --> 00:33:28,613
No.

511
00:33:28,614 --> 00:33:31,242
Bring her inside.

512
00:33:44,588 --> 00:33:47,382
Here we are.

513
00:33:47,383 --> 00:33:49,760
Under the bright lights.

514
00:33:52,846 --> 00:33:57,017
They're taking everything, even what we got left.

515
00:33:59,561 --> 00:34:01,647
They'll come for me.

516
00:34:05,567 --> 00:34:07,945
What can I do?

517
00:34:17,621 --> 00:34:20,498
Pack a bag. Neils is going with you.

518
00:34:20,499 --> 00:34:22,376
You can't stay at home any more.

519
00:34:22,377 --> 00:34:23,751
All right.

520
00:34:23,752 --> 00:34:26,921
I'll meet you tomorrow.

521
00:34:26,922 --> 00:34:28,506
I love you.

522
00:34:28,507 --> 00:34:31,010
I love you.

523
00:34:45,023 --> 00:34:49,445


524
00:34:45,023 --> 00:34:49,445
This is GIA graded with a dossier.

525
00:34:49,486 --> 00:34:51,696
It tests excellent in optical

526
00:34:51,697 --> 00:34:53,615
and symmetry analysis.

527
00:34:53,657 --> 00:34:56,869
Five carats, $700,000.

528
00:34:56,910 --> 00:34:59,371
It'll be between five and six million.

529
00:34:59,413 --> 00:35:01,790
I'd rather split the total among more stones.

530
00:35:01,832 --> 00:35:04,124
They don't all need to be that high-end.

531
00:35:04,125 --> 00:35:06,628
But I'll need the exchange to happen fast.

532
00:35:06,629 --> 00:35:08,921
Then it is not about the stones.

533
00:35:08,922 --> 00:35:11,966
It is about the money behind the stones.

534
00:35:11,967 --> 00:35:15,471
You are changing money you are not supposed to have.

535
00:35:15,472 --> 00:35:18,723
We do not engage in such practices.

536
00:35:18,724 --> 00:35:21,643
The money will be untraceable in itself.

537
00:35:21,685 --> 00:35:24,897
Abner Ehrman told me I could work with you.

538
00:35:24,938 --> 00:35:28,566
Please, articulate the percentage

539
00:35:28,567 --> 00:35:31,570
you'd require in order to transact with me.

540
00:35:32,738 --> 00:35:34,155
40%.

541
00:35:34,156 --> 00:35:36,407
And all exchanges happen here.

542
00:35:36,408 --> 00:35:39,826
As we have not done business, like today, you will come alone.

543
00:35:39,827 --> 00:35:41,997
It includes my guarantee of quality

544
00:35:41,998 --> 00:35:45,125
and a secure exchange.

545
00:35:56,470 --> 00:35:58,512
Have your friends ever been to Venezuela?

546
00:35:58,513 --> 00:36:00,597
No, they've talked about going.

547
00:36:00,598 --> 00:36:02,809
I wanted to treat them. Engagement present.

548
00:36:02,810 --> 00:36:05,561


549
00:36:02,810 --> 00:36:05,561
Barquisimeto is beautiful.

550
00:36:05,562 --> 00:36:08,438
I've got them both booked out of Portland in five days.

551
00:36:08,439 --> 00:36:10,857
And the tickets are alterable? We can change them up if we need to?

552
00:36:10,858 --> 00:36:13,862
Yes, sir. For that price, they let you do what you want.

553
00:36:13,863 --> 00:36:15,821
Ours are the best.

554
00:36:15,822 --> 00:36:19,116
Digital everything, including the chip.

555
00:36:19,117 --> 00:36:22,703
But you still owe us for the consignment, Frank.

556
00:36:22,704 --> 00:36:24,372
300.

557
00:36:24,373 --> 00:36:26,041
Which I'll pay the day after tomorrow.

558
00:36:26,042 --> 00:36:29,044
- With an extra five on top. - With what?

559
00:36:32,422 --> 00:36:34,632
You know about the Russians?

560
00:36:34,633 --> 00:36:37,760
They're dropping roots... women, drugs.

561
00:36:37,761 --> 00:36:40,931
Taking a chunk of development along the rail corridor.

562
00:36:42,891 --> 00:36:45,185
You'll be taken over inside a year.

563
00:36:48,230 --> 00:36:50,022
Give me what I need,

564
00:36:50,023 --> 00:36:52,234
I'll help them choke on their piece of pie.

565
00:36:52,235 --> 00:36:54,360
That's 100 now,

566
00:36:54,361 --> 00:36:57,239
seven, day after tomorrow.

567
00:36:58,198 --> 00:37:00,866
And this buys what?

568
00:37:00,867 --> 00:37:03,536
I need two clean cars that are fast

569
00:37:03,537 --> 00:37:06,163
and some firepower.

570
00:37:06,164 --> 00:37:08,415
Why trust we'd ever see you again?

571
00:37:08,416 --> 00:37:10,752
Because I need that clean passport.

572
00:37:10,753 --> 00:37:12,837
Then I'm moving on.

573
00:37:12,838 --> 00:37:14,880
I get where I'm going,

574
00:37:14,881 --> 00:37:17,133
I got another half mil for you.

575
00:37:17,134 --> 00:37:20,011
What are you planning, Frank?

576
00:37:20,012 --> 00:37:24,306
You might say my ship's come in.

577
00:37:24,307 --> 00:37:26,143
And who sails this ship?

578
00:37:34,775 --> 00:37:36,943
You got an APB on Davis's murder?

579
00:37:36,944 --> 00:37:39,656
Davis was supposed to meet me and get the whole story.

580
00:37:39,657 --> 00:37:41,323
Found her there dead.

581
00:37:41,324 --> 00:37:43,618
They probably did it with one of the pieces I keep at home.

582
00:37:45,120 --> 00:37:47,789
I switched license plates at a fucking mall.

583
00:37:47,790 --> 00:37:51,125
That's it, then. She was our only authority.

584
00:37:51,126 --> 00:37:53,503
You and her are fugitives.

585
00:37:56,798 --> 00:37:59,843
Well, it doesn't make sense.

586
00:38:01,762 --> 00:38:04,180
It was cops.

587
00:38:04,181 --> 00:38:06,515
Back in the '92 robbery,

588
00:38:06,516 --> 00:38:08,641
Burris and Dixon were serving under Holloway.

589
00:38:08,642 --> 00:38:10,812
Caspere worked at the same station.

590
00:38:10,813 --> 00:38:13,189
Jewelry store was their district.

591
00:38:13,190 --> 00:38:15,484
Caspere probably helped them move the stones.

592
00:38:15,485 --> 00:38:17,902
They were all working together.

593
00:38:17,903 --> 00:38:19,862
Orphaned two kids.

594
00:38:19,863 --> 00:38:21,531
Leonard and Laura.

595
00:38:23,116 --> 00:38:24,910
So that's how they bought in.

596
00:38:24,911 --> 00:38:28,162
The diamonds and whatever they got for them

597
00:38:28,163 --> 00:38:30,372
went to Chessani.

598
00:38:30,373 --> 00:38:32,584
Next couple of years, they migrate

599
00:38:32,585 --> 00:38:35,294
into six-figure salaries in Vinci.

600
00:38:35,295 --> 00:38:37,047
Their own private fiefdom.

601
00:38:37,048 --> 00:38:38,839
Except Dixon.

602
00:38:38,840 --> 00:38:40,716
He was just a regular dick.

603
00:38:40,717 --> 00:38:44,513
Dixon was checking in on those diamonds before we ever found them.

604
00:38:46,139 --> 00:38:48,683
Maybe he knew Caspere held onto them.

605
00:38:50,018 --> 00:38:52,143
Maybe it meant leverage for him.

606
00:38:52,144 --> 00:38:53,811
But Dixon taking that headshot,

607
00:38:53,812 --> 00:38:55,730
I checked every arrest record.

608
00:38:55,731 --> 00:38:57,649
Burris busted Ledo Amarilla in '06.

609
00:38:57,650 --> 00:39:00,693
Released after interrogation, no notes kept.

610
00:39:00,694 --> 00:39:02,072
That whole day was a setup.

611
00:39:02,073 --> 00:39:04,156
Amarilla, too.

612
00:39:04,157 --> 00:39:06,574
He thought it was gonna go a different way, I think.

613
00:39:06,575 --> 00:39:09,536
That's what Caspere's place was tossed for.

614
00:39:09,537 --> 00:39:11,246
Burris, Holloway, Dixon, whoever,

615
00:39:11,247 --> 00:39:12,956
they were looking for those diamonds.

616
00:39:12,957 --> 00:39:16,543
The last piece of evidence for a 23-year-old double murder.

617
00:39:16,544 --> 00:39:18,547
Tascha was gonna blackmail Caspere.

618
00:39:18,548 --> 00:39:22,633
So Holloway, Burris, they killed Caspere.

619
00:39:22,634 --> 00:39:24,718
That doesn't make sense.

620
00:39:24,719 --> 00:39:28,471
Him dying bought them all exposure, kicked this whole thing off.

621
00:39:28,472 --> 00:39:31,935
And if they had Caspere, why wouldn't they torture him for the fucking diamonds?

622
00:39:31,936 --> 00:39:34,728
I mean, it's...

623
00:39:40,936 --> 00:39:43,328


624
00:39:50,662 --> 00:39:52,663
I gotta head home soon.

625
00:39:52,664 --> 00:39:54,039
All right.

626
00:39:54,040 --> 00:39:56,083
Could you take this to State?

627
00:39:56,084 --> 00:39:58,294
State? Davis is dead.

628
00:39:58,295 --> 00:40:01,673
Geldof was at the party. How about Ventura Sheriff's?

629
00:40:01,674 --> 00:40:03,590
Oh.

630
00:40:03,591 --> 00:40:05,176
They're looking to do me.

631
00:40:06,678 --> 00:40:11,098
And what have we got? Some documents for a holding company?

632
00:40:11,099 --> 00:40:13,934
A theory on some rogue cops from '92?

633
00:40:13,935 --> 00:40:16,687
- Feds?  - Not without more.

634
00:40:16,688 --> 00:40:18,229
Unless one of you guys got a friend there,

635
00:40:18,230 --> 00:40:19,691
I don't see protection.

636
00:40:24,988 --> 00:40:27,906
That ain't a fucking mayor.

637
00:40:27,907 --> 00:40:32,745
That's a homunculus state corporations slid into office.

638
00:40:32,746 --> 00:40:35,080
Who the fuck even is Los Angeles?

639
00:40:35,081 --> 00:40:37,916
Nobody can say. See? Nobody knows.

640
00:40:37,917 --> 00:40:40,586
Nobody expects shit to actually work.

641
00:40:40,587 --> 00:40:43,047
Me, my family, we are Vinci.

642
00:40:43,048 --> 00:40:45,717
We're a goddamn political dynasty.

643
00:40:47,385 --> 00:40:49,137
Like the Kennedys.

644
00:40:50,430 --> 00:40:53,516
Do me a favor, hum my balls a little, huh?

645
00:40:58,313 --> 00:41:00,189
Maybe later.

646
00:41:00,190 --> 00:41:01,941
Frank.

647
00:41:04,903 --> 00:41:06,779
Another gin.

648
00:41:06,780 --> 00:41:08,906
Time to hit the road, Austin.

649
00:41:10,617 --> 00:41:12,325
You don't tell me what time it is.

650
00:41:12,326 --> 00:41:15,453
I'm just thinking you might want to get home and take care of business.

651
00:41:15,454 --> 00:41:17,205
What the fuck's that mean?

652
00:41:17,206 --> 00:41:20,583
Your boy Prince Tony has been greasing the skids to slide into your chair.

653
00:41:20,584 --> 00:41:23,127
Buying the attorney general with his hookers.

654
00:41:23,128 --> 00:41:25,379
Working with a Russian named Osip Agranov,

655
00:41:25,380 --> 00:41:27,381
Jacob McCandless from Catalast.

656
00:41:27,382 --> 00:41:29,928
All this in your house behind your back.

657
00:41:31,471 --> 00:41:33,765
Sober up. You might realize you're getting fucked.

658
00:41:33,766 --> 00:41:37,227
Now get out of here. Closing time all around.

659
00:41:50,490 --> 00:41:52,992
I'd have known, I'd have gotten the red carpet out.

660
00:41:52,993 --> 00:41:54,953
Let me make you a drink.

661
00:42:11,094 --> 00:42:14,763
Our company bought the lien here, Frank.

662
00:42:14,764 --> 00:42:17,099
Same thing at the Lux.

663
00:42:17,100 --> 00:42:18,600
The clubs are ours.

664
00:42:18,601 --> 00:42:20,394
The clubs?

665
00:42:20,395 --> 00:42:23,940
Shit, man, I'm working just to stay in the black, here.

666
00:42:23,941 --> 00:42:26,733
We think we can do better.

667
00:42:26,734 --> 00:42:30,029
Bringing in our own girls, move our own products,

668
00:42:30,030 --> 00:42:31,905
wash our own money.

669
00:42:31,906 --> 00:42:34,909
We're going to be doing a lot of business in California now.

670
00:42:38,997 --> 00:42:40,998
Good for you.

671
00:42:40,999 --> 00:42:44,793
I tell you, hindsight,

672
00:42:44,794 --> 00:42:47,211
I was out of my element with that land stuff.

673
00:42:47,212 --> 00:42:48,673
Stick to what you know, right?

674
00:42:48,674 --> 00:42:52,760
I must say, you're taking this better than expected.

675
00:42:54,220 --> 00:42:57,055
Is Mr. Churchman around? Blake?

676
00:42:57,056 --> 00:43:00,727
Shit, no. Guy's been around less the last three months

677
00:43:00,728 --> 00:43:02,728
than my wife's period.

678
00:43:02,729 --> 00:43:06,315
You know, Frank, my board,

679
00:43:06,316 --> 00:43:09,401
they thought we should take you out.

680
00:43:09,402 --> 00:43:13,822
I said, "Frank Semyon understands business.

681
00:43:13,823 --> 00:43:15,073
He'll adjust."

682
00:43:15,074 --> 00:43:18,244
So what are my prospects? Straight up.

683
00:43:19,829 --> 00:43:23,082
You can manage the day-to-day of the casino and the club.

684
00:43:23,083 --> 00:43:25,125
We put you on salary.

685
00:43:25,126 --> 00:43:27,503
I said, "Frank knows clubs."

686
00:43:30,256 --> 00:43:32,592
I had ideas of getting out of this, you know.

687
00:43:32,593 --> 00:43:35,802
There's no such thing for you, Frank.

688
00:43:35,803 --> 00:43:39,181
That world isn't yours. You manage clubs.

689
00:43:39,182 --> 00:43:42,101
In time, we find something new to build on.

690
00:43:44,103 --> 00:43:46,271
Well, what can I say to that?

691
00:43:46,272 --> 00:43:49,775
After all, no fighting what you can't change.

692
00:43:49,776 --> 00:43:54,488
Look, I ain't lasted this long without some knowledge

693
00:43:54,489 --> 00:43:56,281
of my own limitations.

694
00:43:56,282 --> 00:44:00,035
And it is my hope that we can fucking build on this.

695
00:44:00,036 --> 00:44:02,621
Going into the future.

696
00:44:15,218 --> 00:44:19,179
- Velcoro.  -  What's up, man?

697
00:44:19,180 --> 00:44:20,807
I wanted to call.

698
00:44:22,475 --> 00:44:24,726
I think...

699
00:44:24,727 --> 00:44:28,397
I ain't told anybody about this other...

700
00:44:30,024 --> 00:44:31,358
thing.

701
00:44:31,359 --> 00:44:34,653
But somebody sent me these pictures.

702
00:44:34,654 --> 00:44:36,196
Pictures of me.

703
00:44:36,197 --> 00:44:37,906
What, of our thing?

704
00:44:37,907 --> 00:44:40,868
No, it's something else. This is mine.

705
00:44:43,329 --> 00:44:45,623
I think I might be walking into something.

706
00:44:46,958 --> 00:44:48,835
Then don't.

707
00:44:50,837 --> 00:44:54,590
- I'll call you back.  -  Listen, hold on. Wait...

708
00:45:07,019 --> 00:45:09,020
What the fuck is this?

709
00:45:09,021 --> 00:45:12,107
Orders. I gotta take your gun.

710
00:45:12,108 --> 00:45:14,610
Don't make a thing of it. You've got eyes all over you.

711
00:45:22,285 --> 00:45:24,704
Come on, I can get you through this.

712
00:45:27,415 --> 00:45:29,124
Black Mountain?

713
00:45:29,125 --> 00:45:31,251
Not anymore.

714
00:45:31,252 --> 00:45:32,918
Ares Security. We rebranded.

715
00:45:32,919 --> 00:45:35,881
We just service one client now... Catalast Group.

716
00:45:40,845 --> 00:45:43,180
When you got in touch, what was that?

717
00:45:43,181 --> 00:45:45,807
I had orders to check on you.

718
00:45:45,808 --> 00:45:48,560
After all that press stuff,

719
00:45:48,561 --> 00:45:50,896
make sure you kept confidentiality.

720
00:45:52,231 --> 00:45:55,818
This is your situation. I didn't make it.

721
00:45:57,987 --> 00:45:59,779
Let's go.

722
00:45:59,780 --> 00:46:01,782
They just want to talk.

723
00:46:17,340 --> 00:46:19,758
That was Woodrugh.

724
00:46:19,759 --> 00:46:21,885
Something's up with him.

725
00:46:21,886 --> 00:46:24,471
- What?  - I don't know.

726
00:46:24,472 --> 00:46:26,264
He said he'd call me back.

727
00:46:26,265 --> 00:46:29,934
We need an exit strategy. Get out of the country.

728
00:46:29,935 --> 00:46:32,855
There's no way they'll let us go to trial.

729
00:46:34,690 --> 00:46:35,899
You hear me?

730
00:46:35,900 --> 00:46:38,277
Vera said this girl's name was Laura.

731
00:46:38,278 --> 00:46:41,613
Does she look... she look familiar?

732
00:46:41,614 --> 00:46:44,115
I swear, there's something...

733
00:46:44,116 --> 00:46:47,036
No. Her name is Erica.

734
00:46:48,204 --> 00:46:51,623
From the city manager's office.

735
00:46:51,624 --> 00:46:53,750
She was Caspere's secretary.

736
00:46:53,751 --> 00:46:55,709
- You met her on the movie set.  - Yeah.

737
00:46:55,710 --> 00:46:58,754
Woodrugh said one of the orphans in that robbery,

738
00:46:58,755 --> 00:47:00,633
- her name was Laura.  - Laura.

739
00:47:04,220 --> 00:47:05,845
- Ooh.  - You got it?

740
00:47:05,846 --> 00:47:07,972
Yeah, it's here.

741
00:47:07,973 --> 00:47:10,226
Let me see.

742
00:47:12,478 --> 00:47:14,063
I don't know. What do you think?

743
00:47:36,252 --> 00:47:39,296
You've been looking for information about me, son.

744
00:47:39,297 --> 00:47:42,007
Well, here's your chance to ask.

745
00:47:47,221 --> 00:47:49,974
All right, Mr. Patterson. Thank you.

746
00:47:50,307 --> 00:47:53,936
No, this was very helpful.

747
00:47:55,646 --> 00:47:58,107
Moved out of her apartment six weeks ago.

748
00:47:58,149 --> 00:48:00,234
Quit the city manager's office around that time.

749
00:48:00,317 --> 00:48:03,152
Woodrugh could do a trace on her. Credit cards, whatever.

750
00:48:03,153 --> 00:48:04,655
Figure out where she went.

751
00:48:04,656 --> 00:48:08,117
Let's try him again. Voicemail.

752
00:48:12,454 --> 00:48:14,080
What now?

753
00:48:14,081 --> 00:48:17,042
Ride it out till morning.

754
00:48:19,128 --> 00:48:21,922
Guess we'll wait for Woodrugh.

755
00:48:33,434 --> 00:48:35,976
We got a gas leak spilling into the AC.

756
00:48:35,977 --> 00:48:38,228
Need to clear the place for three hours or so.

757
00:48:38,229 --> 00:48:40,858
- Are you serious?  - Just fucking do it.

758
00:48:40,859 --> 00:48:42,568
Everybody out.

759
00:48:47,823 --> 00:48:51,283
Ladies and gentlemen, due to a sudden safety issue,

760
00:48:51,284 --> 00:48:54,330
we need to request that you cash out your chips

761
00:48:54,331 --> 00:48:56,457
and vacate the premises.

762
00:48:59,209 --> 00:49:02,378
These tunnels exist under the entire city.

763
00:49:02,379 --> 00:49:05,381
Most people don't know that.

764
00:49:05,382 --> 00:49:10,178
The pictures of you two were a happy coincidence

765
00:49:10,179 --> 00:49:13,432
we came across when clearing Detective Dixon's apartment.

766
00:49:13,433 --> 00:49:17,727
Apparently he was keeping an eye on you.

767
00:49:17,728 --> 00:49:20,938
Teague always had a nose for secrets.

768
00:49:20,939 --> 00:49:22,689
If you had just been honest about who you are,

769
00:49:22,690 --> 00:49:24,443
nobody'd be able to run you.

770
00:49:24,444 --> 00:49:28,697
- You know that, right?  - And this is what?

771
00:49:29,323 --> 00:49:31,784
Some documents were stolen from a private gathering

772
00:49:31,785 --> 00:49:34,452
of citizens in Monterey.

773
00:49:34,453 --> 00:49:37,080
I believe you have these documents.

774
00:49:37,081 --> 00:49:38,791
Do not bother lying.

775
00:49:40,584 --> 00:49:42,460
Not on me.

776
00:49:44,338 --> 00:49:47,007
Velcoro? Bezzerides?

777
00:49:48,467 --> 00:49:50,551
Where are they?

778
00:49:50,552 --> 00:49:54,055
- I don't know.  - Oh.

779
00:49:54,056 --> 00:49:57,309
Velcoro has the papers. He's turning them into the feds.

780
00:50:04,108 --> 00:50:05,566
But I can call him.

781
00:50:05,567 --> 00:50:07,903
We set up a meeting.

782
00:50:09,655 --> 00:50:11,864
But I skate.

783
00:50:11,865 --> 00:50:14,827
And I get every fucking copy of those pictures.

784
00:50:14,828 --> 00:50:18,037
That's accommodating. Maybe too much.

785
00:50:18,038 --> 00:50:20,540
Velcoro don't mean shit to me.

786
00:50:20,541 --> 00:50:22,542
This fuck-up dragging down.

787
00:50:22,543 --> 00:50:24,502
He had me look you up.

788
00:50:24,503 --> 00:50:26,713
Davis used all of us and she's fucking dead.

789
00:50:26,714 --> 00:50:28,756
The other, this Ventura dyke,

790
00:50:28,757 --> 00:50:31,259
she's been on my ass from the jump.

791
00:50:31,260 --> 00:50:33,637
I could give a shit about either of them.

792
00:50:35,347 --> 00:50:38,475
Call Ray. Set a meeting.

793
00:50:52,614 --> 00:50:55,950
Osip wants to know where is gas leak.

794
00:50:55,951 --> 00:50:57,410
It's...

795
00:51:29,359 --> 00:51:30,985
I'm just tired.

796
00:51:30,986 --> 00:51:32,612
There.

797
00:51:32,613 --> 00:51:33,945
I want to go to bed now.

798
00:51:33,946 --> 00:51:35,449
That's "Splendor in the Grass."

799
00:51:37,409 --> 00:51:39,201
I love that one.

800
00:51:39,202 --> 00:51:42,914
You tell Bud Stamper to bring you home earlier.

801
00:51:42,915 --> 00:51:44,874
Looks old.

802
00:51:44,875 --> 00:51:46,460
It is.

803
00:51:47,878 --> 00:51:49,420
Sad.

804
00:51:49,421 --> 00:51:52,299
Good night, sleep tight, don't let the bed bugs bite.

805
00:51:52,300 --> 00:51:53,926
Good night.

806
00:51:56,845 --> 00:51:59,640
I don't get any service down here.

807
00:52:02,309 --> 00:52:05,645
- Let me see.  - Hey, hey!

808
00:52:05,646 --> 00:52:08,607
Oh, boy, you fucking up. Cut the shit, son.

809
00:52:08,608 --> 00:52:10,232
Shut up.

810
00:52:10,233 --> 00:52:12,361
Toss all the guns. Kill the fucking lights.

811
00:52:12,362 --> 00:52:15,154
- Now!  - Do it.

812
00:52:15,155 --> 00:52:16,781
Now...

813
00:52:16,782 --> 00:52:18,866
Kick 'em forward.

814
00:52:18,867 --> 00:52:20,243
Move.

815
00:52:53,110 --> 00:52:56,070
This is gonna be hard on my son.

816
00:52:56,071 --> 00:52:58,073
The things he'll hear about me.

817
00:52:58,074 --> 00:53:00,991
We can get out of this.

818
00:53:00,992 --> 00:53:04,704
We get that girl's story, walk her into the feds.

819
00:53:04,705 --> 00:53:06,748
Fucking CNN.

820
00:53:10,085 --> 00:53:12,170
I'm sorry.

821
00:53:14,631 --> 00:53:16,299
I brought you back in this.

822
00:53:16,300 --> 00:53:18,385
No, I made a choice.

823
00:53:21,388 --> 00:53:23,515
A long time ago.

824
00:53:24,933 --> 00:53:27,768
I, uh...

825
00:53:27,769 --> 00:53:32,190
I thought everything came from something else.

826
00:53:35,652 --> 00:53:37,737
But it came from there.

827
00:53:41,408 --> 00:53:43,743
You had something like that, too, once, right?

828
00:53:51,751 --> 00:53:54,421
It's not something I talk about.

829
00:53:55,589 --> 00:53:57,340
Well...

830
00:53:59,509 --> 00:54:01,678
It's one of the things I admire about you.

831
00:55:07,994 --> 00:55:10,747
You're not a bad man.

832
00:55:16,753 --> 00:55:18,254
Yes...

833
00:55:21,174 --> 00:55:22,759
I am.

834
00:55:34,729 --> 00:55:36,898
Do you miss it?

835
00:55:40,402 --> 00:55:41,944
What?

836
00:55:47,867 --> 00:55:49,869
Anything?

837
01:01:46,392 --> 01:01:49,729
Fuck you. No, no.

838
01:01:49,770 --> 01:01:51,689
No. Fuck you.

839
01:01:59,697 --> 01:02:02,158
Oh, what a fine boy you are.

840
01:02:11,709 --> 01:02:14,376
So now we're expecting another child.

841
01:02:14,377 --> 01:02:16,338
I hope it's a girl this time.

842
01:02:16,380 --> 01:02:19,216
You're a fine boy.

843
01:02:24,638 --> 01:02:26,389
Well, I have to go now.

844
01:02:26,390 --> 01:02:29,433
Oh. You'll come back again sometime?

845
01:02:29,434 --> 01:02:31,020
Will you come back for dinner?

