1
00:03:08,000 --> 00:03:18,000
{\pos(190,278)}本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

3
00:03:18,000 --> 00:03:23,000
{\pos(190,268)}翻译：Silmar  小舞  NoNopig  Greentie  Eve

5
00:03:23,000 --> 00:03:28,000
{\pos(190,268)}翻译：haoyang112  泰斯  时间轴：崽猪  Cath.K

7
00:03:28,000 --> 00:03:33,000
{\pos(190,268)}后期： 孤帆   校对&总监： 泰斯·雪诺

9
00:04:32,500 --> 00:04:37,500
《真爱如血》第五季  第九集
True Blood S05E09

10
00:00:00,100 --> 00:00:01,210
[前情提要]

11
00:00:01,210 --> 00:00:03,540
-刚才到底发生了什么  -我们看见她了
- What the hell just happened? - We saw her.

12
00:00:03,550 --> 00:00:04,810
我们看到了莉莉丝
We saw Lilith.

13
00:00:04,810 --> 00:00:06,320
你看到她了  你当时也在场
You saw her. You were there.

14
00:00:06,320 --> 00:00:09,900
格瑞克也在  他感到恶心
And so was Godric. And it sickened him.

15
00:00:09,910 --> 00:00:12,790
你昨晚见到的格瑞克是堕落的异端
The Godric you say you saw last night was a perversion.

16
00:00:12,790 --> 00:00:14,370
莉莉丝会为你指明方向
Lilith will show you the way.

17
00:00:14,380 --> 00:00:17,970
也许有个办法能找出来谁杀了你们的父母
There may be a way we can find out who killed your parents.

18
00:00:17,970 --> 00:00:21,390
一开始我是妈妈  然后我成了那个吸血鬼
First I was Mama, then I was the vampire.

19
00:00:21,390 --> 00:00:22,800
你看见克劳汀了
You saw Claudine?

20
00:00:22,850 --> 00:00:24,690
沃罗  别去找那女孩
Warlow, leave the girl alone!

21
00:00:24,690 --> 00:00:27,210
-你对沃罗这个名字有印象吗  -没有
- Does Warlow mean anything to you? - No.

22
00:00:27,970 --> 00:00:30,970
你属于我
You are mine!

23
00:00:32,930 --> 00:00:35,840
她来了  她愿意撤回  只要...
She here. She'll lift the curse if--

24
00:00:35,850 --> 00:00:38,020
特里  老兄  你必须杀了帕特里克
Terry, baby, you got to kill Patrick.

25
00:00:38,020 --> 00:00:39,520
或者他杀了你
Or either he got to kill you.

26
00:00:39,520 --> 00:00:41,270
我们必须死一个
One of us has got to die.

27
00:00:42,870 --> 00:00:44,550
我的这位吸血鬼朋友
This vamper friend of mine,

28
00:00:44,560 --> 00:00:47,590
我们喝下他的血  他就知道我们站在他那边
we drink his blood and he knows he can trust us.

29
00:00:47,870 --> 00:00:50,130
你这个瘾君子  你是全狼族的耻辱
You're a drug addict and you're a disgrace to all wolves.

30
00:00:50,560 --> 00:00:53,220
杰·德  不要  你已经赢了
JD, don't! You have won.

31
00:00:53,220 --> 00:00:55,180
去找别的狼群吧
Find yourself a new pack.

32
00:00:56,700 --> 00:00:59,330
我正在病房里  然后就变成你了
I was in my room, and the next thing I know I'm you.

33
00:00:59,330 --> 00:01:01,350
-你会没事的  -有事
- You'll be okay. - No, I won't.

34
00:01:01,350 --> 00:01:02,910
我要死了  山姆
I'm gonna die, Sam.

35
00:01:03,390 --> 00:01:04,300
卢娜
Luna?

36
00:01:05,470 --> 00:01:07,550
我们为你准备了惊喜  霍伊特
We got a surprise for you, Hoyt.

37
00:01:07,550 --> 00:01:09,530
你现在必须这么做  老兄
Now, you need to do this, brother.

38
00:01:11,100 --> 00:01:12,190
你动手了
You did it?

39
00:01:13,720 --> 00:01:16,430
我去找帮手  好心人
I'll send help. A friendly face.

40
00:01:16,590 --> 00:01:19,310
是时候开始摧毁回归主流派
It's time to start crushing the mainstreamers.

41
00:01:19,310 --> 00:01:21,530
真血  炸掉工厂
Tru Blood. You bomb the factories.

42
00:01:21,530 --> 00:01:22,960
一共只有五家
There are only five of them.

43
00:01:22,970 --> 00:01:25,320
回归主流派只好去吸食人类了
And you force mainstreamers to feed on humans.

44
00:01:25,320 --> 00:01:27,620
-正如他们过去一样  -非常好
- As they were meant to. - Well done.

45
00:01:27,620 --> 00:01:29,700
-你在做什么  -转型
- What are you doing? - Evolving.

46
00:01:36,160 --> 00:01:38,070
德克萨斯州休斯顿郊外的一家真血工厂
We're looking at a True Blood factory outside Houston, Texas,

47
00:01:38,070 --> 00:01:42,280
一小时前发生爆炸
where an explosion occurred about an hour ago.

48
00:01:42,280 --> 00:01:44,030
爆炸原因尚未查明
The cause is still undetermined,

49
00:01:44,030 --> 00:01:46,330
但初期报道显示至少
but early reports indicate that there have been

50
00:01:46,330 --> 00:01:48,450
有六名人类遇难
at least six human casualties.

51
00:01:48,500 --> 00:01:51,870
休斯顿工厂是世界最大的真血工厂
The Houston plant is the largest True Blood factory in the world,

52
00:01:51,870 --> 00:01:54,000
生产吸血鬼赖以生存的人造血饮料
producing more than a quarter of the world's supply

53
00:01:54,000 --> 00:01:57,520
产量占世界总产量的四分之一以上
of the synthetic blood beverage that vampires need to survive.

54
00:01:58,560 --> 00:01:59,960
开始了
It's begun.

55
00:01:59,960 --> 00:02:01,300
赞美莉莉丝
Praise Lilith.

56
00:02:01,300 --> 00:02:03,580
为庆祝她的圣战
In celebration of her holy war,

57
00:02:03,580 --> 00:02:06,450
让我们以她的名义畅饮
let us feast in Lilith's name.

58
00:02:06,650 --> 00:02:08,270
要做餐前祈祷吗
Should we say Grace?

59
00:02:10,970 --> 00:02:12,220
诺思曼
Northman?

60
00:02:13,190 --> 00:02:15,900
祈祷对我来说可是个新概念
Well, prayer is a fairly new concept to me.

61
00:02:16,260 --> 00:02:19,820
不如找个祈祷经验丰富的人来
Perhaps someone with a little more experience should do it.

62
00:02:23,550 --> 00:02:25,290
我非常荣幸
It would be my honor.

63
00:02:25,640 --> 00:02:28,650
这一段是我在人类岁月中积淀下来的真心感悟
Here's a tried and true one from my human days.

64
00:02:29,860 --> 00:02:31,790
从前有一只雄鸡和一只雌鸡
There once was a cock and a hen

65
00:02:31,790 --> 00:02:33,910
给围栏中的一只鹅供食
who gave lunch to a goose in a pen.

66
00:02:33,910 --> 00:02:35,550
"仁慈的主啊"  那鹅说
"Good Lord," Said the goose,

67
00:02:35,550 --> 00:02:39,850
"保佑此食长有  吾等长侍汝前"
"Bless this food for our use and us to Thy service."

68
00:02:40,410 --> 00:02:41,450
阿门
Amen.

69
00:02:43,810 --> 00:02:45,010
真不错
Charming.

70
00:04:55,400 --> 00:04:57,240
禁止通过
Access denied.

71
00:05:01,600 --> 00:05:05,010
切尔西  阿古利巴法官一定是忘了给我授权
Chelsea, Chancellor Agrippa must have forgot to clear me.

72
00:05:05,010 --> 00:05:06,420
你能不能帮忙...
Is there any way you can...

73
00:05:06,420 --> 00:05:08,230
一级权限  抱歉了亲
Level one protocols. Sorry, hon.

74
00:05:10,830 --> 00:05:11,880
了解
Gotcha.

75
00:05:19,270 --> 00:05:20,490
拜托
Oh, please.

76
00:05:20,490 --> 00:05:22,150
我比你老一千岁
I'm a thousand years older than you.

77
00:05:22,150 --> 00:05:24,810
快把你的小牙收起来  别惹我生气
Put the baby fangs away before you piss me off.

78
00:05:26,520 --> 00:05:28,450
有没有安全地方可以说句话
Is there somewhere safe we can talk?

79
00:05:29,210 --> 00:05:32,030
放开我这里就安全
Be safe in here if you let me go.

80
00:05:36,590 --> 00:05:38,580
三十秒后监视恢复
We got 30 seconds before we're live again.

81
00:05:38,580 --> 00:05:40,700
拜托快说你有办法让我们出去
Please tell me you have a plan to get us outta here.

82
00:05:41,240 --> 00:05:43,450
-你就是我的办法  -太妙了
- Uh, you were it. - Well, that's great.

83
00:05:43,450 --> 00:05:44,690
一级权限
Level one protocols.

84
00:05:44,690 --> 00:05:46,740
我只有三级通行权  大天才
I only have level three clearance, genius.

85
00:05:46,740 --> 00:05:48,730
封闭系统是识别DNA的
The lockdown system is DNA specific.

86
00:05:48,730 --> 00:05:50,360
我不懂科技词
I don't speak techie.

87
00:05:51,090 --> 00:05:53,960
-翻译一下  -我们他妈的死定了
- Translate. - We're totally fucking fucked.

88
00:05:55,830 --> 00:05:59,430
-除非...  -除非什么
- Unless... - Unless what?

89
00:05:59,610 --> 00:06:02,200
八成是馊主意  八成会害死你
It's probably a really stupid idea and it'll probably get you killed.

90
00:06:02,200 --> 00:06:03,440
听起来很完美
Sounds perfect.

91
00:06:05,710 --> 00:06:08,720
-有没有看到什么  -有啊
- You see anything? - Yep.

92
00:06:09,250 --> 00:06:12,730
一个有着完美新睫毛的混账美人儿
One fine-ass motherfucker with pretty new eyelashes.

93
00:06:12,740 --> 00:06:13,750
拉法耶  严肃点儿
Lafayette, seriously.

94
00:06:13,750 --> 00:06:16,040
这间浴室里有可怕的灵异物
There was a creepy spirit thingy in this bathroom.

95
00:06:16,040 --> 00:06:17,830
你是要帮我找出它是什么
Now, are you gonna help me find out what it was

96
00:06:17,830 --> 00:06:20,050
还是打算整晚就在这里臭美
or are you just gonna stare at your vain-ass self all night?

97
00:06:20,050 --> 00:06:21,210
好吧
Okay.

98
00:06:25,510 --> 00:06:27,240
可怕的灵异物
Creepy spirit thingy,

99
00:06:28,150 --> 00:06:30,050
你为什么在苏琪的浴室里
why you in Sookie bathroom?

100
00:06:32,190 --> 00:06:33,260
喂
Hello?

101
00:06:36,160 --> 00:06:37,510
对不起  苏克
I'm sorry, Sook.

102
00:06:37,510 --> 00:06:39,510
我完全不懂这鬼东西是怎么回事
I ain't got no goddamn clue how this shit work.

103
00:06:39,510 --> 00:06:41,760
我可不是《人鬼情未了》里的乌比·戈德堡
I ain't Whoopi Goldberg in "Ghost,"

104
00:06:41,760 --> 00:06:44,590
虽然我比她漂亮多了
although I am way prettier.

105
00:06:45,270 --> 00:06:46,810
多谢配合
Well, thanks for trying.

106
00:06:47,190 --> 00:06:49,650
我还是要收你一百块
I'm still gonna charge your ass 100 bucks.

107
00:06:49,720 --> 00:06:51,270
记我账上吧
Put it on my tab.

108
00:06:52,530 --> 00:06:56,630
你最近怎么样
So, other than getting possessed

109
00:06:56,630 --> 00:06:58,520
除了被墨西哥妖魔附身之外
by a Mexican demon, how've you been?

110
00:06:58,520 --> 00:07:00,000
有泰拉的消息吗
You heard from Tara?

111
00:07:01,060 --> 00:07:03,000
我给她发过差不多五十条短信
I texted her about 50 times,

112
00:07:03,590 --> 00:07:05,150
她就回了这么一句
and this all she wrote--

113
00:07:07,330 --> 00:07:10,300
"贱人  再发短信我就吃了你"
"Bitch, stop texting me or I will eat you."

114
00:07:11,040 --> 00:07:13,320
听起来她状态好多了
Sounds like she's doing better.

115
00:07:13,320 --> 00:07:14,830
除了八年级我抢了她男朋友那次
She ain't been pissed at me this long

116
00:07:14,830 --> 00:07:16,980
她从没跟我生气这么久过
since I stole her boyfriend in eighth grade.

117
00:07:16,990 --> 00:07:19,010
总有一天她会想通的
Well, she'll get over it someday.

118
00:07:19,370 --> 00:07:21,430
或者她不会
Or she won't.

119
00:07:21,680 --> 00:07:23,350
但至少她还活着
At least she's alive.

120
00:07:24,340 --> 00:07:25,530
算是吧
Sort of.

121
00:07:25,790 --> 00:07:28,270
-什么  -我说至少她还活着
- What? - I said at least she's alive.

122
00:07:28,270 --> 00:07:29,730
不是问你
Not you. Shh.

123
00:07:31,150 --> 00:07:34,050
见鬼啊  你们别吵吵嚷嚷的
Y'all need to simmer the fuck down, shit!

124
00:07:34,400 --> 00:07:38,070
我他妈一次只能听一个声音  操
I can only listen to one of y'all at a goddamn time, fuck.

125
00:07:38,070 --> 00:07:42,060
原谅我失礼  斯塔克豪斯夫人
Oh, excuse my language, Mrs. Stackhouse.

126
00:07:42,140 --> 00:07:44,150
奶奶  奶奶在这里吗
Gran? Gran's here?

127
00:07:44,940 --> 00:07:45,930
那个
It's--

128
00:07:46,050 --> 00:07:48,060
是  夫人  我会告诉她的
Yes, ma'am, I will tell her.

129
00:07:48,060 --> 00:07:51,480
剩下的家伙  我可不是死鬼电子邮箱
The rest of y'all, I ain't Gmail for dead bitches.

130
00:07:51,480 --> 00:07:53,700
你们自己传信去  见鬼
Send your own goddamn messages, hell.

131
00:07:54,250 --> 00:07:58,490
你奶奶说有跳脱衣舞的精灵看护你她很高兴
Your gran says she is glad those striptease fairies is looking after you.

132
00:07:58,490 --> 00:07:59,990
她有说别的吗
Did she say anything else?

133
00:08:00,250 --> 00:08:01,890
比如沃罗是什么人
Like who Warlow is

134
00:08:01,890 --> 00:08:03,150
或者当时是什么东西在我家浴室里
or what that thing was in my bathroom?

135
00:08:05,390 --> 00:08:06,620
睡在上面
Sleep on it.

136
00:08:06,830 --> 00:08:09,390
你睡在上面
You sleep on it?

137
00:08:09,600 --> 00:08:11,320
你就睡在它上面
You're sleeping on top of it.

138
00:08:11,320 --> 00:08:13,000
你就睡在它上面
You're sleeping on top of it.

139
00:08:33,950 --> 00:08:37,610
我说了一百遍了  霍伊特不是面具暴徒
For, like, the hundredth time, Hoyt is not an Obama.

140
00:08:37,610 --> 00:08:40,430
发生这种事的唯一原因就是他还爱着我
The only reason any of this happened is because he still loves me.

141
00:08:40,430 --> 00:08:41,790
他加入了仇恨组织
He joined a hate group.

142
00:08:41,790 --> 00:08:44,900
绑架你  用枪指着你
He tried to kidnap you, pointed a gun at you.

143
00:08:44,900 --> 00:08:46,870
哎呀真是浪漫死了
Oh, yeah, that's real romantic.

144
00:08:46,870 --> 00:08:49,510
至少他没给我头上来一枪
Yeah, well, at least he didn't shoot me in the head.

145
00:08:49,830 --> 00:08:51,620
多谢到场  斯塔克豪斯警官
Thanks for showing up, Officer Stackhouse.

146
00:08:51,620 --> 00:08:53,050
我一听说就赶来了
Well, I came as soon as I heard.

147
00:08:53,050 --> 00:08:54,870
-霍伊特也是面具暴徒吗  -不是
- Hoyt's an Obama? - No!

148
00:08:54,870 --> 00:08:56,910
他是正宗的白马王子
Oh, he's a regular Prince Charming.

149
00:08:57,310 --> 00:08:59,160
自己逃命去了
Ran off to save his own ass.

150
00:08:59,160 --> 00:09:01,970
当时是白天好不好  他去找人帮忙
It was daylight, all right? He went to go get help.

151
00:09:02,730 --> 00:09:05,120
杰森  那群人肯定是把他怎么样了
Jason, they must have done something to him.

152
00:09:05,120 --> 00:09:06,490
霍伊特喝过你的血  不是吗
Hoyt's had your blood, right?

153
00:09:06,500 --> 00:09:08,210
如果他有危险  你能察觉到的是吧
So if he's in danger, you'd feel it, right?

154
00:09:08,210 --> 00:09:09,130
确实有过
I did, all right?

155
00:09:09,130 --> 00:09:11,060
可他后来就没感应了  我没办法...
But then he just went blank, and I can't...

156
00:09:11,530 --> 00:09:13,320
我就再也感觉不到他了
I can't feel him at all anymore.

157
00:09:15,040 --> 00:09:17,090
是我害了他
I did this to him, okay?

158
00:09:17,090 --> 00:09:18,720
如果他有个三长两短
And if anything happens to him,

159
00:09:19,970 --> 00:09:21,360
都是我害的
it's 'cause of me.

160
00:09:31,030 --> 00:09:32,050
给
Here.

161
00:09:41,710 --> 00:09:43,510
我想应该不会再变了
I don't think it's gonna happen again.

162
00:09:44,610 --> 00:09:45,730
你确定吗
You sure?

163
00:09:46,590 --> 00:09:47,560
不确定
No.

164
00:09:48,400 --> 00:09:51,190
可我浑身还是像被针刺着一样疼
But I stopped getting pins and needles all over my body,

165
00:09:51,190 --> 00:09:52,690
这总是好事对吧
so that's a good thing, right?

166
00:09:52,690 --> 00:09:54,980
我要送你回医院
I'm... I'm taking you back to the hospital.

167
00:09:54,980 --> 00:09:57,090
我弟弟变身之后死了
My brother died from skinwalking.

168
00:09:57,090 --> 00:09:58,710
你弟弟是被打死的
Your brother was beaten to death.

169
00:09:58,710 --> 00:10:00,440
他们刚从你体内取出一颗子弹
And they just dug a bullet out of you.

170
00:10:00,440 --> 00:10:03,470
那就别让我浪费精力跟你吵嘴
So stop making me waste my energy by arguing.

171
00:10:03,880 --> 00:10:05,650
我才不会回医院呢
I'm not going back to the hospital.

172
00:10:06,920 --> 00:10:07,950
好吧
Okay.

173
00:10:08,550 --> 00:10:11,970
行  那你就在这里休息
Okay, then you're staying here

174
00:10:11,970 --> 00:10:14,840
我去找人来照顾你
and I'm getting somebody to take care of you.

175
00:10:15,650 --> 00:10:18,390
然后你去追面具暴徒吗
While you're out chasing the Obamas?

176
00:10:18,490 --> 00:10:19,770
你又不是不知道
You know, in case you hadn't noticed,

177
00:10:19,770 --> 00:10:22,130
雷那尔教区的警署不够牛逼
the Renard Parish Sheriff's Department aren't exactly CSI.

178
00:10:22,130 --> 00:10:23,670
他们需要我
They need me.

179
00:10:23,670 --> 00:10:26,390
你又不是不知道  我也没那么脆弱
And in case you haven't noticed, I'm not exactly fragile.

180
00:10:27,020 --> 00:10:29,500
那些混蛋冲我们开了枪
Those cocksuckers shot us

181
00:10:29,510 --> 00:10:31,830
还要杀了我女儿
and they tried to shoot my daughter.

182
00:10:31,830 --> 00:10:34,700
你要是指望我像"豌豆公主"那般
So if you think I'm just gonna lie here in bed

183
00:10:34,700 --> 00:10:36,220
躺在这床上...
like "The Princess and the Pea"...

184
00:10:36,220 --> 00:10:37,410
-卢娜  -那你就大错特错了
- Luna-- - ...then you're dead wrong.

185
00:10:37,410 --> 00:10:38,990
我要和你一起去  你拦不住我
I'm coming with you. You can't stop me.

186
00:10:39,000 --> 00:10:41,390
知道吗  你真他妈烦人
You're really fucking annoying, you know that?

187
00:10:41,390 --> 00:10:43,640
你老古板  你性别歧视
And you're old-fashioned and surprisingly sexist.

188
00:10:43,640 --> 00:10:46,250
想保护我爱的人  这叫性别歧视吗
Trying to protect somebody I love-- that's sexist?

189
00:10:47,300 --> 00:10:48,530
我也爱你
I love you, too.

190
00:10:49,900 --> 00:10:51,760
-很好  -还是要一起去
- Good. - Still coming with you.

191
00:10:51,760 --> 00:10:53,260
该死的
God damn it!

192
00:10:57,990 --> 00:11:01,070
上次鬼妇人附体的拉法耶
Well, last ghost lady Lafayette channeled

193
00:11:01,070 --> 00:11:02,500
要偷走我们的孩子
tried to steal our baby.

194
00:11:02,500 --> 00:11:04,180
我们凭什么要相信这个鬼呢
Why should we trust this one?

195
00:11:04,970 --> 00:11:08,450
-因为我爆了她的脑袋  -那又怎样
- Because I shot her in the head. - Well, so what?

196
00:11:08,450 --> 00:11:12,050
那是很久以前的事  再说也不能怪你
That was a long time ago and it wasn't your fault.

197
00:11:12,050 --> 00:11:15,240
你很内疚  他是真的很内疚
And you're very sorry. He is very sorry.

198
00:11:15,240 --> 00:11:17,250
求求你  求求你  别逼他
Please, please, don't make him do this.

199
00:11:17,250 --> 00:11:19,970
亲爱的  你要把孩子吵醒了
Honey, you're gonna wake up the kids.

200
00:11:21,030 --> 00:11:22,760
你要去干什么
What-- what are you doing?

201
00:11:24,560 --> 00:11:28,500
我和帕特里克  我们都救过对方的命
Me and Patrick, we saved each other's lives.

202
00:11:29,180 --> 00:11:30,470
他是个好人
He's a good man.

203
00:11:30,470 --> 00:11:33,600
所以他像只受惊的兔子一样跑出去了
Oh, is that why he ran out of here like a scalded dog?

204
00:11:33,600 --> 00:11:35,720
在我看来  他想的全是
Looked to me like all he was thinking about

205
00:11:35,720 --> 00:11:37,350
怎么保住他的小命
was saving his own hide.

206
00:11:37,350 --> 00:11:39,840
你死我活的选择暴露了我们的阴暗面
Survival brings out the ugly in all of us.

207
00:11:40,160 --> 00:11:41,830
我打算和他来次公平决斗
I'm gonna offer him a fair fight.

208
00:11:42,690 --> 00:11:44,330
这是他应得的
It's the least he deserves.

209
00:11:44,330 --> 00:11:46,390
那我们怎么办
What about us?

210
00:11:46,890 --> 00:11:49,100
迈奇怎么办
What about Mikey, okay?

211
00:11:49,100 --> 00:11:50,770
我们应得的呢
What about what we deserve?

212
00:11:52,010 --> 00:11:55,400
亲爱的  要不是为了你...
Baby, if it wasn't for you...

213
00:11:58,300 --> 00:12:00,460
你是我要决斗的唯一理由
You're the only reason I'm fighting at all.

214
00:12:06,890 --> 00:12:08,020
特里
Terry.

215
00:12:09,910 --> 00:12:11,080
特里
Terry.

216
00:12:17,350 --> 00:12:21,570
德州休斯顿郊区的真血工厂  火势仍在蔓延
The fire is still raging at the Tru Blood factory outside Houston, Texas.

217
00:12:21,580 --> 00:12:24,310
同时  全国各地恐慌的吸血鬼
Meanwhile, panicked vampires across the country

218
00:12:24,320 --> 00:12:26,080
开始囤积真血饮料
rush to stockpile the beverage.

219
00:12:26,080 --> 00:12:28,990
而许多人类市民提出疑问
And many human citizens are already asking the question:

220
00:12:28,990 --> 00:12:30,530
当人造血消耗完时
what will happen to them... 

221
00:12:30,530 --> 00:12:32,460
他们会怎样
...when the artificial blood runs out?

222
00:12:33,980 --> 00:12:36,750
-你在干什么  -现在要是停售真血
- What are you doing? - We should have enough Tru Blood

223
00:12:36,750 --> 00:12:39,180
我们也要备一些撑几个星期
to last us a couple of weeks if we stop serving it now.

224
00:12:39,180 --> 00:12:40,980
我们不会停售
We're not going to stop serving it.

225
00:12:40,980 --> 00:12:42,580
你不是看见新闻了吗
You've seen the news, right?

226
00:12:42,730 --> 00:12:45,490
工厂烧了  吸血鬼很恐慌
Factories burning, vampires panicking.

227
00:12:45,490 --> 00:12:49,210
所以我们才要继续卖真血
Which is exactly why we need to keep serving the blood--

228
00:12:49,220 --> 00:12:52,790
这样我们的吸血鬼顾客就不会吃了人类顾客
so our vampire customers don't eat our human customers

229
00:12:52,790 --> 00:12:54,330
把生意都吓跑了
and put us out of business.

230
00:12:54,330 --> 00:12:55,640
那都卖完了怎么办
What happens when we run out?

231
00:12:55,640 --> 00:12:59,490
我们就像每一个明智的吸血鬼一样
We do what every sane vampire in this country is gonna do--

232
00:12:59,490 --> 00:13:00,670
假装依然喝着真血
pretend to still be drinking

233
00:13:00,670 --> 00:13:02,740
就跟少数主流派那样
the shit like good little mainstreamers,

234
00:13:02,740 --> 00:13:06,930
私底下我们喝人血
and in private we discreetly feed on humans.

235
00:13:07,050 --> 00:13:09,110
那一定会血流成河的
It's gonna be a bloodbath out there.

236
00:13:10,320 --> 00:13:11,500
甭管是谁烧了工厂
Whoever blew up that factory,

237
00:13:11,500 --> 00:13:13,860
这正是他们的目的  对吧
that's what they want, isn't it?

238
00:13:14,180 --> 00:13:17,250
有两样东西我避之不及
There are two things I try to stay away from:

239
00:13:17,450 --> 00:13:20,570
一是总吃鱼的人  二是政治
humans who eat a lot of fish and politics.

240
00:13:20,570 --> 00:13:24,810
所以不管接下来怎样  我们低头挺胸
So whatever comes next, we keep our heads down, our tits up,

241
00:13:24,810 --> 00:13:26,230
保证真血供货
and the Tru Blood flowing.

242
00:13:26,560 --> 00:13:28,140
明白了吗
Understand?

243
00:13:34,810 --> 00:13:37,620
听着  我可能是还年轻
Hey, I may be, like, a week old,

244
00:13:37,620 --> 00:13:39,260
但我不傻
but I'm not an idiot.

245
00:13:39,840 --> 00:13:41,660
你很担心埃里克
You're worried about Eric.

246
00:13:42,220 --> 00:13:43,960
如果你想找人说说...
If you need someone to talk to--

247
00:13:44,660 --> 00:13:46,470
别以为我们一起吃了一个婊子
Just because we drank a bitch together

248
00:13:46,470 --> 00:13:48,760
就算是好闺蜜了
does not make us Oprah and Gayle.

249
00:13:46,470 --> 00:13:49,360
{\an8}美国脱口秀主持人奥普拉和她的好朋友

250
00:13:48,760 --> 00:13:50,530
赶紧给我滚回去工作
Get the fuck back to work.

251
00:13:50,530 --> 00:13:53,600
操  吸血芭比
Suck me, vampire Barbie.

252
00:14:19,850 --> 00:14:21,440
"嘿  我有个好主意
"Hey, I have a great idea.

253
00:14:22,370 --> 00:14:24,720
我们何不炸了所有真血工厂
Why don't we blow up all the Tru Blood factories

254
00:14:24,720 --> 00:14:26,320
挑起内战呢
and start a civil war?

255
00:14:26,680 --> 00:14:28,110
那该多好玩
Wouldn't that be fun?

256
00:14:28,240 --> 00:14:31,020
赞美莉莉丝"
Praise Lilith."

257
00:14:31,770 --> 00:14:33,570
我不知道你在玩什么把戏  比尔  可是
I don't know what kind of game you're playing, Bill, but--

258
00:14:33,570 --> 00:14:35,220
-这不是游戏  -住嘴
- It's not a game. - Shut up.

259
00:14:35,500 --> 00:14:37,220
这里没有监控摄像
There aren't any cameras in here.

260
00:14:38,130 --> 00:14:40,470
你做的可有点过了  你说呢
You're laying it on a little thick, don't you think?

261
00:14:40,470 --> 00:14:43,280
莎乐美和罗素都有好几千岁了
Salome and Russell are thousands of years old.

262
00:14:43,280 --> 00:14:46,010
诺拉也许还小  但她是个政治天才
And Nora may be young, but she's a political genius.

263
00:14:46,010 --> 00:14:47,890
所以格瑞克才选了她
That's why Godric chose her.

264
00:14:47,890 --> 00:14:50,240
你要是以为他们还会吃你这一套
If you think they're gonna buy this act much longer,

265
00:14:50,240 --> 00:14:51,900
你就跟他们一样疯
you're as crazy as they are.

266
00:14:52,590 --> 00:14:55,690
如果他们没疯呢
What if they're not crazy?

267
00:14:57,000 --> 00:14:59,390
如果神就是吸血鬼呢
What if God is a vampire?

268
00:15:00,280 --> 00:15:02,590
我见过莉莉丝  我们都见过
I saw Lilith. We both did.

269
00:15:02,590 --> 00:15:04,660
我们都嗑药了
And we were high.

270
00:15:05,980 --> 00:15:07,890
我不知道那血里有什么
I don't know what's in that blood,

271
00:15:07,890 --> 00:15:09,950
但我们得离那东西远点儿
but we need to stay away from it.

272
00:15:10,710 --> 00:15:12,250
我很迷惑
I'm lost.

273
00:15:12,940 --> 00:15:14,790
我不知道该相信谁
I don't know who to trust.

274
00:15:16,280 --> 00:15:19,090
我曾信仰的一切都被颠覆了
Everything I believed in has been turned upside down.

275
00:15:23,070 --> 00:15:24,440
那苏琪呢
What about Sookie?

276
00:15:25,720 --> 00:15:27,340
她现在也只是你的食物吗
She just food to you now?

277
00:15:30,290 --> 00:15:31,750
我不相信
I didn't think so.

278
00:15:32,950 --> 00:15:35,590
你是一个比我更虔诚的主流派
You're more of a mainstreamer than I'll ever be.

279
00:15:35,950 --> 00:15:38,710
不管你现在觉得遇到了什么信仰危机
And whatever religious crisis you think you're having,

280
00:15:38,710 --> 00:15:40,320
换个地方再思考也无妨
you can have it somewhere else.

281
00:15:40,780 --> 00:15:42,530
我们离开这鬼地方
We're getting the hell out of here.

282
00:15:44,490 --> 00:15:46,410
现在  这里都已经封闭了
Now, the compound's on lockdown.

283
00:15:47,280 --> 00:15:48,830
只有一条出路
There's only one way out.

284
00:15:51,580 --> 00:15:53,490
大法官的血
The chancellor's blood.

285
00:15:53,520 --> 00:15:55,820
你要我去偷莎乐美的血
You want me to steal Salome's blood?

286
00:15:55,820 --> 00:15:58,040
-那你妹妹呢  -我会搞定诺拉
- What about your sister? - I'll handle Nora.

287
00:15:59,550 --> 00:16:01,020
这是我们唯一的机会
It's our only shot.

288
00:16:01,950 --> 00:16:05,610
明天黎明前
Tomorrow before dawn.

289
00:16:09,010 --> 00:16:12,410
不  不
No! No!

290
00:16:12,410 --> 00:16:15,240
回到以上帝之名屠杀人类的时代
Hmm, we'd better get back to slaughtering people

291
00:16:15,240 --> 00:16:16,920
多好啊
in the name of God.

292
00:16:17,160 --> 00:16:19,140
不  不
No, no!

293
00:16:20,430 --> 00:16:23,730
不  不
No! No!

294
00:16:23,730 --> 00:16:26,620
奶奶的相册  我父母小时候的照片
Gran's photo albums, my parents' baby pictures,

295
00:16:26,620 --> 00:16:30,240
他们的讣告  我不懂
their obituaries-- I-- I don't understand.

296
00:16:30,240 --> 00:16:32,000
这些东西我都看了无数遍
I've been through this stuff a zillion times.

297
00:16:32,000 --> 00:16:33,810
我到底该找什么
What am I supposed to be looking for?

298
00:16:34,360 --> 00:16:36,640
谁知道呢  南茜·朱尔
Shit knows, Nancy Drew.

299
00:16:34,360 --> 00:16:36,640
{\an8} 南茜·朱尔是一部电影中的少女神探

300
00:16:38,030 --> 00:16:40,660
-这是什么  -杰森的成绩单
- What is this? - Jason's report card.

301
00:16:40,660 --> 00:16:42,300
这是他唯一拿过的一次B
It's the only B he ever got.

302
00:16:42,670 --> 00:16:44,590
奶奶特地织了相框
Gran knitted a frame for it.

303
00:16:45,230 --> 00:16:48,090
你想告诉我什么  奶奶
What are you trying to show me, Gran?

304
00:16:48,090 --> 00:16:49,700
我还有什么没看到
What am I not seeing?

305
00:16:49,830 --> 00:16:52,640
林恩·迪亚博是杰森的六年级老师
Lynn Dearborne was Jason's sixth grade teacher?

306
00:16:52,760 --> 00:16:55,050
迪亚博警长的老婆
Sheriff Dearborne's wife?

307
00:16:55,050 --> 00:16:56,360
杰森是她的最爱
Jason was her favorite.

308
00:16:56,370 --> 00:16:57,830
不管他有多少次考试不及格
It didn't matter how many tests he flunked

309
00:16:57,840 --> 00:16:59,370
或者考试作弊
or cheated his way through,

310
00:16:59,370 --> 00:17:01,650
他是每个女老师的心头肉
he was every female teacher's pet.

311
00:17:02,000 --> 00:17:04,560
这个男孩能迷得人抽筋树脱皮
The boy could charm the skirt off a post.

312
00:17:04,560 --> 00:17:05,980
经常让我抓狂
Used to drive me nuts.

313
00:17:08,330 --> 00:17:11,040
米歇尔和科比特·斯塔克豪斯的尸体
"The bodies of Michelle and Corbett Stackhouse

314
00:17:11,050 --> 00:17:13,010
是雷那尔教区警署的
were discovered by Deputy Bud Dearborne

315
00:17:13,010 --> 00:17:15,350
巴德·迪亚博警官发现的
of the Renard Parish Sheriff's Department."

316
00:17:15,430 --> 00:17:17,920
巴德·迪亚博发现了我父母的尸体
Bud Dearborne found my parents' bodies?

317
00:17:18,030 --> 00:17:19,620
我怎么会不知道
How come I didn't know that?

318
00:17:20,440 --> 00:17:21,780
他在场
He was there.

319
00:17:21,790 --> 00:17:24,560
说不定奶奶就想告诉我
Maybe this is what Gran's trying to tell me--

320
00:17:24,650 --> 00:17:27,000
巴德·迪亚博知道一些事情
that Bud Dearborne knows something.

321
00:17:28,520 --> 00:17:30,540
那她应该直接说出来
She could have just said so.

322
00:17:30,540 --> 00:17:33,260
这些死鬼干嘛搞得这么神秘兮兮的
Dead folk, why y'all gotta be so cryptic?

323
00:17:33,740 --> 00:17:35,080
没意思
It ain't cute.

324
00:17:35,080 --> 00:17:36,970
喂  别让她离开你们的视线
Hey, don't let her out of your sight.

325
00:17:36,970 --> 00:17:38,750
不管她是睡觉还是拉屎
I don't care if she's sleeping or taking a dump.

326
00:17:38,750 --> 00:17:41,250
杰森  我才不用拉屎呢
Jason, I don't take dumps.

327
00:17:42,060 --> 00:17:43,750
我没事的  不用担心我
And I'm gonna be fine. Don't worry about me.

328
00:17:43,750 --> 00:17:46,280
担心霍伊特吧  我仍然感觉不到他
Only worry about Hoyt. I still can't feel him.

329
00:17:46,280 --> 00:17:48,780
好像什么都没有  只有虚无
It's like there's nothing, just emptiness.

330
00:17:48,780 --> 00:17:50,790
老天  就像是他睡着了或是...
And, God, it's like he's asleep or--

331
00:17:50,790 --> 00:17:52,430
别说那个词
Don't even say it.

332
00:17:55,840 --> 00:17:57,330
我希望能留下帮忙
I wish I could stay and help.

333
00:17:57,330 --> 00:17:59,320
做个吸血鬼的确有好处
Well, being a vampire's got its perks--

334
00:17:59,320 --> 00:18:01,960
不用拉屎什么的  但是见了太阳就烤焦
the no dumping and all-- but getting deep-fried

335
00:18:01,970 --> 00:18:04,290
也算是跟咱们扯平了
when the sun comes up sure evens the playing field.

336
00:18:04,290 --> 00:18:07,970
听着  有我呢
Look, I got this covered.

337
00:18:07,970 --> 00:18:10,910
我可受过专门训练  霍伊特没事的
It's what I'm trained for. Hoyt's gonna be fine.

338
00:18:12,930 --> 00:18:14,290
向我保证
Promise me.

339
00:18:16,560 --> 00:18:17,710
我保证
Promise.

340
00:18:20,700 --> 00:18:21,710
好的
Okay.

341
00:18:33,070 --> 00:18:38,340
乔·鲍勃上同一个网站超过五百次
Joe Bob visited this same website over 500 times--

342
00:18:38,340 --> 00:18:43,560
www.KeepAmericaHuman.Com

343
00:18:46,360 --> 00:18:50,960
{\an8}维系人性美利坚

344
00:18:44,630 --> 00:18:47,500
人类爱国者宣言
"The Human Patriot Manifesto,

345
00:18:47,500 --> 00:18:48,920
第一部分
Part 1.

346
00:18:49,010 --> 00:18:51,350
吸血鬼和其他种类的隐秘变异体
Vampires and other covert mutants

347
00:18:51,350 --> 00:18:54,370
正在偷走我们的工作岗位  收买我们的政客
are stealing our jobs, buying our politicians,

348
00:18:54,370 --> 00:18:57,580
控制媒体  诱惑我们的子孙
controlling the media, and seducing our children.

349
00:18:57,670 --> 00:19:00,580
如果我们还指望维系人性美利坚
If we have any chance of keeping America human,

350
00:19:00,760 --> 00:19:04,710
像我们一样的勇敢公民们应该站出来抗争
brave citizens like us have got to stand up and fight back."

351
00:19:04,890 --> 00:19:07,800
是啊  如果真勇敢  干嘛戴奥巴马面具
Yeah, if they're so brave, then why the Obama masks, hmm?

352
00:19:07,800 --> 00:19:09,750
因为这样看起来很爱国
'Cause it's like patriotic

353
00:19:09,750 --> 00:19:13,430
或者显得很讽刺
or ironic or something.

354
00:19:13,430 --> 00:19:16,090
说不定他们怕被认出来
Maybe it's 'cause they don't wanna get recognized.

355
00:19:17,190 --> 00:19:18,590
上帝保佑
God help us.

356
00:19:18,590 --> 00:19:19,710
阿门
Amen.

357
00:19:20,480 --> 00:19:21,820
-斯塔克豪斯  -在
- Stackhouse. - Yeah.

358
00:19:21,820 --> 00:19:23,090
来看看这个
Check this out.

359
00:19:25,090 --> 00:19:26,560
见鬼
Fuck me.

360
00:19:26,640 --> 00:19:28,820
用超自然生物煮肉粥
Making soups outta supes!

361
00:19:29,100 --> 00:19:31,580
面具暴徒可不仅仅枪击变形人
Obamas aren't just shooting shifters.

362
00:19:31,580 --> 00:19:33,720
他们把吸血鬼捆着扔到太阳下
They're strapping vampires in the sun,

363
00:19:34,090 --> 00:19:36,610
让他们融得像糖稀一样
melting 'em like marshmallows.

364
00:19:36,850 --> 00:19:38,510
超自然生物都去死
Death to supes!

365
00:19:38,530 --> 00:19:42,900
-阿龙万岁  -阿龙万岁
- Long live the Dragon. - Long live the Dragon.

366
00:19:43,320 --> 00:19:44,820
见鬼
Aw, shit me.

367
00:19:44,860 --> 00:19:46,840
现在连龙都有了
There are dragons now, too.

368
00:19:47,400 --> 00:19:49,140
才不是那种龙呢
Not those kind of dragons.

369
00:19:49,140 --> 00:19:50,460
他们不是说...
That's what they s--

370
00:19:50,960 --> 00:19:53,150
老克里特斯·博德豪斯曾经当过
Back in the day, old Cleetus Bodehouse

371
00:19:53,150 --> 00:19:55,870
三K党的龙头老大
used to be a Grand Dragon for the Ku Klux Klan.

372
00:19:56,250 --> 00:19:58,470
那些面具  十字架
The masks, the cross--

373
00:19:58,470 --> 00:20:01,950
这些操蛋龟儿子居然学三K党
sick sons of bitches are modeling themselves after the Klan.

374
00:20:01,970 --> 00:20:05,260
克里特斯·博德豪斯不是在二十年前
Didn't Cleetus Bodehouse drown in his own bathtub

375
00:20:05,260 --> 00:20:06,970
淹死在自家浴缸里么
like 20 years ago?

376
00:20:07,130 --> 00:20:08,920
那阿龙又是谁
So who's the Dragon?

377
00:20:10,130 --> 00:20:12,590
找到阿龙就能找到霍伊特
We find the Dragon, we find Hoyt.

378
00:20:14,120 --> 00:20:15,620
阿龙是谁
Who the fuck's the Dragon?

379
00:20:15,620 --> 00:20:17,180
他把霍伊特怎么样了
And what's he done with Hoyt?

380
00:20:17,180 --> 00:20:19,610
去你的  你什么都别想知道
Fuck you. I ain't telling you shit.

381
00:20:20,760 --> 00:20:23,040
喂喂喂  别这样  斯塔克豪斯
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey, easy, Stackhouse!

382
00:20:23,040 --> 00:20:25,090
-去你妈的  -放开他
- Fuck you, man! - Get off him!

383
00:20:25,280 --> 00:20:27,190
-拜托  老兄  放松  -站起来
- Come on, man, easy. - Get up!

384
00:20:27,740 --> 00:20:31,390
-别激动  -老兄  高中那会儿你是榜样
- Easy. - Dude, we all wanted to be you in high school--

385
00:20:31,390 --> 00:20:34,760
第一四分卫  美女围着转
QB-1, drowning in cooch.

386
00:20:34,760 --> 00:20:36,070
你就是大英雄
You were the man.

387
00:20:36,070 --> 00:20:39,360
看看你现在  贝弗勒的小跟班
Now look at you-- Bellefleur's bitch boy,

388
00:20:39,540 --> 00:20:43,230
为了个死婊子连最好的兄弟都不要了
screwing over your best friend for some cold, dead pussy.

389
00:20:43,560 --> 00:20:45,560
你就是个该死的大烂人
You're such a fuckin' loser.

390
00:20:45,820 --> 00:20:47,980
闭嘴  你这混账
Shut up, you dumb fuck!

391
00:20:49,740 --> 00:20:52,350
打  打
Yeah! Yeah!

392
00:20:56,490 --> 00:21:00,230
*我想要的生活就快要实现*
*A life in the middle of getting it done*

393
00:21:00,230 --> 00:21:03,160
*天堂就在你面前*
*and heaven, it done to you*

394
00:21:03,590 --> 00:21:08,050
*我看到驾驶员的脖子出现在驾驶座*
*I see the neck of the driver behind the wheel...*

395
00:21:08,470 --> 00:21:11,220
吸血鬼或许更强壮  更迅速
Vampers may be stronger and faster,

396
00:21:11,300 --> 00:21:15,250
变形人或许更灵巧  适应性更强
shifters may be smarter, more adaptable,

397
00:21:15,410 --> 00:21:17,750
但狼人有他们所没有的特点
but wolves have something none of them do.

398
00:21:18,050 --> 00:21:20,060
你知道是什么吗  埃尔希德
You know what that is, Alcide?

399
00:21:21,070 --> 00:21:23,570
-狼群  先生  -狼群
- A pack, sir. - A pack.

400
00:21:24,000 --> 00:21:25,710
这正是狼人们
That's how wolves have survived

401
00:21:25,710 --> 00:21:27,400
存活千年的原因
for thousands of years--

402
00:21:27,780 --> 00:21:30,210
我们把狼群的需求  传统
by putting the needs, traditions,

403
00:21:30,320 --> 00:21:33,090
和生存置于自身需求之前
and survival of our pack before our own.

404
00:21:33,190 --> 00:21:35,160
但我们不仅仅是狼  对吧
But we aren't just wolves, are we?

405
00:21:35,160 --> 00:21:36,620
我们还是男人
We're men, too.

406
00:21:37,510 --> 00:21:39,150
以及女人  黛比
And women, Debbie.

407
00:21:39,160 --> 00:21:42,730
我们内心有人兽同在
Inside each of us is both man and beast.

408
00:21:43,200 --> 00:21:46,180
人类很自私
The man is selfish.

409
00:21:46,390 --> 00:21:48,580
人类想要最好的肉块
He wants the best piece of meat,

410
00:21:49,390 --> 00:21:50,930
最大的房子
the biggest house,

411
00:21:51,790 --> 00:21:54,540
最漂亮的女孩  全部归自己
the prettiest girl all to himself.

412
00:21:54,540 --> 00:21:56,330
人类生来如此
That's how humans are built.

413
00:21:56,470 --> 00:21:59,440
然而狼  野兽
But the wolf, the beast,

414
00:21:59,440 --> 00:22:01,310
与更伟大的东西相连
he's connected to something greater.

415
00:22:01,310 --> 00:22:04,230
他在自己的血液中感受到兄弟姊妹
He feels his brothers and sisters in his blood.

416
00:22:04,230 --> 00:22:06,940
不管去哪里  都与兄弟姊妹们同在
He carries them with him wherever he goes.

417
00:22:06,940 --> 00:22:08,920
他知道我们的力量
He knows our strengths

418
00:22:11,760 --> 00:22:13,390
和我们的团结
and our unity.

419
00:22:14,170 --> 00:22:16,440
今天要给你们这个选择
Today you're given the choice...

420
00:22:19,650 --> 00:22:22,930
所有到了年纪的狼人都要做出的选择
the choice all weres make when they come of age.

421
00:22:22,980 --> 00:22:24,590
谁是你们的向导
Who will be your guide?

422
00:22:24,990 --> 00:22:28,280
人或兽  人或狼
Man or beast? Human or wolf?

423
00:22:28,420 --> 00:22:31,950
你是要将整个狼群的希望  梦想和生存
Will you carry the hopes, dreams, and survival

424
00:22:31,950 --> 00:22:34,230
扛在自己的肩上
of our pack on your shoulders

425
00:22:34,410 --> 00:22:36,220
还是要孤身前行
or will you walk alone?

426
00:22:39,920 --> 00:22:44,270
选择权在你
The choice is yours.

427
00:22:44,970 --> 00:22:49,480
埃尔希德·哈韦欧  我的儿子
Alcide Herveaux, my son...

428
00:22:52,970 --> 00:22:54,380
你选什么
your choice?

429
00:22:55,140 --> 00:22:56,900
我选择狼群
I choose pack.

430
00:23:03,820 --> 00:23:07,080
黛比·佩特  你的选择呢
Debbie Pelt, your choice?

431
00:23:09,050 --> 00:23:10,540
我选择狼群
I choose pack.

432
00:23:19,500 --> 00:23:21,520
*你在后座*
*You're changing your clothes*

433
00:23:21,520 --> 00:23:23,470
*换了身衣服*
*in the backseat, you slip*

434
00:23:23,470 --> 00:23:28,130
*瞬间从女孩变成了女人*
*from a girl to a woman in less than a minute*

435
00:23:30,830 --> 00:23:35,790
*披星戴月  我们飞驰出城*
*As we rode from the city under the stars...*

436
00:23:37,090 --> 00:23:38,990
距离杰克逊192英里

437
00:23:45,690 --> 00:23:47,400
*我赚了大钱...*
*I made a lot of money...*

438
00:23:47,400 --> 00:23:48,910
来点姜汁汽水吧  苏琪
Ginger ale for you, Sookie.

439
00:23:48,910 --> 00:23:51,660
谢谢  警...迪亚博先生
Thanks, Sheriff... Mr. Dearborne.

440
00:23:52,220 --> 00:23:53,690
你的退休生活怎么样
How's retirement treating you?

441
00:23:53,690 --> 00:23:56,570
棒极了  结肠癌缓解了
Fantastic. Colon cancer's in remission.

442
00:23:56,580 --> 00:23:58,920
最后一个肿瘤一个月前也切除了
Had the last of the tumors cut out a month ago.

443
00:23:58,940 --> 00:24:01,130
真为你高兴
I'm glad to hear that.

444
00:24:01,830 --> 00:24:06,240
其实呢  我知道我的父母是你发现的
Anyway, about my parents, I know you were the one who found them.

445
00:24:06,670 --> 00:24:10,560
这个案子有什么疑点吗
Was there anything suspicious to you?

446
00:24:10,660 --> 00:24:12,720
他们身上有没有什么痕迹
Were there any marks on them?

447
00:24:13,430 --> 00:24:14,660
咬痕
Bites?

448
00:24:14,660 --> 00:24:16,780
你要是想问那是不是吸血鬼...
If you're asking if it could have been a vamper...

449
00:24:17,630 --> 00:24:20,740
我不想这么说  但确实是的
I hate to say it, but the answer is yes.

450
00:24:21,340 --> 00:24:24,220
当然了  那时我们还不知道他们的存在
Of course, we didn't know about them at the time,

451
00:24:24,220 --> 00:24:28,430
我们推断尸体是被短吻鳄咬过
so we assumed that gators must've gotten to the bodies.

452
00:24:30,250 --> 00:24:31,450
抱歉
I'm sorry.

453
00:24:31,450 --> 00:24:34,920
我知道你和吸血鬼的关系不一般
I know you had a real special relationship with vamps.

454
00:24:35,240 --> 00:24:37,730
知道他们杀了你祖母  甚至包括你父母
But gotta be hard knowing they killed your grandmother

455
00:24:37,730 --> 00:24:40,090
你肯定不太好受
and now maybe even your parents, too.

456
00:24:40,120 --> 00:24:43,520
是雷内·莱尼埃或者叫他德鲁·马歇尔什么的
Ren Lenier or Drew Marshall or whatever his name was

457
00:24:43,520 --> 00:24:45,930
杀了我祖母  不是吸血鬼
killed my gran, not a vampire.

458
00:24:45,930 --> 00:24:49,190
那要看你怎么看了  不是吗
Well, depends how you look at it, right?

459
00:24:49,770 --> 00:24:54,320
我是说  她被杀是因为你和吸血鬼有关系
I mean, she was killed cause you associated with vampires.

460
00:24:54,320 --> 00:24:58,090
某种程度上说  也算是他们杀了她
So, in a way, they might as well have been the ones who killed her.

461
00:24:58,170 --> 00:25:01,050
-你明白我的意思吗  -不  不明白
- You see what I mean? - No, I don't think I do.

462
00:25:01,050 --> 00:25:03,070
她现在八成在读你的心呢
She's probably reading your mind right now.

463
00:25:03,070 --> 00:25:04,600
她盯上你了
She's onto you.

464
00:25:05,040 --> 00:25:06,610
她知道你隐瞒了什么
Knows what you're hiding.

465
00:25:06,620 --> 00:25:07,780
她会毁了它的
Gonna ruin it.

466
00:25:07,780 --> 00:25:10,110
快喝你的姜汁汽水
Just drink the damn ginger ale.

467
00:25:10,240 --> 00:25:11,940
啊  我靠
Oh, shoot!

468
00:25:11,940 --> 00:25:13,490
真对不起
I am so sorry.

469
00:25:13,490 --> 00:25:15,510
-我帮你吧  -没关系
- Here, let me help you with that. - It's okay.

470
00:25:15,510 --> 00:25:16,980
你干什么
What are you doing?

471
00:25:17,870 --> 00:25:20,400
沃罗这名字你知道吗
Does the name Warlow mean anything to you?

472
00:25:21,010 --> 00:25:23,100
你知道谁杀了我父母吗
Do you know who killed my parents?

473
00:25:23,100 --> 00:25:25,190
苏琪  我不知道你在说什么
Sookie, I got no idea what you're talking about.

474
00:25:25,190 --> 00:25:26,730
放开我  小姑娘
Let go of me, young lady.

475
00:25:26,730 --> 00:25:27,980
谁他妈是沃罗
Who the hell's Warlow?

476
00:25:27,980 --> 00:25:29,960
我已经告诉她吸血鬼杀了她父母
I've already told her vampers killed her parents.

477
00:25:29,960 --> 00:25:31,400
她还想怎样
What's she want from me?

478
00:25:32,910 --> 00:25:36,070
抱歉  是我的错
I'm sorry. I made a mistake.

479
00:25:38,150 --> 00:25:40,130
对头  你错了
Yeah, you sure did.

480
00:25:41,520 --> 00:25:43,080
别傻站着了  巴德
Well, don't just stand there gawking, Bud.

481
00:25:43,080 --> 00:25:45,570
-抬她妈的脚  -遵命  甜心
- Grab her damn feet. - Yes, Sweetie.

482
00:25:47,180 --> 00:25:49,600
贝弗勒警长  传说巴拉克·奥巴马本人
Sheriff Bellefleur, is it true that Barack Obama

483
00:25:49,610 --> 00:25:51,980
是不明枪击案和吸血鬼绑架案
is actually behind the recent unsolved shootings

484
00:25:51,980 --> 00:25:53,960
真正的幕后黑手  这是真的吗
and the kidnapping of a local vampire?

485
00:25:54,070 --> 00:25:56,120
不  美国的总统
No. The President of the United States

486
00:25:56,120 --> 00:26:00,010
跟雷那尔教区枪杀案和绑架案无关
is not actually in Renard Parish shooting and kidnapping people.

487
00:26:00,310 --> 00:26:01,920
我们相信有个仇恨组织
We believe there is a hate group

488
00:26:01,920 --> 00:26:05,030
在用奥巴马面具掩饰身份
who are disguising themselves wearing Obama masks.

489
00:26:05,030 --> 00:26:07,130
该仇恨组织绑架了一名吸血鬼
This hate group, they kidnapped a vampire,

490
00:26:07,130 --> 00:26:09,800
同时他们与门罗的两宗谋杀案
but they've also been linked to a double homicide in Monroe

491
00:26:09,810 --> 00:26:11,690
以及什里夫波特的枪击案有关
and a shooting outside Shreveport.

492
00:26:11,690 --> 00:26:14,540
那些受害者是人类  那么共同点是什么
Those victims were human, so what's the connection?

493
00:26:15,050 --> 00:26:19,060
呃  抱歉  我现在无法对此做评论
Uh, sorry, I-- I can't comment on that at this time.

494
00:26:19,060 --> 00:26:20,990
-失陪  -警长  警长
- Excuse me. - Sheriff. Sheriff!

495
00:26:20,990 --> 00:26:23,600
-贝弗勒警长  -安迪
- Sheriff Bellefleur. - Andy.

496
00:26:20,900 --> 00:26:23,500
{\an8}良辰镇市政厅

497
00:26:25,990 --> 00:26:27,050
嘿  安迪
Hey, Andy,

498
00:26:27,050 --> 00:26:28,630
我们去了那地下室
we went back to that basement,

499
00:26:28,990 --> 00:26:30,970
至少闻出了五六个人的气味
picked up the scent of at least five or six people

500
00:26:30,970 --> 00:26:32,390
还有别的东西
and something else, too.

501
00:26:32,820 --> 00:26:35,210
-猪  -猪
- Pigs. - Pigs?

502
00:26:35,290 --> 00:26:37,090
准确地说  是猪粪
More specifically, pig shit.

503
00:26:37,090 --> 00:26:39,240
到处都是那气味  一定是他们鞋上粘了猪粪
Tracked all over the place. Must have been on their shoes.

504
00:26:41,070 --> 00:26:43,370
好吧  谢谢提醒
Okay, well, thanks for the tip.

505
00:26:43,370 --> 00:26:45,800
我建议在我们抓到他们前  你们保持低调
Now I suggest y'all lie low until we bring them in.

506
00:26:45,810 --> 00:26:47,840
听着  我救了你的命
Hey, listen, I saved your life.

507
00:26:47,940 --> 00:26:51,890
-这事儿我要管  -那是"你"变成你之前
- I'm in this. - That was before you turned into you.

508
00:26:51,890 --> 00:26:53,170
你难道没发现
In case you haven't noticed,

509
00:26:53,170 --> 00:26:54,690
这地方到处都是记者
this place is crawling with reporters.

510
00:26:54,690 --> 00:26:55,960
除非你想让我对着镜头
So unless you want me to go on camera

511
00:26:55,960 --> 00:26:58,990
说你能变成狗  她能变成你
and tell them you turn into a dog and she turns into you,

512
00:26:58,990 --> 00:27:00,500
你们还是快走吧
y'all better get outta here.

513
00:27:01,050 --> 00:27:03,210
安迪  别这么混账
Andy, don't be an asshole.

514
00:27:03,210 --> 00:27:04,620
回家吧  马洛特
Go home, Merlotte.

515
00:27:04,780 --> 00:27:06,670
他不想帮我们  去死好了
If he doesn't wanna help us, fuck him.

516
00:27:09,880 --> 00:27:10,860
过来
Come here.

517
00:27:11,110 --> 00:27:12,700
我们现在怎么办
Okay, what are we doing?

518
00:27:12,730 --> 00:27:14,450
你变过墙上的苍蝇吗
You ever been a fly on a wall?

519
00:27:25,700 --> 00:27:28,270
你再叫我就开枪  懂吗
You scream again, I will shoot. You understand?

520
00:27:34,060 --> 00:27:36,160
-钥匙呢  -特里说要跟你做个了结
- Keys. - Terry said he was gonna settle things with you...

521
00:27:36,160 --> 00:27:37,690
让你把钥匙给我
I said give me your keys now.

522
00:27:41,400 --> 00:27:43,200
去  快走
Go on. Go on.

523
00:27:44,020 --> 00:27:45,740
求求你  求你了  我有孩子
Please, please. My kids.

524
00:27:45,740 --> 00:27:48,020
听着  你只要听话  我就让你回他们身边
Look, you do exactly what I say, I'll let you get home to 'em.

525
00:27:48,020 --> 00:27:49,140
我保证
I promise.

526
00:27:49,160 --> 00:27:50,490
今天还有谁上班
Now who else is working?

527
00:27:50,490 --> 00:27:53,840
山姆今天休假
Sam is taking the day off.

528
00:27:54,130 --> 00:27:56,030
霍利做保姆去了
Holly's babysitting.

529
00:27:56,840 --> 00:27:59,430
拉法耶应该来掌勺的  但他总迟到
Lafayette's supposed to be cooking, but he's always late.

530
00:27:59,430 --> 00:28:01,580
你给他打电话  让他别来了
All right, all right, you call him, you tell him not to come in.

531
00:28:01,580 --> 00:28:03,180
今天不营业
Merlotte's is closed for the day.

532
00:28:03,440 --> 00:28:04,990
-好  -好
- Okay. - Okay.

533
00:28:06,100 --> 00:28:07,560
-上帝啊  -快点
- Oh, God. - Come on!

534
00:28:07,560 --> 00:28:08,980
靠  抱歉
Shit. I'm sorry.

535
00:28:15,480 --> 00:28:17,000
拉法耶  我是阿尔琳
Lafayette, it's Arlene.

536
00:28:17,640 --> 00:28:19,150
没错  你又迟到了
Yep, you're late again.

537
00:28:19,150 --> 00:28:22,490
但你猜怎么着  山姆今天不开门
But guess what, Sam's shut-- shutting down for the day.

538
00:28:23,130 --> 00:28:24,440
没  一切正常
No, nothing's wrong.

539
00:28:24,440 --> 00:28:25,890
我觉得他可能...
I think he's just...

540
00:28:26,700 --> 00:28:28,960
终于要管管男厕所的漏水了
taking care of that leak in the men's room finally.

541
00:28:30,020 --> 00:28:31,470
你知道那话怎么说的
Well, you know what they say...

542
00:28:31,470 --> 00:28:33,590
别人送你礼物可别太挑剔  对吧
don't look a gift horse in the mouth, right?

543
00:28:33,590 --> 00:28:36,940
你今天好好玩吧  好  我会的
Uh, but you have a good day. Yeah, okay, I will.

544
00:29:00,700 --> 00:29:01,820
霍伊特
Hoyt?

545
00:29:05,950 --> 00:29:10,860
霍伊特  醒醒
Hoyt, wake up.

546
00:29:13,560 --> 00:29:15,870
好舒服  好开心
I feel so good and happy.

547
00:29:15,880 --> 00:29:18,050
没想到天堂闻起来是这样的
I never thought heaven would smell like this,

548
00:29:18,050 --> 00:29:20,120
可真美啊
but it sure is pretty.

549
00:29:20,540 --> 00:29:22,980
霍伊特  你喝成这样了
Oh, Hoyt, you're high as a kite.

550
00:29:23,500 --> 00:29:25,230
他们到底给你什么了
What did they give you?

551
00:29:35,720 --> 00:29:38,030
来吧  小猪小猪小猪
Here, piggy, piggy, piggy.

552
00:29:38,040 --> 00:29:39,700
小猪饿了没
Hungry pigs?

553
00:29:40,390 --> 00:29:43,140
看看谁醒了
Well, look who's awake.

554
00:29:44,260 --> 00:29:46,520
我们已经抓了两个奥巴马
We got two Obamas so far...

555
00:29:46,520 --> 00:29:48,070
朱尼尔和乔·鲍勃
Junior and Joe Bob.

556
00:29:48,070 --> 00:29:50,040
他们都是土生土长的良辰镇人
These guys are Bon Temps born and bred.

557
00:29:50,050 --> 00:29:51,270
还有什么共同之处呢
What else they got in common?

558
00:29:51,270 --> 00:29:53,650
都有J打头的垃圾白人名字
Both got dumb-ass white-trash names starting with J,

559
00:29:53,650 --> 00:29:55,470
都为镇高中踢过球
played football for BT High.

560
00:29:56,090 --> 00:29:59,440
都被迪亚博警长拘捕过
Sheriff Dearborne arrested both of them.

561
00:29:59,440 --> 00:30:02,050
乔·鲍勃是因为别人说他是
Joe Bob 'cause folks said he's one of them boys

562
00:30:02,050 --> 00:30:03,650
在门罗火烧吸血鬼住房的家伙之一
torched that vampire house in Monroe.

563
00:30:03,650 --> 00:30:05,110
我们什么证据都没找到
We could never prove anything.

564
00:30:05,110 --> 00:30:07,720
美国吸血鬼联盟盯着我们不放
The American Vampire League was crawling up our ass,

565
00:30:07,720 --> 00:30:11,210
所以巴德把他抓来  关了一夜就放了
so Bud dragged him in, held him overnight, let him go.

566
00:30:11,230 --> 00:30:12,480
那朱尼尔呢
What about Junior?

567
00:30:13,400 --> 00:30:15,610
只有公开酗酒一项
Public drunkenness, all it says.

568
00:30:15,610 --> 00:30:18,010
在这样的镇子上  谁都进过一两次局子
A town like this, everybody spends a night or two in the slammer.

569
00:30:18,010 --> 00:30:19,530
我不觉得这些有什么关系
I don't see much of a connection there.

570
00:30:19,530 --> 00:30:22,210
不管阿龙是谁  他们肯定都怕这个人
Whoever this Dragon is, it's somebody they're scared of.

571
00:30:22,810 --> 00:30:24,830
我们都把乔·鲍勃揍成那样了
I mean, we kicked the bejesus out of Joe Bob--

572
00:30:24,830 --> 00:30:25,870
斯塔克豪斯
Stackhouse!

573
00:30:26,610 --> 00:30:31,030
我是说乔·鲍勃从床上狠狠地摔了下来
I mean, uh, Joe Bob fell off his bunk real hard,

574
00:30:31,030 --> 00:30:33,310
他还是不肯说阿龙是谁
and he still wouldn't turn on the Dragon.

575
00:30:39,470 --> 00:30:41,790
如果这个阿龙伤害了霍伊特
If this Dragon's done anything to Hoyt,

576
00:30:42,060 --> 00:30:45,510
我永远都不能原谅自己
I ain't never gonna forgive myself for a long, long time.

577
00:30:46,330 --> 00:30:49,150
如果我没跟杰西搞在一起
That boy wouldn't be wearing makeup in Fangtasia

578
00:30:49,150 --> 00:30:51,540
那小子不会化浓妆去范塔西娅
or joining hate groups or any of this shit

579
00:30:51,540 --> 00:30:54,960
参加什么仇恨组织
if I hadn't have slept with Jess.

580
00:30:55,000 --> 00:30:56,880
不要太自责了
Don't be too hard on yourself.

581
00:30:57,560 --> 00:30:59,700
人无完人
We all fall short somewhere.

582
00:30:59,800 --> 00:31:01,860
你拿下半身思考人生
You use your dick for a compass.

583
00:31:01,860 --> 00:31:04,650
而我呢  烂警察一个
Me, I'm just a bad cop.

584
00:31:04,650 --> 00:31:07,580
-安迪  -我是本镇史上最差劲的警长
- Andy. - I'm the worst sheriff this town's ever had.

585
00:31:07,580 --> 00:31:08,830
人人都知道
Everybody knows it.

586
00:31:10,290 --> 00:31:13,190
今儿我们打了一个囚犯
We assaulted a prisoner today.

587
00:31:13,600 --> 00:31:15,220
虽然乔·鲍勃是个混蛋
Now, Joe Bob's a son of a bitch,

588
00:31:15,220 --> 00:31:18,200
但我的工作也包括保护混蛋
but it is my job to protect son of a bitches, too,

589
00:31:18,200 --> 00:31:22,050
以及吸血鬼  变形人  变鸡的人
and vampers and shifters, werechickens

590
00:31:22,050 --> 00:31:24,410
什么怪胎老子都要管
and whatever the fuck else is out there!

591
00:31:24,950 --> 00:31:27,310
这世界乱得不成名堂了
The world's going to hell in a hand bucket.

592
00:31:27,540 --> 00:31:29,430
也许我也应该学学巴德
Maybe I oughta do like Bud--

593
00:31:29,850 --> 00:31:31,900
退休走人算了
walk out of here, retire,

594
00:31:32,200 --> 00:31:34,560
搞搞婚外情  跳跳方块舞
cheat on my wife, square-dance.

595
00:31:39,960 --> 00:31:41,500
我的天...
Holy...

596
00:31:42,050 --> 00:31:44,330
阿龙万岁
Long live the Dragon!

597
00:31:46,920 --> 00:31:48,260
他的靴子
His boots.

598
00:31:48,420 --> 00:31:50,000
快看他的靴子
Look at his boots.

599
00:31:49,600 --> 00:31:51,100
{\an8}巴德  退休快乐

600
00:31:50,230 --> 00:31:51,970
既然你要摘下警帽就此退休了
Since you hung up your hat for good,

601
00:31:51,970 --> 00:31:54,890
那你就可以尽情穿上新舞鞋了
it's time you put on your new dancing shoes.

602
00:31:56,050 --> 00:31:58,000
谢谢  鞋子很漂亮
Thank you. They're beautiful.

603
00:32:01,990 --> 00:32:05,310
-巴德就是阿龙  -巴德就是阿龙
- Bud's the Dragon. - Bud's the Dragon.

604
00:32:07,300 --> 00:32:10,130
巴德他妈的就是阿龙
Bud's the goddamn Dragon.

605
00:32:21,210 --> 00:32:22,560
委屈你了
Sorry about this.

606
00:32:22,560 --> 00:32:24,210
因为你有读心术什么的
With your mind-reading and all,

607
00:32:24,210 --> 00:32:26,720
不能冒险让你泄露了我们的秘密
we couldn't risk you telling somebody on us.

608
00:32:26,720 --> 00:32:28,920
迪亚博先生  我不明白你在说什么
Mr. Dearborne, I don't know what you're talking about.

609
00:32:28,920 --> 00:32:31,980
超自然生物企图占领这个世界
The supes are trying to take over the whole world.

610
00:32:31,980 --> 00:32:34,660
狡猾的吸血鬼早就在采取行动了
Crafty suckers have been at it a long, long time.

611
00:32:34,660 --> 00:32:38,710
过去四十年我攒了一堆悬案
I got a stack of unsolved cases dating back over 40 years--

612
00:32:39,170 --> 00:32:41,950
像你父母一样无辜的人们
innocent people like your folks

613
00:32:41,950 --> 00:32:45,320
被吸血鬼或其他怪物谋杀
murdered by vamps and who knows what else.

614
00:32:45,940 --> 00:32:48,120
必须有人去做个了结
Somebody's gotta put an end to it.

615
00:32:48,120 --> 00:32:49,120
怎么了结
How?

616
00:32:49,120 --> 00:32:50,950
射杀像山姆·马洛特一样
Shooting good people like Sam Merlotte

617
00:32:50,950 --> 00:32:53,180
从来不做坏事  只为镇子做贡献的人吗
who've never done anything but help this town?

618
00:32:53,310 --> 00:32:55,110
马洛特没有给镇子做贡献
Merlotte ain't helping this town.

619
00:32:55,620 --> 00:32:57,180
他要买下镇子
He's buying it.

620
00:32:57,240 --> 00:32:59,680
酒吧  公寓楼
Bars, apartment buildings.

621
00:32:59,680 --> 00:33:02,870
买下学校和教堂只是时间问题
Just a matter of time before he starts in on churches and schools.

622
00:33:03,120 --> 00:33:05,210
然后他就能教给所有的孩子
Then he can convert all the innocent children

623
00:33:05,210 --> 00:33:07,250
变形怪信奉的那一套
to his perverted shifter ways.

624
00:33:07,460 --> 00:33:09,020
第四次世界大战不会是
World War IV ain't gonna be fought

625
00:33:09,020 --> 00:33:11,400
为了争夺土地或石油而打响
over land or oil in no foreign country,

626
00:33:11,430 --> 00:33:13,780
而是发生在此地的人性之战
it's gonna be fought right here for our humanity.

627
00:33:13,780 --> 00:33:15,380
打断一下  你是谁啊
Excuse me, who are you?

628
00:33:15,380 --> 00:33:18,610
艺术之甜心  很高兴见到你  怪胎
Sweetie Des Arts. Nice to meet you, freak.

629
00:33:18,610 --> 00:33:20,240
你看起来可不像甜心
You don't look like a Sweetie.

630
00:33:20,640 --> 00:33:23,280
巴德  也许苏琪现在需要来点姜汁汽水
Bud, maybe Sookie'd like some of that ginger ale now.

631
00:33:23,280 --> 00:33:26,070
我...我觉得她不是阴谋集团的一员
I-- I don't think she's part of the conspiracy.

632
00:33:26,070 --> 00:33:27,600
我是看着她长大的
I known her her whole life.

633
00:33:27,600 --> 00:33:29,490
那你一定比我更清楚
Well, then, you know better than I do--

634
00:33:29,490 --> 00:33:31,170
她绝对不是人类
she sure as shit ain't human.

635
00:33:31,170 --> 00:33:32,360
她是有放电的手指
She's a mind-reader with

636
00:33:32,360 --> 00:33:34,380
迷恋吸血鬼的读心者
electric fingers and a fetish for fangers!

637
00:33:34,380 --> 00:33:36,780
要是这都不算超自然生物  那什么才是
If that ain't a supe, I don't know what the hell is.

638
00:33:39,550 --> 00:33:44,870
你不能让你的情绪蒙蔽了你的眼睛  宝贝
You can't let your emotions cloud your vision, baby.

639
00:33:44,870 --> 00:33:48,360
也许他们的外表言行看起来像人类
They may look like us and talk like us,

640
00:33:48,420 --> 00:33:50,910
但毕竟跟我们不同
but they are not like us.

641
00:33:50,920 --> 00:33:52,990
霍伊特呢  他可是如假包换的人类
What about Hoyt? He's about as human as they come.

642
00:33:52,990 --> 00:33:55,230
我们给过他机会成为人性之战的英雄
We gave him a chance to be a hero for humanity

643
00:33:55,230 --> 00:33:56,950
但他临阵脱逃了
and he pussied out.

644
00:33:56,950 --> 00:33:58,020
既然他那么喜欢异类
He loves mutants so much,

645
00:33:58,020 --> 00:33:59,580
那就跟异类一起死吧
he might as well die with them.

646
00:33:59,580 --> 00:34:02,440
巴德  你曾是镇上的警长啊
Bud, you were the sheriff of this town.

647
00:34:02,440 --> 00:34:04,700
你应该保护镇上的人
You're supposed to protect people.

648
00:34:04,910 --> 00:34:07,720
我在做的正是这件事  保护他们
And that's exactly what I'm doing-- protecting people.

649
00:34:08,050 --> 00:34:08,980
法律没有保护好人类
The law don't protect people.

650
00:34:08,980 --> 00:34:10,370
你跟她说吧  巴德
You tell her, Bud.

651
00:34:10,370 --> 00:34:13,190
法律给了怪物们同等的权利
The law gives monsters equal rights

652
00:34:13,200 --> 00:34:15,680
把我兄弟乔·鲍勃那样的爱国者关进监狱
and sends patriots like my cousin Joe Bob to jail

653
00:34:15,680 --> 00:34:17,820
只因为他维护同类的权益
for sticking up for his own kind.

654
00:34:17,820 --> 00:34:21,430
法律给过我的只有屁股上的癌症
All the law ever gave me was cancer in my ass

655
00:34:22,350 --> 00:34:24,280
和无性的婚姻
and a sexless marriage.

656
00:34:24,290 --> 00:34:25,630
那可不  宝贝
That's right, baby.

657
00:34:25,630 --> 00:34:28,150
等这场超自然战争硝烟散尽之后
When the supernatural war's over and the smoke clears,

658
00:34:28,150 --> 00:34:29,800
我们要制定一套新法
we're gonna write us a new law,

659
00:34:29,800 --> 00:34:31,720
一部合乎人性的法律
one that makes sense for humans.

660
00:34:31,720 --> 00:34:32,760
超自然生物不能出生
Supes will be aborted

661
00:34:32,760 --> 00:34:33,910
一经发现立即处死
or shot on sight,

662
00:34:33,910 --> 00:34:36,980
以美国之名  所有的人都会知道
and all of humanity'll know the sacrifices that we made

663
00:34:36,980 --> 00:34:38,900
我们为此所做的牺牲
in the name of America.

664
00:34:38,950 --> 00:34:41,220
未来将有印着我们面孔的旗帜飘扬
There are gonna be flags with our faces on 'em.

665
00:34:41,220 --> 00:34:42,420
说得对极了
That's right!

666
00:34:42,990 --> 00:34:44,990
你经历了什么
What happened to you?

667
00:34:45,490 --> 00:34:47,440
你一定有过非常可怕的遭遇
Something awful must've happened to you

668
00:34:47,440 --> 00:34:51,270
才会有如此疯狂的仇恨
to fill you with so much crazy hate.

669
00:34:54,300 --> 00:34:56,540
我丈夫为了一个喜欢
Husband left me for that shifter bitch

670
00:34:56,760 --> 00:34:58,610
变浣熊的婊子离开了我
liked to turn herself into a damn raccoon.

671
00:34:58,610 --> 00:35:01,510
这要我的脸面往哪儿搁呀
What's that supposed to do for my self-esteem?

672
00:35:02,200 --> 00:35:04,300
滚出我的脑子  你这个怪物
You get outta my head, you freak show!

673
00:35:04,550 --> 00:35:05,960
快给她喝姜汁汽水
Give her the fuckin' ginger ale already

674
00:35:05,960 --> 00:35:07,770
不然我就自己动手了
or I'll do it my damn self.

675
00:35:08,000 --> 00:35:09,890
喝吧  里面就是一些止痛药
Come on, now. It's just got some OxyContin

676
00:35:09,890 --> 00:35:12,400
我做结肠手术时剩下的
left over from my colon surgery in it.

677
00:35:12,400 --> 00:35:13,980
巴德  这不是你的本意
Bud, you don't wanna do this.

678
00:35:13,980 --> 00:35:16,660
-那个女人已经疯了  -说话小心点
- That woman is out of her mind. - Watch your mouth.

679
00:35:16,700 --> 00:35:19,100
这女人可是雷那尔教区之龙
This woman is the Dragon of Renard Parish,

680
00:35:19,100 --> 00:35:21,170
路易斯安那州方块舞后
the Square-Dancing Champion of Louisiana,

681
00:35:22,070 --> 00:35:23,900
我此生的挚爱
and the love of my life.

682
00:35:27,250 --> 00:35:28,490
张开嘴
Open up.

683
00:35:51,420 --> 00:35:52,890
敲碎
Bust it.

684
00:36:16,900 --> 00:36:18,020
安全
Clear!

685
00:36:18,020 --> 00:36:20,460
-安全  -死混蛋
- Clear. - Motherfucker!

686
00:36:20,490 --> 00:36:22,170
你到底躲哪儿去了  巴德
Where the hell are you, Bud?

687
00:36:22,260 --> 00:36:23,580
你在哪儿
Where are you?

688
00:36:26,780 --> 00:36:29,900
这是巴德的老婆  林恩
It's Bud's wife, Lynn.

689
00:36:30,340 --> 00:36:32,180
我六年级的老师
She was my sixth grade teacher.

690
00:36:32,240 --> 00:36:33,710
曾经给我烤曲奇
Used to bake me cookies

691
00:36:33,800 --> 00:36:35,590
还让我趴在她腿上午睡
and let me take naps on her lap.

692
00:36:35,590 --> 00:36:37,430
说这些干嘛  斯塔克豪斯
Is there a point to this, Stackhouse?

693
00:36:40,280 --> 00:36:43,450
她家在去基卡普那边的路上有个养猪场
Her family owned a pig farm out on the way to Kickapoo.

694
00:36:45,600 --> 00:36:47,380
猪粪
Pig shit.

695
00:37:00,610 --> 00:37:02,940
-你他妈的在哪儿  -我正看着你
- Where the fuck are you? - I'm watching you.

696
00:37:03,550 --> 00:37:05,420
放下武器  举起双手走进酒吧
Put your weapon down and come in with your hands in the air.

697
00:37:05,420 --> 00:37:06,720
不要  特...
Don't do it, Terr--

698
00:37:33,260 --> 00:37:34,800
特里  他会杀了你的  快跑
Terry, he's gonna kill you! Run!

699
00:37:34,800 --> 00:37:37,250
孩子需要母亲  不要逼我杀她 
Those kids need their mother. Don't you make me shoot her.

700
00:37:39,210 --> 00:37:40,680
我曾经信任你
I trusted you.

701
00:37:40,930 --> 00:37:44,050
我是那么煎熬  可依然没有泄露秘密
I kept our secret even when it was eating a hole through me.

702
00:37:44,050 --> 00:37:46,650
经历了这么多  你怎么可以这样做
After everything we've been through, how could you do this?

703
00:37:46,650 --> 00:37:48,760
-她是我妻子  -站住  别过来
- She's my wife. - Stop. Stop right there.

704
00:37:48,940 --> 00:37:50,620
现在我也有家室了
Now, I have a family, too.

705
00:37:51,410 --> 00:37:54,570
玛吉怀孕了  我答应她一定会回家
Maggie's pregnant and I promised her I'd come home.

706
00:37:56,330 --> 00:37:58,780
我不想干这破事  你知道的
I don't wanna do this shit. You know I don't.

707
00:38:00,560 --> 00:38:02,070
但没有别的办法了
But there's no other way to end it.

708
00:38:02,070 --> 00:38:03,780
那就公平决斗  强者获胜
A fair fight. Let the best man win.

709
00:38:03,780 --> 00:38:05,300
你比我强壮
You're stronger than I am.

710
00:38:07,030 --> 00:38:10,180
你当兵比我强  做人比我好
You're a better soldier, a better man.

711
00:38:10,200 --> 00:38:13,080
可惜不是你死就是我亡  只能这样
But it's you or me. That's what it's come down to.

712
00:38:13,140 --> 00:38:14,940
死的不能是我  现在给我跪下
And it ain't gonna be me. Now get on your knees.

713
00:38:14,950 --> 00:38:16,570
不要
No.

714
00:38:16,570 --> 00:38:18,180
该死的  贝弗勒  跪下
God damn it, Bellefleur, get on your knees.

715
00:38:18,290 --> 00:38:21,570
-不要  -滚开
- No! - Get outta here.

716
00:38:28,170 --> 00:38:29,600
我...我很抱歉
I'm-- I'm sorry.

717
00:38:32,870 --> 00:38:34,130
天杀的
God damn it!

718
00:38:50,660 --> 00:38:52,610
不准动  混蛋
Don't move, motherfucker,

719
00:38:52,610 --> 00:38:54,900
否则我把你脑浆崩出来
or I will blow your fucking brains out.

720
00:39:15,080 --> 00:39:19,250
真心信仰一定能感到平静吧
Must be peaceful to be so sure of something.

721
00:39:19,320 --> 00:39:22,620
不再有怀疑和悔恨
No room for doubt or remorse.

722
00:39:23,320 --> 00:39:25,400
信仰不是魔法  谁都可以
Faith isn't magic. Anyone can do it.

723
00:39:25,410 --> 00:39:27,600
可它需要屈服
Mm, but it requires surrendering.

724
00:39:29,070 --> 00:39:30,990
我一向对此没有兴趣
I've never been a big fan of that.

725
00:39:32,160 --> 00:39:34,560
还是那个该死的维京人
Still such a fucking Viking,

726
00:39:34,850 --> 00:39:36,950
不论经历了多少岁月
even after all these years.

727
00:39:37,570 --> 00:39:38,970
一直如此
Always.

728
00:39:38,980 --> 00:39:41,910
可你...你已经变了
But you-- you've changed.

729
00:39:42,180 --> 00:39:44,680
不再是我爱过的  热衷权力的婊子
You're not the power-hungry bitch I used to love.

730
00:39:44,680 --> 00:39:47,490
过去我关心的是在当权者中提高地位
All I cared about was rising up the ranks of the Authority

731
00:39:47,870 --> 00:39:49,740
扬名立威
and making my mark,

732
00:39:50,950 --> 00:39:53,350
有一天坐上罗曼的位子
sitting in Roman's chair someday.

733
00:39:53,350 --> 00:39:55,980
过去我不知道真正的权力是什么
I had no idea what true power was.

734
00:39:57,380 --> 00:40:00,350
你是...你是如何找到神的
How-- how did you find God?

735
00:40:00,740 --> 00:40:02,180
莎乐美
Salome.

736
00:40:02,430 --> 00:40:05,920
罗曼睡在地下时  她把我偷偷地带到这儿
She snuck me in here during the day whilst Roman was in ground.

737
00:40:06,760 --> 00:40:08,890
她让我喝了这血
She let me taste the blood.

738
00:40:09,670 --> 00:40:13,020
让我醍醐灌顶  埃里克
And it blew my fucking mind, Eric.

739
00:40:13,940 --> 00:40:16,170
我的野心微不足道
My ambitions seemed trivial,

740
00:40:16,270 --> 00:40:17,960
我曾经在乎的一切
and everything I had once cared about

741
00:40:17,960 --> 00:40:21,570
在神灵的面前是如此渺小
seemed insignificant in the face of such divinity.

742
00:40:21,570 --> 00:40:24,200
我强烈地感受到了
And I felt this overwhelming sense

743
00:40:24,200 --> 00:40:26,730
那种意义和归属
of purpose and belonging.

744
00:40:27,660 --> 00:40:29,840
真希望我也能如此轻信
Well, I wish it were that simple for me.

745
00:40:29,880 --> 00:40:31,300
可以的
It can be.

746
00:40:32,140 --> 00:40:33,840
-不会的  -可以的
- No. - It can be.

747
00:40:34,080 --> 00:40:35,450
信仰他物而非自我
Believing in something other

748
00:40:35,450 --> 00:40:37,710
并不会弱化自身  埃里克
than yourself doesn't make you weak, Eric.

749
00:40:38,190 --> 00:40:40,120
无论树有多高  它都知道其存在
Even the tallest tree knows its existence

750
00:40:40,120 --> 00:40:42,000
依赖于扎根的土壤
depends on the soil beneath its roots

751
00:40:42,010 --> 00:40:45,620
与枝头的阳光雨露
and the sun and the rain upon its branches.

752
00:40:45,620 --> 00:40:47,340
如同莉莉丝之于我们
That's what Lilith is to us.

753
00:40:57,690 --> 00:40:59,660
我不想和你争吵
I don't wanna fight you.

754
00:41:01,450 --> 00:41:03,190
我也渴望信仰
I want to believe.

755
00:41:05,860 --> 00:41:08,630
-你能帮我吗  -当然
- Will you help me? - Yes.

756
00:41:09,380 --> 00:41:10,770
当然
Yeah.

757
00:41:24,730 --> 00:41:28,920
几千年来  莎乐美不过是
Thousands of years, Salome has meant nothing

758
00:41:29,220 --> 00:41:33,500
膝上放着男人头颅的裸体女孩
but a naked girl with a man's head in her lap.

759
00:41:33,640 --> 00:41:37,240
现在我要永远和莉莉丝连结在一起
Now I will be linked to Lilith forever.

760
00:41:38,080 --> 00:41:40,690
这将是我真正的传奇
That will be my true legacy.

761
00:41:44,700 --> 00:41:47,530
很少有人拥有改变历史的机会
So few have the chance to shape history.

762
00:41:47,740 --> 00:41:50,880
不是一次  而是两次
Not once, but twice.

763
00:41:51,490 --> 00:41:53,060
这可不是偶然
It's not an accident.

764
00:41:53,070 --> 00:41:56,940
我被选中了  你也如此
I've been chosen and so have you.

765
00:42:03,350 --> 00:42:06,280
莉莉丝选择你作为我的亚当
Lilith has chosen you as my Adam.

766
00:42:06,930 --> 00:42:09,970
我们将共同孕育一个新世界
We will birth a new world together.

767
00:42:13,130 --> 00:42:15,360
如果我不希望被选中呢
What if I don't want to be chosen?

768
00:42:15,800 --> 00:42:17,990
你身体里有她的血
Her blood is inside you.

769
00:42:19,470 --> 00:42:21,940
让它指引你吧
Let it be your guide.

770
00:42:46,770 --> 00:42:48,140
比尔
Bill.

771
00:42:58,020 --> 00:42:59,850
不要
No.

772
00:43:40,960 --> 00:43:42,470
我们干嘛不杀了他们
Why don't we just shoot 'em?

773
00:43:42,470 --> 00:43:45,800
因为我们要发表一个政治声明  笨蛋
'Cause we're making a political statement, ass-for-brains.

774
00:43:45,940 --> 00:43:48,390
超自然生物快让这世界变成猪圈了
The world's gone to the pigs 'cause of the supes,

775
00:43:48,390 --> 00:43:50,510
所以我们拿超自然生物喂猪
so we're feeding the supes to the pigs.

776
00:43:50,510 --> 00:43:51,660
明白了
Get it?

777
00:43:52,080 --> 00:43:54,330
到时候要传到网上  宝贝  戴上面具
This is going on the website, baby, so put on your mask.

778
00:43:54,330 --> 00:43:55,380
知道了
Right.

779
00:43:58,050 --> 00:43:59,800
天佑美国
God bless America!

780
00:43:59,850 --> 00:44:01,400
把猪放进来
Bring in the pigs!

781
00:44:02,650 --> 00:44:05,410
来吧  小猪小猪小猪
Here, piggy, piggy, piggy.

782
00:44:06,730 --> 00:44:07,920
好了  把她扔进去
All right, toss her in there.

783
00:44:07,920 --> 00:44:09,890
给那些猪来点能啃的东西
Give those porkies something to chew on.

784
00:44:17,330 --> 00:44:18,010
接住你了
I got you.

785
00:44:18,010 --> 00:44:20,400
-山姆  -天哪  救命  别让他过来
- Sam. - Jesus, help me! Keep it away from me!

786
00:44:20,410 --> 00:44:23,770
离我的猪远点  下贱的变形怪
Stay outta my pig, dirty shifter!

787
00:44:48,600 --> 00:44:51,000
跟上  注意周围情况
Stay close. Keep your eye on the perimeter.

788
00:44:56,780 --> 00:44:58,720
警察  不许动
Sheriff's Department! Freeze!

789
00:44:59,620 --> 00:45:01,320
给我他妈的跪下
Get down on your fuckin' knees!

790
00:45:04,240 --> 00:45:06,510
放下武器  巴德  结束了
Drop the weapon, Bud. It's over.

791
00:45:12,930 --> 00:45:15,390
人类是主宰
Humans rule!

792
00:45:23,400 --> 00:45:24,770
杰森
Jason.

793
00:45:25,800 --> 00:45:27,140
苏克
Sook.

794
00:45:28,010 --> 00:45:29,150
天啊
Oh, my God.

795
00:45:32,530 --> 00:45:33,980
你在这儿干什么
The hell are you doing here?

796
00:45:34,780 --> 00:45:36,020
霍伊特
Hoyt.

797
00:45:38,290 --> 00:45:39,950
霍伊特  伙计
Hoyt. Buddy!

798
00:45:54,490 --> 00:45:56,870
这一下是因为开枪打我
That's for shooting me.

799
00:45:57,540 --> 00:45:59,670
这一下是为了我男友
That's for my boyfriend.

800
00:46:00,360 --> 00:46:02,800
这一下是为了我女儿
And this is for my daughter,

801
00:46:02,800 --> 00:46:05,380
你个人类垃圾
you human trash!

802
00:46:11,350 --> 00:46:12,700
苏琪
Sookie.

803
00:46:13,460 --> 00:46:14,670
你还好吗
You okay?

804
00:46:19,290 --> 00:46:23,520
你真变成一头猪还是我做了个梦
Were you a pig or did I dream that?

805
00:46:27,270 --> 00:46:28,880
别这样  霍伊特
Come on, Hoyt.

806
00:46:30,190 --> 00:46:32,700
醒醒  兄弟  是我啊  伙计
Come on, buddy. It's J. I'm right here, man.

807
00:46:32,700 --> 00:46:34,190
挺住  伙计
Stay with me, man.

808
00:46:35,380 --> 00:46:37,040
挺住  兄弟
Stay with me, bubba.

809
00:46:38,120 --> 00:46:39,680
挺住  伙计
Stay with me, man.

810
00:46:42,500 --> 00:46:44,270
她应该戳中动脉了
I think she hit an artery.

811
00:46:44,960 --> 00:46:46,600
如果你不想杀我
If you're not gonna shoot me,

812
00:46:46,750 --> 00:46:48,170
我需要去医院
I need to get to a hospital.

813
00:46:48,170 --> 00:46:50,150
动手啊  特里  杀了他
Do it, Terry. Shoot him.

814
00:46:50,160 --> 00:46:52,060
她很厉害  这很好
She's a fighter. That's good.

815
00:46:52,330 --> 00:46:54,660
如果你在乎什么  就要为之战斗
If you care about something, you gotta fight for it.

816
00:46:54,660 --> 00:46:56,000
我不光是为了我这条命
I'm not just fighting for my life.

817
00:46:56,010 --> 00:46:58,100
别听他的  特里  他会搅昏你的头
Don't listen to him, Terry. He is messing with your head.

818
00:46:58,100 --> 00:46:59,620
你跪着的时候他是要杀你的
He would've shot you on your knees.

819
00:46:59,870 --> 00:47:01,380
玛吉的预产期在十二月
Maggie's due in December.

820
00:47:01,380 --> 00:47:04,350
是个圣诞宝宝  和迈奇一样是小男孩
It's a Christmas baby, a little boy like Mikey.

821
00:47:04,360 --> 00:47:05,790
-闭嘴  -开枪啊
- Shut up! - Do it.

822
00:47:05,790 --> 00:47:07,790
为了你的家庭  立刻开枪打死他
You shoot him in the head right now for your family.

823
00:47:07,790 --> 00:47:09,780
事情就是这么开始的  记得吗
That's how this whole thing got started, remember?

824
00:47:09,860 --> 00:47:11,390
你执行了命令
You taking orders.

825
00:47:12,750 --> 00:47:14,040
结果了她
Dead check her.

826
00:47:14,240 --> 00:47:15,320
动手
Do it.

827
00:47:16,440 --> 00:47:18,280
开枪  杀了他  特里
Shoot him. Shoot him, Terry.

828
00:47:18,280 --> 00:47:20,650
这次你要摸着良心做决定啊
You gotta do what your conscience tells you this time.

829
00:47:21,210 --> 00:47:22,520
做正确的事情
Do what's right.

830
00:47:32,150 --> 00:47:33,900
{\pos(191,247)}做正确的事情

831
00:47:48,080 --> 00:47:50,970
{\pos(191,247)}血债已偿清

832
00:47:55,000 --> 00:47:59,180
{\pos(191,247)}拿去吧  伊夫利特

833
00:48:26,340 --> 00:48:28,240
请给我拿些真血
Can I get some Tru Blood, please?

834
00:48:28,450 --> 00:48:30,670
我要的真血呢
Where the fuck's my Tru Blood?

835
00:48:45,480 --> 00:48:47,190
打扰了
Excuse me.

836
00:48:50,720 --> 00:48:53,190
很好  现在你注意到姐了
Good, now I've got your attention.

837
00:48:53,540 --> 00:48:54,690
第一条
Number one:

838
00:48:54,880 --> 00:48:58,110
范塔西娅里不准吸食人血
there's no feeding on humans in Fangtasia.

839
00:48:58,220 --> 00:49:00,300
该死的第二条
Number fuckin' two:

840
00:49:00,330 --> 00:49:04,420
从我创造者的宝座上滚起来  不然姐钉死你
get out of my maker's throne before I stake you all over it.

841
00:49:05,350 --> 00:49:08,360
公开吸血已经解禁了
Monarchs have lifted the ban on public feeding.

842
00:49:08,740 --> 00:49:10,810
诺思曼是过去时了
And Northman is history.

843
00:49:11,040 --> 00:49:15,500
当权者任命我为第五区的新治安官
The Authority has named me the new Sheriff of Area 5.

844
00:49:25,220 --> 00:49:29,780
诸位  找个人类  饮料我请
Everybody, grab a human. Drinks are on me!

845
00:49:33,010 --> 00:49:34,740
不要
No!

846
00:49:36,340 --> 00:49:37,940
霍伊特没事吧
Is Hoyt gonna be okay?

847
00:49:37,960 --> 00:49:40,400
他还有心跳  不过非常虚弱
He had a pulse, but it was real weak.

848
00:49:40,600 --> 00:49:42,700
杰森在医院  有消息会通知我们
Jason'll call us from the hospital if there's any news.

849
00:49:42,710 --> 00:49:43,600
你呢
What about you?

850
00:49:43,600 --> 00:49:45,210
真的不需要去检查一下吗
You sure you don't want to at least go get checked out?

851
00:49:45,210 --> 00:49:47,570
我把头发里的猪味洗掉就没事了
I'll be fine as soon as I wash the pig out of my hair.

852
00:49:47,920 --> 00:49:49,480
好吧  那我送你回家
All right, you know, I'll drive you home.

853
00:49:51,490 --> 00:49:52,610
多谢
Thanks.

854
00:50:00,750 --> 00:50:01,940
安迪
Hey, Andy.

855
00:50:05,990 --> 00:50:08,330
-听着  我只想说...  -没什么
- Listen, I just wanted to say-- - It's all good.

856
00:50:08,330 --> 00:50:10,570
你救过我的命  我也救了你的
You saved my life. I saved yours back.

857
00:50:10,980 --> 00:50:12,950
不  我要说的是
No, I was gonna say

858
00:50:13,630 --> 00:50:15,980
你不是本镇史上最差劲的警长
you're not the worst sheriff this town ever had.

859
00:50:16,400 --> 00:50:18,620
巴德·迪亚博比你差远了
Bud Dearborne had you beat by a mile.

860
00:50:22,040 --> 00:50:23,260
多谢  山姆
Thanks, Sam.

861
00:50:24,470 --> 00:50:25,800
晚安
Night.

862
00:50:32,160 --> 00:50:33,430
我们去接艾玛
Let's go get Emma.

863
00:50:34,980 --> 00:50:36,230
好
Yeah.

864
00:50:37,150 --> 00:50:38,970
我最初在斯堪的纳维亚召集狼人
I first started collecting werewolves

865
00:50:38,970 --> 00:50:42,380
那是两千年前的事儿了
in Scandinavia almost 2,000 years ago.

866
00:50:42,710 --> 00:50:46,190
第一个是匹可爱的母狼叫吉斯拉
My first was a lovely werebitch named Gisla.

867
00:50:46,190 --> 00:50:50,930
纯白的皮毛  碧绿的眼睛
Whitest pelt, greenest eyes,

868
00:50:51,150 --> 00:50:52,420
我还没喂她喝血
loyal like you wouldn't believe,

869
00:50:52,420 --> 00:50:53,990
就忠诚得难以置信
even before I gave her my blood.

870
00:50:53,990 --> 00:50:56,320
喝了血后  哈哈
But after-- oh, oh, oh!

871
00:50:56,540 --> 00:51:00,190
谁不拿正眼看我  她就发飙
She'd rip apart anything that looked at me sideways.

872
00:51:00,320 --> 00:51:02,320
你以为狗是好宠物
You think dogs are good pets,

873
00:51:02,400 --> 00:51:06,630
瞧瞧喝了血的狼人吧
wait till you try a werewolf on V.

874
00:51:06,920 --> 00:51:08,490
我没养过宠物
I've never had a pet.

875
00:51:09,270 --> 00:51:12,310
我父亲除了神  什么都过敏
My father was allergic to everything except God.

876
00:51:14,190 --> 00:51:16,170
忘掉那个血袋吧
You forget that bloodbag.

877
00:51:17,000 --> 00:51:19,100
跟着我  亲爱的
Stick with me, darlin'.

878
00:51:19,790 --> 00:51:21,780
我会把全世界给你
I'll give you the world.

879
00:51:28,230 --> 00:51:31,270
我听说这里有庆祝大会
I hear a celebration is in order.

880
00:51:31,280 --> 00:51:34,590
选出了新首领
We have a new Packmaster.

881
00:51:36,880 --> 00:51:40,920
杰·德  什里夫波特的首领
To J.D., Packmaster of Shreveport.

882
00:51:56,150 --> 00:51:59,580
好了  都有都有
Oh, okay. All right, all right.

883
00:52:00,950 --> 00:52:02,470
很好  乖
Okay. Yes.

884
00:52:03,740 --> 00:52:05,590
你叫什么  母狼
What's your name, werebitch?

885
00:52:06,160 --> 00:52:08,770
可爱的小崽子又是谁
And who is that adorable little puppy?

886
00:52:08,780 --> 00:52:10,680
真可爱
So cute.

887
00:52:11,050 --> 00:52:12,800
我是玛莎
Name's Martha.

888
00:52:13,200 --> 00:52:15,160
这是我的孙女
This is my granddaughter.

889
00:52:15,560 --> 00:52:18,290
过来  玛莎
Come, Martha.

890
00:52:19,040 --> 00:52:20,940
跟你族人一起
Join your pack.

891
00:52:20,940 --> 00:52:24,860
族群是我的选择  我发誓为之而死
I chose my pack, and I swore I'd die for it,

892
00:52:25,190 --> 00:52:28,530
但我绝不喝你的血  尖牙鬼
but I will never drink from you, fanger.

893
00:52:31,480 --> 00:52:35,830
越聪明的动物  越需要调教
The smarter the creature, the more discipline it needs.

894
00:52:39,320 --> 00:52:43,320
不  放开她
No! You let go of her.

895
00:52:43,600 --> 00:52:45,870
-放了她  -给你的  亲爱的
- You let her go! - For you, my darlin'.

896
00:52:46,100 --> 00:52:47,810
-艾玛  -你的第一个宠物
- Emma! - Your first pet.

897
00:52:50,940 --> 00:52:54,290
杰·德  求你了  别带走我孙女
J.D., please. Not my grandbaby.

898
00:52:54,290 --> 00:52:56,300
拦住他  求你了
Stop him, please.

899
00:52:56,850 --> 00:52:58,380
爱丁顿先生
Mr. Edgington...

900
00:53:00,060 --> 00:53:02,270
艾玛也是群里的一员
see, Emma, she's a member of this pack,

901
00:53:02,270 --> 00:53:04,060
我不能让你这样做
so I can't let you do that.

902
00:53:10,040 --> 00:53:11,920
你以为我的血是免费的吗
Did you think my blood was free?

903
00:53:13,990 --> 00:53:16,140
你这条蠢狗
You silly, silly dog.

904
00:53:20,290 --> 00:53:24,360
-走吧  -罗素  她可爱极了
- Shall we? - Oh, Russell, she's adorable.

905
00:53:24,910 --> 00:53:26,470
艾玛
Emma!

906
00:53:26,960 --> 00:53:30,480
不要
No!

907
00:54:04,090 --> 00:54:05,570
老爸
Dad.

908
00:54:06,730 --> 00:54:08,560
冰箱有啤酒
Beer in the fridge.

909
00:54:08,700 --> 00:54:10,580
顺手给我拿一瓶
Grab me one while you're in there.

910
00:54:28,540 --> 00:54:30,000
你押了多少
How much you got on this?

911
00:54:31,290 --> 00:54:32,650
一百
100.

912
00:54:33,680 --> 00:54:35,630
四五百吧
Four, five.

913
00:54:36,420 --> 00:54:39,460
残疾金都押上了  不错啊
So your whole disability check. Nice.

914
00:54:39,730 --> 00:54:42,800
大老远开车过来就为了教训我
It's a long drive to come out here and give me another lecture.

915
00:54:44,810 --> 00:54:46,380
不是的
It's not why I came.

916
00:54:50,780 --> 00:54:52,230
我没当上首领
I lost Packmaster.

917
00:54:53,500 --> 00:54:54,820
我被放逐了
I've been abjured.

918
00:54:57,150 --> 00:54:59,180
那你现在是独狼了
So you're a lone wolf now.

919
00:55:00,960 --> 00:55:02,850
跟你老头一样
Just like your old man.

920
00:55:06,280 --> 00:55:07,900
我跟你不一样
I'm nothing like you.

921
00:55:08,930 --> 00:55:10,620
当然  不一样
Sure, you're not.

922
00:55:14,240 --> 00:55:19,210
日本和科威特的另外两家真血工厂也发生爆炸
Two more explosions at Tru Blood factories in Japan and Kuwait.

923
00:55:19,410 --> 00:55:21,720
美国吸血鬼联盟的史蒂夫·纽林
Steve Newlin of the American Vampire League

924
00:55:21,720 --> 00:55:24,630
声称这是"恶性恐怖事件"
has called the attacks "A vicious act of terrorism"

925
00:55:24,630 --> 00:55:28,530
针对全世界所有虔诚的  爱好和平的吸血鬼
against all God-fearing, peace-loving vampire citizens of the world.

926
00:55:28,540 --> 00:55:29,660
胡扯
Oh, bollocks.

927
00:55:29,810 --> 00:55:31,790
克劳德  克劳德特
Claude? Claudette?

928
00:55:33,060 --> 00:55:34,620
不好意思  我不认识你
I'm sorry, I don't know you.

929
00:55:34,620 --> 00:55:35,920
克劳迪佳
Oh, Claudija.

930
00:55:35,920 --> 00:55:38,340
很高兴认识你  不过你们大半夜
Well, it's nice to meet you, but what are y'all doing

931
00:55:38,340 --> 00:55:39,670
来我的客厅做什么
in my living room in the middle of the night?

932
00:55:39,670 --> 00:55:41,200
我们给你带了些汤  苏琪
We brought you some soup, Sookie.

933
00:55:41,660 --> 00:55:42,890
过去点
Move over.

934
00:55:45,660 --> 00:55:47,240
一个字都别信
Don't believe a word of it.

935
00:55:47,240 --> 00:55:49,640
-都是吸血鬼搞的鬼  -为什么
- Vampires are behind it all. - Why?

936
00:55:49,790 --> 00:55:51,730
他们要占领世界
They're taking over the world.

937
00:55:54,410 --> 00:55:56,870
我们又站到一边了
Us together again on the same side.

938
00:55:57,350 --> 00:55:59,310
这是格瑞克所希望的
That's what Godric would have wanted.

939
00:55:59,340 --> 00:56:00,530
你说的对
You're right.

940
00:56:03,640 --> 00:56:05,880
你带我去哪儿
Where are you taking me?

941
00:56:09,590 --> 00:56:10,930
回家
Home.

942
00:56:12,300 --> 00:56:14,010
埃里克  不要
Eric, no.

943
00:56:23,120 --> 00:56:25,220
我们要快点  她不会昏迷太久
We gotta move fast. She won't be out long.

944
00:56:29,290 --> 00:56:31,530
-比尔呢  -我们没时间等他了
- Where's Bill? - We can't wait for him.

945
00:56:33,960 --> 00:56:35,840
你还让我担心了一会儿
You had me worried there for a minute.

946
00:56:36,150 --> 00:56:37,720
准备好离开这里了吗
Ready to get the hell outta here?

947
00:56:40,280 --> 00:56:41,530
同意使用
Access granted.

948
00:56:51,850 --> 00:56:53,770
你他妈的叛徒
You fuckin' traitor.

949
00:56:54,960 --> 00:56:56,720
我这是为你
I'm doing this for you.

950
00:56:57,620 --> 00:56:59,780
你是莉莉丝选的
You've been chosen by Lilith.

951
00:57:00,430 --> 00:57:02,380
这是神的意愿
This is what God wants.

