1
00:02:36,000 --> 00:02:46,000
{\pos(190,278)}本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

3
00:02:46,000 --> 00:02:52,000
{\pos(190,268)}翻译：Silmar  AlbotScorpy  郁金香骨朵  NoNopig

5
00:02:52,000 --> 00:02:57,000
{\pos(190,268)}翻译：Greentie  小白龙QIQI  泰斯

7
00:02:57,000 --> 00:03:02,000
{\pos(190,268)}校对：泰斯  Silmar时间轴：舍我其谁  子衿  崽猪

9
00:03:02,000 --> 00:03:07,000
{\pos(190,268)}后期： 孤帆   总监： 泰斯·雪诺

11
00:04:00,700 --> 00:04:05,700
《真爱如血》第五季  第五集
True Blood S05E05

12
00:00:05,360 --> 00:00:06,780
[前情提要]

13
00:00:06,780 --> 00:00:08,640
-什么时候发生的  -我不记得了
- When did this happen? - I don't remember.

14
00:00:08,720 --> 00:00:11,260
好像有人在我脑子里按了删除键
It's like somebody hit "Delete" In my brain.

15
00:00:11,340 --> 00:00:12,470
你被魅惑了
You've been glamoured.

16
00:00:12,560 --> 00:00:14,590
罗素最想要的是乱局
Russell wants nothing more than anarchy.

17
00:00:14,630 --> 00:00:17,040
我们会抓他归案  不死不休
We'll bring him in or die trying.

18
00:00:19,480 --> 00:00:22,150
是谁组织极端分子想颠覆我们
Who is gathering the extremists to bring us down?

19
00:00:22,170 --> 00:00:23,380
就算你不顾自己的命
You care nothing for your own life.

20
00:00:23,450 --> 00:00:25,760
那么康普顿和诺思曼的命呢
What about the lives of Compton and Northman?

21
00:00:25,820 --> 00:00:27,160
告诉我
Tell me.

22
00:00:27,220 --> 00:00:29,290
某人需要吸血
Someone needs to feed.

23
00:00:29,310 --> 00:00:31,630
我命令你  咬她
I command you-- bite her.

24
00:00:32,470 --> 00:00:34,370
这就是现在的你
This is who you are now.

25
00:00:34,440 --> 00:00:36,060
一个班  四场大火
One squad, four fires.

26
00:00:36,110 --> 00:00:38,790
这跟我们在伊拉克那晚的事有关  你知道
This is about what happened that night in Iraq and you know it.

27
00:00:42,040 --> 00:00:44,430
埃勒没死  我知道他在哪儿
Eller ain't dead. I know where he's holed up.

28
00:00:45,530 --> 00:00:48,250
回到我们身边  一起奔跑
Come back. Run with us.

29
00:00:48,270 --> 00:00:49,840
抱歉来晚了
Sorry I'm late.

30
00:00:50,480 --> 00:00:51,920
天哪
Oh, God.

31
00:00:52,340 --> 00:00:54,150
我去找了佩特夫妇  把黛比的事告诉他们了
I went to the Pelts, told 'em Debbie was dead.

32
00:00:54,180 --> 00:00:56,200
别的事情都是我瞎编的
Everything else that came out of my mouth was a lie.

33
00:00:56,230 --> 00:00:57,440
我觉得他们信了我
I think they believed me.

34
00:00:57,510 --> 00:00:59,450
我能不能给你倒点喝的
Can I at least offer you something to drink?

35
00:00:59,490 --> 00:01:00,630
我们去庆祝一下吧
What say we celebrate?

36
00:01:00,660 --> 00:01:02,450
我找到了一地方
I found me a place

37
00:01:02,500 --> 00:01:05,220
保证你爽翻天
that is gonna blow your top.

38
00:01:05,250 --> 00:01:07,080
-杰森  -海德莉
- Jason? - Hadley?

39
00:01:07,130 --> 00:01:08,250
苏琪知道你回来了吗
Does Sookie know you're here?

40
00:01:08,270 --> 00:01:09,820
苏琪  我们得去接她
Sookie? We got to go get her.

41
00:01:09,840 --> 00:01:12,820
吸血鬼会杀死她  就跟他们对你父母一样
The vampires will kill her just like they did your parents.

42
00:01:12,870 --> 00:01:15,190
啥  海德莉  你在说什么
What? Hadley, what are you talking about?

43
00:01:17,690 --> 00:01:20,700
正如诺拉所说  还有一个叛徒
It is as Nora said. There is another traitor.

44
00:01:20,750 --> 00:01:22,210
杜鲁法官
Chancellor Drew.

45
00:01:24,290 --> 00:01:25,870
你爱上我了
You're in love with me.

46
00:01:27,900 --> 00:01:29,490
我们继续找罗素吧
Can we go back to looking for Russell now?

47
00:01:29,520 --> 00:01:30,740
苏琪可能有用
Sookie could be useful.

48
00:01:30,820 --> 00:01:32,620
我想她不愿意再跟我们扯上关系了
I don't think she wants anything to do with us again.

49
00:01:32,640 --> 00:01:34,360
谁说要给她选择
I don't think we give her the choice.

50
00:01:46,150 --> 00:01:49,060
-苏琪  -不  别说话
- Sookie. - No, don't talk anymore.

51
00:02:16,890 --> 00:02:19,030
我等了这么久
I've waited so long for this.

52
00:02:19,450 --> 00:02:21,610
埃尔希德
Alcide.

53
00:02:28,400 --> 00:02:32,600
埃尔希德  你还真懂怎么对待女士
Alcide, you sure know how to treat a lady.

54
00:04:10,280 --> 00:04:14,170
不不  我才没跟什么狗屁巫术扯上关系
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I ain't down with this hinky brujo shit.

55
00:04:14,240 --> 00:04:17,350
那次车祸差点儿害死苏琪
Sookie could've died in that car crash.

56
00:04:23,180 --> 00:04:24,800
操你妈
Fuck you!

57
00:04:33,280 --> 00:04:34,490
听我说
Listen up.

58
00:04:35,420 --> 00:04:38,100
我以前从来不是特别虔诚
I ain't never put too much stock

59
00:04:38,170 --> 00:04:41,060
敬奉主  可是如果你真的在
in You, Lord God, but if you up there,

60
00:04:41,130 --> 00:04:44,240
我受够了这些事情
I'm tired of all this bullshit.

61
00:04:44,280 --> 00:04:46,920
-放弃吧  -你已经完蛋了
- Give it up. - You're fucked now.

62
00:04:46,950 --> 00:04:49,360
活着就要遭罪  贱人
Oh, life is suffering, bitch.

63
00:04:52,030 --> 00:04:53,640
我是好人
I'm a good man!

64
00:04:53,710 --> 00:04:57,570
我是做过些烂事
I did some shitty stuff,

65
00:04:57,670 --> 00:04:59,240
可是跟外面那些妖魔鬼怪比起来
but compared to all evil out there,

66
00:04:59,300 --> 00:05:01,870
我就是个好人  比大多数人都好
I'm good enough. Better than most.

67
00:05:01,900 --> 00:05:05,080
所以你们放过我吧
So cut me a break.

68
00:05:15,460 --> 00:05:18,280
约瑟  如果你在
Jesus, if you're out there,

69
00:05:19,490 --> 00:05:21,750
能给我个信儿吗
can you give me a sign?

70
00:05:22,600 --> 00:05:24,740
什么都可以
Anything?

71
00:05:25,810 --> 00:05:27,930
因为我需要帮助
'Cause I need some help.

72
00:05:30,180 --> 00:05:32,820
我真他妈需要帮助
I just need some fucking help.

73
00:05:34,430 --> 00:05:35,930
把他绑好
Tie him up.

74
00:05:38,330 --> 00:05:39,960
走
Let's go.

75
00:05:48,570 --> 00:05:50,710
有没有什么东西跟着你们
Did anything follow you here?

76
00:05:52,320 --> 00:05:53,930
埃勒老兄  就我们俩  你不用担心
Eller, man, it's just us. You got nothing to worry...

77
00:05:53,940 --> 00:05:56,770
有没有什么东西跟着你们
Did anything follow you here?

78
00:05:57,000 --> 00:05:59,730
没有  伙计  就我们自己
No, man. We're alone.

79
00:05:59,780 --> 00:06:01,700
没人跟着我们
Nobody followed us here.

80
00:06:18,290 --> 00:06:21,150
我现在觉着真不该过来这一趟
I'm thinking maybe this was a not-so-great idea.

81
00:06:26,270 --> 00:06:28,240
我当然需要你  鲁道夫
Of course I need you, Rudolph!

82
00:06:28,290 --> 00:06:31,290
真的吗  圣诞老人  给你拉雪橇
Really, Santa? To guide your sleigh?

83
00:06:31,330 --> 00:06:35,600
你有其它麋鹿不具备的能力  来吧
You can do the thing that all the other reindeer can't. Come on!

84
00:06:35,670 --> 00:06:37,590
苏琪宝贝  吃麦片
Sookie, honey? Eat your cereal.

85
00:06:37,660 --> 00:06:39,700
瞧你这一身肥肉
Ooh, you can so pinch an inch.

86
00:06:39,760 --> 00:06:42,360
-这儿  -别闹了  别闹
- Right there. - Hey, stop it. Come on.

87
00:06:42,780 --> 00:06:45,650
小帅哥  过来吃早餐
Hey, champ. Come get some breakfast.

88
00:06:52,800 --> 00:06:54,600
今儿有信心干掉刺魟队吗
You ready to take the Stingrays today?

89
00:06:54,650 --> 00:06:56,010
绝对有  完虐他们
Yeah. We gonna kill 'em.

90
00:06:56,030 --> 00:06:57,920
小孩子玩玩而已  科比特
It's just Pee Wee, Corbett.

91
00:06:57,940 --> 00:06:59,840
那也是比赛
Pee Wee's still ball.

92
00:07:08,670 --> 00:07:11,230
-爸爸  -怎么啦  杰森
- Dad... - What's the matter, Jason?

93
00:07:11,270 --> 00:07:11,780
你...
You...

94
00:07:12,330 --> 00:07:14,410
怎么啦  宝贝
What's the matter, pumpkin?

95
00:07:16,260 --> 00:07:17,700
妈妈
Mom...

96
00:07:17,760 --> 00:07:20,920
-你的脖子  你在流血  -没事  宝贝
- Your neck. You're bleeding! - Oh, there, there, sweetie.

97
00:07:21,220 --> 00:07:22,640
想不想做爱
Do you want a little sex?

98
00:07:22,680 --> 00:07:25,570
做爱总能让你感觉好起来  不是吗
Sex always makes you feel better, doesn't it?

99
00:07:26,000 --> 00:07:28,040
口交也不用吗
Not even a blow job?

100
00:07:36,240 --> 00:07:39,070
喂  谁
Hello? Who?

101
00:07:39,180 --> 00:07:41,060
罗西呀
Hey, Rosie, hey.

102
00:07:41,310 --> 00:07:44,070
那个  现在是哪一年
Listen, what year is it?

103
00:07:44,140 --> 00:07:47,490
哪一年  很好
What year? Good.

104
00:07:47,880 --> 00:07:49,740
没事  很好
No, that's good.

105
00:07:49,930 --> 00:07:51,990
好  我这就来
Yeah, yeah. I'm on my way.

106
00:07:56,720 --> 00:07:58,280
操他娘的精灵
Fucking fairies.

107
00:07:58,350 --> 00:08:00,920
安迪·贝弗勒  你能不能接下电话
Andy Bellefleur, would you answer your phone?

108
00:08:00,980 --> 00:08:03,320
安迪  接电话
Andy, pick it up.

109
00:08:03,370 --> 00:08:05,000
会吵醒孩子的
You're gonna wake the baby.

110
00:08:05,030 --> 00:08:07,510
都响了几千次了
It's only rung about 4,000 times.

111
00:08:07,550 --> 00:08:10,480
-安迪  -我掉在...
- Andy! - I fell in a...

112
00:08:10,530 --> 00:08:12,450
我的天哪  安迪
Cheese and crackers, Andy.

113
00:08:12,500 --> 00:08:15,790
套件衣服好不好  你是疯了吗
Would you put some clothes on? Have you lost your mind?

114
00:08:17,270 --> 00:08:18,970
就不能给人点儿隐私吗
Can a man have some privacy?

115
00:08:19,010 --> 00:08:21,930
快接电话行不行
Would you just pick up the phone?

116
00:08:22,220 --> 00:08:24,060
你看吧
Ya see?

117
00:08:32,080 --> 00:08:33,390
我是贝弗勒
Bellefleur.

118
00:08:35,130 --> 00:08:37,400
对
Uh, yeah.

119
00:08:38,660 --> 00:08:40,570
好  我就来
Okay, I'll be there.

120
00:08:42,100 --> 00:08:44,130
我都不确定这种事有没有可能
I'm not even sure that's possible.

121
00:08:44,220 --> 00:08:46,090
你以前成功过  在泰拉身上
You succeeded before, with Tara.

122
00:08:46,150 --> 00:08:47,840
那是女祭司的法术
That was a maenad spell.

123
00:08:47,880 --> 00:08:51,920
我从没试过破除魅惑效果
I've never tried to un-glamour someone.

124
00:08:53,480 --> 00:08:55,510
你们两个去哪儿了
Where were you guys anyway?

125
00:08:55,600 --> 00:08:57,940
-我们都急死了  -看得出来
- We were worried. - Clearly.

126
00:08:59,980 --> 00:09:03,020
现在唯一能够辨认出释放罗素的黑手
Alcide's employee is the only person who can identify

127
00:09:03,090 --> 00:09:05,220
只有埃尔希德的雇员
whoever it was that freed Russell.

128
00:09:05,260 --> 00:09:07,670
我不想让道格卷进这摊子烂事
I don't want Doug mixed up in this bullshit.

129
00:09:07,720 --> 00:09:09,730
你们尖牙鬼只会带来麻烦和死亡
You fangers bring nothing but trouble and death.

130
00:09:09,760 --> 00:09:11,850
我们做事不用你批准  臭狼
Well, we don't need your permission, wolf.

131
00:09:11,910 --> 00:09:13,600
罗素在地下埋了一年多
Russell has been under the ground for over a year.

132
00:09:13,690 --> 00:09:15,080
需要几天时间休养
It'll take him a few days to recuperate,

133
00:09:15,100 --> 00:09:15,910
一旦他恢复
and then when he does,

134
00:09:15,940 --> 00:09:17,870
会立即来追杀我们
he will be straight out after us on the hunt.

135
00:09:17,880 --> 00:09:20,310
还不是因为你们能干掉他的时候没有动手
'Cause you didn't kill him when you had the chance.

136
00:09:20,330 --> 00:09:21,510
-你说什么  -你听到了
- What did you say? - You heard me.

137
00:09:37,500 --> 00:09:39,780
对不起
I'm sorry.

138
00:09:40,490 --> 00:09:43,630
我一直以为  只要我做出正确选择
I just keep thinking that if I make the right choice,

139
00:09:43,710 --> 00:09:46,990
这些疯狂的事可以了结  生活能恢复正常
all this madness will end and my life will go back to normal.

140
00:09:47,000 --> 00:09:49,150
可根本不会了结  对吧
But it's not gonna end, is it?

141
00:09:49,220 --> 00:09:51,530
就这样了
This is it.

142
00:09:51,560 --> 00:09:53,820
不会有什么改变
It's not gonna change.

143
00:09:53,860 --> 00:09:56,830
我们分了手  然后呢
We say goodbye, and the next thing,

144
00:09:56,920 --> 00:09:58,410
你们又到我家里来了
you guys are back in my house

145
00:09:58,450 --> 00:10:03,450
还有一个三千岁的吸血鬼要吸干我
and a 3,000-year-old vampire wants to suck my blood.

146
00:10:04,510 --> 00:10:06,940
今儿肯定是周四
Must be Thursday!

147
00:10:11,030 --> 00:10:13,110
快点
Well, come on.

148
00:10:13,160 --> 00:10:16,140
你们还等什么呢  赶紧去抓罗素吧
What are y'all waiting for? Let's go hunt Russell.

149
00:10:16,210 --> 00:10:19,270
再向虎山行
Onwards into the jaws of death!

150
00:10:19,350 --> 00:10:21,080
玩个痛快
Boot and rally!

151
00:10:22,370 --> 00:10:24,360
多谢你了  泰拉
Thanks a lot, Tara.

152
00:10:52,640 --> 00:10:54,860
你这样子还算马马虎虎
You actually look halfway decent.

153
00:10:55,060 --> 00:10:56,830
如果我想扮成变装皇后
If I wanted to look like a drag queen,

154
00:10:56,870 --> 00:10:59,780
我就去打劫拉法耶的衣柜了
I would've raided Lafayette's closet.

155
00:11:01,030 --> 00:11:03,940
给  第一班由你负责
Here. You take the first shift.

156
00:11:04,000 --> 00:11:05,460
你要我在吧台干活吗
You want me to bartend?

157
00:11:05,490 --> 00:11:09,030
不  我要你就坐在那儿玩拼字游戏
No, I want you to sit on your ass and play Scrabble.

158
00:11:09,100 --> 00:11:10,370
废话  我就是要你在吧台干活
Yes, I want you to bartend.

159
00:11:10,370 --> 00:11:11,640
范塔西娅酒吧归我管
Fangtasia's mine now

160
00:11:11,660 --> 00:11:14,720
现在人手不足  你就出点力气吧
and we're understaffed. So make yourself useful.

161
00:11:14,740 --> 00:11:16,650
说白了我就是你的奴隶
So, basically, I'm your slave.

162
00:11:16,690 --> 00:11:18,630
差不多吧
Pretty much.

163
00:11:19,220 --> 00:11:20,490
不管事情怎么变
The more things change,

164
00:11:20,540 --> 00:11:23,360
到头来还是一模一样
the more they fucking stay the same.

165
00:11:23,620 --> 00:11:26,050
乖宝贝  给我拿瓶真血  要O型阴性的
Can I get a True Blood, O-neg, sweet thing?

166
00:11:26,350 --> 00:11:29,610
能形容我的词儿多了  但"乖"字就免了
I am many things, but "sweet" ain't one of them.

167
00:11:29,680 --> 00:11:31,230
好吧
All right.

168
00:11:33,160 --> 00:11:35,660
-你好  -你要什么
- Hi. - What can I get you?

169
00:11:35,730 --> 00:11:38,230
你是新来的
You're new here.

170
00:11:38,810 --> 00:11:41,220
那好吧
Oh, okay, well.

171
00:11:41,940 --> 00:11:43,720
那咱们闲话少说
If you wanna skip the small talk--

172
00:11:45,380 --> 00:11:49,280
跟着我念  我永远永远永远
Repeat after me. I will never, ever, ever

173
00:11:49,310 --> 00:11:51,980
都不会在公共场合  众目睽睽之下
fucking feed in public where people can see me

174
00:11:52,060 --> 00:11:54,410
在有可能让人告发的地方吸血
and report me to the goddamn authorities.

175
00:11:54,460 --> 00:11:57,510
-但你先前说过...  -听仔细了
- But you said before-- - Listen close.

176
00:11:57,640 --> 00:11:58,640
是我救了你这条贱命
I saved your fucking life

177
00:11:58,690 --> 00:12:01,180
还借给你几件真正上档次的衣服
and lent you some truly exquisite clothes.

178
00:12:01,260 --> 00:12:04,140
要是你的行为影响了范塔西娅的生意
But if you do anything to mess with Fangtasia,

179
00:12:04,210 --> 00:12:06,560
我就用银链子把你绑在棺材里
I will silver you and stick you in a coffin

180
00:12:06,600 --> 00:12:09,120
由着你烂到下个千禧年
to rot until the next millennium.

181
00:12:09,260 --> 00:12:13,300
听明白了没
Do you understand me?

182
00:12:28,290 --> 00:12:30,520
道格  这是苏琪
Doug, this here's Sookie.

183
00:12:30,580 --> 00:12:32,820
-苏琪  这是道格  -很高兴见到你
- Sookie, this is Doug. - It's real nice to meet you.

184
00:12:32,840 --> 00:12:35,030
找我什么事啊
What can I do for you folks?

185
00:12:36,210 --> 00:12:40,570
你不是特别介意的话  我要读读你的想法
Would you mind terribly if I took a little peek inside your head?

186
00:12:42,870 --> 00:12:44,870
那天晚上的事儿你还记得什么
What do you remember about that night?

187
00:12:44,910 --> 00:12:47,030
什么都不记得  我发誓
Nothing. I swear.

188
00:12:47,750 --> 00:12:50,560
跟往常一样  我在休息
I was taking my break, like always.

189
00:12:51,980 --> 00:12:53,560
有人走向他
Somebody's coming up to him.

190
00:12:53,610 --> 00:12:56,120
-他们长什么样  -很模糊
- What do they look like? - It's blurry.

191
00:12:56,190 --> 00:12:58,320
我看不清楚
I can't make it out.

192
00:13:00,560 --> 00:13:02,260
是个女的
It's a woman.

193
00:13:04,320 --> 00:13:06,730
她徒手挖出了罗素
She's digging Russell up with her hands.

194
00:13:08,030 --> 00:13:11,030
-轻点儿  -见鬼
- Gently. - What the fuck?

195
00:13:11,170 --> 00:13:15,030
这是什么东西  这他妈的是什么东西
What is this? What the fuck is this?

196
00:13:15,110 --> 00:13:16,280
等等
Wait.

197
00:13:16,340 --> 00:13:18,840
她戴有项链
She has a necklace.

198
00:13:18,870 --> 00:13:22,500
那挂件像是蜘蛛或者是...
A pendant, like a spider or...

199
00:13:22,840 --> 00:13:24,550
蝙蝠
a bat?

200
00:13:26,340 --> 00:13:29,160
是一个女性当权者成员放掉了罗素
A female member of the Authority released Russell.

201
00:13:29,240 --> 00:13:31,630
你告诉过诺拉我们活埋了罗素吗
Did you tell Nora that we buried Russell alive?

202
00:13:31,670 --> 00:13:33,650
-没有  -我不相信你
- No. - I don't believe you.

203
00:13:33,670 --> 00:13:35,490
我很遗憾你这么说
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.

204
00:13:35,600 --> 00:13:38,010
-你说你什么事都告诉诺拉  -这事没说
- You said you and Nora share everything. - Not that.

205
00:13:38,040 --> 00:13:38,920
就因为你管不住嘴
You couldn't keep your mouth shut

206
00:13:38,950 --> 00:13:40,590
现在她利用罗素来整我们
and now she's using Russell against us.

207
00:13:40,610 --> 00:13:42,330
胡扯
That's absurd.

208
00:13:42,400 --> 00:13:47,060
诺拉当时冒着生命危险来救我们
Nora risked her life to free me and you, too.

209
00:13:59,610 --> 00:14:03,970
你的宝贝杜鲁法官已经死了
Your boy, Chancellor Drew, is dead.

210
00:14:04,030 --> 00:14:07,000
你把他像羔羊一样送去被宰
You served him up like a lamb to slaughter.

211
00:14:07,030 --> 00:14:09,760
他现在已经是地上的一摊血浆了
Now he's just a pile of guts on the floor.

212
00:14:09,850 --> 00:14:12,660
杜鲁变血浆啦
Drew is goo.

213
00:14:13,390 --> 00:14:15,900
杜鲁变血浆啦
Drew is goo.

214
00:14:16,090 --> 00:14:18,570
我们一定能崛起
We will rise up.

215
00:14:19,440 --> 00:14:22,200
莉莉丝的勇士们必将找到你们
The warriors of Lilith are coming for you.

216
00:14:22,910 --> 00:14:25,470
一个也不放过
Coming for all of you.

217
00:14:29,550 --> 00:14:33,640
你亵渎神灵的日子不长了  罗曼
Your nights of sacrilege are numbered, Roman!

218
00:14:38,390 --> 00:14:40,700
康普顿先生和诺思曼先生那边有消息吗
Any news yet from Mr. Compton and Mr. Northman?

219
00:14:40,820 --> 00:14:42,950
没有  他们还在良辰镇磨蹭
No, they dawdled about Bon Temps,

220
00:14:42,990 --> 00:14:45,270
去一个女服务员的家里转了转
visited the home of a local waitress,

221
00:14:45,330 --> 00:14:47,760
去快易店
went to the Kwik-E-Mart for a

222
00:14:45,330 --> 00:14:47,760
{\an8}快易店  《辛普森一家》中虚构的便利店

223
00:14:47,840 --> 00:14:50,640
买了一大杯咖啡和一盒纳特黄油饼干
jumbo coffee and box of Nutter Butters,

224
00:14:50,820 --> 00:14:55,280
然后坐货车到什里夫波特的一个停车场
then traveled by cube van to a parking facility in Shreveport.

225
00:14:56,730 --> 00:14:59,390
请你通知康普顿先生和诺思曼先生
Please notify Mr. Compton and Mr. Northman

226
00:14:59,470 --> 00:15:02,080
守护者命令他们在日出前
that the Guardian has instructed that they have until dawn

227
00:15:02,150 --> 00:15:05,480
找到罗素·爱丁顿  否则就要他们的命
to find Russell Edgington or they will be terminated.

228
00:15:41,720 --> 00:15:44,620
杜鲁法官是个好人
Chancellor Drew was a great man.

229
00:15:46,370 --> 00:15:48,670
我以为他是好人
I thought he was a great man.

230
00:15:50,670 --> 00:15:54,180
我们一同起草了吸血鬼权利修正案
We drafted the Vampire Rights Amendment together.

231
00:15:58,440 --> 00:16:01,860
他全心全意地为主流化事业付出
He was deeply committed to mainstreaming.

232
00:16:05,600 --> 00:16:07,750
怎么就迷失方向了
How could he lose his way?

233
00:16:09,890 --> 00:16:11,890
我怎么就没发现呢
How could I not see it?

234
00:16:12,160 --> 00:16:15,570
-他耍了我们  守护者  -流了那么多血
- He fooled us all, Guardian. - So much blood.

235
00:16:17,180 --> 00:16:19,350
都是为何
For what?

236
00:16:19,730 --> 00:16:21,160
有些吸血鬼相信
Some vampires believe the

237
00:16:21,190 --> 00:16:23,990
封存在此的就是莉莉丝的血
blood in this urn is the actual blood of Lilith.

238
00:16:24,480 --> 00:16:26,910
他们受到了误导  一如人类
They are just as misguided as the humans

239
00:16:26,940 --> 00:16:29,470
相信圣饼就是
who think that their Communion wafer's

240
00:16:29,510 --> 00:16:31,540
基督的身体
the literal body of Christ.

241
00:16:31,570 --> 00:16:32,760
而我呢
And there I am,

242
00:16:32,850 --> 00:16:36,370
拿着这管液体又唱又跳
doing my little song and dance with the dropper.

243
00:16:36,810 --> 00:16:39,520
仪式罢了  毫无意义
Symbolic ritual, nothing more.

244
00:16:40,320 --> 00:16:42,240
恕我直言  守护者
Forgive me, Guardian.

245
00:16:42,680 --> 00:16:45,540
原教旨派正在不断壮大
But the Sanguinistas are gaining ground.

246
00:16:45,790 --> 00:16:50,000
他们甚至策反了您最亲密的战友
They are recruiting followers even among your closest allies.

247
00:16:50,580 --> 00:16:52,680
是的  没错
Yes, no shit.

248
00:16:54,020 --> 00:16:55,810
两名首席法官
Two of my own chancellors.

249
00:16:55,870 --> 00:16:59,190
绝对不能低估他们
It is a mistake to underestimate them.

250
00:16:59,670 --> 00:17:03,930
-也许您可以  -我绝不迎合那些狂徒
- Perhaps if you-- - I refuse to pander to fanatics.

251
00:17:03,970 --> 00:17:06,450
我不是这个意思
But this is not what I'm suggesting.

252
00:17:06,510 --> 00:17:09,360
只要扔给信徒们一根骨头即可
Just throw the religious base a bone.

253
00:17:10,280 --> 00:17:13,000
按照您的理念
Control the message.

254
00:17:13,310 --> 00:17:15,920
控制讯息
But on your own terms.

255
00:17:20,490 --> 00:17:23,780
没疑问了  纵火的就是埃勒
Well, there's no denying it. Eller's the firebug.

256
00:17:24,170 --> 00:17:25,830
就是他放火烧了凯斯勒和杰佛瑞斯
He's the one who torched Kessler and Jeffries.

257
00:17:25,870 --> 00:17:27,340
你说他在这儿呆了多久
How long do you think he's been out here?

258
00:17:27,390 --> 00:17:29,100
至少也有好几年
Couple years at least.

259
00:17:29,170 --> 00:17:32,400
伙计  他是真的疯了
Man, he has really lost his fucking shit.

260
00:17:33,040 --> 00:17:34,410
我必须这么干
I just gotta do it.

261
00:17:43,880 --> 00:17:45,730
-埃勒  -看在上帝的分上  埃勒
- Eller. - For the love of God, Eller--

262
00:17:45,730 --> 00:17:47,190
也许我杀了你们  它就会宽恕我
Maybe if I kill you, it will forgive me.

263
00:17:47,210 --> 00:17:50,170
-埃勒  你不必这么做  -谁要宽恕你
- Eller, you do not have to do this. - Who needs to forgive you?

264
00:17:52,150 --> 00:17:54,810
-我看到他们被烧  -谁
- I saw them burn. - Who?

265
00:17:54,870 --> 00:17:57,730
凯斯勒  还有他老婆
Kessler-- Him and his wife.

266
00:17:58,030 --> 00:17:59,550
你怎么看到的
How?

267
00:18:06,530 --> 00:18:09,040
我们回来后
After we got back,

268
00:18:09,880 --> 00:18:12,760
有一段时间  我睡他们沙发上
I was crashing on their couch for a while.

269
00:18:13,450 --> 00:18:15,930
然后有天晚上  我醒来
And this one night, I woke up

270
00:18:15,990 --> 00:18:17,930
发现他们的房子着火了
and their house was on fire.

271
00:18:18,050 --> 00:18:20,580
约马卡斯和拉娜被困在过道里
JeMarcus and Lana were trapped down a hall.

272
00:18:20,630 --> 00:18:24,750
我想冲进去救他们  可那火动起来了
I tried to get to them, but the fire moved.

273
00:18:24,780 --> 00:18:26,700
不是普通的大火那么移动
It didn't move like it was supposed to.

274
00:18:26,730 --> 00:18:30,090
普通的大火是从一个地方烧到另一个地方
It didn't burn one thing and move on to the next.

275
00:18:30,140 --> 00:18:32,080
可这火看到他们逃跑
The fire saw them running

276
00:18:32,140 --> 00:18:34,390
就过去堵截他们
and intercepted them.

277
00:18:34,460 --> 00:18:38,290
他们尖叫  然后我看到它了
And they were screaming and then I saw it.

278
00:18:38,380 --> 00:18:40,870
就在火焰中  它看着我
It was in the flames, it was looking at me.

279
00:18:40,910 --> 00:18:42,600
冲我扑来
Coming for me.

280
00:18:43,150 --> 00:18:44,240
于是我跳下窗子
So I jumped out the window

281
00:18:44,270 --> 00:18:47,320
跑啊跑啊  不停地跑
and I ran and ran and just kept running.

282
00:18:50,020 --> 00:18:52,390
我到处去查  还他妈的谷歌了
I looked it up. Fucking Googled it.

283
00:18:52,420 --> 00:18:55,250
终于他妈的搜索到了
Came right up on the goddamn search engine.

284
00:18:58,290 --> 00:19:00,210
它叫伊夫利特
It's called Ifrit.

285
00:18:58,290 --> 00:19:00,210
{\an8}伊夫利特  阿拉伯神话中火属性的魔神

286
00:19:00,760 --> 00:19:02,850
意思是"魔鬼"
It means "The evil."

287
00:19:03,280 --> 00:19:06,080
是烟与火的恶魔
An infernal being of smoke and fire.

288
00:19:07,600 --> 00:19:11,840
-它来杀我们了  -埃勒  伙计
- It's coming for us. - Eller, man,

289
00:19:11,900 --> 00:19:13,440
根本没有什么火怪来杀我们
there's no fire monster coming for us.

290
00:19:13,460 --> 00:19:14,940
不  有的
Yeah, there is.

291
00:19:15,030 --> 00:19:17,880
我们不该那么做  我们不该做那种事
We shouldn't have done it. We shouldn't have done what we did.

292
00:19:17,910 --> 00:19:19,510
-闭嘴  -我们什么也没做
- Shut up. - We didn't do anything.

293
00:19:19,560 --> 00:19:20,730
-她诅咒了我们  伙计  -闭嘴
- She cursed us, man. - Shut up.

294
00:19:20,780 --> 00:19:23,150
她临死的时候诅咒我们
She was dying and she cursed us.

295
00:19:38,180 --> 00:19:39,670
贝弗勒  镇定  该死的
Bellefleur, you stay with me, God damn it.

296
00:19:39,700 --> 00:19:44,360
-我们不该做那种事  -我不想提起来
- Shouldn't have done what we did! - I don't wanna talk about it.

297
00:20:07,420 --> 00:20:09,050
她还活着  中士
She's alive, Sergeant.

298
00:20:19,520 --> 00:20:20,610
结果了她
Dead check her.

299
00:20:20,740 --> 00:20:22,780
什么  不  我们能救他  中士
What? No. We can save her, Sergeant.

300
00:20:22,780 --> 00:20:23,350
我们可以调来...
We can call in a medevac--

301
00:20:23,350 --> 00:20:24,680
我们驻扎在这儿太久
We've been in country too long

302
00:20:24,680 --> 00:20:26,140
这种破事不值得耽搁
to get dragged down by this bullshit.

303
00:20:26,140 --> 00:20:27,920
-听懂了没有  -我们能救她
- Do you understand me? - We can help her.

304
00:20:27,920 --> 00:20:30,180
在这里只有一件事情是重要的
There is only one thing that's important out here.

305
00:20:30,180 --> 00:20:31,840
现在你他妈的告诉我是什么
Now tell me what the fuck that is.

306
00:20:35,100 --> 00:20:36,770
身边的兄弟
The man to your left and the man to your right.

307
00:20:36,770 --> 00:20:39,630
-没错  -现在你他妈的结果了她
- That's right. - Now you fucking dead check her.

308
00:20:49,770 --> 00:20:51,630
{\pos(191,247)}愿伊夫利特烧尽你们

309
00:20:51,770 --> 00:20:54,930
{\pos(191,247)}和你们所爱的一切

310
00:21:10,390 --> 00:21:13,460
干净利落  直接就被干掉了
Plucked off, just like virgins in a whorehouse.

311
00:21:28,930 --> 00:21:29,960
斯塔克豪斯
Stackhouse.

312
00:21:30,770 --> 00:21:33,410
-别发呆了  斯塔克豪斯  -嗯
- Earth to Stackhouse. - Huh?

313
00:21:33,520 --> 00:21:35,570
-过来  -嘿
- Come on. - Hey.

314
00:21:36,310 --> 00:21:37,280
安迪
Andy.

315
00:21:38,190 --> 00:21:42,060
你记得晚上我们是怎么从那俱乐部回来的吗
Do you remember how we got back from the club earlier tonight?

316
00:21:42,600 --> 00:21:43,980
还指望你告诉我呢
I was hoping you could tell me.

317
00:21:44,930 --> 00:21:47,090
我最后就记得那些精灵保镖
The last thing I remember was getting blasted out of there

318
00:21:44,930 --> 00:21:47,090
{\an8}fairy  有男同性恋之意

319
00:21:47,090 --> 00:21:50,640
把我们轰了出来  然后我就光着屁股醒了
by those fairy bouncers. And waking up buck naked.

320
00:21:52,400 --> 00:21:54,010
注意同性恋字眼  斯塔克豪斯
Watch that homo talk, Stackhouse.

321
00:21:54,010 --> 00:21:56,020
为这种鸟事他们都会起诉你
Folks'll sue you for that shit.

322
00:21:56,500 --> 00:21:57,560
不  安迪
No, Andy.

323
00:21:57,560 --> 00:21:59,740
那些家伙  所有的脱衣舞女
Those guys and all those strippers?

324
00:21:59,740 --> 00:22:02,310
他们是精灵  就像《奇妙仙子》里的
They're fairies. Like "Tinker Ball."

325
00:22:02,870 --> 00:22:04,350
超自然生物啊  老兄
They're supes, man.

326
00:22:07,420 --> 00:22:10,250
那些女士都是精灵
Those ladies are fairies?

327
00:22:10,250 --> 00:22:12,550
-是啊  -我上了个精灵
- Yeah. - I fucked a fairy?

328
00:22:12,550 --> 00:22:15,630
如果你真和她们其中一位搞上了的话
Well, if you did it with one of them ladies,

329
00:22:15,630 --> 00:22:17,800
那你就说对了
then, yeah.

330
00:22:19,440 --> 00:22:21,240
喂  怎么了  老兄
Whoa, what is it, man?

331
00:22:22,500 --> 00:22:23,450
去他妈的
Fuck it.

332
00:22:23,490 --> 00:22:25,890
我才不管那些女的是精灵还是矮妖
I don't care if those ladies are fairies or leprechauns

333
00:22:23,490 --> 00:22:25,890
{\an8}矮妖  爱尔兰民间传说中的小妖精

334
00:22:25,890 --> 00:22:27,450
或是见鬼的伊渥克人
or frickin' Ewoks.

335
00:22:25,890 --> 00:22:27,450
{\an8}伊渥克人  星球大战中的外星种族

336
00:22:27,620 --> 00:22:29,820
我跟霍莉的关系刚刚走上正轨
I got a good thing starting up with Holly,

337
00:22:29,820 --> 00:22:32,870
我才不要被玛瑞拉和她那帮惹火的精灵朋友
and I ain't gonna let Maurella and her sexy fairy friends

338
00:22:32,870 --> 00:22:36,230
搅了我的好事  我要彻底避开那地方
mess it up for me. So I'm gonna steer clear of that place.

339
00:22:36,230 --> 00:22:39,480
至于咱俩  这事儿到此为止
And you and me? We ain't gonna talk about it no more.

340
00:22:39,650 --> 00:22:40,750
明白了吗
You get me?

341
00:22:41,620 --> 00:22:43,570
搜索周边
Sweep the perimeter.

342
00:22:44,190 --> 00:22:45,890
我去跟目击证人谈谈
I'm gonna interview our witness.

343
00:22:53,550 --> 00:22:55,600
那些家伙是你朋友吗
These folks friends of yours?

344
00:22:56,140 --> 00:22:58,190
我要问你几个问题
I gotta ask you a few questions.

345
00:22:59,100 --> 00:23:00,110
好的
Yeah.

346
00:23:00,980 --> 00:23:02,400
今晚这里发生什么事情了
What happened here tonight?

347
00:23:03,040 --> 00:23:05,720
我们准备聚在一起吃晚餐
Well, we were getting together for dinner.

348
00:23:06,790 --> 00:23:10,440
我到了之后  发现埃默里和苏珊娜
When I got here, I found Emory and Suzanne

349
00:23:10,440 --> 00:23:13,650
死在了门廊里
on the porch, dead.

350
00:23:14,080 --> 00:23:15,780
你跟死者认识多久了
How long did you know the victims?

351
00:23:17,130 --> 00:23:18,300
一年左右
About a year.

352
00:23:19,360 --> 00:23:22,660
-知道谁想要他们死  -不
- Know anybody who'd want them dead? - No.

353
00:23:23,690 --> 00:23:24,910
不知道  他们都是好人
No, they're good people.

354
00:23:25,830 --> 00:23:27,810
你还知道什么别的事情吗
Is there anything else you wanna tell me?

355
00:23:28,400 --> 00:23:29,870
特别值得注意的
Anything hinky?

356
00:23:32,470 --> 00:23:34,980
那个  我们都是变形人
Well, we're shifters.

357
00:23:37,110 --> 00:23:39,740
-全部都是  -对
- All of you? - Yeah.

358
00:23:39,740 --> 00:23:40,960
我们每过几周就聚在一起
We get together every couple weeks,

359
00:23:40,960 --> 00:23:43,250
变形  在森林中奔跑
we shift, we run in the woods.

360
00:23:46,270 --> 00:23:47,500
你等我一下
Now, hang tight.

361
00:23:47,530 --> 00:23:48,920
我过会儿来找你
I'll come get you in a while.

362
00:24:06,150 --> 00:24:09,020
-你好  -你好
- Hey. - Hey.

363
00:24:10,880 --> 00:24:12,810
给我来杯真血
I'll take a Tru Blood.

364
00:24:12,980 --> 00:24:16,110
双份的O型阴性加一份B型阳性
It's two parts O-neg, one part B-pos.

365
00:24:17,100 --> 00:24:18,110
谢了
Thanks.

366
00:24:22,890 --> 00:24:24,650
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?

367
00:24:28,400 --> 00:24:29,790
跟你换创造者
Trade you makers.

368
00:24:30,700 --> 00:24:32,330
帕姆没那么糟糕啦
Pam is not so bad.

369
00:24:32,710 --> 00:24:34,990
怎么了  没准她愿意让你吸人血呢
What? She'll probably let you feed off of a human.

370
00:24:35,850 --> 00:24:39,670
比尔只让我喝人造血  绝不例外
Bill made me drink nothing but Tru Blood forever.

371
00:24:43,850 --> 00:24:47,410
如果你不乐意  我对你的遭遇感到很抱歉
Hey, I'm sorry this happened to you if you didn't want it to.

372
00:24:47,410 --> 00:24:50,980
其实呢  我知道这有多可怕
It's just, I know how awful and scary...

373
00:24:51,940 --> 00:24:53,570
感觉有多么孤单
and lonely it can be.

374
00:24:54,960 --> 00:24:56,130
但一切都会好的
But it gets better.

375
00:24:56,560 --> 00:24:58,150
是真的
It really does.

376
00:25:00,430 --> 00:25:03,490
我觉得最痛苦的是  没人能够真正了解你
You know, I think the hardest part is that nobody gets you.

377
00:25:03,810 --> 00:25:05,980
像帕姆  埃里克和比尔
Like Pam and Eric and Bill, they're all

378
00:25:05,990 --> 00:25:08,760
都那么老
just so old.

379
00:25:08,760 --> 00:25:12,200
而人类呢  即使他们爱你
And then humans, you know, even if they love you, or--

380
00:25:12,700 --> 00:25:14,240
或者说他们想要爱你
I mean, if they try,

381
00:25:15,100 --> 00:25:16,390
他们也不会真正懂你
no, they don't get it.

382
00:25:18,420 --> 00:25:21,450
我最近已经是孤家寡人了
Been feeling fresh out of friends lately.

383
00:25:22,510 --> 00:25:24,020
你可以跟我在一起啊
You could hang with me.

384
00:25:25,600 --> 00:25:27,420
咱们可以做好朋友
We can be girlfriends.

385
00:25:36,220 --> 00:25:39,110
我现在脑子里都是疯狂的念头
I feel crazy in my head.

386
00:25:39,110 --> 00:25:41,040
我懂  我懂  我刚转化那会儿
Yeah, I know, I know. When I was turned,

387
00:25:41,040 --> 00:25:42,970
脑子里一团乱麻
I didn't understand at all.

388
00:25:42,970 --> 00:25:45,120
亢奋得狠
I had all these impulses,

389
00:25:45,120 --> 00:25:47,390
什么时候都饥渴难耐
and then I was hungry all the time.

390
00:25:47,390 --> 00:25:48,900
我都没办法直视别人
It's like I can't see straight.

391
00:25:48,900 --> 00:25:51,410
周围那些跳动的心脏和...
Like there's all these beating hearts around me and...

392
00:25:52,110 --> 00:25:54,960
我只想把这些人的头拧下来
I just wanna rip these people's fucking heads off

393
00:25:54,960 --> 00:25:56,710
把他们的血喝光光
and just drink out their insides.

394
00:25:56,710 --> 00:26:00,630
就像笼罩在欲望的大雾里
It's like this haze of, I don't know, desire?

395
00:26:00,630 --> 00:26:02,220
别的事情你一概不想
You can't think about anything else.

396
00:26:02,220 --> 00:26:06,130
-很操蛋  -不对  不对
- It's fucked up. - No. No, it's not.

397
00:26:08,330 --> 00:26:10,270
这话不对  听我说
No. No, listen.

398
00:26:10,270 --> 00:26:13,060
我经历了那么多悲伤
I put myself through a lot of grief

399
00:26:13,060 --> 00:26:15,700
老天啊  流了几吨血泪
and, oh, God, a ton of blood tears

400
00:26:15,700 --> 00:26:18,780
才搞明白这种感觉不是坏事
before I realized that these feelings are not bad.

401
00:26:22,580 --> 00:26:23,790
这种感觉很爽
They're awesome.

402
00:26:24,290 --> 00:26:27,280
我是说  至少可以感觉很爽
No, I mean, at least they can be.

403
00:26:28,150 --> 00:26:29,770
无论如何  现在都成了我们的一部分
Either way, they're part of who we are now.

404
00:26:29,770 --> 00:26:33,460
我觉得我已经开始弄明白
And I feel like I am just now starting to figure out

405
00:26:33,460 --> 00:26:36,760
做吸血鬼是个什么概念
what it even means to be a vampire.

406
00:26:39,340 --> 00:26:41,400
你吸过人血吗
Have you fed on a human yet?

407
00:26:43,430 --> 00:26:44,510
感觉如何
How was it?

408
00:26:46,400 --> 00:26:47,630
还不错啦
It was all right.

409
00:26:49,570 --> 00:26:53,360
那就对了  到底有多爽
Yeah, uh, how fucking great is it?

410
00:26:53,360 --> 00:26:55,700
-爽爆了  -比打炮还爽  对吧
- Really fucking great. - Better than sex, right?

411
00:26:55,700 --> 00:26:57,250
确实是
Yeah, actually.

412
00:26:57,550 --> 00:26:58,930
等到...
Just wait--

413
00:27:00,080 --> 00:27:04,490
等到哪天你可以试试一边吸血一边吸精
Wait until you try feeding and fucking at the same time.

414
00:27:06,720 --> 00:27:09,590
不行不行  我对这些完全不在行
No, no, I don't know about all that.

415
00:27:09,590 --> 00:27:10,380
我知道你不行
No, I know.

416
00:27:10,380 --> 00:27:12,610
不过呢  也不是只有吸血和做爱
But it's not just about the feeding and the sex

417
00:27:12,610 --> 00:27:15,180
以及力量  还有...
and the power, but--

418
00:27:16,010 --> 00:27:17,350
我是想说
I mean,

419
00:27:18,820 --> 00:27:22,580
我们会永生不死
we're gonna live forever.

420
00:27:23,860 --> 00:27:26,460
我们将永葆青春
We're gonna be young forever.

421
00:27:27,320 --> 00:27:29,220
这个世界
The world, it's, like,

422
00:27:30,290 --> 00:27:31,770
我们可以尽情探索
wide open to us.

423
00:27:38,240 --> 00:27:39,350
埃尔希德
Alcide?

424
00:27:39,470 --> 00:27:42,310
我们要不要谈谈我吐在你鞋上的事
Are we gonna talk about the fact that I puked on your shoes?

425
00:27:42,310 --> 00:27:43,360
不要
Nope.

426
00:27:44,940 --> 00:27:46,680
这简直乱成一团糟
This is so damn messed up.

427
00:27:46,920 --> 00:27:49,370
我根本不记得有来过这里
I don't remember ever being down this way.

428
00:27:52,240 --> 00:27:53,590
左转往上开
Turn left up ahead.

429
00:28:03,820 --> 00:28:06,410
这一切该不会是诺拉精心安排的吧
What if Nora orchestrated this whole thing?

430
00:28:06,410 --> 00:28:09,370
她假装救我们  其实是想把我们交给罗素
She pretended to save us so she could send us to Russell?

431
00:28:09,370 --> 00:28:10,570
她为什么要这样做
And why would she do that?

432
00:28:10,570 --> 00:28:13,260
罗素可以成为她的强大同盟
Russell could be a powerful ally to her cause.

433
00:28:13,260 --> 00:28:15,260
而且他不可能毫无条件地帮她
Though he'd never agree to do it for free.

434
00:28:15,260 --> 00:28:17,620
若她能把我俩交给罗素
But if she were to serve the two of us up to him,

435
00:28:17,620 --> 00:28:20,060
她就有与罗素谈判的资本了
then she'd be in a position to negotiate with him.

436
00:28:20,060 --> 00:28:21,700
是吗  但她并没有这么做
Yeah, well, that's not what she did.

437
00:28:22,550 --> 00:28:24,180
她本打算把我俩送出国
She tried to get us out of the country.

438
00:28:24,180 --> 00:28:26,230
那只是她的一面之词
Well, that's what she said she was doing.

439
00:28:26,790 --> 00:28:28,070
你太多虑了
You're just being paranoid.

440
00:28:28,070 --> 00:28:30,870
那她为什么还能活着
Then why is she still alive?

441
00:28:30,870 --> 00:28:32,110
我不知道  比尔
I don't know, Bill.

442
00:28:32,480 --> 00:28:35,330
她和她哥哥一样  都是骗子与叛徒
She's a traitor and a liar just like her brother.

443
00:28:36,460 --> 00:28:37,940
把你的话收回去
Take that back.

444
00:28:46,150 --> 00:28:47,620
-你好  -嘿  伙计们
- Hello? - Hey, guys.

445
00:28:47,620 --> 00:28:49,060
我是莫莉  记得吗
It's Molly, remember me?

446
00:28:49,060 --> 00:28:50,330
告诉你们一声
Just giving you a shout-out

447
00:28:50,330 --> 00:28:52,180
你们的倒计时已经开始了
to let you know that your countdown has started.

448
00:28:52,180 --> 00:28:55,090
-什么倒计时  -你们的爱戳
- Our countdown? - Yeah, your iStakes

449
00:28:55,090 --> 00:28:58,170
在黎明时就会激活  很扫兴  对吧
are set to activate at dawn. Bummer, right?

450
00:28:58,170 --> 00:29:00,280
一定是有什么误会吧
There must be some kind of mistake.

451
00:29:00,390 --> 00:29:02,630
没有  我正在启动测试
No, I'm launching a test.

452
00:29:02,630 --> 00:29:04,190
你们的爱戳是不是在闪
Are your iStakes glowing?

453
00:29:07,980 --> 00:29:09,940
-是在闪  -棒极了
- Yeah, they're glowing. - Cool.

454
00:29:09,940 --> 00:29:12,590
这代表设备运作正常  祝你们好运
That means we're good to go. Good luck.

455
00:29:13,020 --> 00:29:14,040
如果你们没能活下来
And if you don't make it,

456
00:29:14,040 --> 00:29:15,620
我很高兴曾经为你们服务
it's been rad serving you.

457
00:29:15,620 --> 00:29:16,870
别了
Peace out.

458
00:29:20,100 --> 00:29:21,470
我们时间不多了
We don't have much time.

459
00:29:57,580 --> 00:29:58,520
他们把罗素送到楼里去了
They took Russell inside.

460
00:29:58,520 --> 00:30:00,700
时间紧迫  我们应该分头行事
We don't have much time. We should split up.

461
00:30:00,700 --> 00:30:03,290
我搜查北侧  你去南侧
I'll take the north wing, and you take the south.

462
00:30:03,290 --> 00:30:04,270
就算用最快的速度
Even at full speed,

463
00:30:04,270 --> 00:30:05,630
要搜的范围还是很大
it's a lot of ground to cover.

464
00:30:06,630 --> 00:30:08,890
苏琪  谢谢你帮我们找到这里
Sookie, we'd like to thank you for getting us this far,

465
00:30:08,900 --> 00:30:10,290
剩下的就留给我跟埃里克吧
but Eric and I will take it from here.

466
00:30:10,290 --> 00:30:12,580
你可以和道格还有埃尔希德留在外面
You can stay outside with Doug and Alcide.

467
00:30:12,580 --> 00:30:14,920
-是啊  -我们没时间去担心你
- Yeah, right. - We don't have time to worry about you.

468
00:30:14,920 --> 00:30:17,280
首先  那些恐怖片告诉我
First of all, I've seen enough horror movies

469
00:30:17,280 --> 00:30:18,280
在又大又阴森的房子里
to know you don't split up

470
00:30:18,280 --> 00:30:19,950
面对一个四处游荡的杀人狂
when you're in a big, scary asylum

471
00:30:19,960 --> 00:30:21,990
大家绝对不能单独行动
and there's a crazed killer on the loose.

472
00:30:21,990 --> 00:30:25,170
再者  我认为这里除了太阳
Second, I think it's fair to say that my microwave fingers

473
00:30:25,170 --> 00:30:26,730
我的微波指是唯一能
and the sun are about the only things around here

474
00:30:26,730 --> 00:30:28,860
伤到罗素的了
that seem to have any effect on Russell,

475
00:30:28,860 --> 00:30:32,130
因此在我看来  是我在保护你们吧
so the way I see it, it's me protecting you from him,

476
00:30:32,130 --> 00:30:33,360
而不是要你俩来担心我
instead of the other way around.

477
00:30:33,360 --> 00:30:35,980
最后  我头很疼
Third, I got a headache

478
00:30:35,990 --> 00:30:37,150
而且正内急
and I gotta pee something fierce,

479
00:30:37,160 --> 00:30:39,290
所以还是快点完事走人吧
so I'd just as soon get this over with.

480
00:30:41,450 --> 00:30:42,530
道格
Doug.

481
00:30:44,550 --> 00:30:46,390
找到一颗木质子弹
We got us a wooden bullet here.

482
00:30:49,620 --> 00:30:50,880
银芯的
Silver core.

483
00:30:51,950 --> 00:30:53,880
木质子弹能杀死变形人吗
Wooden bullets kill shifters?

484
00:30:54,650 --> 00:30:56,780
可以  但一般的子弹就行了
Sure, but so do regular bullets.

485
00:30:57,000 --> 00:30:58,470
但木制子弹能杀吸血鬼
Wooden bullets kill vamps, though.

486
00:30:58,470 --> 00:31:00,230
如果射中心脏的话
If they hit the heart.

487
00:31:00,360 --> 00:31:02,750
也许凶手也在追杀吸血鬼
Maybe the killers are after vamps, too.

488
00:31:02,760 --> 00:31:05,470
或者他们就是不喜欢超自然生物
Or maybe they got a grudge against supes in general.

489
00:31:06,950 --> 00:31:08,710
你们还有什么需要吗
You guys need anything else?

490
00:31:08,710 --> 00:31:10,180
没了  有事再找你
Nah, we'll be in touch.

491
00:31:10,400 --> 00:31:13,520
很遗憾你的朋友出事了
Hey, uh, sorry about your friends, man.

492
00:31:13,520 --> 00:31:14,660
谢谢  杰森
Thanks, Jason.

493
00:31:14,710 --> 00:31:16,980
子弹是从这个方向射出来的
Bullet came from this direction.

494
00:31:17,550 --> 00:31:19,320
你知道哪里出问题了吗
Hey, you know what's fucked up?

495
00:31:19,320 --> 00:31:21,090
哪里都出了问题
I got a pretty long list.

496
00:31:21,980 --> 00:31:24,940
不  这些超自然的烂事
No, all this supernatural shit,

497
00:31:24,940 --> 00:31:26,160
这些凶杀案
these killings.

498
00:31:26,730 --> 00:31:28,950
这几年来没完没了
They've been going on for years.

499
00:31:29,270 --> 00:31:30,720
因为吸血鬼出棺
Us humans just started paying

500
00:31:30,720 --> 00:31:33,460
我们人类才开始注意这些事
attention 'cause the vamps came out of the coffin.

501
00:31:33,750 --> 00:31:35,910
但在那之前
But before that,

502
00:31:35,910 --> 00:31:37,800
这些超自然生物一直在杀人
the supes had been killing people,

503
00:31:37,860 --> 00:31:38,780
而且假装是人为的
making it look all natural,

504
00:31:38,790 --> 00:31:40,760
而我们像白痴一样什么都不知道
and we've been none the fucking wiser.

505
00:31:42,550 --> 00:31:43,970
吸血鬼们
The vampires--

506
00:31:44,940 --> 00:31:47,600
他们总能逃脱罪责
they've been getting away with this shit forever.

507
00:31:48,330 --> 00:31:50,150
看起来像轮胎印
Looks like tire tracks.

508
00:31:53,970 --> 00:31:55,870
百路驰的纹路
BF Goodrich radials.

509
00:31:57,350 --> 00:32:01,340
开枪的人就站在这儿  砰
Shooter stood right here and, boom,

510
00:32:01,740 --> 00:32:04,370
无情地射死了那些可怜的人
shot down those poor people in cold blood.

511
00:32:06,400 --> 00:32:08,000
他们连反抗的机会都没有
They never had a chance.

512
00:32:21,440 --> 00:32:22,600
狼人来过
Wolves have been here.

513
00:32:23,930 --> 00:32:25,280
他们和罗素一起来的
They come with Russell.

514
00:32:43,620 --> 00:32:44,850
我不喜欢这里
I don't like this.

515
00:33:05,070 --> 00:33:07,940
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.

516
00:33:09,130 --> 00:33:12,040
以后提醒我别喝桃味烈酒了
Remind me to avoid peach schnapps in future.

517
00:33:12,870 --> 00:33:14,310
向左转
Turn left.

518
00:33:22,490 --> 00:33:24,350
我从来没去过纽约市
I've never been to New York City.

519
00:33:24,480 --> 00:33:27,760
我只是想说  如果我死了
I'm just saying. If I die,

520
00:33:27,760 --> 00:33:29,740
我永远也没法去纽约了
I will never have made it to the Big Apple.

521
00:33:31,300 --> 00:33:32,990
纽约满是骚臭味
New York City smells like pee

522
00:33:32,990 --> 00:33:34,370
那儿净是蛮子
and the people are rude.

523
00:33:54,270 --> 00:33:55,580
我的天啊
Oh, my God.

524
00:33:57,010 --> 00:33:59,450
没事的  道格  没事
It's okay, Doug. It's okay.

525
00:34:11,100 --> 00:34:13,660
老天哪
Good Lord in heaven.

526
00:34:14,060 --> 00:34:16,870
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.

527
00:34:18,210 --> 00:34:19,810
看来我们来对地方了
Seems like we're in the right place.

528
00:34:54,980 --> 00:34:56,160
霍伊特
Hoyt?

529
00:34:58,870 --> 00:35:01,520
嘿  泰拉
Oh, hey, Tara.

530
00:35:03,450 --> 00:35:04,540
你怎么打扮成这样
What's with the get-up?

531
00:35:04,590 --> 00:35:06,660
-装扮而已  -尖牙控的装扮
- It's the look. - For fangbangers.

532
00:35:06,660 --> 00:35:08,390
我一直以为你不是尖牙控
Never took you for no fangbanger.

533
00:35:08,390 --> 00:35:10,300
我还一直以为你不是吸血鬼呢
I never took you for no vamper.

534
00:35:11,110 --> 00:35:12,520
人是会变的
People change.

535
00:35:25,660 --> 00:35:26,950
你意下如何
Well, what do ya say?

536
00:35:30,610 --> 00:35:32,470
回家找你妈去吧  霍伊特
Go home to your mama, Hoyt.

537
00:35:34,550 --> 00:35:35,510
我怎么了
What the fuck is wrong with me?

538
00:35:37,190 --> 00:35:39,350
你是觉得我的血不够好吗
What, my blood's not good enough for you?

539
00:35:57,500 --> 00:35:58,890
这边
This way.

540
00:36:05,160 --> 00:36:08,280
太平间  真够方便的
The morgue. How convenient.

541
00:36:09,770 --> 00:36:11,010
贝弗勒  嘿
Bellefleur, hey.

542
00:36:11,080 --> 00:36:13,240
醒醒  贝弗勒
Hey, come on, Bellefleur!

543
00:37:03,720 --> 00:37:05,020
我也看到了
I saw it, too.

544
00:37:06,320 --> 00:37:09,430
我看到了伊夫利特
I saw the Ifrit.

545
00:37:16,680 --> 00:37:18,030
你看到了
You saw it?

546
00:37:19,200 --> 00:37:20,690
它在看着我们
It was watching us.

547
00:37:22,300 --> 00:37:25,570
-我没有疯  -我们必须离开这儿
- I'm not crazy? - We've gotta get out of here.

548
00:37:25,700 --> 00:37:28,350
不  这儿很安全
No. We're protected here.

549
00:37:28,900 --> 00:37:30,720
这儿的墙壁是阻燃的
The walls are flame-retardant.

550
00:37:30,720 --> 00:37:33,280
-我安装了喷水系统  -埃勒
- I installed a sprinkler system. - Eller.

551
00:37:33,670 --> 00:37:35,590
我们必须
We've got to get

552
00:37:35,590 --> 00:37:37,930
离开这鬼地方
the fuck out of here.

553
00:37:37,930 --> 00:37:40,060
它等的就是这个机会  我们都聚在一起
This is what it's been waiting for, to get us all together.

554
00:37:40,060 --> 00:37:42,120
我们在这儿是坐以待毙
We are sitting ducks down here.

555
00:37:44,760 --> 00:37:45,820
你说得没错
You're right.

556
00:37:46,210 --> 00:37:47,310
你是对的
You're fucking right.

557
00:38:02,370 --> 00:38:03,630
我有个朋友
I got a friend.

558
00:38:05,940 --> 00:38:07,990
他住在海湾的一个船屋里
He lives on a house boat down on the Gulf.

559
00:38:08,040 --> 00:38:09,280
也许我们可以去那里
Maybe we could go there.

560
00:38:09,280 --> 00:38:10,840
中士  你什么意思
Sergeant, what the fuck?

561
00:38:10,840 --> 00:38:12,410
我真佩服你  你演技太强了
I gotta hand it to you. That performance was fucking brilliant.

562
00:38:12,410 --> 00:38:14,150
不  我是真相信他  他说得没错
No, I did believe him. He was right.

563
00:38:14,150 --> 00:38:15,570
我看到了火中的魔鬼
I saw that monster in the flames.

564
00:38:15,570 --> 00:38:16,260
帮我一把
Help me with him.

565
00:38:16,260 --> 00:38:17,660
不成  中士  我说的都是真的
No way, Sergeant. I meant what I said.

566
00:38:17,660 --> 00:38:18,680
那个女人诅咒了我们
That woman cursed us.

567
00:38:18,680 --> 00:38:20,410
我们必须离开这里  一起走
We gotta get the fuck out of here. All of us.

568
00:38:20,410 --> 00:38:22,750
我受够你们的疯话了
I am sick of you crazy fucks.

569
00:38:22,750 --> 00:38:23,740
现在你要么帮我绑住囚犯
Now you either help me secure the prisoner,

570
00:38:23,740 --> 00:38:25,740
要么就滚出去
or get the fuck out.

571
00:38:30,030 --> 00:38:31,890
该死的  贝弗勒
God damn it, Bellefleur.

572
00:38:47,470 --> 00:38:48,950
我们得帮帮他
We're gonna get him some help.

573
00:38:49,690 --> 00:38:51,960
明天一早  我们把他交给地方政府
Come morning, we'll turn him in to local authorities.

574
00:38:56,350 --> 00:38:57,660
我看到了  中士
I saw it, Sergeant.

575
00:38:58,470 --> 00:39:01,050
伊夫利特
The Ifrit.

576
00:39:01,660 --> 00:39:04,020
我以为是幻觉  但我也看到了
I thought I was hallucinating, but I saw it, too.

577
00:39:04,030 --> 00:39:05,560
我们杀了那些人
We killed those people

578
00:39:06,390 --> 00:39:08,640
人死不能复生  现在我们要付出代价了
and we can't undo it and now we gotta pay.

579
00:39:08,640 --> 00:39:11,770
我们那晚嗑药了  贝弗勒
Hey, we were on drugs that night, Bellefleur.

580
00:39:11,940 --> 00:39:13,550
根本是神志不清
Jacked out of our minds.

581
00:39:13,770 --> 00:39:15,690
你当然会看到幻象
'Course you were seeing things.

582
00:39:16,030 --> 00:39:17,980
但有件事我们必须说清楚
But let's get one thing real clear.

583
00:39:18,710 --> 00:39:21,420
根本没有什么火魔鬼
There is no fucking "Uh-freet."

584
00:39:21,420 --> 00:39:23,970
埃勒只是一个喜欢点火的
Eller is just some poor sick fuck

585
00:39:23,970 --> 00:39:24,840
可怜的变态混蛋
who likes to light fires

586
00:39:24,840 --> 00:39:26,260
因为他没法一个人生活
'cause he can't stand to live with himself.

587
00:39:26,260 --> 00:39:28,210
明白吗
Okay?

588
00:39:29,890 --> 00:39:31,110
明白了  长官
Yes, sir.

589
00:40:27,070 --> 00:40:28,370
约瑟
Jesus!

590
00:40:29,600 --> 00:40:31,370
你这是去哪儿了
Where have you been?

591
00:40:36,690 --> 00:40:38,640
我会告诉他的
Well, I will tell him.

592
00:40:38,790 --> 00:40:40,500
拉法耶
Lafayette!

593
00:40:41,050 --> 00:40:43,990
哇哦  拉法耶
Whoo-hoo! Lafayette!

594
00:41:02,450 --> 00:41:04,790
-我们被盯上了  -我干不了这个
- We're being watched. - I can't do this.

595
00:41:04,790 --> 00:41:07,930
对不起  我的天啊
I'm sorry. Holy shitcakes.

596
00:41:07,930 --> 00:41:09,410
我真的很抱歉
I'm so fucking sorry,

597
00:41:09,410 --> 00:41:11,050
但这也太疯狂了
but this is crazy.

598
00:41:11,520 --> 00:41:12,550
道格
Doug!

599
00:41:14,520 --> 00:41:15,580
道格
Doug!

600
00:41:28,360 --> 00:41:30,600
求你们救救我  别抓我走
Please help me. Don't take me.

601
00:41:30,600 --> 00:41:31,820
还没有轮到我
It's not my turn.

602
00:41:31,820 --> 00:41:32,630
我太瘦了
I'm too skinny.

603
00:41:32,630 --> 00:41:35,150
我靠阿特金斯减肥法瘦了四十磅
I was on Atkins and I lost 40 pounds.

604
00:41:32,630 --> 00:41:35,150
{\an8}阿特金斯减肥法  是一种低碳饮食减肥法

605
00:41:35,150 --> 00:41:37,160
抓别人吧  拜托  求你们了
Take the others, please. Please.

606
00:41:37,810 --> 00:41:39,370
胖子们优先
Fatties first.

607
00:41:39,750 --> 00:41:41,140
他们把犯人抓到哪里去了
Where do they take the prisoners?

608
00:41:41,140 --> 00:41:42,320
走廊那边
Down the hallway.

609
00:41:42,320 --> 00:41:45,030
开始有尖叫声  然后就安静了
There's screaming and then there's not.

610
00:41:45,030 --> 00:41:47,120
我不要过去  我要呆在这里
I'm not going. I'm staying here.

611
00:41:47,450 --> 00:41:49,150
求你们把我放下来
Please get me down from here.

612
00:41:49,150 --> 00:41:51,660
-我有钱  我可以给你们钱  -嘘
- I've got money. I can pay you. - Shh!

613
00:41:54,770 --> 00:41:56,800
不  不要
No, no.

614
00:41:58,790 --> 00:42:00,020
准备好了吗
You ready?

615
00:42:03,580 --> 00:42:05,710
回来  别把我留在这里
Come back! Don't leave me here!

616
00:42:07,180 --> 00:42:08,290
求你们了
Please!

617
00:42:14,180 --> 00:42:16,830
-我打过电话...  -山姆  抱歉
- I tried calling-- - Sam, I'm sorry.

618
00:42:16,830 --> 00:42:18,670
-现在不是时候  -卢娜
- But this is a bad time, okay? - Luna...

619
00:42:18,670 --> 00:42:20,580
苏珊娜和埃默里死了
Suzanne and Emory, they're dead.

620
00:42:21,250 --> 00:42:22,810
晚上遭人枪杀了
They were shot tonight.

621
00:42:31,000 --> 00:42:34,970
你知道有什么人想伤害他们吗
Do you know anybody who would want to hurt them?

622
00:42:36,020 --> 00:42:37,200
不知道
No.

623
00:42:39,180 --> 00:42:41,140
他们都是很好的人
They're wonderful people.

624
00:42:44,230 --> 00:42:45,520
谁会...
Who could've--

625
00:42:46,430 --> 00:42:48,180
宝贝
Baby.

626
00:42:49,920 --> 00:42:52,890
听我说  我希望能留下来陪你
Hey, listen. I wanna know how I can be here for you.

627
00:42:54,810 --> 00:42:55,910
谢谢
Thank you.

628
00:42:56,260 --> 00:42:58,230
我知道我们俩先前有点问题...
I know things have been hard between us--

629
00:43:01,000 --> 00:43:03,420
-什么声音  -没什么  是艾玛
- What was that? - Nothing. It's Emma.

630
00:43:03,930 --> 00:43:06,560
她最近不怎么睡得好
She's been having trouble sleeping lately.

631
00:43:10,080 --> 00:43:11,350
天啊
Oh, God.

632
00:43:11,880 --> 00:43:13,070
山姆
Sam...

633
00:43:14,210 --> 00:43:18,340
对不起  你还是走吧
I'm sorry, but you should probably go.

634
00:43:20,750 --> 00:43:22,400
-好的  -好
- Okay. - Okay.

635
00:43:28,550 --> 00:43:30,470
我明早再过来看你
I'm gonna come check on you tomorrow.

636
00:43:30,720 --> 00:43:32,240
-好  -好
- Okay. - Okay.

637
00:43:32,370 --> 00:43:33,320
过来
Come here.

638
00:43:41,600 --> 00:43:42,470
好了
Okay.

639
00:43:57,440 --> 00:43:59,700
嘿  变形人
Hey, shifter! Whoo!

640
00:44:00,010 --> 00:44:01,020
打中了
Got him!

641
00:44:02,610 --> 00:44:05,090
死变形人才是好变形人
The only good shifter is a dead shifter.

642
00:44:06,640 --> 00:44:09,570
-山姆  -卢娜  不要
- Sam! - Luna, no!

643
00:44:23,490 --> 00:44:25,440
天啊  卢娜
Oh, my God, Luna.

644
00:44:25,440 --> 00:44:28,530
-妈妈  -艾玛  快跑
- Mommy! - Emma, run!

645
00:44:29,130 --> 00:44:31,240
别放跑那个
Get the shifter!

646
00:44:34,220 --> 00:44:35,360
跑
Run!

647
00:44:38,160 --> 00:44:40,370
我们当中有叛徒
There are traitors in our midst.

648
00:44:43,520 --> 00:44:45,730
他们企图摧毁
Those who seek to tear down

649
00:44:45,730 --> 00:44:47,640
我们共同构筑的一切
all that we have built together.

650
00:44:47,640 --> 00:44:50,670
如今身为守护者  我不仅要兼顾执政
Now, as Guardian, I am tasked with not only our political future,

651
00:44:50,670 --> 00:44:52,380
还肩负各地血族
but the spiritual salvation

652
00:44:52,380 --> 00:44:54,930
精神救赎的重任
of vampires everywhere.

653
00:44:56,040 --> 00:44:58,000
我们面临的问题是
The question before us is:

654
00:44:58,000 --> 00:45:01,650
我们是否愿意共享这个世界
are we willing to share this world?

655
00:45:02,630 --> 00:45:06,170
身为血族  我们对人类犯过重罪
As vampires, we have committed crimes against humanity,

656
00:45:06,170 --> 00:45:07,470
{\an8}米歇尔·特纳·斯塔克豪斯之墓

657
00:45:06,180 --> 00:45:09,720
如今我们必须赎罪
crimes for which we must now atone.

658
00:45:10,220 --> 00:45:12,870
原教旨派想让时光倒流
The Sanguinistas want to turn the clock backwards,

659
00:45:10,520 --> 00:45:13,020
{\an8}科比特·詹姆斯·斯塔克豪斯之墓

660
00:45:12,870 --> 00:45:15,690
渴望肆无忌惮地屠杀
want to murder with impunity.

661
00:45:16,660 --> 00:45:19,690
他们只把人类当成食物
They think of humans as nothing but sustenance.

662
00:45:20,670 --> 00:45:22,760
选择权在我们手上
So the choice is ours.

663
00:45:23,620 --> 00:45:25,410
我们是要回到
Do we to return to a time

664
00:45:25,410 --> 00:45:27,220
潜行于黑暗
where we skulked in the dark

665
00:45:27,230 --> 00:45:29,620
躲躲藏藏的时代
hiding in the shadows?

666
00:45:29,620 --> 00:45:32,340
还是要
Or are we willing

667
00:45:32,340 --> 00:45:34,810
将莉莉丝的许诺
to extend the promise of Lilith

668
00:45:34,810 --> 00:45:37,450
以及最慷慨的仁慈  遍洒人间
and the bountiful mercy to all of humanity?

669
00:45:38,490 --> 00:45:39,940
一起
And live...

670
00:45:40,150 --> 00:45:41,730
平等生活
as equals?

671
00:45:42,820 --> 00:45:45,740
原旨教派指责我们违背天性
The Sanguinistas say we are going against our nature,

672
00:45:45,740 --> 00:45:48,610
莉莉丝命令我们捕食人类
that Lilith commands us to feed.

673
00:45:50,320 --> 00:45:52,410
置身食物链之顶端
The pinnacle of the food chain.

674
00:45:52,410 --> 00:45:55,680
-泰拉  求你了  -但是他们错了
- Tara, please. Please. - But they are wrong.

675
00:45:56,300 --> 00:45:59,370
-放开他  -如果我们任由罪恶滋生...
- Get off of him. - For if we let our sins flourish...

676
00:45:59,370 --> 00:46:00,850
关你屁事
What the fuck's your problem?

677
00:46:01,390 --> 00:46:04,270
如果我们臣服于嗜血欲望
...if we are slaves to our blood lust,

678
00:46:04,850 --> 00:46:07,780
如果我们任由饥渴
if we let our hunger for power surpass

679
00:46:07,780 --> 00:46:09,960
凌驾于尊严之上
our common decency,

680
00:46:10,110 --> 00:46:12,520
我们的灵魂必万劫不复
we doom our souls to damnation.

681
00:46:13,640 --> 00:46:15,410
我郑重声明
So let it be known...

682
00:46:17,360 --> 00:46:19,550
我们绝不能就此放弃
we will not cede the floor to the depraved

683
00:46:19,550 --> 00:46:22,260
任由疯子与狂徒残暴统治
and desperate tyranny of madmen and fanatics.

684
00:46:22,260 --> 00:46:24,350
我们绝不袖手旁观
We will not stand by

685
00:46:24,350 --> 00:46:26,280
任由狂热的暴徒
while zealots hijack

686
00:46:26,280 --> 00:46:28,720
践踏我们的大业
the righteousness of our cause.

687
00:46:28,720 --> 00:46:31,250
我们必将抗争
We will fight.

688
00:46:33,040 --> 00:46:36,910
让夜晚净化我们的罪孽  引导我们走向胜利
And let the night cleanse us of our sins and lead us to victory.

689
00:46:42,790 --> 00:46:45,320
你们太慢了
Took you long enough.

690
00:46:45,650 --> 00:46:47,870
你们这帮人
What an infernal racket

691
00:46:47,870 --> 00:46:49,700
弄出来的动静太大了
you people have been making.

692
00:46:55,420 --> 00:46:57,590
斯塔克豪斯小姐
Miss Stackhouse.

693
00:46:57,600 --> 00:46:59,810
看到你就高兴
Always a pleasure.

694
00:47:00,670 --> 00:47:02,740
我何以言谢呢
To what do I owe?

695
00:47:02,750 --> 00:47:05,460
去你妈的  你这该死的疯子
Fuck you, you psychotic piece of shit.

696
00:47:09,140 --> 00:47:10,790
你好啊  老朋友
Hello, old friend.

697
00:47:15,140 --> 00:47:16,740
记得我吗
Do you remember me?

698
00:47:18,460 --> 00:47:20,750
我们来结束这场闹剧了
We've come to finish what we started.

699
00:47:21,580 --> 00:47:22,750
是吗
Well...

700
00:47:23,030 --> 00:47:25,520
正如我最爱的托博
as my great love Talbot used to say

701
00:47:25,520 --> 00:47:28,580
在猎鹿时爱说的那句话
when we were buck hunting,

702
00:47:30,390 --> 00:47:32,350
你要使出全力啊
give it your best shot.

