1
00:03:39,200 --> 00:03:49,000
{\pos(190,278)}本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

3
00:03:49,000 --> 00:03:54,000
{\pos(190,268)}翻译：Silmar  NoNopig  Eve  Greentie  泰斯

5
00:03:54,000 --> 00:03:59,000
{\pos(190,268)}翻译：haoyang112   时间轴：崽猪  烟幕迟迟

7
00:03:59,000 --> 00:04:04,000
{\pos(190,268)}后期： 孤帆   校对&总监： 泰斯·雪诺

9
00:05:04,000 --> 00:05:09,000
《真爱如血》第五季  第十一集
True Blood S05E11

10
00:00:00,100 --> 00:00:01,520
[前情提要]

11
00:00:01,520 --> 00:00:04,460
你要是一直不接受莉莉丝  你很快就没命了
The true death will come very soon if you do not accept Lilith.

12
00:00:04,460 --> 00:00:06,300
莉莉丝是邪恶的神
Lilith is a godless god.

13
00:00:06,300 --> 00:00:08,820
她会带领你和你周围所有的人走向毁灭
She will lead you and all around you to destruction.

14
00:00:08,820 --> 00:00:11,120
-阿拉斯加  -下周过去
- Alaska? - I'll be there next week.

15
00:00:11,120 --> 00:00:14,170
我想要你魅惑我  让我忘了你
I want you to glamour me. Make me forget about you.

16
00:00:14,170 --> 00:00:17,010
-我要他也消失  -再见了  霍伊特
- I want him gone, too. - Goodbye, Hoyt.

17
00:00:17,110 --> 00:00:19,380
今晚路易斯安那州新奥尔良市
Tonight, live from New Orleans, Louisiana,

18
00:00:19,380 --> 00:00:20,890
直播史蒂夫·纽林牧师
Reverend Steve Newlin.

19
00:00:20,990 --> 00:00:23,210
他就在本州  我们必须出发了
He's in the state. We have to go.

20
00:00:22,210 --> 00:00:23,210
{\an8}史蒂夫·纽林更衣室

21
00:00:23,400 --> 00:00:24,940
可能把她留在哪里了
He probably left for somewhere.

22
00:00:24,940 --> 00:00:29,070
你知道爸爸不喜欢你人类的样子
You know that Daddy doesn't like it when you're human.

23
00:00:29,070 --> 00:00:31,390
那你想怎样  让以利亚拿走一切
So what, then? You let Elijah take everything from you?

24
00:00:31,390 --> 00:00:34,360
你和我就风餐露宿  跟我以前和埃里克一样
We live in the wind just like I did with Eric.

25
00:00:36,560 --> 00:00:37,900
我们不会逃走
We're not running.

26
00:00:37,900 --> 00:00:40,530
我没当上首领  我被放逐了
I lost Packmaster. I've been abjured.

27
00:00:41,760 --> 00:00:44,920
那你现在是独狼了  跟你老头一样
You're a lone wolf now, just like your old man.

28
00:00:44,920 --> 00:00:48,080
莉莉丝找到了我  她摧毁了我的创造者
Lilith came to me and she destroyed my maker

29
00:00:48,080 --> 00:00:50,090
那个我曾经当作伪神一样崇拜的人
whom I was worshipping as a false god.

30
00:00:50,090 --> 00:00:51,680
我们是莉莉丝的孩子
We are the children of Lilith.

31
00:00:51,690 --> 00:00:53,840
你会发现自己和我
You'll see that you and I

32
00:00:53,840 --> 00:00:56,300
必须领导我们血族迎接新纪元
were meant to lead our kind into the coming age.

33
00:00:56,300 --> 00:00:57,930
什么新纪元
What coming age?

34
00:00:57,930 --> 00:01:01,970
精灵的血能让我们拥有日行能力
The blood of the fae allows us to daywalk.

35
00:01:01,970 --> 00:01:04,370
我们是夜晚的种族
We are of the night.

36
00:01:04,370 --> 00:01:06,980
我可以再把你埋进去
I can put you back in the ground.

37
00:01:08,440 --> 00:01:09,580
随你们信仰莉莉丝吧
You can have your Lilith.

38
00:01:09,580 --> 00:01:13,240
我要拥有太阳
I will have the sun!

39
00:01:14,140 --> 00:01:15,400
你们从哪儿弄来的
Where did you get this?

40
00:01:15,400 --> 00:01:17,730
我奶奶家的地板下面
Underneath the floorboards in my gran's house.

41
00:01:17,730 --> 00:01:18,910
这是合同
It's a contract

42
00:01:18,910 --> 00:01:22,060
"我  约翰·威廉·斯塔克豪斯
"I, John William Stackhouse

43
00:01:22,060 --> 00:01:24,250
赠予M·沃罗先生
grant Mr. M. Warlow

44
00:01:24,250 --> 00:01:27,290
我的第一位女性精灵继承人"
my first fae-bearing female heir."

45
00:01:27,290 --> 00:01:28,260
苏琪
Sookie.

46
00:01:40,480 --> 00:01:44,470
比尔·康普顿
Bill Compton.

47
00:01:57,280 --> 00:02:01,940
比尔·康普顿
Bill Compton.

48
00:02:07,820 --> 00:02:09,540
比尔
Bill...

49
00:02:12,090 --> 00:02:13,640
康普顿
Compton.

50
00:02:40,310 --> 00:02:42,220
我们只能有一个领袖
Only one can lead us.

51
00:02:42,600 --> 00:02:44,560
我选择你
I choose you.

52
00:02:56,640 --> 00:02:58,310
喝了那血
Drink the blood.

53
00:02:58,780 --> 00:03:00,280
通通喝掉
Drink it all.

54
00:03:09,940 --> 00:03:10,940
不
No.

55
00:03:13,180 --> 00:03:14,280
不
No.

56
00:05:13,390 --> 00:05:15,330
莉莉丝是邪恶的神
Lilith is a godless god.

57
00:05:16,070 --> 00:05:18,610
她会带领你和你周围所有的人走向毁灭
She will lead you and all around you to destruction.

58
00:05:18,610 --> 00:05:21,610
不停杀戮  你将一无所有
If you kill and kill, there will be nothing left,

59
00:05:21,620 --> 00:05:23,080
连自我也失去
not even you.

60
00:05:23,580 --> 00:05:25,880
-不  -父亲
- No! - Father!

61
00:05:26,830 --> 00:05:29,030
卡瓦诺将军来了
General Cavanaugh is coming.

62
00:05:30,140 --> 00:05:31,090
诺拉
Nora?

63
00:05:31,720 --> 00:05:32,570
什么
Yes?

64
00:05:32,580 --> 00:05:35,900
我们收到通知  卡瓦诺将军来访
We've received word that General Cavanaugh will be paying us a visit.

65
00:05:36,430 --> 00:05:38,540
-抱歉  -你没事吧
- Sorry. - Are you all right?

66
00:05:38,570 --> 00:05:40,380
我没事
Yes, I'm fine.

67
00:05:40,680 --> 00:05:44,100
有什么不一样了  你变了
Something's different. You've changed.

68
00:05:45,480 --> 00:05:48,120
-你有疑虑吗  -不  当然没有
- Are you having doubts? - No. No, of course not.

69
00:05:49,190 --> 00:05:50,770
我担心罗素
I'm worried about Russell.

70
00:05:50,920 --> 00:05:53,680
他的冒进会毁掉我们辛苦取得的成果
His recklessness could destroy everything we've worked for.

71
00:05:53,680 --> 00:05:55,560
罗素无关紧要
Russell's inconsequential.

72
00:05:55,910 --> 00:05:57,020
他什么也不是
He's nothing.

73
00:05:57,930 --> 00:05:59,910
一切都在莉莉丝伟大的规划之中
This is all part of Lilith's plan.

74
00:05:59,910 --> 00:06:01,890
这是当然
Yes, of course.

75
00:06:01,960 --> 00:06:04,260
你与我  我们一同开创了新的局面
We started this together, you and I.

76
00:06:04,950 --> 00:06:08,690
现在我们梦想中的一切都将实现
And now everything we've dreamed of is coming to pass.

77
00:06:10,170 --> 00:06:12,910
-世界将溢满鲜血  -是的
- The world will run with blood. - Yes.

78
00:06:13,600 --> 00:06:17,210
我们会在血海中痛饮
And we'll be there to drink it down.

79
00:06:17,440 --> 00:06:19,690
在黑暗中欢庆
And in the darkness we shall rejoice.

80
00:06:33,140 --> 00:06:36,160
-我去通知其他人  -好  去吧
- I'll let the others know. - Yeah. Go.

81
00:06:50,720 --> 00:06:51,690
杰西卡
Jessica.

82
00:06:52,760 --> 00:06:56,100
比尔  我在想  能不能用一下你的电话
Hey, Bill. I was wondering if I could use your phone.

83
00:06:56,100 --> 00:06:58,490
-我的手机在这儿没信号  -你要做什么
- Mine doesn't work down here. - For what purpose?

84
00:07:00,070 --> 00:07:01,770
我必须提醒杰森
I've got to warn Jason.

85
00:07:02,270 --> 00:07:04,190
你不在的时候  史蒂夫·纽林两次攻击他
When you were gone, I had to stop Steve Newlin

86
00:07:04,190 --> 00:07:05,580
幸好我阻止了
from attacking him twice.

87
00:07:05,580 --> 00:07:08,740
现在纽林跟罗素跑了出去
And now that Russell and him are on the loose,

88
00:07:09,710 --> 00:07:11,220
我很担心他会再去找杰森
I'm really afraid he's gonna do it again.

89
00:07:11,230 --> 00:07:13,480
-能用一下吗  -抱歉  不行
- So can I use it? - I'm sorry, but no.

90
00:07:15,070 --> 00:07:16,000
不行
No?

91
00:07:16,940 --> 00:07:19,400
可是杰森还在外面  坐以待毙
But Jason is out there. He's a sitting duck.

92
00:07:20,180 --> 00:07:21,590
还有苏琪
Sookie, too.

93
00:07:21,630 --> 00:07:26,230
杰西卡  我自己也经历了很长时间的挣扎
Jessica, it has taken me a long while to come to terms with the fact that

94
00:07:26,230 --> 00:07:29,710
才明白要真正接受莉莉丝的教义
part of accepting the word of Lilith into my heart

95
00:07:29,710 --> 00:07:33,780
就必须使自己远离人类的琐事
has been distancing myself from the trivial matters of humans.

96
00:07:33,810 --> 00:07:35,370
这些事情曾令我疯狂
It used to drive me crazy

97
00:07:35,770 --> 00:07:40,130
担心他们的感受  他们的短命和脆弱
worrying about their feelings and their mortality and their weakness

98
00:07:40,390 --> 00:07:43,000
直到我发现了正道
until I found a better way--

99
00:07:43,990 --> 00:07:45,360
莉莉丝之道
Lilith's way.

100
00:07:45,360 --> 00:07:47,900
杰森  苏琪和良辰镇的居民
And Jason and Sookie and the inhabitants of Bon Temps

101
00:07:47,900 --> 00:07:49,760
都不必再关心
are no longer our concern.

102
00:07:49,760 --> 00:07:52,320
他们只是食物  仅此而已
They are food and nothing more.

103
00:07:52,350 --> 00:07:53,760
你不是认真的
You can't mean that.

104
00:07:53,860 --> 00:07:56,640
总有一天你会明白
You will see in time.

105
00:07:57,380 --> 00:08:00,840
很遗憾  我还有其它事情要处理
Now, I'm sorry, but I have other matters that I have to attend to.

106
00:08:02,740 --> 00:08:05,130
要是我把他变成吸血鬼呢
But what if I made him a vampire?

107
00:08:07,330 --> 00:08:08,770
你要成为创造者
You want to be a maker?

108
00:08:09,540 --> 00:08:10,660
我
I was--

109
00:08:11,740 --> 00:08:13,040
我读了莉莉丝的书
I was reading the Book of Lilith

110
00:08:13,050 --> 00:08:15,140
上面说你能给予一个人类
and it says that the greatest gift

111
00:08:15,140 --> 00:08:17,930
最好的礼物  就是把他变成吸血鬼
you can give a human is to make them a vampire.

112
00:08:18,630 --> 00:08:19,960
的确如此
That is true.

113
00:08:20,150 --> 00:08:22,700
我觉得很有道理  因为我爱杰森
Well, that makes sense to me because I love Jason,

114
00:08:22,700 --> 00:08:24,290
可我们总是走不到一起
but it never seems to work out with him.

115
00:08:24,290 --> 00:08:28,510
我想或许就是因为他是人类而我是吸血鬼
And I was thinking that's probably because he's a human and I'm a vampire.

116
00:08:29,280 --> 00:08:32,320
把他变成吸血鬼  我们就可以在一起了
But if I made him a vampire, then we can be together.

117
00:08:33,890 --> 00:08:36,520
受到莉莉丝祝福
You know, blessed by Lilith.

118
00:08:39,010 --> 00:08:40,920
你以为我是白痴吗
Do you think I'm an idiot?

119
00:08:41,920 --> 00:08:43,010
什么
What?

120
00:08:43,140 --> 00:08:45,480
你真打算站在我面前
Are you really gonna stand there and try

121
00:08:45,480 --> 00:08:48,750
用这愚蠢的谎言愚弄我
and manipulate me with your foolish lies?

122
00:08:50,260 --> 00:08:52,090
-我没有  -是我
- I'm not. - Yes.

123
00:08:52,750 --> 00:08:54,890
请派冈瑞和兰伯特进来
Please, can you send in Gondry and Lambert?

124
00:08:55,860 --> 00:08:56,720
你要做什么
What are you doing?

125
00:08:56,720 --> 00:08:58,600
我要让你慷慨的建议成真
I'm taking you up on your generous offer.

126
00:08:59,310 --> 00:09:02,300
如果你想把杰森·斯塔克豪斯变成吸血鬼
If you want to make Jason Stackhouse into a vampire,

127
00:09:02,300 --> 00:09:04,010
那么就付诸行动
then by all means, please do so.

128
00:09:04,020 --> 00:09:05,520
不  比尔  我没有要愚弄你
No, Bill, I wasn't trying to manipulate you.

129
00:09:05,520 --> 00:09:07,820
不不  你是对的
No, no, no. You're right.

130
00:09:07,980 --> 00:09:09,470
可预见的将来
In the time to come,

131
00:09:10,310 --> 00:09:13,890
加强康普顿这支血脉或许是很重要的
it may be important for me to bolster the Compton bloodline.

132
00:09:13,900 --> 00:09:15,590
何不现在就开始呢
So why not start right now?

133
00:09:15,650 --> 00:09:18,330
如你刚才所言  我身为法官
As you rightly said, as chancellor,

134
00:09:18,330 --> 00:09:21,430
指令其他吸血鬼成为创造者
it would be hypocritical of me to demand that vampires become makers

135
00:09:21,430 --> 00:09:25,230
对你却没有要求  未免言行不一
without requiring the same thing of you.

136
00:09:25,230 --> 00:09:27,100
-等等  比尔  -冈瑞
- Wait, Bill. - Gondry.

137
00:09:27,630 --> 00:09:29,690
这是我的后裔杰西卡
This is my progeny Jessica.

138
00:09:29,810 --> 00:09:31,260
你们带她去良辰镇
I want you to take her to Bon Temps

139
00:09:31,260 --> 00:09:34,640
她要转化一个名叫杰森·斯塔克豪斯的年轻人
where she is gonna sire a young man named Jason Stackhouse.

140
00:09:34,640 --> 00:09:37,480
坐直升机去  一定要做好
Take the helicopter. I want this thing done properly.

141
00:09:37,480 --> 00:09:38,880
不  不需要的  比尔
No, I don't need to, Bill.

142
00:09:38,880 --> 00:09:39,980
别让她离开你们的视线
Don't let her out of your sight.

143
00:11:22,680 --> 00:11:25,470
原谅我  原谅我
Forgive me. Forgive me. Forgive me. Forgive me.

144
00:11:30,030 --> 00:11:31,470
我们怎么办
What are we going to do?

145
00:11:34,370 --> 00:11:35,710
我们离开这儿
I'll get us out of here.

146
00:11:42,050 --> 00:11:43,270
你会没事吧
You gonna be okay?

147
00:11:44,090 --> 00:11:49,030
发现自己三百年前被卖给吸血鬼确实古怪
Kinda strange to find out you were sold to a vampire 300 years ago.

148
00:11:49,030 --> 00:11:51,500
那卷轴就是狗屎
Hey, that scroll thing is bullshit.

149
00:11:51,500 --> 00:11:54,310
我不管上面写了什么  谁也不能卖了你
I don't care what it says, ain't nobody selling you.

150
00:11:54,310 --> 00:11:55,780
有我在就不行
Not on my watch.

151
00:11:56,830 --> 00:11:58,550
我想他找过我
I think he came for me.

152
00:11:59,560 --> 00:12:00,270
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?

153
00:12:00,270 --> 00:12:02,360
只是他不是吸血鬼
Except he wasn't a vampire.

154
00:12:02,430 --> 00:12:05,360
他是古怪的气体状态
He was this weird air shape.

155
00:12:06,140 --> 00:12:08,190
说"你属于我"
He said, "You are mine."

156
00:12:10,500 --> 00:12:11,580
这可
Well, that is...

157
00:12:12,270 --> 00:12:13,810
够他妈吓人的
really fucking creepy.

158
00:12:16,030 --> 00:12:19,450
玛瑞拉说去找长老谈谈
Maurella, she said talking to this Elder person,

159
00:12:19,920 --> 00:12:21,550
或许会有答案
that could give us some answers.

160
00:12:21,550 --> 00:12:23,100
她说值得一试
She said it's worth a shot.

161
00:12:25,730 --> 00:12:27,650
苏克  过来
Oh, Sook. Come here.

162
00:12:31,110 --> 00:12:32,240
我得走了
I've got to go.

163
00:12:32,540 --> 00:12:35,670
吸血鬼袭击事件太多  安迪要我们三班倒
Andy's got us doing triple shifts with all these vamp attacks.

164
00:12:35,920 --> 00:12:38,320
我明天回来看你
I'll come back tomorrow and check up on you.

165
00:12:38,700 --> 00:12:40,730
你留在这儿  这里很安全
You stay here where it's nice and safe.

166
00:12:40,730 --> 00:12:41,740
好
Okay.

167
00:12:43,580 --> 00:12:45,360
你得帮我出去
I just need your help to get me out of here.

168
00:12:48,850 --> 00:12:50,880
杰森  答应我要当心
Jason, promise me you'll be careful.

169
00:12:53,640 --> 00:12:55,130
怎么都习惯不了
Never gonna get used to that.

170
00:13:28,900 --> 00:13:31,760
长官  这边走
Sir. This way.

171
00:13:33,170 --> 00:13:34,800
我们在这里随时候命  长官
We'll be standing by right here, sir.

172
00:13:55,080 --> 00:13:57,770
卡瓦诺将军  稀客啊
General Cavanaugh. What a surprise.

173
00:13:58,290 --> 00:14:00,210
很荣幸再次见到您
So nice to see you again.

174
00:14:01,420 --> 00:14:04,040
别废话了  首席法官  罗曼在哪儿
Cut the crap, Chancellor. Where's Roman?

175
00:14:05,440 --> 00:14:09,020
很抱歉  守护者现在没空
Unfortunately, the Guardian is unavailable at this time.

176
00:14:09,030 --> 00:14:10,420
你又是哪位
Who the fuck are you?

177
00:14:10,420 --> 00:14:13,290
将军  这位是康普顿法官
General, this is Chancellor Compton.

178
00:14:13,710 --> 00:14:14,820
新上任的
He's new.

179
00:14:16,320 --> 00:14:17,700
外面出了一堆破事儿
Well, there's a shit-storm out there

180
00:14:17,700 --> 00:14:19,390
罗曼还不接我电话
and Roman's been ducking my calls.

181
00:14:19,390 --> 00:14:21,590
现在我要求你们通报事件状况
Now I demand to know what's going on.

182
00:14:21,590 --> 00:14:24,210
您可没这个资格要求我们
Well, you're not in a position to be making demands.

183
00:14:24,320 --> 00:14:26,180
是吧  你又是哪位
Oh, I see. And who the fuck are you?

184
00:14:26,180 --> 00:14:28,830
卡瓦诺将军  非常抱歉罗曼未能出席
General Cavanaugh, we deeply regret that Roman's not here,

185
00:14:28,830 --> 00:14:30,670
有什么我们可以效劳的吗
but can we do anything to help you?

186
00:14:31,220 --> 00:14:33,450
我们知道是你们炸掉了真血工厂
We know you bombed the Tru Blood factories.

187
00:14:33,450 --> 00:14:36,910
荒谬  那些工厂都是被恐怖分子炸掉的
That is absurd. Those factories were bombed by terrorists.

188
00:14:36,910 --> 00:14:38,760
拿鬼话骗鬼呢  罗莎琳
Don't bullshit a bullshitter, Rosalyn.

189
00:14:39,620 --> 00:14:41,850
美国政府与贵方有一项协议
The US government and this Authority have an arrangement.

190
00:14:41,850 --> 00:14:43,760
这项协议名为"主流化"
The arrangement is called mainstreaming.

191
00:14:43,760 --> 00:14:47,120
说白了就是我们井水不犯河水
It means you don't fuck with us, we don't fuck with you.

192
00:14:47,340 --> 00:14:49,080
我和罗曼合作了二十年
Now, I've been working with Roman to protect this

193
00:14:49,080 --> 00:14:50,730
就是为了保护你们
Authority for 20 years.

194
00:14:50,730 --> 00:14:52,590
但你们这次做得太过头了
But this time you've gone too far.

195
00:14:52,750 --> 00:14:54,650
五角大楼正在召开高层会议
There are high-level talks at the Pentagon right now

196
00:14:54,650 --> 00:14:58,120
商讨如何彻底铲除吸血鬼
about how to eradicate vampires from the face of the planet.

197
00:14:58,560 --> 00:15:00,920
因此我必须与罗曼对话
So I need to speak with Roman.

198
00:15:07,040 --> 00:15:09,890
罗曼离开我们了
Roman is no longer with us.

199
00:15:11,240 --> 00:15:12,270
怎么回事
How?

200
00:15:12,380 --> 00:15:15,200
他不能与时俱进  只能离开
He couldn't get with the program, so he had to go.

201
00:15:15,540 --> 00:15:17,840
现在是原教旨派掌权
This is a Sanguinist regime now.

202
00:15:17,890 --> 00:15:20,150
莉莉丝为我们指明了正确的方向
Lilith has guided us to our rightful place,

203
00:15:20,150 --> 00:15:22,730
我们要领导血族向前迈进
and there we shall lead all vampire-kind.

204
00:15:22,750 --> 00:15:24,800
我建议您
I would advise you to be...

205
00:15:25,420 --> 00:15:26,690
注意
careful

206
00:15:27,200 --> 00:15:29,710
接下来的言辞
about what words you choose next.

207
00:15:30,350 --> 00:15:32,570
你们这群变态的吸血狂
You psychotic bloodsuckers.

208
00:15:33,950 --> 00:15:35,780
罗曼是控制事态的唯一人选
Roman was the only one keeping a lid on this.

209
00:15:35,780 --> 00:15:37,210
只有他能阻止世界
He was the only one stopping the world

210
00:15:37,210 --> 00:15:39,320
退回到黑暗年代
from sliding back into the Dark Ages.

211
00:15:39,320 --> 00:15:43,080
罗曼是异教徒  他不听莉莉丝的话
Roman was an infidel who defied the word of Lilith.

212
00:15:44,320 --> 00:15:45,850
所以他不在了
And now he's gone.

213
00:15:46,480 --> 00:15:49,230
我发现您很坦率  卡瓦诺将军
You strike me as a man of integrity, General Cavanaugh.

214
00:15:49,640 --> 00:15:51,400
也很武断
Also a pragmatist.

215
00:15:51,400 --> 00:15:54,580
现在的情况是这样子的
Now this is the situation that we find ourselves in.

216
00:15:55,230 --> 00:15:57,570
与我们合作  或者不合作
You can join us or not.

217
00:15:58,520 --> 00:16:01,370
我真诚希望您选择第一条路
I sincerely hope that you choose the path forward.

218
00:16:04,430 --> 00:16:05,970
我们有视频
We have video

219
00:16:08,010 --> 00:16:10,230
是罗素·爱丁顿和史蒂夫·纽林
of Russell Edgington and Steve Newlin

220
00:16:10,230 --> 00:16:12,680
昨晚血洗当地GKT兄弟会所
eviscerating 22 fraternity brothers

221
00:16:12,680 --> 00:16:15,880
把二十二个成员开肠破肚的视频
at the local Gamma Kappa Tau house last night.

222
00:16:18,800 --> 00:16:20,330
有很多备份
There are copies of this.

223
00:16:20,620 --> 00:16:22,660
如果我现在或将来发生任何事情
If anything happens to me now or in the future,

224
00:16:22,660 --> 00:16:24,660
这一视频将会向公众公开
this is gonna be released to the public.

225
00:16:26,170 --> 00:16:29,290
你们向全世界  向总统保证
You assured the world, you assured the president

226
00:16:29,430 --> 00:16:32,400
说罗素·爱丁顿已经死了  这都是谎言
that Russell Edgington was dead, and you lied.

227
00:16:32,820 --> 00:16:34,560
如果视频公开
So if that video goes viral,

228
00:16:34,560 --> 00:16:36,970
全人类就会奋起反抗吸血鬼
the human population is gonna rise up against vampires

229
00:16:36,970 --> 00:16:39,090
比你们动动嘴皮子要快多了
faster than you can say "Molotov cocktail."

230
00:16:39,090 --> 00:16:40,950
您这是虚张声势  将军
Your threats are empty, General.

231
00:16:41,340 --> 00:16:43,080
你是真蠢还是假蠢
Are you really that stupid?

232
00:16:43,420 --> 00:16:44,810
我们早有准备
We're prepared.

233
00:16:44,810 --> 00:16:47,340
你以为我们没做好应对计划吗  我们有武器
You don't think we've been planning for this? We have weapons.

234
00:16:47,340 --> 00:16:49,400
有你们听都没听说过的武器
Weapons you have never heard of.

235
00:16:49,400 --> 00:16:51,600
白天是我们的
We own the day.

236
00:16:51,760 --> 00:16:54,390
你们吸血鬼毫无胜算可言
Vampires don't stand a fucking chance.

237
00:16:55,440 --> 00:16:57,390
现在只有一个人能够阻止你们
Now there's only one person standing between you

238
00:16:57,390 --> 00:16:59,760
和人类爆发战争  这个人就是我
and all-out war with the humans, and you're looking at him.

239
00:17:00,930 --> 00:17:02,900
所以我建议你们谨慎选择
So I suggest you think very carefully

240
00:17:02,900 --> 00:17:05,380
接下来的言辞
about what you say next.

241
00:17:17,680 --> 00:17:19,070
这正是我的想法
That's what I thought.

242
00:17:23,910 --> 00:17:24,960
噢  上帝
Oh, God.

243
00:17:24,960 --> 00:17:26,310
上帝是吸血鬼
God is a vampire.

244
00:17:28,970 --> 00:17:30,220
我的天
Oh, my.

245
00:17:41,310 --> 00:17:42,420
你好  杰森
Hi, Jason.

246
00:17:43,210 --> 00:17:44,140
杰西
Jess.

247
00:17:44,840 --> 00:17:47,510
怎么了  他们是什么人
What's going on? Who are these guys?

248
00:17:50,350 --> 00:17:51,460
喂  伙计们
Hey, guys,

249
00:17:51,830 --> 00:17:54,860
你们有点碍事  能给点私人空间吗
you're kind of cramping my style. Do you mind?

250
00:17:54,860 --> 00:17:56,530
你的创造者要我监视你
Your maker told me to supervise,

251
00:17:56,530 --> 00:17:59,520
所以我要做的就是  监视你
so that's what I'm going to do-- supervise.

252
00:18:00,410 --> 00:18:01,320
好吧
Okay.

253
00:18:03,860 --> 00:18:04,880
杰森
Jason,

254
00:18:05,330 --> 00:18:07,830
我们一起经历了很多事情
we've been through a lot together,

255
00:18:08,030 --> 00:18:09,750
我认为  既然经历了那么多
and I think through all of that, you know,

256
00:18:09,750 --> 00:18:12,720
我们应该可以信任对方
we've learned we can trust each other.

257
00:18:12,890 --> 00:18:14,280
这我可不知道
I don't know about that.

258
00:18:14,390 --> 00:18:16,370
这算是我们之间存在的问题之一
It's kind of been one of our issues.

259
00:18:16,510 --> 00:18:18,400
-说说而已  -我知道
- Just saying. - Yeah, I know.

260
00:18:18,430 --> 00:18:21,020
但我觉得  你知道你可以信任我
But I think you know that you can trust me.

261
00:18:21,410 --> 00:18:24,450
而我是可以信任你的
And I know that I can trust you

262
00:18:24,920 --> 00:18:27,580
相信你会做正确的事
to do the right thing.

263
00:18:27,580 --> 00:18:31,050
这也是个问题  我们从来没做过正确的事
Well, that's another thing-- we never do the right thing.

264
00:18:31,560 --> 00:18:33,690
什么是正确的  就是我们不应该
The right thing would be not sleeping with each other

265
00:18:33,690 --> 00:18:35,100
背着霍伊特上床
behind Hoyt's back.

266
00:18:35,100 --> 00:18:37,750
咱们都想当好人
You, me, we try to be good people,

267
00:18:37,750 --> 00:18:39,500
-但好人不是想当就能当  -杰森
- but that don't mean that we are. - Jason--

268
00:18:39,500 --> 00:18:42,670
别拖拉了  我们要把你俩埋到地下去
This is getting tiresome. We need to get you two in the ground.

269
00:18:42,870 --> 00:18:44,500
让我来
Let me do this.

270
00:18:44,500 --> 00:18:46,300
你不动手就让我来
If you don't do it, I will.

271
00:18:47,070 --> 00:18:48,650
他到底在说什么
What the hell is he talking about?

272
00:18:50,060 --> 00:18:51,110
杰西
Jess!

273
00:18:53,470 --> 00:18:54,580
去他妈的
Fuck it.

274
00:18:57,180 --> 00:18:58,340
相信我
Trust me.

275
00:19:00,000 --> 00:19:01,160
不要
No!

276
00:19:02,090 --> 00:19:04,080
见鬼
Oh, fuck!

277
00:19:04,080 --> 00:19:07,140
你个蠢货  你脑子出了什么毛病
You fucking idiot. What the fuck is wrong with you?

278
00:19:07,140 --> 00:19:09,170
知道你刚刚做了什么吗
Do you have any idea what you have done?

279
00:19:09,170 --> 00:19:10,070
他是个混蛋
He was a dick.

280
00:19:10,070 --> 00:19:11,970
我很高兴他杀了这个大话精
I'm glad he killed the bloated windbag.

281
00:19:11,970 --> 00:19:13,760
他们有武器  我们现在有危险了
They have weapons. Now we're vulnerable.

282
00:19:13,760 --> 00:19:15,460
-他那是吹牛  -你们都没抓住要点
- He was bluffing. - You're all missing the point.

283
00:19:15,460 --> 00:19:17,400
我只是说我了解这只老狐狸
I'm just saying I have known this rattlesnake.

284
00:19:17,400 --> 00:19:18,720
-我认识他全家  -闭嘴  罗莎琳
- I knew his family. - Shut up, Rosalyn!

285
00:19:18,720 --> 00:19:21,780
-咱们得收拾这个烂摊子  -怎么办
- We need to clear this up. - What do we do?

286
00:19:22,490 --> 00:19:23,450
听着
Listen!

287
00:19:23,940 --> 00:19:25,820
我承认  我刚刚有点儿冲动
I admit, I might have been a bit impulsive here,

288
00:19:25,820 --> 00:19:28,010
但我能搞定
but I can fix this.

289
00:19:28,010 --> 00:19:29,660
我要来一次大规模的魅惑行动
I'll go on a glamouring campaign,

290
00:19:29,660 --> 00:19:32,340
消除掉关于这个视频的一切记忆
eliminate all memory that the video exists.

291
00:19:32,540 --> 00:19:34,220
就像什么事情都没发生过
It'll be like none of this ever happened.

292
00:19:34,220 --> 00:19:36,310
没错  我认识这位将军的幕僚
Yes, and I know the general's chief of staff.

293
00:19:36,310 --> 00:19:38,560
如果速度够快  就能控制形势
If we act quickly, we can contain the situation.

294
00:19:38,560 --> 00:19:39,940
去吧  搭我们联盟的飞机
Okay, go. Take the AVL jet

295
00:19:39,940 --> 00:19:41,810
完事后给我回话
and report back when it is done.

296
00:19:43,990 --> 00:19:45,680
带几个安保队员去
Take a security detail.

297
00:19:46,880 --> 00:19:48,320
可能需要支援
Might need the backup.

298
00:19:49,960 --> 00:19:50,940
好
Of course.

299
00:19:54,150 --> 00:19:56,450
将军的随从就交给我了
I'll handle the general's entourage.

300
00:20:02,930 --> 00:20:04,690
亲爱的  我对不起你
Baby, I am so sorry.

301
00:20:05,690 --> 00:20:07,120
不会有事的
It's gonna be okay.

302
00:20:07,590 --> 00:20:09,410
再睁眼时你就是吸血鬼了
Cause you're gonna wake up a vampire.

303
00:20:11,490 --> 00:20:13,000
你不该哭  小姑娘
You shouldn't cry, little girl.

304
00:20:13,410 --> 00:20:14,930
这是大喜的日子
This is a happy day.

305
00:20:16,430 --> 00:20:18,280
明晚你和白马王子醒来之后
When you and Prince Charming wake tomorrow night,

306
00:20:18,720 --> 00:20:20,540
他也可以咬你了
he can bite you right back.

307
00:20:21,970 --> 00:20:23,930
我们回去的路上要不要找点外卖
Should we pick up some takeout on our way back?

308
00:20:23,940 --> 00:20:24,960
动手
Do it.

309
00:20:30,230 --> 00:20:32,450
-操  -对不起
- Fuck! - I'm sorry.

310
00:20:32,450 --> 00:20:34,340
-靠  -对不起  真的对不起
- Fuck! - I'm sorry, I'm sorry.

311
00:20:34,340 --> 00:20:36,030
我已经尽量少吸你的血了
I tried not to drink too much of your blood.

312
00:20:36,040 --> 00:20:37,100
为什么
Why?

313
00:20:37,180 --> 00:20:39,080
罗素·爱丁顿和史蒂夫·纽林
Russell Edgington and Steve Newlin,

314
00:20:39,150 --> 00:20:40,480
他们在找苏琪
they are coming for Sookie,

315
00:20:40,480 --> 00:20:42,470
比尔和埃里克对吸血鬼宗教信仰得发了疯
and Bill and Eric have gone crazy on vampire religion

316
00:20:42,470 --> 00:20:44,290
这次没人会来救她
and nobody is gonna save her this time.

317
00:20:45,890 --> 00:20:47,790
-上帝啊  -等等  杰森
- Oh, Jesus. - Wait, Jason.

318
00:20:47,790 --> 00:20:50,560
-干嘛  -我知道这次不是真的
- What? - I know this wasn't real.

319
00:20:51,190 --> 00:20:53,510
可如果我必须永远跟谁在一起
But if I was gonna have to spend eternity with somebody

320
00:20:53,510 --> 00:20:54,500
我是说...
I mean...

321
00:20:56,620 --> 00:20:58,620
这方面我是真心的
I wasn't faking that part.

322
00:21:00,180 --> 00:21:01,990
我要去警告苏琪了
I've got to go warn Sookie.

323
00:21:12,300 --> 00:21:13,540
我们已经清干净了
We cleaned it all up.

324
00:21:13,540 --> 00:21:15,150
这里一滴以利亚也不剩
There's not a drop of Elijah anywhere.

325
00:21:15,150 --> 00:21:16,990
我用牙刷把这儿刷遍了
I went over this place with a toothbrush.

326
00:21:18,910 --> 00:21:22,570
杀死治安官  这一定会惊动上层
Killing a sheriff... this is going to go up the chain.

327
00:21:22,570 --> 00:21:25,350
-什么上层  -当权者呗
- What chain? - The fucking Authority.

328
00:21:25,350 --> 00:21:26,710
当权者是什么鬼东西
What's the damn Authority?

329
00:21:26,720 --> 00:21:28,750
是我们的政教合一的管理机构
It's our government and church combined.

330
00:21:28,750 --> 00:21:30,160
教会掌控政府
The church runs the government.

331
00:21:30,160 --> 00:21:33,330
-像梵帝冈那样吗  -差不多
- Like the Vatican? - Kind of.

332
00:21:33,330 --> 00:21:36,190
他们宣布法律  我们就遵守
They hand down the laws and we follow them.

333
00:21:36,300 --> 00:21:37,510
就是这样
It's how it works.

334
00:21:37,510 --> 00:21:39,370
让教皇和当权者都去吃屎吧
Well, the Pope can fuck me and so can the Authority.

335
00:21:39,370 --> 00:21:41,410
他们的法律在我身上没用
They can both keep their laws off of my body.

336
00:21:41,410 --> 00:21:47,550
当权者可以对你和你的身体采取任何手段
The Authority can do whatever they want with you and your body.

337
00:21:48,620 --> 00:21:50,940
我们再也别谈论此事
We're not going to talk about this ever again.

338
00:21:50,940 --> 00:21:53,580
-但你觉得...  -我操  泰拉
- But do you think... - For fuck's sake, Tara.

339
00:21:54,190 --> 00:21:56,800
作为你的创造者  我命令你永远不要提起
As your maker, I command you to never speak

340
00:21:56,800 --> 00:22:00,130
斯多莫治安官和他不合时宜的死亡
of Sheriff Stormer and his untimely true death.

341
00:22:08,730 --> 00:22:10,700
-嗨  -你出什么屁事了
- Oh, hey. - What the hell happened to you?

342
00:22:10,700 --> 00:22:12,620
-我要你把我藏起来  -不
- I need you to hide me. - No.

343
00:22:13,190 --> 00:22:14,220
为什么
Why not?

344
00:22:14,270 --> 00:22:18,170
我这里什么时候变成任性小吸血鬼的收容所了
Since when did I become a halfway house for wayward baby vamps?

345
00:22:18,180 --> 00:22:19,920
不管你有什么麻烦  别来找我
Whatever trouble you're in, leave me out of it.

346
00:22:19,920 --> 00:22:21,280
我自己的都处理不过来
I got enough of my own.

347
00:22:25,100 --> 00:22:26,710
我知道埃里克在哪里
I know where Eric is.

348
00:22:31,290 --> 00:22:34,040
-哪里  -你答应藏我  我就告诉你
- Where? - I'll tell you if you hide me.

349
00:22:35,410 --> 00:22:38,640
别跟我耍花样  你这个红发小贱人
Don't play games with me, you little ginger bitch.

350
00:22:39,400 --> 00:22:40,570
把我藏起来
Hide me.

351
00:22:47,200 --> 00:22:49,310
从储藏室里给她找副棺材出来
Get her a coffin out of storage.

352
00:22:51,620 --> 00:22:54,510
立刻回答我
Answers, now.

353
00:22:57,110 --> 00:22:58,010
吸血鬼去死

354
00:23:02,790 --> 00:23:06,210
不管美国吸血鬼联盟发言人史蒂夫·纽林
And despite what AVL spokesperson Steve Newlin

355
00:23:06,210 --> 00:23:07,860
在今晚的辩论中怎么说
said in his debate tonight,

356
00:23:07,860 --> 00:23:11,140
本地贸易量下跌了75%
local business has dropped off 75%,

357
00:23:11,140 --> 00:23:13,950
进一步引发了对真血供应量下降
leading to worries that dwindling supplies of Tru Blood

358
00:23:13,950 --> 00:23:16,150
和经济危机的恐慌...
coupled with the struggling economy...

359
00:23:16,370 --> 00:23:18,060
我转台你们介意吗
You guys mind if I change the station?

360
00:23:18,850 --> 00:23:21,800
在华尔街  道琼斯指数急跌200点...
On Wall Street, the Dow is down 200 points...

361
00:23:35,340 --> 00:23:36,890
他们会追来的
They'll be coming for us.

362
00:23:57,780 --> 00:23:59,550
距日出还有两分钟
Dawn in two minutes.

363
00:23:59,560 --> 00:24:03,510
请回到住所  安全程序已启动
Please retire to quarters. Security protocols initiated.

364
00:24:10,570 --> 00:24:12,050
我们这他妈是在哪儿呢
Where the hell are we?

365
00:24:13,040 --> 00:24:16,490
-我觉得是在地下  -这是什么地方
- I think we're underground. - What is this place?

366
00:24:16,490 --> 00:24:18,660
吸血鬼的秘密司令部吗
A fucking vampire secret headquarters?

367
00:24:19,200 --> 00:24:22,420
艾玛在这里的某处
Emma's here somewhere.

368
00:24:28,970 --> 00:24:31,860
记住  能见长老是莫大的荣幸
Remember, it is truly a great honor to meet the Elder.

369
00:24:31,860 --> 00:24:33,180
她到底是谁
Who is she, exactly?

370
00:24:33,180 --> 00:24:35,230
她是从传送门逃脱的最年迈的精灵
She's the oldest fairy to escape through the portal.

371
00:24:35,230 --> 00:24:37,270
-只有一个问题  -这不算是问题
- There's only one problem. - It's not a problem.

372
00:24:38,150 --> 00:24:40,170
长老去过太多领域
The Elder has been through so many realms,

373
00:24:40,170 --> 00:24:43,400
变过太多形象  说过太多种语言
she's assumed so many shapes and spoken so many languages

374
00:24:43,400 --> 00:24:45,550
所以她有时难以...
that she sometimes has a difficult time...

375
00:24:45,930 --> 00:24:47,670
-集中精神  -集中精神
- focusing. - Focusing?

376
00:24:47,670 --> 00:24:50,270
她同时应对多个频率
She operates on many frequencies at once.

377
00:24:50,280 --> 00:24:52,020
时间对她毫无意义
Time has no meaning for her.

378
00:24:52,020 --> 00:24:53,400
但你觉得她能帮我
But you think she can help me?

379
00:24:53,400 --> 00:24:54,610
拭目以待吧
We shall see.

380
00:25:00,390 --> 00:25:01,730
长老阁下
Your Grace.

381
00:25:01,730 --> 00:25:03,360
这是苏琪·斯塔克豪斯
This is Sookie Stackhouse,

382
00:25:03,360 --> 00:25:05,220
跟您说过的那个半精灵
the halfling you were told about.

383
00:25:06,710 --> 00:25:08,840
卡莎  支持或反对
Ke$ha-- for or against?

384
00:25:06,710 --> 00:25:09,840
{\an8}卡莎  美国新生流行女歌手兼作曲者

385
00:25:09,570 --> 00:25:10,730
什么
Excuse me?

386
00:25:10,730 --> 00:25:14,130
-你喜欢她的音乐吗  -抱歉
- Do you like her music? - I'm sorry.

387
00:25:14,130 --> 00:25:15,950
我对她的音乐不太熟悉
I'm not that familiar with her music.

388
00:25:15,950 --> 00:25:17,630
她其实不太唱歌  对吧
She doesn't really sing, does she?

389
00:25:17,830 --> 00:25:18,910
她说
She talks.

390
00:25:19,670 --> 00:25:21,530
我认为这说明她算是诗人
I suppose that makes her some sort of a poet.

391
00:25:22,240 --> 00:25:25,540
这太可怕了  她的拼写水平惨不忍睹
That's alarming because her spelling is atrocious.

392
00:25:26,770 --> 00:25:28,160
哈  退下
Ha! Leave us.

393
00:25:32,280 --> 00:25:34,130
恕我直言  长老女士
Begging your pardon, Miss Elder.

394
00:25:34,870 --> 00:25:37,800
玛瑞拉说您可能认识我的曾曾曾
Maurella said that you might know my great-great-great,

395
00:25:37,800 --> 00:25:40,950
带十五个曾的祖父约翰·斯塔克豪斯
like, times 15 grandfather John Stackhouse.

396
00:25:42,530 --> 00:25:44,080
约翰尼·斯塔克豪斯
Johnny Stackhouse?

397
00:25:44,620 --> 00:25:46,800
没错  我认识他
Yes, I did know him.

398
00:25:48,160 --> 00:25:50,530
是个地主  非常英俊
He was a landowner. Very handsome.

399
00:25:50,810 --> 00:25:52,940
有点古怪  无意冒犯
Bit of a creep. No offense.

400
00:25:52,940 --> 00:25:53,980
没关系
None taken.

401
00:25:55,590 --> 00:25:59,580
你知道他为何把我许给一个叫沃罗的吸血鬼吗
Do you know why he might have promised me to a vampire named Warlow?

402
00:25:59,920 --> 00:26:01,740
这些事情是不能谈论的
It is forbidden to speak of these things.

403
00:26:01,740 --> 00:26:02,460
哪些事
What things?

404
00:26:02,460 --> 00:26:04,200
约翰·康加·麦伦坎普  支持或反对
John Cougar Mellencamp, for or against?

405
00:26:02,460 --> 00:26:05,200
{\an8}约翰·康加·麦伦坎普  摇滚歌手

406
00:26:04,200 --> 00:26:05,600
反对  哪些事
Against. What things?

407
00:26:05,600 --> 00:26:11,300
听着  你对吸血鬼没有抵抗力是有原因的
Look, there is a reason that you find vampires irresistible,

408
00:26:12,250 --> 00:26:14,330
你倾心于所有长尖牙的
a reason that you slut your heart out

409
00:26:14,340 --> 00:26:16,150
帅哥吸血鬼的原因
to every cute guy out there with fangs.

410
00:26:16,150 --> 00:26:19,040
-您说什么  -你  我和沃罗
- I beg your pardon? - You, me, Warlow--

411
00:26:19,040 --> 00:26:20,800
我们的命运是紧紧相连的
our destinies are entwined.

412
00:26:20,800 --> 00:26:23,030
好吧  但那是什么意思
Yes, okay, but what is that supposed to mean?

413
00:26:23,230 --> 00:26:26,330
暗黑时代即将来临  你会受到考验
A dark time is coming. You will be tested.

414
00:26:27,020 --> 00:26:28,650
握紧你的光
Hold on to your light.

415
00:26:29,360 --> 00:26:32,490
只要我们精灵能掌控自己的光
As long as we fairies control our light,

416
00:26:33,770 --> 00:26:34,980
我们就是自由的
we will be free.

417
00:26:37,760 --> 00:26:39,540
男孩到男人  支持或反对
Boyz II Men, for or against?

418
00:26:37,760 --> 00:26:40,540
{\an8}男孩到男人  美国著名的R&B演唱组合

419
00:26:39,540 --> 00:26:41,970
支持  抱歉  我知道你有转换频率的难处
For. I'm sorry, I know you have trouble with frequencies,

420
00:26:41,970 --> 00:26:45,810
但有个可怕的空气吸血怪先杀了我父母
but there's a creepy vampire ghost air monster who killed my parents

421
00:26:45,810 --> 00:26:47,390
现在又来找我
and now he's coming to get me

422
00:26:47,400 --> 00:26:49,740
我真的需要您给我提供点靠谱的信息
and I really need you to give me something concrete,

423
00:26:50,130 --> 00:26:51,070
有用的信息
something useful.

424
00:26:51,490 --> 00:26:52,550
很抱歉
My apologies.

425
00:26:53,570 --> 00:26:55,850
我的脑子里装了太多的信息
There's so much information in my head.

426
00:26:55,850 --> 00:26:56,970
奔流不息
Eons of data.

427
00:26:59,840 --> 00:27:02,470
-沃罗是个非常...  -苏琪
- Warlow is very- - Sookie!

428
00:27:04,360 --> 00:27:06,490
-苏克  我有事要跟你说  -杰森
- Sook! I've got to talk to you! - Jason.

429
00:27:06,490 --> 00:27:07,430
让我进去
Let me in!

430
00:27:12,490 --> 00:27:14,110
-她在哪儿  -他被咬了
- Where is she? - He's been bitten.

431
00:27:14,110 --> 00:27:15,640
我们得马上把你藏起来
We got to hide you right now.

432
00:27:15,640 --> 00:27:17,400
上帝呀  你怎么了  还好吗
Oh, my God. What happened to you? Are you okay?

433
00:27:17,400 --> 00:27:19,790
别管这个  罗素·爱丁顿和史蒂夫·纽林
Forget this. Russell Edgington and Steve Newlin,

434
00:27:19,790 --> 00:27:22,460
要来抓你啦  比尔和埃里克也都疯了
they're coming for you. Bill, Eric, they've both gone crazy.

435
00:27:22,460 --> 00:27:23,960
他们信奉了吸血鬼宗教
They found vampire religion,

436
00:27:23,960 --> 00:27:25,310
所以没人会来救你
so nobody's coming to save you.

437
00:27:25,320 --> 00:27:27,070
罗素·爱丁顿还活着吗
Russell Edgington is alive?

438
00:27:27,280 --> 00:27:29,760
-是的  -长老女士  你刚才说沃罗什么
- Yeah. - Please, Miss Elder, you said Warlow is...?

439
00:27:29,760 --> 00:27:31,580
罗素·爱丁顿还活着吗
Russell Edgington is alive?

440
00:27:37,600 --> 00:27:38,940
你好呀  小美人
Hey there, sunshine.

441
00:27:39,130 --> 00:27:41,290
早上好  贝弗勒警长
Good morning, Sheriff Bellefleur.

442
00:27:42,180 --> 00:27:44,130
鸡蛋三明治和酥脆培根
Egg sandwich, crispy bacon,

443
00:27:44,130 --> 00:27:46,300
大杯咖啡  加奶加糖
large coffee, extra milk, extra sugar.

444
00:27:46,680 --> 00:27:47,210
你真贴心
You're so sweet,

445
00:27:47,210 --> 00:27:49,210
这里的食物因你而更加美味了
you make the food here taste good.

446
00:27:50,780 --> 00:27:52,220
我还有一样小礼物送你
I got a little something else for you.

447
00:27:52,810 --> 00:27:54,030
过来
Come here.

448
00:27:58,660 --> 00:28:03,020
我的儿子们有话想对你说
My boys here have something they want to say to you.

449
00:28:03,630 --> 00:28:05,790
你好  贝弗勒警长
Uh, hey, Sheriff Bellefleur.

450
00:28:05,790 --> 00:28:08,910
我只想跟你道个歉
Uh, I just want to say that I'm sorry

451
00:28:08,910 --> 00:28:11,010
就是把你的屁股放上脸谱网的事
for putting your butt up on Facebook.

452
00:28:11,920 --> 00:28:13,670
这是不对的
Uh, it was wrong

453
00:28:14,360 --> 00:28:17,440
还有  看起来  你让我妈非常幸福
and it seems like you're making my mom real happy.

454
00:28:17,700 --> 00:28:20,260
我爸可从没让她这么开心过
You know, way happier than my pops ever did.

455
00:28:20,260 --> 00:28:22,590
所以  对不起
So, sorry.

456
00:28:24,530 --> 00:28:26,480
是啊  我也很抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.

457
00:28:27,320 --> 00:28:29,570
抱歉没能把你屁股的图象
Sorry that I cannot scrape the image of your ass

458
00:28:29,570 --> 00:28:31,200
-从我脑子里面擦掉  -洛奇
- from the back wall of my mind. - Rocky.

459
00:28:31,200 --> 00:28:34,280
抱歉我要把我妈辛苦挣的小费都花在
Sorry I'm gonna have to waste all of my mama's hard-earned tips

460
00:28:34,280 --> 00:28:35,860
长年的心理治疗上了
to pay for years of therapy

461
00:28:35,860 --> 00:28:37,300
而且最后可能还得蹲监狱
and probably end up incarcerated anyway.

462
00:28:37,300 --> 00:28:39,290
洛奇·克利里  你给我礼貌点儿
Rocky Cleary, you quit your sass right now.

463
00:28:39,290 --> 00:28:41,340
你不能逼我说违心的话
You can't make me say stuff that I don't feel.

464
00:28:41,340 --> 00:28:42,500
没关系  霍莉
It's all right, Holly.

465
00:28:43,590 --> 00:28:45,200
他没有理由相信我
He's got no reason to trust me.

466
00:28:47,360 --> 00:28:48,400
至少目前没有
Yet.

467
00:28:51,320 --> 00:28:53,300
但我要向你们兄弟俩保证
But I'm gonna make you boys a promise.

468
00:28:54,560 --> 00:28:57,110
我会好好对待你们的妈妈
I am gonna do right by your mama

469
00:28:58,030 --> 00:28:59,610
只要她不甩了我
for as long as she'll have me.

470
00:29:01,020 --> 00:29:02,620
把承诺存银行去吧
You can take that to the bank.

471
00:29:02,870 --> 00:29:04,930
银行最烂了  收了我们的房子
Banks suck. They took our house.

472
00:29:05,380 --> 00:29:07,350
这只是个修辞  孩子
It's a figure of speech, son.

473
00:29:10,010 --> 00:29:11,140
你觉得呢
What do you say?

474
00:29:15,190 --> 00:29:16,350
来吧
Come on.

475
00:29:22,340 --> 00:29:23,820
好嘞
All right.

476
00:29:26,900 --> 00:29:28,990
行了  这下好了
No, that's all right. Okay.

477
00:29:30,050 --> 00:29:31,040
那么
All righty, then.

478
00:29:34,650 --> 00:29:36,250
午餐时再见啦
I'll see you at lunch.

479
00:29:48,720 --> 00:29:49,920
杰克逊
Jackson.

480
00:29:51,290 --> 00:29:53,140
埃尔希德  看看你
Alcide, look at you.

481
00:29:53,790 --> 00:29:55,700
上次见你的时候你还是小崽子
Ain't seen you since you was a pup.

482
00:29:55,700 --> 00:29:56,850
罗林斯先生
Mr. Rollins.

483
00:29:57,710 --> 00:29:58,800
你想干什么
What do you want?

484
00:29:59,070 --> 00:30:00,680
只是来给你们报个信
Just out warning folks.

485
00:30:01,050 --> 00:30:03,330
在麦迪逊和兰金县发生了多起
There's been a bunch of baby vamp attacks

486
00:30:03,330 --> 00:30:05,150
新生吸血鬼袭击事件
in Madison and Rankin Counties.

487
00:30:05,400 --> 00:30:07,620
场面惨不忍睹
Kills are messy, savage.

488
00:30:07,870 --> 00:30:10,240
我们认为吸血鬼在增加他们的数量
We think the vamps are upping their numbers,

489
00:30:10,470 --> 00:30:12,820
转变居民  再放出去肆意觅食
turning folks, letting them run wild.

490
00:30:13,810 --> 00:30:17,090
新生吸血鬼形成帮派  集体猎食
Baby vamps are forming into packs, hunting.

491
00:30:17,360 --> 00:30:18,560
往我们这边来了
Coming our way.

492
00:30:19,130 --> 00:30:21,200
我们有镀银的栅栏
Silver-plated box fence.

493
00:30:21,570 --> 00:30:22,970
成年吸血鬼拦不住
Won't stop the grown vamps,

494
00:30:22,970 --> 00:30:24,360
但新生儿还是进不来的
but it'll keep the baby ones out.

495
00:30:26,800 --> 00:30:28,330
滚出我的地盘
Get off my land.

496
00:30:28,830 --> 00:30:31,610
很高兴看到你还是那么讨人厌  哈韦欧
Good to see you're still a son of a bitch, Herveaux.

497
00:30:32,510 --> 00:30:35,560
我来这儿是因为我尊敬曾经的那个男人
I come out here out of respect for a man I once knew.

498
00:30:35,560 --> 00:30:38,070
真是好人难做啊
No good deed goes unpunished, I guess.

499
00:30:41,740 --> 00:30:44,910
你曾是首领  但你抛弃了那一切
You were a Packmaster, but you threw it all away.

500
00:30:45,430 --> 00:30:47,740
是你们这些叛徒逼走我的
I was forced out by you turncoats.

501
00:30:50,360 --> 00:30:52,910
别让你老子把你拖下水  埃尔希德
Don't let your old man drag you down, Alcide.

502
00:30:53,570 --> 00:30:54,850
他危险着呢
He's quicksand.

503
00:31:01,910 --> 00:31:03,760
罗林斯就知道撒谎
Rollins is a lying shit.

504
00:31:03,770 --> 00:31:06,030
到这儿摆出一副高高在上的姿态
Comes out here acting all high and mighty.

505
00:31:07,150 --> 00:31:08,120
他可以去死了
He can go to hell.

506
00:31:09,570 --> 00:31:11,500
事实就是  不能相信他
Can't trust him, that's the truth.

507
00:31:15,530 --> 00:31:16,660
你做了
You did it.

508
00:31:16,930 --> 00:31:19,160
能不能别再假装你没做那事儿
So why don't we just stop pretending like you didn't?

509
00:31:19,640 --> 00:31:21,260
你偷了帮里的钱
You stole that money from the pack.

510
00:31:21,930 --> 00:31:23,120
所以他们把你赶下台
That's why they kicked you out.

511
00:31:23,940 --> 00:31:26,010
而且现在你做什么都无法改变了
And there ain't a damn thing you can do to change that.

512
00:31:26,010 --> 00:31:27,900
我不需要罗林斯来这里
I don't need Rollins coming out here

513
00:31:27,910 --> 00:31:29,510
抖陈芝麻烂谷子的事儿
digging up ancient history.

514
00:31:30,450 --> 00:31:34,580
更不需要我的孩子来教训我
And I sure as hell don't need my kid passing judgment.

515
00:31:36,380 --> 00:31:37,680
明白了吗
You get it?

516
00:31:38,790 --> 00:31:40,460
狼群优先的原则去哪儿了
Whatever happened to pack first?

517
00:31:44,200 --> 00:31:46,040
狼群不管我是死是活
Pack left me out here to rot.

518
00:31:47,570 --> 00:31:49,290
他们全都可以去死了
Pack can go fuck themselves.

519
00:32:05,690 --> 00:32:07,110
听我说
Listen to me!

520
00:32:07,650 --> 00:32:10,550
罗素·爱丁顿不找到我决不罢休
Russell Edgington is gonna keep coming for me.

521
00:32:11,320 --> 00:32:12,780
他不会放弃
He's not gonna stop.

522
00:32:13,170 --> 00:32:16,470
抓到我以后  他就会把魔爪伸向你们
And after he's gotten me, he's gonna come for you.

523
00:32:16,470 --> 00:32:17,820
现在  我不知道你们怎么想
Now, I don't know about you guys,

524
00:32:17,830 --> 00:32:19,080
但我已经厌倦了逃亡
but I am tired of running.

525
00:32:19,800 --> 00:32:21,410
我们必须反抗
We have to fight him,

526
00:32:21,690 --> 00:32:24,240
大家同心协力
all of us together.

527
00:32:24,490 --> 00:32:27,300
我很抱歉  那是自杀
I'm sorry. It's suicide.

528
00:32:29,100 --> 00:32:30,630
但我们必须如此
And yet we must.

529
00:32:33,870 --> 00:32:36,940
我们是良辰镇的精灵部落
We, the fairy tribe of Bon Temps,

530
00:32:37,190 --> 00:32:39,560
在此位面  在此时刻
in this plane, in this time,

531
00:32:40,760 --> 00:32:44,860
我们会与你并肩作战  苏琪·斯塔克豪斯
will fight with you, sookie Stackhouse.

532
00:32:52,050 --> 00:32:54,860
计划你都听明白了吗  老实说
You clear on the plan? Just be honest.

533
00:32:54,860 --> 00:32:56,030
讲实话
Tell the truth.

534
00:32:57,060 --> 00:32:58,840
不  我不需要讲实话
No, I won't have to tell the truth.

535
00:32:59,070 --> 00:33:01,300
-因为我要宰了他  -你不需要那么做
- 'Cause I'm gonna kill him. - You don't have to do that.

536
00:33:01,300 --> 00:33:03,170
你可以就在这儿  跟我在一起
You could just stay here with me.

537
00:33:03,530 --> 00:33:04,690
不  我想做
No, I want to do it.

538
00:33:05,740 --> 00:33:10,170
苏琪  如果说我当四分卫时学到了什么
Sook, if there's one thing I learned from my time as QB-1,

539
00:33:11,310 --> 00:33:14,140
那一定是"进攻就是最好的防守"
it's that the best defense is a good offense.

540
00:33:14,820 --> 00:33:17,590
不能再在罗素面前做胆小鬼了
So no more pussyfooting around Russell.

541
00:33:20,260 --> 00:33:21,480
比赛开始了
It's game time.

542
00:33:27,730 --> 00:33:28,720
我爱你
I love you.

543
00:33:32,810 --> 00:33:34,340
我也爱你  苏克
I love you, too, Sook.

544
00:33:41,880 --> 00:33:43,140
你好好整整他
You give him hell.

545
00:33:43,140 --> 00:33:44,300
瞧我的吧
I always do.

546
00:33:53,290 --> 00:33:55,480
哥俩好呀  吃的来啦
Hey, y'all. Here you go.

547
00:33:57,200 --> 00:33:58,370
过来
Come here.

548
00:33:58,810 --> 00:34:01,030
特里·贝弗勒  你会给我添麻烦的
Terry Bellefleur, you're gonna get me in trouble.

549
00:34:01,290 --> 00:34:02,480
山姆今天又不在店里
Sam's not even around.

550
00:34:02,680 --> 00:34:04,760
是的  但拉法耶最爱打小报告了
Yeah, but Lafayette is a snitch.

551
00:34:04,760 --> 00:34:07,020
我是贱人  不是打小报告的人
I'm a bitch, not a snitch.

552
00:34:07,350 --> 00:34:08,320
我爱死了
Love it.

553
00:34:10,230 --> 00:34:12,720
真高兴看到你们都回来了  这么幸福
I'm so glad to see y'all back and happy

554
00:34:12,720 --> 00:34:15,170
这么相爱  你懂的
and, you know, in love and all.

555
00:34:15,960 --> 00:34:18,310
谢谢你  堂哥  谢谢你这么说
Thank you, cuz. I appreciate that.

556
00:34:19,410 --> 00:34:21,040
她每天都在拯救我的生命
She saves my life every day.

557
00:34:22,010 --> 00:34:24,620
你们是怎么坚持过来的
How do you make it last for the long haul?

558
00:34:25,220 --> 00:34:26,050
这个
Well...

559
00:34:27,900 --> 00:34:29,260
我想首先要有信任
I think it starts with trust.

560
00:34:29,560 --> 00:34:31,550
-信任最重要  -对的
- Trust most of all. - Yeah.

561
00:34:31,550 --> 00:34:33,880
还有诚实  一定要诚实
And honesty. Got to have honesty.

562
00:34:33,880 --> 00:34:35,710
-对  还有诚实  -还要忠诚
- Yeah, that, too. - And loyalty.

563
00:34:36,050 --> 00:34:38,080
你要知道有人会陪着你
You got to know that person's gonna be there for you

564
00:34:38,080 --> 00:34:38,830
同甘共苦
through thick and thin

565
00:34:38,840 --> 00:34:41,670
因为你不知道何时会有个伊拉克女鬼
'cause you never know when some Iraqi ghost lady

566
00:34:41,670 --> 00:34:43,320
诅咒你全家
is gonna curse your entire family.

567
00:34:46,040 --> 00:34:47,140
可找到你了
There you are.

568
00:34:48,960 --> 00:34:50,900
玛瑞拉  你来干什么
Maurella, what are you doing here?

569
00:34:50,900 --> 00:34:53,180
危险正在临近  安德鲁
There's danger afoot, Andrew.

570
00:34:54,800 --> 00:34:57,310
你对光发誓会保护我
You swore on the light to protect me

571
00:34:57,910 --> 00:35:00,470
还有我们爱的结晶
and the fruit of our union.

572
00:35:01,260 --> 00:35:02,840
安迪·贝弗勒
Andy Bellefleur!

573
00:35:03,280 --> 00:35:05,100
是你把她肚子搞大的吗
Did you put that bun in her oven?

574
00:35:07,610 --> 00:35:11,520
我一周前才见到过你
But I just saw you about a week ago,

575
00:35:11,530 --> 00:35:12,860
你当时没怀孕
and you weren't pregnant.

576
00:35:13,140 --> 00:35:15,210
就是那一晚我们播下了种子
That was the night we conceived.

577
00:35:15,560 --> 00:35:17,480
一个星期而已  现在你...
One week ago, and now you're...

578
00:35:17,480 --> 00:35:19,380
对的  进度正常啊
Yes. Right on schedule.

579
00:35:20,180 --> 00:35:22,420
玛瑞拉  你看起来是个可爱的姑娘
Look, Maurella, you seem like a lovely person.

580
00:35:22,420 --> 00:35:23,810
我就是
Mmm, I am.

581
00:35:23,810 --> 00:35:27,070
-我知道我们干了...  -两次
- And I know that we have-- - Twice.

582
00:35:28,090 --> 00:35:29,280
但是我不傻
But I'm not stupid.

583
00:35:29,530 --> 00:35:31,270
也许很多人以为我傻
A lot of people might think I'm stupid,

584
00:35:31,270 --> 00:35:32,490
不过他们错了
but those people are wrong.

585
00:35:32,490 --> 00:35:35,600
对  我不认为你傻
No, I don't think you're stupid.

586
00:35:35,600 --> 00:35:37,060
你明显就是这么想的
Well, apparently you do

587
00:35:37,360 --> 00:35:39,150
所以你要把这事儿赖在我头上
if you think you can pull this over on me.

588
00:35:39,160 --> 00:35:43,000
你到底有没有对光发誓
Did you or did you not swear upon the light?

589
00:35:43,000 --> 00:35:45,630
我只记得你的手指亮了  我碰了一下
All I know is your finger lit up and I touched it.

590
00:35:45,630 --> 00:35:48,480
你接受我的光进入你的身体
You accepted my light into you.

591
00:35:49,320 --> 00:35:51,990
否则我不会和你有肌肤之亲
Otherwise I never would have shared flesh with you.

592
00:35:52,270 --> 00:35:53,400
况且是两次
Twice.

593
00:35:54,580 --> 00:35:56,490
但我不能...
But I can't--

594
00:35:58,150 --> 00:36:00,020
我和霍莉发展得不错
I got a good thing starting with Holly.

595
00:36:00,680 --> 00:36:04,270
我和我的同类在一起  感觉更舒服
And I just feel more comfortable with somebody who's the same species.

596
00:36:05,420 --> 00:36:08,760
无视光之契约是对我以及全部族人
To ignore the light pact will bring great dishonor

597
00:36:08,760 --> 00:36:11,160
极大的侮辱
upon me and all my clan.

598
00:36:11,890 --> 00:36:14,990
等同于挑起战争
It is an act of war.

599
00:36:18,790 --> 00:36:21,680
比尔  我从没见过那样的他
Bill-- I've never seen him like that.

600
00:36:21,680 --> 00:36:25,420
他很冷漠  甚至是残忍
He was cold, cruel even.

601
00:36:25,630 --> 00:36:27,650
那是群居行为
That's nest behavior.

602
00:36:29,390 --> 00:36:32,320
当吸血鬼长时间生活在一起
When vampires live together for a long time

603
00:36:32,320 --> 00:36:34,070
相互吸食血液
and feed off of each other's blood,

604
00:36:34,070 --> 00:36:35,800
形成群居状态
they form a nest

605
00:36:36,070 --> 00:36:38,300
就变得疯狂且残酷
and become sadistic and crazy.

606
00:36:38,770 --> 00:36:41,720
根据你所说的  共饮莉莉丝的血
From what you're telling me, drinking that Lilith's blood

607
00:36:41,720 --> 00:36:44,160
让他们在类固醇作用下形成群居状态
is making them into a nest on steroids.

608
00:36:44,160 --> 00:36:45,790
你跟谁群居过吗
Have you ever been in a nest?

609
00:36:45,790 --> 00:36:47,480
埃里克和我避之不及
Eric and I have steered clear.

610
00:36:47,970 --> 00:36:51,380
我发现大多数吸血鬼和大多数人类一样讨厌
I find most vampires as irritating as most humans.

611
00:36:51,760 --> 00:36:53,240
你担心埃里克吗
Are you worried about Eric?

612
00:36:54,700 --> 00:36:57,260
他是成人了  能照顾好自己
He's a big boy. He can take care of himself.

613
00:36:58,420 --> 00:37:00,230
再次谢谢你
Well, thank you again

614
00:37:01,210 --> 00:37:02,690
允许我留在这儿
for letting me stay here.

615
00:37:02,940 --> 00:37:06,160
是啊  说不定等会儿我们可以互编辫子
Totally. Maybe later we can braid each other's hair

616
00:37:06,160 --> 00:37:07,440
谈谈帅哥
and talk about boys.

617
00:37:09,080 --> 00:37:10,930
该死的新生吸血鬼
Fucking baby vamps.

618
00:37:14,870 --> 00:37:17,140
她就是嘴巴刻薄  对不
She's all bark, isn't she?

619
00:37:18,090 --> 00:37:20,240
不是  她嘴巴刻薄
Nah, she's a lot of bark

620
00:37:21,200 --> 00:37:22,920
咬起来也厉害
and a lot of bite.

621
00:37:26,650 --> 00:37:27,960
你喜欢她吗
Do you like her?

622
00:37:28,730 --> 00:37:29,730
什么
What?

623
00:37:29,730 --> 00:37:30,810
就像是
You know, like...

624
00:37:31,790 --> 00:37:33,510
像是  喜欢她
like, like her.

625
00:37:33,510 --> 00:37:34,890
不
No.

626
00:37:34,900 --> 00:37:36,710
你怎么会说这种话
Why would you even say something like that?

627
00:37:36,710 --> 00:37:37,960
我只是问问
I'm just asking.

628
00:37:38,390 --> 00:37:40,820
我认识的人当中没几个是同志
I don't know that many people of the gay persuasion.

629
00:37:40,820 --> 00:37:42,790
看起来你们很合得来
It just looked like maybe you two were getting along.

630
00:37:42,790 --> 00:37:44,660
抱歉  你根本不知道你在说什么
I'm sorry, but you have no idea what you're talking about.

631
00:37:44,660 --> 00:37:46,470
我就是不知道  所以我才问的
I didn't say that I did. That's why I was asking.

632
00:37:46,470 --> 00:37:48,270
帕姆和我  永远不可能
Pam and me-- never gonna happen.

633
00:37:48,270 --> 00:37:50,820
好  好的  抱歉问你这个
Okay. Fine. Sorry I asked.

634
00:37:50,830 --> 00:37:53,470
为什么你要操心我的事
Why you feel the need to get all up in my business?

635
00:37:56,580 --> 00:37:58,140
因为我没有朋友
'Cause I don't have any friends.

636
00:37:59,700 --> 00:38:00,970
没有人可以和我谈心
I don't have anyone to talk to.

637
00:38:00,970 --> 00:38:03,260
就算是你生气了
And even if you freak out

638
00:38:03,260 --> 00:38:05,370
气得发疯  又要打我一顿
and go crazy now and again and beat me up,

639
00:38:05,370 --> 00:38:07,200
我现在是吸血鬼  很快就好了
I'm a vampire now, so I heal.

640
00:38:08,590 --> 00:38:10,020
我喜欢和你聊天
And I like talking to you.

641
00:38:12,230 --> 00:38:14,210
过会儿我给你找个尖牙控
I'll try and bring you a fangbanger later.

642
00:38:16,560 --> 00:38:17,730
谢谢
Thanks.

643
00:38:55,330 --> 00:38:57,010
我们的真血卖光了
We're all out of Tru Blood.

644
00:38:57,810 --> 00:38:59,090
还有别的东西吗
What else you serving?

645
00:38:59,360 --> 00:39:01,540
你尽可以在这些不错的人类样品中
You're welcome to try your luck with this fine

646
00:39:01,540 --> 00:39:03,110
试试运气
cross section of humanity.

647
00:39:04,520 --> 00:39:07,130
我在找人  我的后裔
I'm looking for someone. My progeny.

648
00:39:07,410 --> 00:39:08,760
他是这个地区的治安官
He's sheriff of these parts.

649
00:39:09,920 --> 00:39:11,330
昨晚来过
Came by here last night.

650
00:39:12,110 --> 00:39:14,520
我们交了税  他就走了
We paid our taxes and he moved on.

651
00:39:14,790 --> 00:39:16,580
-就这样  -对
- Oh, is that right? - Yeah.

652
00:39:18,510 --> 00:39:21,170
我能闻到你身上有以利亚的血
I can smell Elijah's blood on you.

653
00:39:22,030 --> 00:39:24,000
创造者永远都能知道
A maker always knows

654
00:39:24,000 --> 00:39:26,140
她的后裔何时死了
when her progeny dies.

655
00:39:26,770 --> 00:39:28,740
虽然有二百零四个后裔
He was only one of 204,

656
00:39:28,750 --> 00:39:31,780
他的死依然像刺中你心脏的冰针
but it's still like a cold spike in your heart.

657
00:39:33,230 --> 00:39:35,890
谁杀了他  是你吗
Who killed him? Was it you?

658
00:39:36,220 --> 00:39:37,480
是姐姐我
It was me.

659
00:39:40,620 --> 00:39:42,920
你哪儿来的胆子
What possessed you

660
00:39:43,270 --> 00:39:44,970
敢杀我的后裔
to murder my progeny?

661
00:39:45,260 --> 00:39:48,070
他惹毛我了
He was getting on my nerves.

662
00:39:50,780 --> 00:39:54,090
以真正的吸血鬼当权者之名
In the name of the one true Vampire Authority,

663
00:39:54,090 --> 00:39:57,320
其智慧与正义皆由莉莉丝所赐
in whose wisdom and justice all is made manifest by Lilith,

664
00:39:57,610 --> 00:40:02,130
我以谋杀治安官以利亚·斯多莫的罪名逮捕你
I arrest you for the murder of Sheriff Elijah Stormer.

665
00:40:18,350 --> 00:40:20,540
你的爸爸在找你
Your daddy is looking for you.

666
00:40:30,830 --> 00:40:34,100
比尔·康普顿
Bill Compton.

667
00:40:40,970 --> 00:40:43,190
我们只能有一个领袖
Only one can lead us.

668
00:40:43,530 --> 00:40:45,280
我选择你
I choose you.

669
00:40:51,250 --> 00:40:52,840
我难当此任
I'm not worthy.

670
00:40:55,390 --> 00:40:57,060
饮吾之血
Drink of me.

671
00:40:59,470 --> 00:41:02,360
尽饮吾之血
Drink all of me.

672
00:41:37,730 --> 00:41:39,280
他干翻那家伙了
He's all over the guy.

673
00:41:39,560 --> 00:41:42,380
那臭小子完全顶不住  你们这些瞎子
He's hanging all over the fucking guy, you blind prick!

674
00:41:45,530 --> 00:41:48,620
-哈哈  -操
- Yeah. - Ah! Fuckin' A!

675
00:41:49,160 --> 00:41:50,580
操
Fuckin' A.

676
00:41:50,950 --> 00:41:52,190
我在恢复
I'm healing.

677
00:41:52,790 --> 00:41:55,190
别出去
Don't go out there.

678
00:41:58,440 --> 00:42:00,240
他们往里夫斯家去了
They're heading over to the Reeves place.

679
00:42:00,250 --> 00:42:02,580
你总爱逞英雄
You always got to be the fuckin' hero.

680
00:42:02,920 --> 00:42:04,930
我是你养大的男子汉  真正的狼
You raised me to be a man and a wolf,

681
00:42:05,140 --> 00:42:06,540
我不是贼  不当懦夫
not a thief and a coward.

682
00:42:31,070 --> 00:42:31,970
耶稣啊
Jesus!

683
00:42:32,770 --> 00:42:34,060
其实我见过他
I actually met him.

684
00:42:34,340 --> 00:42:37,440
就是个浑身广藿香  无聊的嬉皮士
He was a boring hippie who stank of patchouli.

685
00:42:38,790 --> 00:42:40,190
嗨  杰森
Hi, Jason.

686
00:42:41,000 --> 00:42:42,320
看啊
Oh, look.

687
00:42:42,320 --> 00:42:45,270
这块三明治好大
We got ourselves a hunk sandwich.

688
00:42:45,270 --> 00:42:46,610
都他妈的别碰我
Get your fucking hands off me.

689
00:42:46,610 --> 00:42:48,170
滚远点
Get off me!

690
00:42:48,350 --> 00:42:49,510
你妹妹呢
Where's your sister?

691
00:42:50,020 --> 00:42:51,700
你们永远别想找到她
Yeah, you ain't never gonna find her.

692
00:42:51,700 --> 00:42:53,700
她在的地方  你们进不去
'Cause she's someplace you can't get in.

693
00:42:53,700 --> 00:42:55,540
那是什么地方
And where might that be?

694
00:42:55,990 --> 00:42:57,410
她跟精灵们在一起
She's with the fairies.

695
00:42:59,130 --> 00:43:01,050
什么精灵们
What fairies?

696
00:43:01,050 --> 00:43:02,440
很多很多
There's a bunch of them.

697
00:43:02,690 --> 00:43:05,140
他们在提波多农场旁有个俱乐部
They got a club out by the Thibodeaux Farm.

698
00:43:07,640 --> 00:43:11,760
不如你带我们去那个自助餐会吧
How about you lead us to this spritely smorgasbord?

699
00:43:11,760 --> 00:43:12,750
好啊
Okay.

700
00:43:13,060 --> 00:43:14,930
找到她之前保持这个状态
Stay just like that until we find her.

701
00:43:14,940 --> 00:43:16,000
没问题
Oh, you bet.

702
00:43:16,810 --> 00:43:18,700
谁能给你带来美好时光
Who knows how to show you a good time?

703
00:43:18,700 --> 00:43:20,020
当然是你
You do.

704
00:43:20,020 --> 00:43:21,690
滚出来
Come out here!

705
00:43:21,690 --> 00:43:25,740
-我们不会伤害你们  -只是要吃了你们
- We're not gonna hurt ya. - We're just gonna eat ya.

706
00:43:25,740 --> 00:43:27,460
-把这玩意儿翻过来  -滚远点
- Let's flip this fucker. - Leave her be!

707
00:43:31,170 --> 00:43:32,840
我们死的时候是黏糊糊的啊
When we die, we're goo?

708
00:43:32,840 --> 00:43:34,100
你们已经死了
You're already dead.

709
00:43:41,250 --> 00:43:42,910
扭断他的脑袋
Twist his head off!

710
00:43:45,550 --> 00:43:46,700
混蛋
Motherfucker.

711
00:43:48,480 --> 00:43:49,570
不要
No!

712
00:44:10,580 --> 00:44:12,380
-艾玛  -操
- Emma? - Oh, shit.

713
00:44:12,380 --> 00:44:13,950
你们是什么怪物
What the fuck kind of monsters are you?

714
00:44:16,940 --> 00:44:18,950
天啊  宝贝儿
Oh, my God. Hey there, baby.

715
00:44:18,950 --> 00:44:21,370
你没事了  别变身
You're fine. Just don't shift.

716
00:44:22,340 --> 00:44:23,440
抓紧时间
We have to hurry.

717
00:44:24,220 --> 00:44:25,810
你俩在外面做什么
What the fuck are you doing out?

718
00:44:27,800 --> 00:44:29,590
-快变身  -我不会丢下她
- Shift. - I'm not gonna leave her.

719
00:44:30,230 --> 00:44:31,310
绝不
We won't.

720
00:44:31,310 --> 00:44:33,730
康普顿法官要吃早餐
Chancellor Compton is requesting his breakfast.

721
00:44:34,200 --> 00:44:35,540
等等
Hey, wait.

722
00:44:37,230 --> 00:44:38,010
我去
I'll go.

723
00:44:38,010 --> 00:44:40,590
头一个啊  你这么着急去送死
That's a first. You in a hurry to die?

724
00:44:40,590 --> 00:44:42,090
早完早了事
Just as soon get it over with.

725
00:44:42,390 --> 00:44:44,300
你一定要不惜代价
Do whatever you have to!

726
00:44:44,910 --> 00:44:45,710
山姆
Sam!

727
00:45:05,400 --> 00:45:06,420
法官
Chancellor?

728
00:45:11,930 --> 00:45:14,000
莉莉丝找我了
Lilith came to me.

729
00:45:16,710 --> 00:45:18,230
她选了我
She chose me.

730
00:45:22,220 --> 00:45:23,290
不对
No.

731
00:45:25,130 --> 00:45:26,400
她选的是我
She chose me!

732
00:45:35,470 --> 00:45:36,770
带她去牢房
Take her to the cells.

733
00:45:37,030 --> 00:45:40,110
切尔西  请广播通知康普顿法官
Chelsea, will you please page Chancellor Compton?

734
00:45:48,800 --> 00:45:50,170
你他妈的怎么在这儿
What the fuck are you doing here?

735
00:45:50,180 --> 00:45:53,480
你来干什么  帮帮卢娜
What are you doing here? Hey, help Luna!

736
00:45:53,480 --> 00:45:55,260
卢娜是哪根葱
Who the fuck is Luna?

737
00:45:55,260 --> 00:45:56,660
操你
Fuck you!

738
00:46:03,500 --> 00:46:05,060
康普顿法官
Chancellor Compton,

739
00:46:05,060 --> 00:46:07,740
您的后裔在大厅里等您
your progeny will meet you in the main chamber.

740
00:46:21,050 --> 00:46:22,620
你有什么要说的吗
What do you have to say for yourself?

741
00:46:23,420 --> 00:46:24,480
对不起
I'm sorry.

742
00:46:26,000 --> 00:46:27,430
我
I just--

743
00:46:28,700 --> 00:46:30,480
我去了  杰森不乐意
when I got there, Jason wasn't into it.

744
00:46:30,490 --> 00:46:31,960
我觉得那样不对
I didn't think it was right.

745
00:46:32,180 --> 00:46:35,750
所以你觉得杀掉两个吸血鬼就对了
So you decided it would be better to kill two vampires instead?

746
00:46:36,210 --> 00:46:39,590
那个保安  他逼我转化他
That security guy, he was gonna make me turn him.

747
00:46:39,590 --> 00:46:42,850
他那是执行任务  服从我的命令
He was doing his job-- following my orders.

748
00:46:42,860 --> 00:46:45,600
你为区区一个人类牺牲两个吸血鬼
You chose a human over two vampires.

749
00:46:45,600 --> 00:46:47,490
他不是什么区区人类  他是杰森
He's not a human. He's Jason.

750
00:46:48,090 --> 00:46:49,710
你曾为了苏琪钉死了朗莎多
You staked Longshadow for Sookie.

751
00:46:49,720 --> 00:46:52,400
莉莉丝命令血族统治人类
Lilith commands that vampire hath dominion over human.

752
00:46:52,400 --> 00:46:54,190
管他什么莉莉丝
Who cares about Lilith?

753
00:46:54,380 --> 00:46:57,480
帕姆说你们正在群居  所以神智不正常
Pam says you are in a nest and it is making you crazy.

754
00:46:59,180 --> 00:47:00,980
你胆敢对抗我
Who are you to defy me?

755
00:47:03,250 --> 00:47:05,410
我是神选之人
I am the chosen one!

756
00:47:06,220 --> 00:47:07,930
莉莉丝选了我
Lilith chose me!

757
00:47:16,610 --> 00:47:18,370
我们只能有一个领袖
Only one can lead us.

758
00:47:18,990 --> 00:47:20,150
我选择你
I choose you.

759
00:47:21,830 --> 00:47:23,140
饮吾之血
Drink of me.

760
00:47:23,470 --> 00:47:25,200
尽饮吾之血
Drink all of me.

761
00:47:34,430 --> 00:47:35,750
宝贝儿  让我下车
Baby, let me out.

762
00:47:36,040 --> 00:47:37,980
宝贝儿  开门
Baby, open the door.

763
00:47:43,250 --> 00:47:45,420
这是什么味道
What is that smell?

764
00:47:45,770 --> 00:47:47,370
精灵
Fairy.

765
00:47:49,200 --> 00:47:50,150
他们在哪儿
Where are they?

766
00:47:50,150 --> 00:47:51,470
就在那边
Right there.

767
00:47:53,750 --> 00:47:54,650
哪里
Where?

768
00:47:55,810 --> 00:47:56,990
那边
There.

769
00:47:57,980 --> 00:48:00,800
-这味道  -在哪里
- That smell. - Where are they?

770
00:48:01,150 --> 00:48:04,380
我能感觉到  他们就在周围
I can feel them. They're all around me.

771
00:48:04,380 --> 00:48:07,620
这是什么精灵魔法
What fucking fairy magic is this?

772
00:48:10,270 --> 00:48:11,400
在哪儿
Where are they?

773
00:48:15,240 --> 00:48:17,650
哇哇
Oh, mercy!

774
00:48:28,250 --> 00:48:31,010
-还在等什么  -我们做好了战斗的准备
- What are you waiting for? - We're ready to fight.

775
00:48:31,020 --> 00:48:33,160
杰森把他们带过来  计划就是这样
Jason brought them here. That was the plan.

776
00:48:33,850 --> 00:48:35,080
计划变了
The plan has changed.

777
00:48:35,510 --> 00:48:37,520
你在哪儿  精灵
Where are you, fairy?

778
00:48:37,810 --> 00:48:40,130
苏琪·斯塔克豪斯  你不出来
Sookie Stackhouse, I will tear your brother

779
00:48:40,130 --> 00:48:41,870
我就把你哥哥的四肢挨个扯下来
limb from limb unless you show yourself.

780
00:48:42,110 --> 00:48:43,310
我们必须反抗
We have to fight them.

781
00:48:45,240 --> 00:48:47,400
我不会让你们出去送死
I'm not letting you out there to get yourselves killed.

782
00:48:47,400 --> 00:48:50,160
-你说我们...  -别担心  我来
- You said we were-- - Don't worry. I got this.

783
00:48:51,150 --> 00:48:54,100
苏琪·斯塔克豪斯
Sookie Stackhouse!

784
00:48:59,920 --> 00:49:01,390
太意外了
As I live and breathe.

785
00:49:03,010 --> 00:49:04,280
精灵
A fairy.

786
00:49:12,920 --> 00:49:14,170
厉害
Impressive.

787
00:49:14,480 --> 00:49:16,750
你真是强大
You are turbocharged.

788
00:49:19,890 --> 00:49:25,010
吸血鬼  我在此将你打入异界
Vampire, I hereby banish you to the realms and beyond.

789
00:49:25,010 --> 00:49:26,350
滚吧
Begone!

790
00:49:26,910 --> 00:49:28,200
杰森
Jason!

791
00:49:31,030 --> 00:49:32,030
杰森
Jason.

792
00:49:32,720 --> 00:49:34,430
我说了  滚蛋
I said begone.

793
00:49:50,530 --> 00:49:54,920
爽翻天了
Oh, sweet merciful fuck!

794
00:49:55,210 --> 00:49:57,380
太美味了
That was delicious!

795
00:49:57,880 --> 00:50:04,670
天堂  你的名字叫精灵
Heaven, thy name is fairy.

796
00:50:13,310 --> 00:50:15,690
天啊  他能看见我们
Oh, God. He can see us.

797
00:50:16,530 --> 00:50:19,400
万分感谢
Why, thank you so much.

798
00:50:21,010 --> 00:50:24,110
我很乐意享用晚餐
I'd love to come to dinner.

