1
00:02:50,600 --> 00:03:00,000
{\pos(190,278)}本字幕由YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

3
00:03:00,000 --> 00:03:05,000
{\pos(190,268)}翻译：Silmar  小舞  NoNopig  Eve  Greentie

5
00:03:05,000 --> 00:03:10,000
{\pos(190,268)}翻译：泰斯  时间轴：加森  子衿  烟幕迟迟

7
00:03:10,000 --> 00:03:15,000
{\pos(190,268)}后期： 孤帆   校对&总监： 泰斯·雪诺

9
00:04:14,990 --> 00:04:19,990
《真爱如血》第五季  第十二集
True Blood S05E12

10
00:00:00,200 --> 00:00:01,330
[前情提要]

11
00:00:01,330 --> 00:00:04,580
我们有罗素·爱丁顿和史蒂夫·纽林
We have video of Russell Edgington and Steve Newlin

12
00:00:04,580 --> 00:00:07,200
血洗兄弟会所的视频
eviscerating 22 fraternity brothers.

13
00:00:07,200 --> 00:00:09,090
如果我现在或将来发生任何事情
If anything happens to me now or in the future,

14
00:00:09,090 --> 00:00:11,460
这一视频将会向公众公开
this is gonna be released to the public.

15
00:00:12,270 --> 00:00:13,800
我要来一次大规模的魅惑行动
I'll go on a glamouring campaign,

16
00:00:13,800 --> 00:00:16,130
消除掉关于这个视频的一切记忆
eliminate all memory that the video exists.

17
00:00:16,130 --> 00:00:19,230
带几个安保队员去  可能需要支援
Take a security detail. Might need the backup.

18
00:00:21,650 --> 00:00:23,320
只是来给你们报个信
Just out warning folks.

19
00:00:23,320 --> 00:00:25,590
发生了多起新生吸血鬼袭击事件
Been a bunch of baby vamp attacks.

20
00:00:25,590 --> 00:00:26,840
滚远点
Leave her be!

21
00:00:28,600 --> 00:00:31,670
我们只能有一个领袖  我选择你
Only one can lead us. I choose you.

22
00:00:31,680 --> 00:00:33,720
喝了那血  通通喝掉
Drink the blood. Drink it all.

23
00:00:33,720 --> 00:00:36,850
-莉莉丝选了我  -她选了我
- Lilith chose me. - She chose me!

24
00:00:36,850 --> 00:00:39,650
罗素·爱丁顿不找到我决不罢休
Russell Edgington is gonna keep coming for me.

25
00:00:39,650 --> 00:00:42,700
抓到我以后  他就会把魔爪伸向你们
And after he's got me, he's gonna come for you.

26
00:00:42,700 --> 00:00:45,050
我能闻到你身上有以利亚的血
I can smell Elijah's blood on you.

27
00:00:45,050 --> 00:00:46,980
-谁杀了他  -是姐姐我
- Who killed him? - It was me.

28
00:00:46,990 --> 00:00:50,790
我以谋杀治安官以利亚·斯多莫的罪名逮捕你
I arrest you for the murder of Sheriff Elijah Stormer.

29
00:00:50,790 --> 00:00:53,300
-宝贝儿  -抓紧时间
- Hey, there, baby. - We have to hurry.

30
00:00:53,300 --> 00:00:55,120
你俩在外面做什么
What are you doing out?

31
00:00:55,290 --> 00:00:57,300
康普顿法官要吃早餐
Chancellor Compton is requesting his breakfast.

32
00:00:57,310 --> 00:00:58,870
-我去  -玛瑞拉
- I'll go. - Maurella.

33
00:00:58,870 --> 00:01:02,250
你发誓会保护我们爱的结晶
You swore to protect the fruit of our union.

34
00:01:02,250 --> 00:01:05,990
帕姆说你们正在群居  所以神智不正常
Pam says you are in a nest and it is making you crazy.

35
00:01:06,480 --> 00:01:08,800
我是神选之人
I am the chosen one!

36
00:01:08,800 --> 00:01:10,140
我选择你
I choose you.

37
00:01:10,150 --> 00:01:12,160
尽饮吾之血
Drink all of me.

38
00:01:12,160 --> 00:01:14,630
-你妹妹呢  -她在的地方  你们进不去
- Where's your sister? - She's someplace you can't get in.

39
00:01:14,630 --> 00:01:17,060
-那是什么地方  -她跟精灵们在一起
- And where might that be? - She's with the fairies.

40
00:01:17,060 --> 00:01:20,190
-他们在哪儿  -我们必须反抗
- Where are they? - We have to fight them.

41
00:01:20,210 --> 00:01:21,240
滚吧
Begone!

42
00:01:25,030 --> 00:01:26,870
天啊  他能看见我们
Oh, God. He can see us.

43
00:01:26,870 --> 00:01:29,570
我很乐意享用晚餐
I'd love to come to dinner.

44
00:01:35,990 --> 00:01:37,600
用光打他
Blast him!

45
00:01:52,760 --> 00:01:56,940
开玩笑  你们就这点儿本事
Seriously, is that the best you can do?

46
00:01:56,950 --> 00:01:59,460
我都感觉不到
I can't even feel it

47
00:01:59,800 --> 00:02:04,380
只是有一点小小的刺痛
except for a very slight tingling sensation,

48
00:02:04,380 --> 00:02:08,630
正好让我胃口大开  美丽的小精灵
which, unfortunately for you gorgeous little pixies,

49
00:02:08,630 --> 00:02:13,310
你们真是不走运哪
only whets my appetite!

50
00:02:31,950 --> 00:02:34,490
操
Oh, fuck.

51
00:02:46,420 --> 00:02:49,140
比我想象的还要美
Well, that felt even better than I thought it would.

52
00:04:21,180 --> 00:04:23,230
-杰森  -别去
- Jason! - No!

53
00:04:23,230 --> 00:04:25,070
-苏琪  -外面还有吸血鬼
- Sookie! - There are still vampires out there.

54
00:04:25,070 --> 00:04:26,460
杰森
Jason!

55
00:04:28,800 --> 00:04:31,380
这美妙的味道是什么
What is that amazing smell?

56
00:04:32,660 --> 00:04:34,830
不许你吸苏琪的血
You will not feed on Sookie.

57
00:04:34,830 --> 00:04:37,710
-她是什么  -她是个女招待
- What is she? - She's a waitress,

58
00:04:37,710 --> 00:04:40,510
救过我不止一次
a waitress who's saved my life more than once

59
00:04:40,510 --> 00:04:43,840
今晚正是她的恐惧将我带到这里
and whose fear vibe very graciously brought me here tonight,

60
00:04:43,840 --> 00:04:46,440
得以了结一桩陈年旧怨
allowing me to settle an ancient debt.

61
00:04:46,870 --> 00:04:48,540
这事儿我要多谢你
Thank you for that, by the way.

62
00:04:48,550 --> 00:04:50,410
可是我想要她
But I want her.

63
00:04:51,780 --> 00:04:53,720
你真的这样缺乏自制力吗
Are you really this undisciplined?

64
00:04:54,850 --> 00:04:58,190
天哪  杰森  你没事吧
God, Jason. Are you okay?

65
00:04:58,190 --> 00:04:59,980
杰森  醒醒
Jason, wake up.

66
00:04:59,990 --> 00:05:02,260
父亲会非常失望的
Now, Father would be very disappointed.

67
00:05:02,260 --> 00:05:05,010
-杰森  拜托  -好吧  我不吃她
- Jason, come on. - All right, I won't eat her.

68
00:05:05,010 --> 00:05:07,610
-向格瑞克发誓  -拜托
- Swear on Godric. - Please.

69
00:05:08,450 --> 00:05:12,960
-杰森  醒醒  -向格瑞克发誓
- Jason, come on. - Swear on Godric.

70
00:05:13,300 --> 00:05:16,540
我向格瑞克发誓
I swear on Godric.

71
00:05:16,550 --> 00:05:19,050
醒醒呀  杰森
Wake up. Jason.

72
00:05:23,420 --> 00:05:25,000
杰森  你没事吧
Jason, are you okay?

73
00:05:27,070 --> 00:05:30,100
杰森宝贝
Jason, baby.

74
00:05:30,760 --> 00:05:32,180
妈妈
Mama?

75
00:05:33,660 --> 00:05:35,110
什么
What?

76
00:05:36,810 --> 00:05:38,980
杰森  是我呀  苏琪
Jason, it's me, Sookie.

77
00:05:42,300 --> 00:05:44,260
饮吾之血
Drink of me.

78
00:05:44,270 --> 00:05:48,180
尽饮吾之血
Drink all of me.

79
00:05:53,590 --> 00:05:55,010
康普顿法官
Chancellor Compton.

80
00:05:55,010 --> 00:05:57,390
很好  早餐
Oh, good. Breakfast.

81
00:06:01,600 --> 00:06:03,260
这是变形人
This is a shifter.

82
00:06:05,010 --> 00:06:06,590
你们闻不出区别吗
Can you not smell the difference?

83
00:06:06,600 --> 00:06:10,090
还真是没见识过外面的世界
You guys really don't spend much time in the outside world, do you?

84
00:06:10,870 --> 00:06:12,300
让他说话
Ungag him.

85
00:06:13,090 --> 00:06:15,300
比尔  请你听我说
Bill, just hear me out.

86
00:06:15,300 --> 00:06:16,790
你不该来
You should never have come here.

87
00:06:16,790 --> 00:06:19,210
我女朋友的女儿被史蒂夫·纽林绑架了
My girlfriend's daughter was kidnapped by Steve Newlin.

88
00:06:19,210 --> 00:06:20,510
我只想把她找回来
I just want to get her back.

89
00:06:20,510 --> 00:06:21,700
可是你知道的太多了
But now you know too much.

90
00:06:21,700 --> 00:06:24,930
-我可以保证  绝不会  -我不能相信
- I give you my word, I will never... - I can't trust that!

91
00:06:36,280 --> 00:06:39,580
该死  他飞进通风管了
God damn it, he flew into the ventilation duct.

92
00:06:39,580 --> 00:06:43,400
还有  我们被入侵了
Oh, and by the way, we've been breached.

93
00:06:45,730 --> 00:06:48,880
我活了这么久怎么会从没见过精灵
How could I have lived for so long and never encountered a fairy?

94
00:06:48,880 --> 00:06:50,210
因为你唯一关心的事情
Because the only thing you ever cared about

95
00:06:50,210 --> 00:06:52,690
就是在当权者中往上爬
was rising up the ranks of the Authority.

96
00:06:53,000 --> 00:06:54,220
成果斐然
Overachiever.

97
00:06:54,220 --> 00:06:57,000
总得有人做些事情让父亲骄傲吧
Well, somebody had to do something to make Father proud.

98
00:06:57,000 --> 00:06:59,260
他更爱我一定让你嫉妒得要死
It must kill you that he loved me more.

99
00:06:59,260 --> 00:07:01,600
你这样以为才让我烦到死
It kills me that you think he did.

100
00:07:03,610 --> 00:07:05,270
他们抓了帕姆
They got Pam.

101
00:07:08,400 --> 00:07:10,680
你还回来真是疯了
You're insane to go back in there.

102
00:07:10,680 --> 00:07:13,650
她是我的后裔  诺拉  她是一家人
She's my progeny, Nora. She's family.

103
00:07:13,650 --> 00:07:15,430
她当过妓女
She's a former prostitute.

104
00:07:15,430 --> 00:07:19,000
把这些转移到安全的地方我们就走
We're going just as soon as we stash this somewhere safe.

105
00:07:19,000 --> 00:07:21,080
你确定这玩意不透光
You sure this thing is light-tight?

106
00:07:21,080 --> 00:07:22,610
看着像特百惠保鲜盒
Looks like Tupperware.

107
00:07:22,610 --> 00:07:25,540
百分百不透光  而且非常结实
It's 100% light-tight and virtually indestructible.

108
00:07:25,540 --> 00:07:28,110
开玩笑吗  连我也能弄坏它
Are you kidding? Even I can destroy it.

109
00:07:29,880 --> 00:07:32,930
顺便说一下  她也是一家人  要客气
Oh, by the way, she's family, too. So be nice to her.

110
00:07:40,930 --> 00:07:43,890
或许我该送你去急诊室
Maybe I should take you to the emergency room.

111
00:07:44,210 --> 00:07:45,910
你的样子很古怪
You're acting pretty weird.

112
00:07:45,910 --> 00:07:48,770
你妹妹现在还没被尖牙鬼杀死真是个奇迹
It's a wonder one of those fangers ain't killed your baby sister by now.

113
00:07:48,770 --> 00:07:50,550
他们可是前仆后继
Lord knows they tried.

114
00:07:50,550 --> 00:07:53,120
杰森  你有没有听到我说话
Jason, are you even hearing me?

115
00:07:53,430 --> 00:07:54,830
搞什么
What the...?

116
00:07:55,050 --> 00:07:58,130
天哪  泰拉
Oh, my God, Tara.

117
00:07:58,570 --> 00:07:59,570
你没事吧
Are you okay?

118
00:07:59,570 --> 00:08:02,430
操  泰拉
Oh, fuck, Tara.

119
00:08:02,430 --> 00:08:04,730
我忘了你现在...
I forgot that you were...

120
00:08:04,740 --> 00:08:06,260
跟他们一样了
one of them.

121
00:08:06,350 --> 00:08:08,560
我倒想起来了  你都还没有
Well, this reminds me. You still haven't gotten around

122
00:08:08,560 --> 00:08:11,230
把房子的所有权还给我
to transferring the ownership of my house back to me.

123
00:08:11,230 --> 00:08:13,540
我妈妈的房子归尖牙鬼所有了
A fucking fanger owns my mama's house?

124
00:08:13,540 --> 00:08:15,340
明晚马上转给你
I'll do it first thing tomorrow night.

125
00:08:15,340 --> 00:08:17,980
-还要明晚  -如果我们能活过今晚
- Ain't right. - If we survive tonight.

126
00:08:17,980 --> 00:08:19,850
你说什么胡话呢
What the fuck are you talking about?

127
00:08:19,860 --> 00:08:22,730
我需要你跟我们去吸血鬼总部
I need you to come with us into the Vampire Authority.

128
00:08:22,910 --> 00:08:24,680
他们抓了比尔和杰西卡
They got Bill and Jessica.

129
00:08:25,980 --> 00:08:28,820
-还有帕姆  -你欠帕姆的
- And Pam. - And you owe Pam.

130
00:08:29,310 --> 00:08:30,900
别他妈扯了
There ain't no fucking way

131
00:08:30,900 --> 00:08:33,630
我才不让她跟你们走
I'm gonna let her go anywhere with you.

132
00:08:33,630 --> 00:08:35,090
杰森  让我处理
Jason, I got this.

133
00:08:35,090 --> 00:08:36,750
爸爸妈妈怎么办
What about Mama and Daddy?

134
00:08:36,750 --> 00:08:39,810
苏克  你得告诉这群尖牙鬼
Sook, you ought to tell all these fucking fangers

135
00:08:39,810 --> 00:08:42,520
滚回他们的地狱去
to go back to hell where they came from.

136
00:08:44,110 --> 00:08:45,810
好笑吗  尖牙鬼
Something funny, fanger?

137
00:08:45,810 --> 00:08:48,270
-很好笑  血袋  -吸血虫
- Yes, bloodbag. - Leech.

138
00:08:48,270 --> 00:08:49,710
-废气桶  -死僵尸
- Breather. - Dead fuck.

139
00:08:49,710 --> 00:08:52,250
-酒囊饭袋  -别耍小孩子脾气了
- Meatsack. - Stop acting like children.

140
00:08:52,260 --> 00:08:55,300
你闻起来像我梦里的什么东西
You smell like something I once dreamed of.

141
00:08:55,330 --> 00:08:57,850
埃里克  请你让你妹妹别那样看着我
Eric, please ask your sister not to look at me like that.

142
00:08:57,860 --> 00:09:00,240
我都已经知道了
Look, I already know vampires

143
00:09:00,240 --> 00:09:02,320
真血工厂爆炸是吸血鬼幕后主使的
are behind the Tru Blood factory bombings.

144
00:09:02,320 --> 00:09:04,700
是比尔幕后主使的
Bill was behind those bombings.

145
00:09:05,140 --> 00:09:08,850
他要强迫主流派吸血鬼吸食人血
And he did it to force mainstreaming vampires to feed on humans.

146
00:09:08,850 --> 00:09:09,890
我们得把他弄出来
Now, we've got to get him out of there

147
00:09:09,890 --> 00:09:12,010
趁他还没完全失去自我
before he loses himself completely.

148
00:09:12,590 --> 00:09:14,940
如果现在还有人能打动他
Now, if anybody can get through to him,

149
00:09:17,330 --> 00:09:18,760
就是你了
it's you.

150
00:09:19,970 --> 00:09:22,200
而且你欠帕姆的
And you owe Pam.

151
00:09:28,520 --> 00:09:29,920
好吧
Okay.

152
00:09:30,200 --> 00:09:34,150
苏克  求你别去
Sook, please don't do this.

153
00:09:34,150 --> 00:09:36,350
你不想救杰西卡吗
Don't you want to save Jessica?

154
00:09:37,830 --> 00:09:41,020
想想有多少吸血鬼可以杀  小帅哥
Just think how many vampers you can kill in there, champ.

155
00:09:43,910 --> 00:09:45,310
好吧
Okay.

156
00:09:46,230 --> 00:09:47,400
但我要跟你去
But I'm coming with you.

157
00:09:47,400 --> 00:09:49,720
亲爱的  别犯傻
Oh, sweetie, don't be a fool.

158
00:09:49,720 --> 00:09:53,080
我想犯傻时就能犯傻
If I wanna be a fool, then I will be a fool.

159
00:09:53,400 --> 00:09:56,490
这是我生为美国人天赋的权利
That is my God-given right as an American.

160
00:09:58,130 --> 00:09:59,770
被入侵
Breached.

161
00:10:00,600 --> 00:10:02,920
这是什么意思
What does that mean exactly?

162
00:10:03,270 --> 00:10:07,010
意思就是  巡视通道和围墙的
It means that whether you patrol our halls

163
00:10:07,010 --> 00:10:10,230
盯着监控器的
or our borders, you watch a surveillance screen

164
00:10:10,230 --> 00:10:12,420
或者看守活人储备库的
or you tend to our human livestock,

165
00:10:12,420 --> 00:10:14,710
有人搞砸了
you fucked up.

166
00:10:15,740 --> 00:10:18,430
你知不知道有多少人
Do you have any idea how many people,

167
00:10:18,430 --> 00:10:21,810
无论人类还是吸血鬼  希望看到我们全死光
human and vampire, want to see us all dead?

168
00:10:21,810 --> 00:10:24,600
多谢你们给他们大开方便之门
Well, thanks for making it easier for them.

169
00:10:25,170 --> 00:10:28,500
可是最最至关重要的
But ultimately what matters most

170
00:10:28,700 --> 00:10:32,220
是那扇门里面的东西
is what lies just on the other side of that door.

171
00:10:33,730 --> 00:10:37,460
我们最早的祖先实实在在的精华
The actual essence of the very first of our kind.

172
00:10:37,460 --> 00:10:40,180
神为我们规划的蓝图
God's blueprint for us.

173
00:10:42,260 --> 00:10:45,820
给我在这儿挖地三尺
Scour every inch of this place.

174
00:10:45,820 --> 00:10:49,550
好好找找诸如老鼠  苍蝇
Look for rats, mice, flies,

175
00:10:49,550 --> 00:10:52,620
蟑螂  白蚁  跳蚤之类的
cockroaches, termites, fleas.

176
00:10:52,620 --> 00:10:53,980
尽力搜
Have fun.

177
00:10:53,980 --> 00:10:55,820
找到什么就灭掉什么
Whatever you find, kill it.

178
00:10:55,820 --> 00:10:59,200
如果它死后没变回人形
And if it doesn't shift back into human form after it's dead,

179
00:10:59,200 --> 00:11:00,980
那就继续搜
then keep on looking.

180
00:11:02,660 --> 00:11:04,220
解散
Dismissed.

181
00:11:18,800 --> 00:11:21,420
你见过肯杰达法官吗
Have you seen Chancellor Akinjide?

182
00:11:23,950 --> 00:11:26,580
早些时候我看到他在圣血祭坛
I found him earlier in the blood shrine.

183
00:11:27,150 --> 00:11:30,150
他打算喝掉所有的圣血
He was about to drink all of the sacred blood.

184
00:11:31,090 --> 00:11:34,530
他说莉莉丝向他显身了
He said Lilith had appeared to him

185
00:11:35,330 --> 00:11:38,650
选择了他来领导我们
and chosen him to lead us.

186
00:11:41,290 --> 00:11:42,920
所以我杀了他
So I killed him.

187
00:11:45,230 --> 00:11:47,510
因为莉莉丝向我显身了
Because Lilith appeared to me.

188
00:12:00,230 --> 00:12:03,800
她说你是她选的人
She said you were chosen.

189
00:12:04,640 --> 00:12:07,850
她让我来服侍你  保护你
She told me to serve and protect you.

190
00:12:08,900 --> 00:12:13,900
她说你是新时代的先知
She said you were the prophet for the new age.

191
00:12:40,640 --> 00:12:42,180
放松  宝贝
Just breathe, baby.

192
00:12:42,180 --> 00:12:44,800
我们很快就会离开这里  好吗
We're gonna get out of here soon, okay?

193
00:12:44,800 --> 00:12:46,250
我保证
I promise.

194
00:12:50,610 --> 00:12:51,560
我劝过他
I tried reasoning.

195
00:12:51,560 --> 00:12:54,330
不过显然他已经神经错乱了
Apparently he's lost his motherfucking mind.

196
00:12:54,750 --> 00:12:56,610
我要到处探查一下
I'm gonna case this place,

197
00:12:56,750 --> 00:12:58,330
这地方很大  而且
which is huge, by the way,

198
00:12:58,330 --> 00:13:00,560
到处都是监控摄像头
and there are surveillance cameras everywhere.

199
00:13:00,560 --> 00:13:02,180
所以如果他们来抓你  就变形
So if they come for you, shift.

200
00:13:02,180 --> 00:13:03,810
我不会丢下她
I'm not leaving her.

201
00:13:05,300 --> 00:13:07,090
艾玛很安全
Emma's safe.

202
00:13:07,160 --> 00:13:09,210
她是宠物  他们不会吃狼人的
She's a pet. They don't feed on wolves.

203
00:13:09,210 --> 00:13:11,360
我不会离开她
I'm not leaving her.

204
00:13:11,690 --> 00:13:14,700
你死了也帮不上忙啊  对不对
You're not gonna be much use to her dead, now, are you?

205
00:13:16,070 --> 00:13:17,490
听好了
Now listen.

206
00:13:17,530 --> 00:13:19,830
我会尽量早点回来
I'll be back as soon as I can.

207
00:13:19,990 --> 00:13:23,800
如果他们来抓你  就变形逃跑
If they come for you, shift and escape.

208
00:13:23,800 --> 00:13:26,530
天花板上有通风管道
There's ventilation ducts in the ceiling.

209
00:13:26,540 --> 00:13:30,160
我会来找你  再想办法接走艾玛
I'll find you and we'll come back for Emma.

210
00:13:32,390 --> 00:13:33,860
祝你好运
Good luck.

211
00:13:40,080 --> 00:13:41,340
别害怕
Don't be scared.

212
00:13:41,350 --> 00:13:44,360
他们两个都成了宗教的狂热分子
They're religious fanatics, both of them.

213
00:13:45,220 --> 00:13:48,110
比尔我倒是完全相信
Well, I can totally believe it about Bill.

214
00:13:48,110 --> 00:13:50,820
他总是没事找事觉得愧疚
He's always looking for something to feel guilty about.

215
00:13:50,820 --> 00:13:52,960
但埃里克  不可能
But Eric, no way.

216
00:13:52,960 --> 00:13:54,410
我告诉你吧  他们比我那开教堂的叔叔
I'm telling you, they're worse than my uncle

217
00:13:54,420 --> 00:13:55,660
还要疯狂
who started his own church.

218
00:13:55,660 --> 00:13:58,360
他在我堂弟们很小的时候就告诉他们
He told my cousins there was no Santa Claus when they were little

219
00:13:58,360 --> 00:14:01,390
圣诞老人根本不存在  这样耶稣就没对手了
just so that Jesus wouldn't have any competition.

220
00:14:02,460 --> 00:14:06,060
-埃里克总是取笑宗教  -在这儿可不是
- Eric has always made such fun of religion. - Not in here.

221
00:14:06,060 --> 00:14:07,540
他们就像入了邪教
It's like they're in a cult.

222
00:14:07,540 --> 00:14:08,980
他们的眼神变得疯狂
You know, their eyes get crazy.

223
00:14:08,980 --> 00:14:11,590
你知道疯子加疯子有多疯吗
And you know how crazy feeds crazy?

224
00:14:11,590 --> 00:14:12,750
他们要征服世界
They want to conquer the world and

225
00:14:12,750 --> 00:14:13,990
他们也够疯狂去干那傻事
they're just crazy enough to do it.

226
00:14:13,990 --> 00:14:16,490
他们根本不在乎有多少人会受伤
And it doesn't matter how many people get hurt

227
00:14:16,490 --> 00:14:17,920
或是死亡
or killed.

228
00:14:18,300 --> 00:14:21,530
永生之后最糟糕的事
One of the worst things about being immortal

229
00:14:21,530 --> 00:14:24,360
就是只能看着同样的傻事
is having to watch the same stupid scenario

230
00:14:24,360 --> 00:14:26,390
一遍又一遍发生
happen over and over.

231
00:14:26,400 --> 00:14:28,400
一般来说是人类
It's usually the humans, though.

232
00:14:28,400 --> 00:14:31,470
这次倒是证明了我们跟人类一样笨
Guess this proves we're just as fucking retarded as they are.

233
00:14:31,470 --> 00:14:32,320
我还是不敢相信
I still can't believe

234
00:14:32,330 --> 00:14:34,100
埃里克和比尔没去警告苏琪
Eric and Bill weren't even gonna warn Sookie

235
00:14:34,100 --> 00:14:35,730
罗素·爱丁顿在追杀她
Russell Edgington was coming after her.

236
00:14:35,730 --> 00:14:38,980
怎么总跟该死的苏琪扯上关系
Must all roads lead to fucking Sookie?

237
00:14:38,980 --> 00:14:40,820
他们居然会允许罗素吸干她
They were just gonna let him drain her,

238
00:14:40,820 --> 00:14:43,510
就因为这是血族圣经上说的
all because according to their vampire Bible,

239
00:14:43,510 --> 00:14:45,410
说她可憎可恶
she's an abomination.

240
00:14:46,760 --> 00:14:49,980
这宗教理论还是有几分道理的嘛
Maybe there's something to this religion after all.

241
00:14:57,040 --> 00:15:00,380
我们俩今早好不容易才猎到鹿
It took both of us to take that buck down this morning.

242
00:15:00,390 --> 00:15:03,000
如果你烤焦了那就可惜了
Sure would be a shame if you overcooked it.

243
00:15:05,380 --> 00:15:06,890
干掉一个吸血鬼  忽然之间
Take down one vamp, and all of a sudden

244
00:15:06,890 --> 00:15:09,190
你就无所不知了吗
you're the world's expert on everything?

245
00:15:10,590 --> 00:15:13,240
对我的衣着有什么建议吗
Any advice you want to give me on how I'm dressed?

246
00:15:13,240 --> 00:15:15,900
既然你提到了  我还真有一点建议
Now that you mention it, I do have a few ideas

247
00:15:15,900 --> 00:15:18,340
可以让你扬长避短
of how you can play to your strengths a little better.

248
00:15:19,270 --> 00:15:21,350
或许我们可以去做个美甲
Maybe we can go get a mani-pedi.

249
00:15:25,590 --> 00:15:27,790
为人父母最糟的是
Worst part of being a parent--

250
00:15:30,040 --> 00:15:32,580
不论你如何努力  你都无法阻止你的孩子
no matter how hard you try, you can't keep your kids

251
00:15:32,590 --> 00:15:36,320
了解到这个世界的丑恶
from eventually learning what a shithole this world is,

252
00:15:36,910 --> 00:15:40,250
腐败  卑鄙  霸道
how corrupt, mean, arbitrary.

253
00:15:40,250 --> 00:15:42,880
你想为他们遮风挡雨
And you just want to shield them from it,

254
00:15:43,130 --> 00:15:45,890
让他们相信生活是安全而又美好的
let them believe life is safe and fair.

255
00:15:46,790 --> 00:15:48,820
恶人有恶报
Bad gets punished.

256
00:15:49,560 --> 00:15:51,430
好人有好报
Good gets rewarded.

257
00:15:52,010 --> 00:15:53,780
因为如果他们能相信
'Cause if they can believe that,

258
00:15:53,790 --> 00:15:55,890
那你也可以相信了
you almost can, too.

259
00:15:56,600 --> 00:15:58,860
可是呢  当你成了教给他们
But when you yourself end up being the one

260
00:15:58,860 --> 00:16:01,570
这世界有多丑恶的人
to teach them how fucked up things are...

261
00:16:03,610 --> 00:16:07,060
那么  这事情就无法挽回了
well, that's a hell of a thing to ever come back from.

262
00:16:07,930 --> 00:16:09,390
老爸
Dad,

263
00:16:10,410 --> 00:16:13,280
我之前就听到过这说法
I heard this exact same speech before.

264
00:16:14,380 --> 00:16:16,070
还不止一次
More than once.

265
00:16:16,150 --> 00:16:17,710
豪言壮语不错
Words are great...

266
00:16:18,680 --> 00:16:20,370
付诸行动更好
deeds are better.

267
00:16:20,540 --> 00:16:24,590
是啊  我总是光说不练啊  对吧
Yup, it's the deeds I always had a hard time with, huh?

268
00:16:25,000 --> 00:16:26,470
也不总是
Not always.

269
00:16:32,600 --> 00:16:34,640
谢天谢地你在这里  埃尔希德
Thank God you're here, Alcide.

270
00:16:34,640 --> 00:16:36,160
我不知道还有什么地方能去
I don't know where else I would have turned.

271
00:16:36,160 --> 00:16:38,200
帮我把瑞琪抬出车吧
Help me get Rikki out of the car.

272
00:16:46,450 --> 00:16:47,960
埃尔希德
Alcide!

273
00:16:47,960 --> 00:16:50,880
埃尔希德  他们逼着我喝
Alcide, they made me drink it.

274
00:16:51,470 --> 00:16:52,900
死亡
Death.

275
00:16:53,290 --> 00:16:56,280
我想吐出来
I wanted to fucking puke it up,

276
00:16:56,280 --> 00:16:58,380
可我又想要更多
and then I wanted more.

277
00:16:58,390 --> 00:17:00,570
我想杀掉所有活物
I wanted to kill everything that ever lived,

278
00:17:00,570 --> 00:17:03,170
挖出它的心脏生吃了
rip out its heart and eat it raw.

279
00:17:05,050 --> 00:17:07,550
别他妈的碰我  死婆子
Don't fucking touch me, dyke!

280
00:17:07,550 --> 00:17:09,790
-过来  -好啊
- Hey, come here. - Oh, yeah!

281
00:17:09,790 --> 00:17:12,780
你喜欢粗暴  脱了你的裤子  小子
You like it rough. Take your pants off, cowboy.

282
00:17:12,780 --> 00:17:14,710
我要你知道狼婊子真正的厉害
I'll show you what a real werebitch can do.

283
00:17:14,710 --> 00:17:15,660
到底发生了什么
What the fuck happened?

284
00:17:15,660 --> 00:17:18,430
杰·德强迫族群里的每个人
JD's been force-feeding vampire blood

285
00:17:18,430 --> 00:17:19,740
喝了吸血鬼的血
to everyone in the pack.

286
00:17:19,740 --> 00:17:22,600
他说为了迎接圣战  他们需要喝血
He says they'll need it to fight the holy wars.

287
00:17:22,600 --> 00:17:24,600
恐怕她是喝过量了
I'm afraid she might have OD'd.

288
00:17:24,600 --> 00:17:27,670
我担心她可能会死  埃尔希德
I'm afraid she might die, Alcide.

289
00:18:00,800 --> 00:18:02,680
你就不能稍微低调点吗
Shouldn't you try to be a little less conspicuous?

290
00:18:02,680 --> 00:18:04,390
我是说我们的货物
I mean, given our cargo.

291
00:18:05,070 --> 00:18:07,480
这几天  如果有人知道这里装的是什么
These days, if anyone knew what was inside those things...

292
00:18:07,480 --> 00:18:09,390
坦白说  苏克  有人要是想打开
Honestly, Sook, somebody wants to pop 'em open

293
00:18:09,390 --> 00:18:12,680
烤了这些家伙  我是很欢迎的啊
and fry these bitches up, they can be my guest.

294
00:18:13,300 --> 00:18:14,360
杰森
Jason.

295
00:18:15,320 --> 00:18:17,850
杰森  杰森  他们是我们的朋友
Jason. Jason, these are our friends.

296
00:18:17,850 --> 00:18:19,350
但不是我的
They ain't my friends.

297
00:18:19,840 --> 00:18:22,100
我们进入吸血鬼总部需要他们的帮助
We're gonna need their help getting into the Authority.

298
00:18:22,780 --> 00:18:24,130
只要我们进去
And once we're in,

299
00:18:24,620 --> 00:18:26,260
怎么对尖牙鬼们都不为过
anything with fangs is fair game.

300
00:18:26,260 --> 00:18:27,660
不好笑
This isn't funny.

301
00:18:32,440 --> 00:18:35,020
我准备好了  老爸  就今晚
I'm on it, Daddy, tonight.

302
00:18:35,030 --> 00:18:36,160
杰森  杀一堆吸血鬼
Jason, killing a bunch

303
00:18:36,160 --> 00:18:38,450
也不能让爸妈死而复生
of vampires won't bring Mama and Daddy back.

304
00:18:38,450 --> 00:18:40,860
是不能  但能让我舒服点儿
No, but it'll make me feel better.

305
00:18:40,870 --> 00:18:43,420
-杰森  -别在那儿唧唧歪歪了
- Jason! - Well, don't just stand there bellyaching.

306
00:18:43,420 --> 00:18:46,370
-帮我装袋子  -你先看着我
- Fill up the bag. - No, not until you look at me.

307
00:18:47,120 --> 00:18:49,720
埃里克  泰拉  诺拉  他们跟我们一边
Eric, Tara, and Nora, they're on our side.

308
00:18:49,720 --> 00:18:51,270
他们想把比尔救出来  以免事情...
They want to get Bill out of there before things get--

309
00:18:51,270 --> 00:18:54,400
怎么样  完全失控
Before things what? Spin out of control?

310
00:18:54,680 --> 00:18:56,660
由不得他们了
That train has already sailed.

311
00:18:56,660 --> 00:19:00,080
你把妹妹照顾得这么好  我真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you taking such good care of your sister.

312
00:19:00,080 --> 00:19:01,510
战争就要来了
There's a fucking war coming.

313
00:19:01,510 --> 00:19:03,550
因为她活在梦幻世界里
'Cause she is living in a dream world.

314
00:19:03,560 --> 00:19:07,100
真相很残酷  我们得跟他们决斗
It's us against them, and that is the sad reality.

315
00:19:07,100 --> 00:19:10,160
太对了  你死我活
Damn straight. Us or them.

316
00:19:10,160 --> 00:19:12,590
如果今晚我不得不杀死比尔
So if I have to kill Bill tonight

317
00:19:13,000 --> 00:19:14,930
或者他们中任何一个
or any of the rest of them,

318
00:19:15,720 --> 00:19:17,300
我绝不手软
I am gonna do it.

319
00:19:18,380 --> 00:19:20,510
你最好也做好这样的准备
And you'd better be prepared to do the same.

320
00:19:21,730 --> 00:19:24,470
起来  不愿做奴隶的人们
The time for tolerance is over.

321
00:19:25,380 --> 00:19:28,300
位于路易斯安那一个兄弟会的保安摄像头
Infamous vampire terrorist Russell Edgington,

322
00:19:28,300 --> 00:19:32,110
拍下了臭名昭著的恐怖分子罗素·爱丁顿
recorded by a security camera at a Louisiana fraternity house,

323
00:19:32,110 --> 00:19:35,890
这起残忍的吸血鬼屠杀案共有22名受害者
the site of a brutal vampire attack that claimed 22 lives.

324
00:19:39,940 --> 00:19:42,130
-胶质银  -是
- Colloidal silver? - Yeah.

325
00:19:42,780 --> 00:19:45,840
使得吸血鬼血排出体外  一般通过汗水
Makes the V want to leave the body, usually through sweat.

326
00:19:49,170 --> 00:19:52,000
这种感觉可不怎么好  但排出后就没事儿了
It's not a pleasant feeling, but once it's passed, she'll feel better.

327
00:19:52,320 --> 00:19:53,480
不错啊
That's good to know.

328
00:19:54,350 --> 00:19:56,450
你说如果我也弄点这个给杰·德
You mean if I could have got some of this into JD,

329
00:19:56,450 --> 00:19:59,180
我们就能来次公平较量  决定谁当首领了
we could have had a real Packmaster competition, fair and square?

330
00:19:59,180 --> 00:20:01,330
他以前是个好狼人
He was a good wolf once.

331
00:20:01,330 --> 00:20:02,560
有谁不是吗
Weren't we all?

332
00:20:04,290 --> 00:20:06,710
这个开始见效了  亲爱的
It's working its way out of you, honey.

333
00:20:10,210 --> 00:20:11,780
杰·德还对你做了什么
Did JD do anything else to you?

334
00:20:11,780 --> 00:20:15,350
如果你能告诉我为什么
Um, maybe I'll tell you if you tell me

335
00:20:15,980 --> 00:20:17,460
你不接电话  告诉我你在哪儿
why you couldn't pick up a phone

336
00:20:17,460 --> 00:20:19,180
我就考虑告诉你
and let me know where you were.

337
00:20:21,140 --> 00:20:24,600
你一声不吭就走了
You just left without a word.

338
00:20:25,840 --> 00:20:27,000
莫非那晚上的事儿
Don't pretend like that night

339
00:20:27,000 --> 00:20:28,920
你一点儿也不放在心上
didn't mean anything to you.

340
00:20:29,830 --> 00:20:32,450
我当然放在心上
I'm not. It did.

341
00:20:36,280 --> 00:20:37,400
告诉我到底怎么了
Tell me what happened.

342
00:20:37,860 --> 00:20:39,960
杰·德召开族群大会
JD called a pack meeting.

343
00:20:41,220 --> 00:20:43,300
说有紧急事件
Said it was an emergency.

344
00:20:43,610 --> 00:20:47,240
我们到达之后  就把我们控制住了
When we got there, they held us down.

345
00:20:48,890 --> 00:20:50,820
把血灌进我们的嘴里
He poured it into our mouths.

346
00:20:51,780 --> 00:20:52,890
就这样
Is that all?

347
00:20:53,950 --> 00:20:55,200
对我来说是
It was for me...

348
00:20:57,410 --> 00:20:59,380
但对年轻些的女孩子就不是了
but not for some of the younger girls.

349
00:21:03,680 --> 00:21:05,350
他以前或许是个好狼人
He might have been a good wolf once,

350
00:21:06,570 --> 00:21:08,000
但那都是过去时了
but he isn't anymore.

351
00:21:08,750 --> 00:21:09,930
毫无疑问
Clearly.

352
00:21:10,630 --> 00:21:13,070
如果不是因为他嗑血  我恨不得马上杀了他
If he wasn't all jacked up on V, I'd kill him right now.

353
00:21:13,070 --> 00:21:14,850
但他那次差点杀了我
But as it is, he practically killed me.

354
00:21:14,850 --> 00:21:17,870
只有按照他的游戏规则来  才能杀得了他
The only way to beat him is to play by his rules.

355
00:21:18,860 --> 00:21:21,260
如果他喝的是和瑞琪一样的血
If he's on the same blood that Rikki's on,

356
00:21:21,260 --> 00:21:23,960
那都是最次的货
it's some seriously inferior shit.

357
00:21:24,440 --> 00:21:26,710
我这里有上等的
I got some of the best shit available

358
00:21:27,480 --> 00:21:29,220
专门留到关键时刻用
I keep for special occasions

359
00:21:29,220 --> 00:21:30,900
比如现在这情况
just like this one.

360
00:21:34,020 --> 00:21:36,740
这些年来很多人都想杀我
Lots of folks wanted to kill me over the years.

361
00:21:37,290 --> 00:21:39,770
我这都是为了生存
I do what I have to to stay alive.

362
00:22:13,420 --> 00:22:16,210
-喂  -我有个主意
- Hey. - I have an idea.

363
00:22:16,520 --> 00:22:17,680
会有用吗
Will it work?

364
00:22:18,560 --> 00:22:19,720
希望如此
I hope so.

365
00:22:21,540 --> 00:22:22,670
好了
Okay.

366
00:22:23,740 --> 00:22:25,080
-再见  -再见
- Bye-bye. - Bye-bye.

367
00:22:25,080 --> 00:22:29,100
喂  女人们  我做了点法式玛格丽塔
Hey, bitches. I made some Cajun Margaritas.

368
00:22:30,180 --> 00:22:33,390
我可不想知道里面都放了什么
I do not want to even know what is in that.

369
00:22:33,390 --> 00:22:35,360
但你肯定想尝尝
Oh, but you want to taste it.

370
00:22:36,440 --> 00:22:37,560
没错
I do.

371
00:22:40,580 --> 00:22:41,830
我的天
Oh, my goddess.

372
00:22:43,110 --> 00:22:44,280
太爽了
That is amazing.

373
00:22:44,280 --> 00:22:47,510
嗯  你好像也要来一杯
Mmm. You look like you can use a cup.

374
00:22:47,800 --> 00:22:50,220
我不晓得  太阳快下山了
Oh, I don't know. It's pretty close to sundown.

375
00:22:50,220 --> 00:22:54,040
拜托  美女  来一小口
Oh, come on, peaches. Just a little sippy-sip.

376
00:22:54,040 --> 00:22:55,220
阿尔琳
Arlene,

377
00:22:56,060 --> 00:22:58,720
这几天你经历那么多  应该放松一下
after the last few days, you deserve a little R&R.

378
00:22:59,600 --> 00:23:00,840
听你的  美女
I heard that, girl.

379
00:23:03,810 --> 00:23:06,530
天啦  跟嗑药一样爽
Mmm! God, it's like candy.

380
00:23:07,110 --> 00:23:10,630
拉法耶  这是什么音乐
Lafayette, what is this music?

381
00:23:10,630 --> 00:23:12,780
我都不敢想我有多少生命
I don't even want to think about how many hours of my life

382
00:23:12,780 --> 00:23:16,810
浪费在山姆·马洛特选的烂音乐上了
I've spent listening to sam Merlotte's redneck-ass taste in music.

383
00:23:16,810 --> 00:23:18,560
我要趁他不在的时候
I'm gonna take full advantage of his absence

384
00:23:18,560 --> 00:23:20,270
好好享受美妙的音乐
and listen to something decent for a change.

385
00:23:20,270 --> 00:23:22,280
没错  超棒的
Oh, all right. Something nasty.

386
00:23:22,280 --> 00:23:25,060
喔  看他摆臀的样子
Oh, look at him work that thing.

387
00:23:25,060 --> 00:23:26,920
这就对了
Oh, yeah.

388
00:23:26,920 --> 00:23:28,950
尽情摇摆吧
Roll it out.

389
00:23:35,520 --> 00:23:40,520
麻烦你就在这里坐一会儿
Okay, you mind just sitting tight here for a while

390
00:23:40,830 --> 00:23:43,360
我想私下跟我朋友谈谈
so I can talk to my friend privately?

391
00:23:43,360 --> 00:23:46,350
因为跟她说通这件事儿肯定很不容易
'Cause what I got to say to her is not gonna be too easy.

392
00:23:46,350 --> 00:23:47,730
别着急
Take your time.

393
00:23:47,930 --> 00:23:50,390
哦  你能不能先给我拿点儿盐
Oh, will you get me some salt first?

394
00:23:55,820 --> 00:23:57,220
你今晚有重要约会吗
So you got a big date tonight?

395
00:24:03,320 --> 00:24:04,640
你好  警长
Hey, Sheriff.

396
00:24:05,210 --> 00:24:08,870
-嗨  博德豪斯小姐  -安迪  叫我简
- Oh, hey, Miss Bodehouse. - Andy, Jane, please.

397
00:24:08,870 --> 00:24:11,080
咱们难道没睡过吗
Haven't we slept together by now?

398
00:24:11,320 --> 00:24:15,590
-没有  -我觉得我们睡过呢
- I don't think so. - I think we slept together at some point.

399
00:24:15,590 --> 00:24:16,790
在树林里
In the woods.

400
00:24:18,530 --> 00:24:19,560
不对  那不是我
Nope, wasn't me.

401
00:24:19,560 --> 00:24:22,180
安迪  你跟简·博德豪斯睡过  什么时候
Andy, you slept with Jane Bodehouse? When?

402
00:24:22,180 --> 00:24:25,070
-没有  她醉了  -我是醉了
- No, she's drunk. - I am.

403
00:24:25,170 --> 00:24:28,040
幸亏你没有
Well, I'm glad you didn't.

404
00:24:28,250 --> 00:24:30,310
这种感觉可真不舒服
I don't like the way that made me feel.

405
00:24:30,600 --> 00:24:31,700
真的吗
Really?

406
00:24:32,390 --> 00:24:33,840
你有什么感觉
How'd it make you feel?

407
00:24:34,320 --> 00:24:36,750
就像是我们俩之间的感情
Like something special that only we share

408
00:24:36,750 --> 00:24:38,650
突然就不那么特别了
was suddenly not so special anymore.

409
00:24:38,650 --> 00:24:41,230
那我可伤心了
And that made me sad.

410
00:24:42,700 --> 00:24:43,800
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?

411
00:24:44,870 --> 00:24:46,050
私底下
Alone?

412
00:24:47,390 --> 00:24:48,400
没问题
Sure.

413
00:24:55,060 --> 00:24:59,090
安迪·贝弗勒什么时候变得这么迷人了
When did Andy Bellefleur get to be so fucking hot?

414
00:25:01,580 --> 00:25:05,420
霍莉  我是真心在乎你
Holly, I really care about you.

415
00:25:05,720 --> 00:25:08,460
我很久都没有这种感觉了  自从...
I haven't felt something like this since--

416
00:25:08,810 --> 00:25:10,630
其实从来没有过
well, my whole life.

417
00:25:10,630 --> 00:25:12,620
她是谁  你们俩搞了几次
Who was it and how many times?

418
00:25:13,610 --> 00:25:15,270
她叫玛瑞拉
Her name's Maurella.

419
00:25:16,230 --> 00:25:17,590
就两次
And twice.

420
00:25:17,820 --> 00:25:19,340
第一次在几周前
Once a couple weeks ago

421
00:25:19,340 --> 00:25:21,740
早于你和我...
before you and I had ever...

422
00:25:22,680 --> 00:25:24,110
还有一次是
And the other time was

423
00:25:25,760 --> 00:25:28,670
差不多一周前
almost a week ago,

424
00:25:29,800 --> 00:25:32,980
当然是在我们那个之后  我很抱歉
clearly after we had... I'm so sorry.

425
00:25:34,200 --> 00:25:37,720
她现在怀孕了
And now she's pregnant

426
00:25:38,490 --> 00:25:40,510
还不肯去圣弗朗西斯医院
and she refuses to go to St. Francis.

427
00:25:40,510 --> 00:25:44,220
说她那族不在医院里下崽
Says her kind don't whelp in hospitals.

428
00:25:56,750 --> 00:25:59,480
我...我的光破了
My... my light broke.

429
00:26:08,290 --> 00:26:10,670
我美丽的先知
My beautiful prophet.

430
00:26:38,760 --> 00:26:40,270
比尔才不邪恶
Bill's not evil.

431
00:26:40,450 --> 00:26:41,600
我了解他
I know him.

432
00:26:42,110 --> 00:26:45,020
在吸血鬼和人类间挑起内战
And starting a civil war between vampires and humans

433
00:26:45,020 --> 00:26:46,960
不是他的本性
it's not who he really is.

434
00:26:47,410 --> 00:26:49,400
可怜的孩子  爱蒙蔽了她的眼睛
Poor thing, blinded by love.

435
00:26:49,400 --> 00:26:52,090
太害怕了  所以她看不清真相
Too scared to let herself see the truth.

436
00:26:54,140 --> 00:26:59,110
你觉得真有人能彻底了解另一个人吗
You ever think anyone can really know anybody else?

437
00:26:59,110 --> 00:27:02,330
我是说  我们不都只看自己想看的吗
I mean, don't we just see what makes us feel good?

438
00:27:03,250 --> 00:27:05,510
我觉得你可以了解一个人
I think you can know somebody else.

439
00:27:05,870 --> 00:27:09,450
可能不容易  可能结果不尽人意
It's not easy and it's not always nice,

440
00:27:09,770 --> 00:27:12,320
但通过和那人一起渡过生活中的逆境
but going through some life-changing experiences

441
00:27:12,320 --> 00:27:14,650
-有助于判断...  -真的吗
- with that person can help you... - Really?

442
00:27:15,710 --> 00:27:18,520
我觉得这道理在你身上也行不通
It seems to me that philosophy ain't exactly working for you.

443
00:27:18,520 --> 00:27:20,670
你老是爱上死掉的男人
I mean, you just keep falling for boys who are dead.

444
00:27:20,670 --> 00:27:23,660
这不就是典型的"行不通"吗
Ain't that like the ultimate in being unavailable?

445
00:27:23,660 --> 00:27:26,850
-我真不觉得这是我...  -我也一样
- I really don't think that's why I... - No, hey, me, too.

446
00:27:27,350 --> 00:27:30,490
唐恩  艾米  克莉斯多  杰西
Dawn, Amy, Crystal, Jess...

447
00:27:30,500 --> 00:27:32,940
每个到头来都行不通
every last one of them unavailable

448
00:27:32,940 --> 00:27:35,940
最基本的那种行不通
in some basic unavailable way.

449
00:27:39,680 --> 00:27:43,290
其实问题出在我们身上
You know, the problem is us.

450
00:27:43,290 --> 00:27:45,950
我们觉得自己就只配这样了
We think we don't deserve better than that.

451
00:27:47,800 --> 00:27:48,900
或许真的是吧
Maybe we don't.

452
00:27:48,900 --> 00:27:51,500
这不是配不配的问题
It is not a question of deserving.

453
00:27:51,710 --> 00:27:55,050
问题是你总觉得生活欠了你什么
It is a question of thinking life owes you something.

454
00:27:55,980 --> 00:27:57,120
其实没有
It doesn't.

455
00:27:57,400 --> 00:28:01,500
杰森  我知道你现在要对付很多破事儿
Jason, I know you've got a lot to deal with right now,

456
00:28:01,700 --> 00:28:04,480
但你不能这样就垮掉了
but you can't let it tear you down like this.

457
00:28:05,710 --> 00:28:06,990
为什么不能
Why the hell not?

458
00:28:07,610 --> 00:28:09,550
也许我们不去想明天会更好
Maybe we'd be better off going through life

459
00:28:09,550 --> 00:28:13,420
我们这辈子反而能轻松愉快许多
without thinking there's something good waiting for us down the road.

460
00:28:13,420 --> 00:28:17,270
如果只抱最坏的打算  我们就不会失望
Maybe we wouldn't keep getting hurt if we just expected the worst.

461
00:28:17,270 --> 00:28:19,600
没错  小帅哥  是吸血鬼把你们变成孤儿
That's right, champ. Vampers made you orphans.

462
00:28:19,600 --> 00:28:21,050
要吸取教训
Learn from it.

463
00:28:21,780 --> 00:28:24,420
-因为我们就没碰到过好事  -不
- Cause that's all we've been getting. - No.

464
00:28:25,980 --> 00:28:27,790
我拒绝这样思考
I refuse to think that way.

465
00:28:27,790 --> 00:28:29,450
那是你的选择
Well, that's your choice.

466
00:28:30,870 --> 00:28:33,380
但如果我愿意这么想  你得由着我
But you've got to let me think that way if I want to.

467
00:28:34,500 --> 00:28:35,580
好吧
Okay.

468
00:28:38,430 --> 00:28:39,670
你的头怎么样了
How's your head?

469
00:28:44,620 --> 00:28:46,830
杰森  这肿得跟核桃一样大
Jason, that's as big as a walnut.

470
00:28:48,300 --> 00:28:50,530
-靠边停  -操你大爷的
- Pull over. - Fuck, man!

471
00:28:51,030 --> 00:28:52,380
拜托啦
Please?

472
00:29:03,020 --> 00:29:06,040
不敢相信  我刚刚听说你有个怀孕的女朋友
I cannot believe I am midwifing for your pregnant girlfriend

473
00:29:06,060 --> 00:29:07,590
就要给她助产了
that I just found out about.

474
00:29:07,590 --> 00:29:11,190
相信我  我跟你一样不希望这事儿发生
Believe me, I'd prefer this was not happening just as much as you.

475
00:29:11,190 --> 00:29:14,550
快了  甜心  保持呼吸
Okay, we're almost there, honey, okay? Just keep breathing.

476
00:29:14,550 --> 00:29:17,020
噢  好棒
Oh, yes. Yes!

477
00:29:17,070 --> 00:29:19,260
好  好
Yes! Yes!

478
00:29:19,260 --> 00:29:21,320
貌似这对你来说不太痛苦啊
This doesn't seem too hard for you.

479
00:29:21,320 --> 00:29:24,190
我猜这不是你第一次怀孕吧
I'm guessing this isn't your first pregnancy.

480
00:29:24,200 --> 00:29:27,430
自从我发现怎么生后  这是第七十三次
73 times since I first discovered how.

481
00:29:27,430 --> 00:29:31,480
好吧  够狠
Okay, that's extreme.

482
00:29:31,820 --> 00:29:36,050
谁会知道看外星人生小孩这么舒坦
Who knew watching an alien give birth could be so comforting?

483
00:29:36,050 --> 00:29:39,670
你开玩笑吧  怪事儿永远是群众喜闻乐见的
Are you kidding me? It's always the weird stuff that's the best.

484
00:29:44,500 --> 00:29:45,650
靠
Shit.

485
00:30:03,920 --> 00:30:08,190
-是个没脐带的姑娘  -上帝啊
- It's a girl with no umbilical cord. - Oh, my God.

486
00:30:16,380 --> 00:30:18,580
你要好好对她  安迪·贝弗勒
You'd better be good to her, Andy Bellefleur.

487
00:30:19,540 --> 00:30:24,520
在这世上做女人可真够难的
She's gonna have a hard enough time as it is being a woman in this world.

488
00:30:24,520 --> 00:30:27,180
我会的  我发誓
I will. I swear.

489
00:30:28,970 --> 00:30:31,130
我完全不知道发生了什么
I have no idea what's happening.

490
00:30:31,140 --> 00:30:34,380
谁知道呢  小简简  谁知道呢
Who does, baby Jane? Who does?

491
00:30:38,370 --> 00:30:40,910
呃  这儿还没完
Uh, we're not done.

492
00:30:47,540 --> 00:30:49,060
不  不  不
No, no, no.

493
00:30:55,210 --> 00:30:57,210
不  不  求你了
No. No, please.

494
00:30:57,310 --> 00:30:59,020
不  不要
No, no.

495
00:31:02,690 --> 00:31:03,730
我来吧
I got it.

496
00:31:10,220 --> 00:31:11,430
嗨  宝贝儿
Hi, baby.

497
00:31:19,580 --> 00:31:22,670
我找到你了  宝贝  我永远不会离开你了
I've got you, baby, and I am never letting you go.

498
00:31:22,960 --> 00:31:25,270
别变形
Do not shift.

499
00:31:25,690 --> 00:31:28,220
谢谢  她被关了几个小时了
Thank you. She's been cooped up for hours.

500
00:31:28,220 --> 00:31:30,040
该出去玩玩了
Could use a little playtime.

501
00:31:42,520 --> 00:31:43,700
纽林牧师
Reverend Newlin.

502
00:31:46,240 --> 00:31:49,160
我的统计学拿A了
I aced my statistics exam.

503
00:31:49,160 --> 00:31:51,580
是吗  太棒了
You did? That's fantastic.

504
00:31:51,580 --> 00:31:54,040
加油  切尔西  加油  切尔西
Go, Chelsea! Go, Chelsea!

505
00:31:54,160 --> 00:31:56,280
没错  切尔西  加油
Yes, Chelsea, go.

506
00:31:56,520 --> 00:31:59,100
我想带艾玛去散散步
So I thought I would take Emma here for a little walk.

507
00:31:59,110 --> 00:32:01,060
要不要我叫人来帮你
Oh, well, do you want me to have someone do that for you?

508
00:32:01,060 --> 00:32:02,730
不  谢谢
No! Thank you.

509
00:32:02,730 --> 00:32:07,180
我喜欢自己来  可以培养感情
I-- I like doing it. It gives us a little bonding time.

510
00:32:08,720 --> 00:32:10,600
你的南方口音哪儿去了
Where's your Southern accent?

511
00:32:13,410 --> 00:32:14,740
有时候...
Sometimes...

512
00:32:14,950 --> 00:32:18,590
我喜欢不用南方口音
I like to not have a Southern accent.

513
00:32:18,710 --> 00:32:19,310
真的吗
Really?

514
00:32:19,310 --> 00:32:23,620
但那是你这人的特点啊  是你的招牌
But it's such a part of who you are, of your brand.

515
00:32:23,820 --> 00:32:27,170
是啊  但有时候
Yes, but sometimes...

516
00:32:27,560 --> 00:32:30,110
我喜欢时而换换招牌
I like to keep the brand evolving

517
00:32:30,110 --> 00:32:33,680
这样对观众来说更有吸引力嘛
so consumers are more inclined to stay on their toes.

518
00:32:34,060 --> 00:32:37,850
但这对观众来说岂不是莫名其妙吗
But doesn't that make it more complicated for consumers

519
00:32:37,850 --> 00:32:40,550
这是很大的忌讳吧
and isn't that like a huge no-no?

520
00:32:40,550 --> 00:32:43,410
你这个问题太好了
That is a very good question,

521
00:32:43,410 --> 00:32:46,650
等我回来再和你探讨  切尔西
which I will have to get back to you on, Chelsea.

522
00:32:56,060 --> 00:32:59,660
纽林牧师  你知道这里已经全面封闭了吧
Reverend Newlin, you do know that we're on lockdown, don't you?

523
00:33:00,230 --> 00:33:03,930
纽林  你这个小笨蛋
Newlin, you fucking little dipshit.

524
00:33:04,340 --> 00:33:09,090
你的尖牙就是藏不住  是吧
Just because you couldn't keep your fangs in your pants, could you?

525
00:33:09,260 --> 00:33:12,240
我要你尽快挽回声誉
Now, I'm gonna need you on damage control ASAP.

526
00:33:12,240 --> 00:33:16,500
那二十二个翘辫子的兄弟会成员是不能挽回了
Not that you actually can control 22 dead frat boys.

527
00:33:19,940 --> 00:33:21,580
同意使用
Access granted.

528
00:33:27,820 --> 00:33:29,130
你他妈聋了吗
Are you fucking deaf?

529
00:33:29,760 --> 00:33:30,870
快进来
Get in here!

530
00:33:37,310 --> 00:33:40,090
你和爱丁顿到底是他妈怎么想的
What the fuck were you and Edgington thinking?

531
00:33:40,130 --> 00:33:43,040
他在哪儿呢  还有基布韦
And where is he? Or Kibwe?

532
00:33:43,200 --> 00:33:45,480
很明显  盖恩斯伯和诺思曼都失败了
Clearly Gainesborough and Northman weren't successful.

533
00:33:45,480 --> 00:33:48,530
政府八成已经干掉他们  要来找我们了
The government probably killed them and is coming out for us now.

534
00:33:48,530 --> 00:33:50,590
你这犯贱的白痴
You stupid little bitch!

535
00:33:59,690 --> 00:34:03,500
对一个正常而且健康的美国人类来说
Yeah, well, for a normal red-blooded American human,

536
00:34:03,500 --> 00:34:06,060
生小孩可不是这样的
giving birth ain't nothing like that.

537
00:34:06,060 --> 00:34:08,600
她让我也想生了
Hell, she make me want to do it.

538
00:34:12,150 --> 00:34:13,480
又是个女儿
Another girl.

539
00:34:16,910 --> 00:34:20,630
嗨  宝贝儿
Hey, sweetie.

540
00:34:37,240 --> 00:34:38,490
照顾好他们
Take good care of them.

541
00:34:39,340 --> 00:34:40,280
等等
Wait a minute.

542
00:34:40,280 --> 00:34:42,860
你不是想把他们都丢给我吧
You ain't thinking about leaving them with me?

543
00:34:43,190 --> 00:34:44,780
他们是你的种
You sired them.

544
00:34:44,780 --> 00:34:46,620
接下来  把他们抚养长大
Now it is your sacred duty to see

545
00:34:46,620 --> 00:34:49,030
就是你的神圣职责了  至少得活两个
that at least half of them survive into adulthood.

546
00:34:49,040 --> 00:34:51,710
你这不是...
Whoa! That ain't...

547
00:34:51,720 --> 00:34:54,270
光之契约此刻已经生效
The light pact has been made flesh now.

548
00:34:54,370 --> 00:34:57,990
向过去  现在  和不存在的未来致敬
I honor what was, what is, and what will never be.

549
00:34:58,750 --> 00:35:00,370
别了  安迪·贝弗勒
Farewell, Andy Bellefleur.

550
00:35:05,070 --> 00:35:06,840
真是太牛逼了
That was awesome.

551
00:35:11,160 --> 00:35:12,480
你是个大混球
You're a dick.

552
00:35:18,880 --> 00:35:20,130
来呀  杰·德
Come on, JD.

553
00:35:26,080 --> 00:35:28,010
你就要被活活烧死了  吸血的傻逼
You're about to plain get burned, sucker!

554
00:35:29,590 --> 00:35:31,340
我请大家嗑血
Drinks on me, everybody.

555
00:35:32,600 --> 00:35:33,840
谁要第一个来
Who's up first?

556
00:35:34,070 --> 00:35:36,140
闭嘴  死东西
Shut the fuck up, dead man.

557
00:35:39,580 --> 00:35:40,540
我们还没嗑够吗
Ain't we had enough?

558
00:35:40,540 --> 00:35:43,250
嗑血哪里有够的时候
Ain't no such thing as too much V.

559
00:35:44,680 --> 00:35:46,040
够了  杰·德
That's enough, JD!

560
00:35:48,700 --> 00:35:50,110
搞什么鬼
The fuck?

561
00:35:51,550 --> 00:35:52,940
你已经除名了
I abjured you.

562
00:35:52,940 --> 00:35:54,190
除你妈逼
Abjure this.

563
00:36:10,700 --> 00:36:11,990
他要打死他啦
He's killing him.

564
00:36:13,340 --> 00:36:14,500
你们都别插手
Stay out of it.

565
00:36:15,150 --> 00:36:17,590
这是杰·德和埃尔希德之间的事
This is between JD and Alcide.

566
00:36:20,570 --> 00:36:22,260
你已经赢了  儿子
I think you've won this one, son.

567
00:36:24,510 --> 00:36:25,840
老天呀
Oh, my God!

568
00:36:26,600 --> 00:36:28,010
打死他了
He killed him.

569
00:36:28,010 --> 00:36:29,150
他死了
He's dead.

570
00:36:29,440 --> 00:36:31,270
我们狼群有新首领了吧
Guess we got a new Packmaster.

571
00:36:56,060 --> 00:36:57,610
这事儿到此为止
This stops tonight.

572
00:36:58,360 --> 00:37:01,720
我们是狼  我们有自尊
We're wolves. We respect ourselves.

573
00:37:02,280 --> 00:37:03,680
我们尊重族群
We respect our pack.

574
00:37:04,650 --> 00:37:07,320
我们全都尊重大自然
We respect nature without exception.

575
00:37:07,930 --> 00:37:09,820
我们绝不屈从于恐怖主义
We do not surrender to nihilism.

576
00:37:11,700 --> 00:37:15,530
我们绝对不做欺凌弱小的事
We do not take advantage of those who are younger or weaker than we are.

577
00:37:18,640 --> 00:37:21,220
此时此刻起  这就是我们族群所遵守的原则
This is how it's going to be in this pack from now on.

578
00:37:22,200 --> 00:37:25,040
如果有人不赞同  在二十四小时内
And if you don't like it, then you have 24 hours

579
00:37:25,260 --> 00:37:26,560
给我滚出去
to get the hell out

580
00:37:26,560 --> 00:37:28,610
否则现在就来找我
or you face me right now.

581
00:37:30,650 --> 00:37:31,770
今晚
Tonight...

582
00:37:34,390 --> 00:37:35,920
我们选择狼群
we choose pack.

583
00:37:52,300 --> 00:37:53,520
法官们
Chancellors.

584
00:37:54,300 --> 00:37:56,660
我们以为你们明晚才会回来呢
We weren't expecting you until tomorrow evening.

585
00:37:57,120 --> 00:37:59,220
去华盛顿的航班临时被取消了
Well, our flight was aborted halfway to DC.

586
00:37:59,220 --> 00:38:00,610
没人告诉我们原因
No one has told us why or

587
00:38:00,610 --> 00:38:02,450
到新奥尔良的时候也没人来迎接
was there to meet us when we got back to New Orleans.

588
00:38:02,620 --> 00:38:05,420
-出什么事了吗  -有外部人员入侵
- Has there been trouble? - There's been a breach.

589
00:38:05,880 --> 00:38:08,580
一个变形人  我们还在禁闭状态
A shape-shifter. We're still on lockdown.

590
00:38:08,810 --> 00:38:10,190
我必须汇报一下
I'll need to call this in.

591
00:38:11,080 --> 00:38:13,670
切尔西  诺思曼法官和盖恩斯伯法官
Chelsea, I have Chancellors Northman and Gainesborough

592
00:38:13,670 --> 00:38:15,820
在大门处等待许可
at the gate requesting access.

593
00:38:19,790 --> 00:38:21,340
你们运的是什么人
What's your cargo?

594
00:38:21,340 --> 00:38:22,890
主流派吸血鬼的奸细
The vampire's a mainstreaming spy.

595
00:38:23,640 --> 00:38:24,760
人类是午餐
The humans are lunch.

596
00:38:25,490 --> 00:38:27,040
金发妞闻着太香了
The blonde smells amazing.

597
00:38:28,220 --> 00:38:29,560
是啊  她确实很香
Yeah, she is pretty amazing.

598
00:38:30,620 --> 00:38:31,730
而且是我的
And mine.

599
00:38:32,990 --> 00:38:34,250
收到
Roger.

600
00:38:34,520 --> 00:38:36,430
他们正在搜寻一个法官
They're just trying to track down a chancellor.

601
00:38:38,730 --> 00:38:42,250
没问题  把诺思曼法官一行送下来吧
Of course. Send Chancellor Northman and his party on down.

602
00:38:42,640 --> 00:38:44,420
-你们可以进入了  -谢谢
- You've been cleared. - Thank you.

603
00:39:07,060 --> 00:39:09,080
混蛋
Fuckin' igits!

604
00:39:09,450 --> 00:39:12,110
跟往常一样  什么事儿都该我做
As usual, everything falls to me.

605
00:39:12,110 --> 00:39:15,540
人都没影了  康普顿和莎乐美一多半
I can't ever find anybody. Compton and Salome are off

606
00:39:15,540 --> 00:39:18,080
都在忙着翻云覆雨
buttering each other's biscuits half the time.

607
00:39:18,560 --> 00:39:19,940
虽然我不想这么说
You know, I hate to say this,

608
00:39:19,950 --> 00:39:21,930
但自从罗曼翘辫子以后
but ever since Roman cashed in his chips,

609
00:39:21,930 --> 00:39:24,970
大家的职业道德都跌到谷底了
the work ethic around here has just gone straight to hell.

610
00:39:26,660 --> 00:39:27,860
好了  你看起来有点紧张
Okay, you look a little nervous.

611
00:39:27,860 --> 00:39:30,030
发言的时候可别给我出岔子
Now you are not gonna veer off this script.

612
00:39:30,520 --> 00:39:32,180
等等  五分钟之后我们就要直播了吗
Wait a minute. We're going live in five?

613
00:39:32,180 --> 00:39:34,950
-是五分钟吗  -是五秒
- Is that five minutes? - Five seconds.

614
00:39:35,120 --> 00:39:38,090
而且你最好表现得有说服力  传教士先生
And you'd better sell the shit out of this, preacher man,

615
00:39:38,460 --> 00:39:41,710
因为你和罗素有可能引发了一场战争
'cause it looks like you and Russell may have just started a war.

616
00:39:42,940 --> 00:39:45,960
有一段监视录像最近成为网络热点
The surveillance video, which has become an Internet sensation,

617
00:39:45,960 --> 00:39:48,150
史蒂夫·纽林以及疑似罗素·爱丁顿的男子
shows Reverend Newlin and someone who appears to be

618
00:39:48,150 --> 00:39:50,970
进入了一家兄弟会所
Russell Edgington entering the fraternity house

619
00:39:51,340 --> 00:39:53,650
随后有人发现二十二名青年男子
where those 22 young men were later found

620
00:39:53,820 --> 00:39:55,200
血尽而亡
drained of their blood.

621
00:39:55,640 --> 00:39:57,580
请跟我一起现场连线
Joining me now live via satellite,

622
00:39:57,580 --> 00:39:59,570
访问美国吸血鬼联盟的发言人
American Vampire League spokesperson

623
00:39:59,570 --> 00:40:01,060
史蒂夫·纽林本人
Steve Newlin himself.

624
00:40:02,220 --> 00:40:03,750
纽林牧师  感谢您来参加节目
Reverend Newlin, thanks for joining us.

625
00:40:06,390 --> 00:40:08,200
苏珊娜  我很荣幸
It's my pleasure, Suzanne,

626
00:40:08,200 --> 00:40:12,420
能够拒绝...驳斥这些无耻的指控
to be able to refuse-- refute these heinous charges,

627
00:40:12,430 --> 00:40:16,250
这明显是有人恶意捏造出来的
which have obviously been fabricated by a sick and hateful mind.

628
00:40:16,250 --> 00:40:18,310
我们能从这段低劣的
Can we please start with the cheap

629
00:40:18,730 --> 00:40:20,920
明显是人工合成的视...
and obviously manufactured vid--

630
00:40:22,320 --> 00:40:23,660
视频说起吗
--video?

631
00:40:26,910 --> 00:40:28,370
纽林牧师
Reverend Newlin?

632
00:40:28,750 --> 00:40:31,220
牧师  牧师  你还好吗
Rev-- Reverend? Reverend, are you all right?

633
00:40:33,200 --> 00:40:34,450
老天呀
Christ!

634
00:40:47,970 --> 00:40:50,160
我可没料到有这一幕
I did not see that shit coming.

635
00:40:50,430 --> 00:40:52,870
吸血鬼把人类监禁在
Vampires are keeping humans prisoner

636
00:40:52,880 --> 00:40:55,520
新奥尔良市的一个地下基地
in an underground bunker somewhere in New Orleans.

637
00:40:55,520 --> 00:40:57,730
他们吸人类的血  他们在屠杀人类
They are feeding on them. They're killing them!

638
00:40:58,150 --> 00:40:59,900
来这儿  宝贝  好了
Come here, baby. Here we go.

639
00:41:00,160 --> 00:41:01,750
好了  没事了
Okay, all right. You're fine.

640
00:41:24,910 --> 00:41:25,700
卢娜
Luna?

641
00:41:26,900 --> 00:41:27,860
卢娜
Luna?

642
00:42:08,350 --> 00:42:09,940
谢谢  莉莉丝
Thank you, Lilith,

643
00:42:11,170 --> 00:42:12,570
圣母
O Mother,

644
00:42:13,500 --> 00:42:16,130
感谢您赐给我的礼物
for the gift you have bestowed upon me.

645
00:42:17,200 --> 00:42:19,200
我以生命起誓
And I swear upon my life

646
00:42:20,200 --> 00:42:21,850
我必实现汝之意愿
thy will shall be done.

647
00:42:23,060 --> 00:42:26,720
吸血鬼将名正言顺地统治地球
Vampires shall rightfully rule this earth.

648
00:42:41,880 --> 00:42:42,860
动手
Now.

649
00:42:52,240 --> 00:42:53,960
指引我吧  圣母
Guide me, O Mother,

650
00:42:54,960 --> 00:42:58,360
我是全心全意臣服于您
as I surrender to you completely.

651
00:43:03,580 --> 00:43:07,140
正在启动二级警戒
Initiating level two protocols.

652
00:43:08,070 --> 00:43:11,650
-走  -正在启动二级警戒
- Go! - Initiating level two protocols.

653
00:43:13,020 --> 00:43:15,800
正在启动二级警戒
Initiating level two protocols.

654
00:43:15,800 --> 00:43:17,020
别出来
Stay back!

655
00:43:17,530 --> 00:43:20,260
正在启动二级警戒
Initiating level two protocols...

656
00:43:22,480 --> 00:43:24,570
-五  四...  -安全了
- in five, four... - Clear.

657
00:43:24,700 --> 00:43:27,700
三  二  一
three, two, one.

658
00:43:28,070 --> 00:43:30,250
二级警戒启动
Level two protocols.

659
00:43:36,090 --> 00:43:37,650
小心点  很滑
Watch out, it's slippery.

660
00:43:42,910 --> 00:43:44,860
好  拿好武器  走
Okay, weapons tight. Go!

661
00:44:08,830 --> 00:44:10,280
你看  给当权者效力
See what you've been missing

662
00:44:11,640 --> 00:44:13,800
你错过了多少带劲儿的事
working for the fucking Authority?

663
00:44:15,340 --> 00:44:16,650
去控制室
Control room.

664
00:44:20,640 --> 00:44:22,040
好吧  又怎么了
Great, now what?

665
00:44:25,220 --> 00:44:27,500
-苏琪  嗨  -杰西卡
- Sookie? Hi. - Jessica.

666
00:44:27,710 --> 00:44:29,510
-你还好吗  -你在搞什么鬼
- You okay? - What the fuck are you doing?

667
00:44:29,740 --> 00:44:31,340
我在救你出监狱  贱人
I'm getting you the fuck out of jail, bitch.

668
00:44:34,460 --> 00:44:36,830
你俩再坚持一下  我们要在这儿等一会
Y'all need to hold tight. We need to wait a second here.

669
00:44:37,040 --> 00:44:38,110
等  等什么
Wait? For what?

670
00:44:38,120 --> 00:44:40,200
等埃里克和诺拉搞定武装部队和各种门锁
Eric and Nora to disarm and unlock everything.

671
00:44:40,430 --> 00:44:43,280
-好计划  -肯定比你的强
- Nice plan. - Sure beats yours.

672
00:44:45,460 --> 00:44:47,290
等等  你要先按这个
No, wait, you've got to do that thing first.

673
00:44:47,290 --> 00:44:48,880
-别乱动...  -要调整传感器
- Can you not-- - You've got to reroute the sensors.

674
00:44:48,880 --> 00:44:51,420
-我刚才就调了  -根本没有
- That's the first thing I did. - No, you didn't.

675
00:44:51,640 --> 00:44:52,960
-让我来吧  -你真以为
- Please, let me just-- - Do you honestly think

676
00:44:52,960 --> 00:44:55,560
你比我还了解这个由我参与设计的系统吗
that you understand the system I helped design better than I do?

677
00:44:55,790 --> 00:44:57,170
好吧  没你懂
Okay, maybe not.

678
00:45:01,810 --> 00:45:03,050
出来
Come on.

679
00:45:03,890 --> 00:45:05,490
我知道你们在外面
I know you're out there.

680
00:45:09,820 --> 00:45:12,800
太恶心了  该死的垃圾
Suck on that, you dead piece of shit.

681
00:45:17,180 --> 00:45:18,980
苏琪  你能帮我打开门吗
Oh, Sookie, can you get these doors?

682
00:45:19,320 --> 00:45:22,550
对了  这些门是银的  你们是吸血鬼
Right, 'cause they're made of silver and y'all are vampires. Duh.

683
00:45:25,070 --> 00:45:26,130
泰拉
Tara.

684
00:45:37,490 --> 00:45:38,680
很好
Oh, okay.

685
00:45:39,630 --> 00:45:41,360
我就知道
I knew it!

686
00:45:57,070 --> 00:45:59,380
这调调还真是仪式化
Quite the ritualistic tone you're setting.

687
00:45:59,550 --> 00:46:01,860
你不觉得很适合这个场合吗
Do you not think the occasion befitting?

688
00:46:02,840 --> 00:46:06,660
今夜  莉莉丝最黑暗的梦就要成真了
Tonight, Lilith's darkest dream will be made real.

689
00:46:07,950 --> 00:46:08,950
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.

690
00:46:10,190 --> 00:46:11,900
我知道你也想要
I know you want this for yourself,

691
00:46:13,210 --> 00:46:14,470
但被选中的是我
but I was chosen.

692
00:46:17,500 --> 00:46:19,470
以莉莉丝的智慧
Lilith in her wisdom

693
00:46:21,110 --> 00:46:22,880
她要的是最强者
wanted the strongest.

694
00:46:25,430 --> 00:46:27,340
很高兴你作为见证人
I'm glad you're here to witness.

695
00:46:29,000 --> 00:46:32,450
你将永世传颂我的故事
You will tell this story many times.

696
00:46:33,070 --> 00:46:34,380
莎乐美
Salome.

697
00:46:35,450 --> 00:46:36,810
再考虑一下
Think about this.

698
00:46:37,300 --> 00:46:39,350
你不知道全部喝掉会怎样
You don't know what drinking all of it will do.

699
00:46:40,350 --> 00:46:41,760
莉莉丝知道
Lilith knows.

700
00:46:42,540 --> 00:46:44,060
那就够了
That's good enough for me.

701
00:46:44,320 --> 00:46:46,300
如果对你的影响
If it were to affect you...

702
00:46:47,640 --> 00:46:48,650
不利呢
adversely,

703
00:46:49,850 --> 00:46:52,170
那我们的行动就要遭受到巨大的损失
you would be a tremendous loss to the movement.

704
00:46:53,170 --> 00:46:55,120
这不是什么行动  比尔
This is not a movement, Bill.

705
00:46:55,760 --> 00:46:57,800
这是无上的喜悦
This is the fucking rapture.

706
00:46:59,270 --> 00:47:01,400
你都见识过了  还心存怀疑吗
All you've seen and you still doubt?

707
00:47:03,760 --> 00:47:08,720
所以我更为强大
That is why I am stronger.

708
00:47:10,350 --> 00:47:11,470
没错
Apparently.

709
00:47:40,210 --> 00:47:42,000
快点
Come on, now.

710
00:47:43,800 --> 00:47:45,250
快啊
Come on.

711
00:47:46,900 --> 00:47:48,620
杰森  是我们
Jason, it's us.

712
00:47:48,930 --> 00:47:50,640
安全
Oh, clear.

713
00:47:50,640 --> 00:47:52,090
过来
Come on.

714
00:47:55,020 --> 00:47:56,060
操
Fuck.

715
00:47:57,570 --> 00:47:58,660
天啊
Oh, my God.

716
00:47:59,400 --> 00:48:01,960
见到你真好  我好想你
It's good to see you. I've missed you so much.

717
00:48:02,490 --> 00:48:04,790
我过去太傻了  我爱你
I've been an idiot and I love you and--

718
00:48:06,930 --> 00:48:09,030
我不能爱上吸血鬼
I can't ever love a vampire.

719
00:48:09,310 --> 00:48:10,840
对不起  我做不到
Sorry. I can't do it.

720
00:48:15,550 --> 00:48:17,420
他们会在地面上等你们
They'll be waiting for you up top,

721
00:48:18,040 --> 00:48:20,480
我建议大家都装好弹药准备战斗
so I suggest you all reload on the ride up.

722
00:48:23,470 --> 00:48:24,850
你好
Hello.

723
00:48:29,740 --> 00:48:32,240
等等  你们不走吗
Wait, aren't you coming with us?

724
00:48:32,560 --> 00:48:34,220
我们去找比尔
We're going to get Bill.

725
00:48:34,480 --> 00:48:37,740
-埃里克  你开玩笑吧  -苏琪
- Eric, you can't be serious. - Sookie!

726
00:48:38,000 --> 00:48:41,260
你们负责清除地面  我们很快就上去
Make sure it's safe up there for us. We'll be up momentarily.

727
00:48:51,030 --> 00:48:53,510
这当然是竞争
Of course it was a competition.

728
00:48:55,350 --> 00:48:59,060
莎乐美  你致命的弱点
But the weak spot for you, Salome,

729
00:48:59,060 --> 00:49:00,760
一直存在
and it always has been,

730
00:49:01,080 --> 00:49:03,180
那就是你不大擅长
is that you're not very good

731
00:49:03,380 --> 00:49:06,710
预测对手的行为
at predicting an adversary's behavior.

732
00:49:07,550 --> 00:49:10,450
可能因为你太过自恋
Possibly because of your monumental narcissism.

733
00:49:11,580 --> 00:49:14,770
太容易欣喜若狂
You were so impatient for the rapture

734
00:49:15,250 --> 00:49:18,860
居然没有闻出血液里面的银
that you didn't even smell the silver in the blood.

735
00:49:20,060 --> 00:49:22,150
我放了不少呢
And I put in a lot.

736
00:49:22,860 --> 00:49:25,180
我知道你不会闻
But I knew that you would never smell it

737
00:49:25,180 --> 00:49:27,690
因为你的欲望太强
because you were too impatient

738
00:49:27,900 --> 00:49:30,360
一点儿耐心也没有
in your lust for greatness.

739
00:49:32,230 --> 00:49:33,840
你
You...

740
00:49:34,320 --> 00:49:39,000
用银玷污了圣母的血
defiled the Mother's blood...with silver?

741
00:49:42,500 --> 00:49:45,070
我绝不会玷污
I would never desecrate

742
00:49:45,320 --> 00:49:46,940
圣物
the Holy Grail.

743
00:50:01,420 --> 00:50:02,940
莉莉丝
Lilith...

744
00:50:05,380 --> 00:50:07,550
做了明智的选择
chose wisely.

745
00:50:38,980 --> 00:50:42,840
看来  莉莉丝也对你显身了
So, Lilith appeared to you as well.

746
00:50:43,330 --> 00:50:45,870
她只是残忍地干掉了我的创造者
Only to savagely obliterate my maker.

747
00:50:47,130 --> 00:50:48,610
比尔  她是个疯神
She's a mad god, Bill.

748
00:50:49,730 --> 00:50:51,230
只会带来毁灭
She's nothing but destruction.

749
00:50:53,540 --> 00:50:55,230
别喝
Don't do it.

750
00:50:56,510 --> 00:50:57,660
你想喝
So you can?

751
00:50:57,890 --> 00:51:00,210
倒进火里
Pour it in the fucking fire.

752
00:51:00,410 --> 00:51:01,690
你阻止不了我
You'll never stop me.

753
00:51:01,690 --> 00:51:03,510
那你为什么批准我们进来
So why'd you authorize our entry, then?

754
00:51:03,510 --> 00:51:04,770
你知道我们的意图
You knew we would try.

755
00:51:05,000 --> 00:51:06,280
因为我不确定
Because I wasn't yet sure

756
00:51:06,280 --> 00:51:08,160
能否独自干掉莎乐美
I'd be able to get rid of Salome on my own.

757
00:51:08,160 --> 00:51:09,560
比尔  这不是你
Bill, this isn't you.

758
00:51:09,560 --> 00:51:11,300
你他妈的又了解我多少
What the fuck do you know about me?

759
00:51:12,190 --> 00:51:15,710
如你所知  我对你所做的一切都是演戏
For all you know, everything I did while with you was an act

760
00:51:16,090 --> 00:51:18,640
都是为了得到你的回应
calculated to elicit a particular response.

761
00:51:18,830 --> 00:51:20,080
我知道你这是谎话
I know that's not true.

762
00:51:20,080 --> 00:51:21,630
为什么  就因为你有光吗
Why, because of the light you bear?

763
00:51:21,820 --> 00:51:24,760
你就没有想过那可能是你的缺陷吗
Did you ever consider the possibility that it's a handicap?

764
00:51:24,960 --> 00:51:27,750
要你看不清再明显不过的事实
One that blinds you to the most obvious of truths--

765
00:51:28,640 --> 00:51:30,470
不知道你是多么令人厌恶
that you are an abomination,

766
00:51:31,560 --> 00:51:33,610
正如血族圣经所记述的一样
just like the vampire Bible states.

767
00:51:34,960 --> 00:51:37,890
比尔  你没有这么脆弱
Bill, you are stronger than this.

768
00:51:38,100 --> 00:51:42,890
你心怀同情  你是那么仁慈和慷慨
You are capable of sympathy and kindness and generosity.

769
00:51:43,660 --> 00:51:46,440
你是我见过的吸血鬼里最特别的一个
You are unique among all the vampires I have met.

770
00:51:47,980 --> 00:51:49,450
不要全都抛弃了
Don't throw that away.

771
00:51:53,770 --> 00:51:57,820
我这辈子都为自己是吸血鬼而愧疚
I have spent my entire life as a vampire apologizing,

772
00:51:58,460 --> 00:52:01,820
相信自己生性邪恶不堪
believing I was inherently wrong somehow,

773
00:52:02,970 --> 00:52:04,100
活在恐惧当中
living in fear--

774
00:52:05,930 --> 00:52:07,920
害怕神抛弃了我
fear that God had forsaken me,

775
00:52:09,070 --> 00:52:10,300
我是被诅咒的
that I was damned.

776
00:52:12,000 --> 00:52:14,540
是莉莉丝将我们从恐惧中解救
But Lilith grants us freedom from fear.

777
00:52:16,140 --> 00:52:17,990
枯荣录第九章二十四节
Vicissitudes 9:24.

778
00:52:19,090 --> 00:52:20,170
"无需恐惧
"Fear not,

779
00:52:20,670 --> 00:52:23,350
吾之血超乎恐惧之外
for my blood is beyond fear--

780
00:52:23,350 --> 00:52:26,450
对罪恶之恐惧  对人类之恐惧
fear of sin, fear of mankind,

781
00:52:26,900 --> 00:52:29,080
对报应之恐惧
fear of retribution,

782
00:52:29,590 --> 00:52:32,420
因汝为神之子
for thou art begat by God.

783
00:52:32,860 --> 00:52:34,730
此界只是消解
And this world is but a spring

784
00:52:34,730 --> 00:52:37,060
汝圣渴之泉水"
to slake thy sacred thirst."

785
00:52:39,500 --> 00:52:42,870
如果你还有那么一点
If I ever meant anything

786
00:52:43,050 --> 00:52:44,380
在乎我...
to you at all--

787
00:52:44,380 --> 00:52:47,050
见面第一晚我就告诉过你
I told you the first night we met...

788
00:52:48,430 --> 00:52:51,550
吸血鬼常常袭击他们最爱的人
vampires often turn on those they love the most.

789
00:53:05,490 --> 00:53:06,660
天啊
Oh, God!

790
00:53:15,160 --> 00:53:16,640
天啊
Oh, God.

791
00:53:22,240 --> 00:53:23,410
不要
No.

792
00:53:36,780 --> 00:53:38,010
苏琪
Sookie.

793
00:53:58,820 --> 00:54:00,320
操
Fuck.

794
00:54:03,020 --> 00:54:04,320
快跑
Run!

