1
00:00:08,495 --> 00:00:10,596


2
00:00:14,495 --> 00:00:16,296
{\an8}http://hd.cnscg.com/

3
00:00:18,795 --> 00:00:20,796


4
00:00:23,595 --> 00:00:25,396


5
00:00:27,695 --> 00:00:29,796


6
00:00:30,145 --> 00:00:31,996


7
00:00:32,295 --> 00:00:34,596


8
00:00:35,145 --> 00:00:37,146


9
00:00:38,895 --> 00:00:41,046


10
00:00:43,595 --> 00:00:45,296


11
00:00:47,695 --> 00:00:49,796


12
00:00:56,495 --> 00:00:58,496


13
00:01:07,095 --> 00:01:08,696


14
00:00:05,475 --> 00:00:07,459
# The war was lost #

15
00:00:07,461 --> 00:00:09,744
# The treaty signed #

16
00:00:09,746 --> 00:00:11,913
# I was not caught #

17
00:00:11,915 --> 00:00:14,215
# I crossed the line #

18
00:00:14,217 --> 00:00:16,251
# I was not caught #

19
00:00:16,253 --> 00:00:18,587
# Though many tried #

20
00:00:18,589 --> 00:00:20,755
# I live among you #

21
00:00:20,757 --> 00:00:23,091
# Well disguised #

22
00:00:23,093 --> 00:00:25,093
# I had to leave #

23
00:00:25,095 --> 00:00:27,479
# My life behind #

24
00:00:27,481 --> 00:00:29,814
# I dug some graves #

25
00:00:29,816 --> 00:00:31,933
# You'll never find #

26
00:00:31,935 --> 00:00:34,152
# The story's told #

27
00:00:34,154 --> 00:00:36,438
# With facts and lies #

28
00:00:36,440 --> 00:00:38,690
# I have a name #

29
00:00:38,692 --> 00:00:40,909
# But never mind #

30
00:00:40,911 --> 00:00:43,194
# Never mind #

31
00:00:43,196 --> 00:00:45,030
# Never mind #

32
00:00:45,032 --> 00:00:48,917
# The war was lost, the treaty signed #

33
00:00:48,919 --> 00:00:54,089
# There's truth that lives and truth that dies #

34
00:00:54,091 --> 00:00:58,209
# I don't know which, so never mind #

35
00:01:00,681 --> 00:01:03,048
# My woman's here #

36
00:01:03,050 --> 00:01:05,350
# My children, too #

37
00:01:05,352 --> 00:01:08,853
# Their graves are safe from ghosts like you #

38
00:01:08,855 --> 00:01:14,192
# In places deep with roots entwined #

39
00:01:14,194 --> 00:01:18,613
# I live the life I left behind #

40
00:01:18,615 --> 00:01:21,032
# The war was lost #

41
00:01:21,034 --> 00:01:22,817
# The treaty signed #

42
00:01:22,819 --> 00:01:25,286
# I was not caught #

43
00:01:25,288 --> 00:01:27,489
# I crossed the line #

44
00:01:27,491 --> 00:01:29,741
# I was not caught #

45
00:01:29,743 --> 00:01:31,993
# Though many tried #

46
00:01:31,995 --> 00:01:34,329
# I live among you #

47
00:01:34,331 --> 00:01:36,731
# Well disguised #

48
00:01:25,628 --> 00:01:28,879


49
00:01:45,042 --> 00:01:46,875
Trees.

50
00:01:49,146 --> 00:01:52,347
That little place in the rock

51
00:01:52,349 --> 00:01:54,482
in the trees.

52
00:01:55,769 --> 00:01:57,902
A cave

53
00:01:57,904 --> 00:01:59,738
is how I remember it.

54
00:02:01,158 --> 00:02:03,241
It's like a fairy tale.

55
00:02:07,781 --> 00:02:09,330
Four days?

56
00:02:10,917 --> 00:02:13,668
No, maybe he gave me something.

57
00:02:14,921 --> 00:02:17,372
Maybe I blocked it out.

58
00:02:20,377 --> 00:02:23,011
It's a black hole.

59
00:02:23,013 --> 00:02:24,679
This empty space,

60
00:02:24,681 --> 00:02:27,599
those four days.

61
00:02:27,601 --> 00:02:30,051
And what I remember when I got...

62
00:02:35,692 --> 00:02:37,776
I got in the car.

63
00:02:46,369 --> 00:02:48,403
He didn't force me.

64
00:02:49,456 --> 00:02:52,073
He didn't even get near me.

65
00:02:54,294 --> 00:02:56,294
He called me pretty.

66
00:03:02,753 --> 00:03:04,919
I remember.

67
00:03:07,724 --> 00:03:10,341
I remember it made me feel...

68
00:03:11,595 --> 00:03:13,561
I liked...

69
00:03:20,654 --> 00:03:24,572
I got in the van with a stranger.

70
00:03:27,494 --> 00:03:31,112
Every time I remember

71
00:03:31,114 --> 00:03:33,448
that feeling,

72
00:03:33,450 --> 00:03:36,167
like pride,

73
00:03:36,169 --> 00:03:39,454
I get sick to my stomach.

74
00:03:39,456 --> 00:03:41,673
I could lie to myself,

75
00:03:41,675 --> 00:03:44,425
but I felt proud.

76
00:03:44,427 --> 00:03:47,846
I was proud that he thought

77
00:03:47,848 --> 00:03:50,431
I was pretty.

78
00:04:00,894 --> 00:04:02,977
Makes me sick.

79
00:04:05,398 --> 00:04:07,699
None of that was your fault.

80
00:04:44,821 --> 00:04:47,071
I walk up behind him.

81
00:04:48,191 --> 00:04:50,825
It's him. It's the guy.

82
00:04:50,827 --> 00:04:52,694
I've been thinking about him.

83
00:04:52,696 --> 00:04:56,030
I've been picturing him for months.

84
00:04:56,032 --> 00:04:59,167
I'm not sleeping.

85
00:04:59,169 --> 00:05:01,669
Passing strangers who was wondering.

86
00:05:02,756 --> 00:05:05,123
He turned his head

87
00:05:05,125 --> 00:05:07,175
right as I was up on him.

88
00:05:09,429 --> 00:05:11,796
I planned to say it...

89
00:05:13,099 --> 00:05:15,383
but I didn't say anything.

90
00:05:15,385 --> 00:05:18,052
I got sick, and to keep from being sick,

91
00:05:18,054 --> 00:05:19,637
I raised up...

92
00:05:29,232 --> 00:05:31,199
right when he was turning.

93
00:05:36,907 --> 00:05:38,656
And I...

94
00:05:44,581 --> 00:05:46,998
It didn't make anything better.

95
00:05:48,835 --> 00:05:50,585
It made it worse.

96
00:05:53,006 --> 00:05:55,723
And I know now,

97
00:05:55,725 --> 00:05:57,425
you know, the act,

98
00:05:57,427 --> 00:06:02,597
it described a trajectory.

99
00:06:04,401 --> 00:06:05,767
People...

100
00:06:08,521 --> 00:06:10,355
whole cultures

101
00:06:10,357 --> 00:06:12,607
wouldn't blame you.

102
00:06:14,244 --> 00:06:15,994
I don't.

103
00:06:23,036 --> 00:06:25,119
It wasn't him.

104
00:06:27,791 --> 00:06:30,458
They got the real guy.

105
00:06:30,460 --> 00:06:33,261
Something in Venice, you know?

106
00:06:33,263 --> 00:06:35,296
Weeks ago.

107
00:06:42,605 --> 00:06:44,389
Who was he?

108
00:06:45,809 --> 00:06:48,776
I don't even know if it matters.

109
00:07:04,711 --> 00:07:07,829
So I haven't been like this in a long time.

110
00:07:10,667 --> 00:07:12,550
Years.

111
00:07:13,720 --> 00:07:15,586
I could tell.

112
00:07:17,173 --> 00:07:19,640
Why?

113
00:07:24,014 --> 00:07:26,481
You seemed like

114
00:07:26,483 --> 00:07:28,983
you were making up for lost time.

115
00:07:42,365 --> 00:07:44,498
I'd do anything for 10 more years.

116
00:07:44,500 --> 00:07:46,167
We should have met when we were young.

117
00:07:46,169 --> 00:07:49,337
We said we wouldn't regret the past.

118
00:07:49,339 --> 00:07:52,423
Anyway, who said we don't have 10 more years?

119
00:07:54,594 --> 00:07:56,894
There's 100,000 there.

120
00:07:56,896 --> 00:07:58,979
You're gonna go with Nails.

121
00:07:58,981 --> 00:08:01,182
I'll meet you in two weeks or less.

122
00:08:01,184 --> 00:08:04,018
Like hell. I'm not leaving you.

123
00:08:04,020 --> 00:08:07,822
I know about the clubs. I saw Blake.

124
00:08:07,824 --> 00:08:10,358
- I'm not...  - You don't have a choice.

125
00:08:10,360 --> 00:08:13,244
I always have a choice.

126
00:08:14,864 --> 00:08:17,081
And I'm not going anywhere.

127
00:08:21,454 --> 00:08:24,839
It's not gonna work, the you and me thing.

128
00:08:26,426 --> 00:08:28,876
The way I see it is you weren't up front with me.

129
00:08:28,878 --> 00:08:31,712
If you can't have a kid, then what good is the design, see?

130
00:08:31,714 --> 00:08:33,848
You had me on the fairy tale for a while,

131
00:08:33,850 --> 00:08:36,217
and it was good,

132
00:08:36,219 --> 00:08:37,768
but now it's time to go.

133
00:08:37,770 --> 00:08:40,438
You can't act for shit.

134
00:08:40,440 --> 00:08:42,606
Take it from me.

135
00:08:42,608 --> 00:08:44,892
Where one goes, the other goes. That's what we said.

136
00:08:44,894 --> 00:08:48,979
That's not acting. Now take your payout and get the fuck on.

137
00:08:57,206 --> 00:09:00,708
Your ring? What is that?

138
00:09:00,710 --> 00:09:03,127
You think that I... here.

139
00:09:04,247 --> 00:09:06,997
You think I give a fuck about rings?

140
00:09:08,968 --> 00:09:11,001
- That was a big diamond.  - Fuck you.

141
00:09:11,003 --> 00:09:14,088
I am not leaving you. I know what you're doing, Frank.

142
00:09:14,090 --> 00:09:16,807
Stop reading into things. Listen to what I'm saying.

143
00:09:16,809 --> 00:09:19,143
I am listening and you're not convincing.

144
00:09:19,145 --> 00:09:20,978
So you listen to me.

145
00:09:20,980 --> 00:09:22,980
Whatever they do to you, they do to me.

146
00:09:22,982 --> 00:09:25,933
Do you understand? There's us.

147
00:09:25,935 --> 00:09:29,854
There's us, and everything else is in the gray.

148
00:09:31,240 --> 00:09:32,606
So fuck your martyrdom.

149
00:09:32,608 --> 00:09:35,609
I came in this with my eyes open, same as you.

150
00:09:45,538 --> 00:09:47,004
You have to go.

151
00:09:47,006 --> 00:09:50,791
I got us new cars. Nails is gonna watch out for you.

152
00:09:50,793 --> 00:09:52,960
No.

153
00:09:52,962 --> 00:09:54,962
You come with me.

154
00:09:54,964 --> 00:09:57,465
100,000 is more than enough.

155
00:09:57,467 --> 00:10:00,468
- To start over?  - To hold on to what's ours.

156
00:10:00,470 --> 00:10:02,269
I can't run.

157
00:10:02,271 --> 00:10:04,939
They'll come for me and they'll keep coming.

158
00:10:04,941 --> 00:10:06,524
I need to finish this.

159
00:10:06,526 --> 00:10:08,309
You can't finish this.

160
00:10:08,311 --> 00:10:11,312
They made sure of that before they threw the first punch.

161
00:10:11,314 --> 00:10:14,198
I have a play. One thing they don't know.

162
00:10:14,200 --> 00:10:16,200
It's not worth it.

163
00:10:16,202 --> 00:10:20,070
I cannot run. It'll never stop.

164
00:10:20,072 --> 00:10:22,406
If I do that and I come home

165
00:10:22,408 --> 00:10:25,075
and I find you, no.

166
00:10:26,162 --> 00:10:27,745
No.

167
00:10:30,967 --> 00:10:33,501
I'm not... I'm not leaving you.

168
00:10:34,971 --> 00:10:39,807
Baby, you made it all mean something.

169
00:10:41,227 --> 00:10:43,761
Everything before we met.

170
00:10:46,098 --> 00:10:48,849
If they came to me through you,

171
00:10:48,851 --> 00:10:51,235
if they hurt you,

172
00:10:51,237 --> 00:10:53,654
I couldn't,

173
00:10:53,656 --> 00:10:56,240
I wouldn't deserve to live.

174
00:10:56,242 --> 00:10:58,692
If you love me,

175
00:10:58,694 --> 00:11:01,328
I cannot do the things I have to do

176
00:11:01,330 --> 00:11:03,781
unless I know you're safe.

177
00:11:03,783 --> 00:11:05,866
If I don't think you're safe,

178
00:11:05,868 --> 00:11:07,535
I'm lost.

179
00:11:07,537 --> 00:11:08,702
They got me.

180
00:11:08,704 --> 00:11:11,372
Nails has two tickets.

181
00:11:11,374 --> 00:11:14,375
Venezuela, out of Oregon.

182
00:11:14,377 --> 00:11:16,460
Not unless you're with me.

183
00:11:16,462 --> 00:11:19,046
Otherwise the last six years are nothing.

184
00:11:19,048 --> 00:11:21,382
No, they weren't.

185
00:11:21,384 --> 00:11:23,467
Never nothing.

186
00:11:23,469 --> 00:11:25,886
I know.

187
00:11:25,888 --> 00:11:29,273
I know. That was never our story.

188
00:11:31,894 --> 00:11:33,694
I got my ticket out.

189
00:11:33,696 --> 00:11:36,780
I'll meet you inside of two weeks, I promise.

190
00:11:41,370 --> 00:11:43,404
Two weeks.

191
00:11:43,406 --> 00:11:45,406
Or less.

192
00:11:45,408 --> 00:11:46,624
Barquisimeto.

193
00:11:46,626 --> 00:11:49,460
You'll meet me in two weeks

194
00:11:49,462 --> 00:11:51,579
or less.

195
00:11:51,581 --> 00:11:53,964
El Obelisco.

196
00:11:53,966 --> 00:11:55,549
There's a park there.

197
00:11:57,837 --> 00:11:59,920
Wear a white dress.

198
00:12:02,758 --> 00:12:06,477
You wear a white suit with a red rose in your jacket.

199
00:12:07,763 --> 00:12:10,598
I'll wear a red rose in my jacket.

200
00:12:13,019 --> 00:12:15,235
I'll see you coming out of the crowd,

201
00:12:15,237 --> 00:12:17,605
a head higher than everybody else.

202
00:12:19,241 --> 00:12:21,825
At first I'm worried.

203
00:12:21,827 --> 00:12:23,611
I can't see you.

204
00:12:26,616 --> 00:12:28,499
But then you do.

205
00:12:30,002 --> 00:12:31,585
I see the white dress.

206
00:12:44,016 --> 00:12:45,849
You don't have to do that, Frank.

207
00:12:45,851 --> 00:12:47,801
I mean the money.

208
00:12:47,803 --> 00:12:49,720
Couldn't see.

209
00:12:49,722 --> 00:12:51,138
Blood in my eyes.

210
00:12:51,140 --> 00:12:53,857
Nail in my fucking head.

211
00:12:53,859 --> 00:12:55,693
I heard him saying leave me.

212
00:12:55,695 --> 00:12:58,228
Fucking teamster. A nail gun.

213
00:12:58,230 --> 00:13:01,815
Slung me over your shoulder. I don't forget that.

214
00:13:01,817 --> 00:13:04,068
I know you don't.

215
00:13:07,456 --> 00:13:09,823
Nobody's gonna get near her.

216
00:13:09,825 --> 00:13:11,792
I promise.

217
00:13:11,794 --> 00:13:13,494
We'll see you in two weeks.

218
00:13:13,496 --> 00:13:14,745
Or less.

219
00:13:49,532 --> 00:13:53,500
The security camera right down the street.

220
00:13:53,502 --> 00:13:55,035
Yeah, he, uh...

221
00:13:55,037 --> 00:13:58,038
he worked under the prosecutor for the AG that got murdered.

222
00:13:58,040 --> 00:14:00,874
Excuse me.

223
00:14:03,045 --> 00:14:04,461
- Yeah?  - Woodrugh?

224
00:14:04,463 --> 00:14:06,930
He's no longer with us, I'm afraid.

225
00:14:06,932 --> 00:14:09,183
Hello, Ray.

226
00:14:11,220 --> 00:14:14,388
- What happened?  - Why don't you tell me, Ray?

227
00:14:14,390 --> 00:14:18,192
Hmm? Davis, Woodrugh.

228
00:14:18,194 --> 00:14:19,727
It's all you, right?

229
00:14:21,313 --> 00:14:23,397
You know I know, right?

230
00:14:23,399 --> 00:14:25,783
The robbery in '92.

231
00:14:25,785 --> 00:14:27,985
Caspere kept some diamonds.

232
00:14:27,987 --> 00:14:30,788
He was holding them over you, yeah?

233
00:14:32,124 --> 00:14:35,492
We should meet. Let's talk this over.

234
00:14:35,494 --> 00:14:37,628
You could come out of this good, Ray.

235
00:14:38,798 --> 00:14:40,748
I can make it go away.

236
00:14:40,750 --> 00:14:44,468
Put you right. Get you paid.

237
00:14:44,470 --> 00:14:46,720
Sure.

238
00:14:46,722 --> 00:14:50,841
Yeah, I'll drop by PD later today.

239
00:14:53,095 --> 00:14:54,344
Where are you?

240
00:14:54,346 --> 00:14:57,014
Come on, Ray. You're one of us.

241
00:14:58,434 --> 00:15:01,101
Why Woodrugh? There was no reason.

242
00:15:01,103 --> 00:15:04,571
Why do you care? You know the guy was a fag, right?

243
00:15:04,573 --> 00:15:06,190
Come on, you're a player, Ray.

244
00:15:06,192 --> 00:15:08,108
Let's talk. We can work this out.

245
00:15:08,110 --> 00:15:09,777
Yeah, sure thing, Lieutenant.

246
00:15:12,782 --> 00:15:15,032
What was that?

247
00:15:16,452 --> 00:15:18,418
Woodrugh.

248
00:15:20,172 --> 00:15:21,672
He's dead.

249
00:15:31,317 --> 00:15:33,434
Who?

250
00:15:33,436 --> 00:15:35,352
Why? What...

251
00:15:35,354 --> 00:15:39,156
Jesus Christ. He was gonna have a fucking kid.

252
00:15:39,158 --> 00:15:41,358
It was Burris.

253
00:15:41,360 --> 00:15:43,777
They're putting it on me.

254
00:15:43,779 --> 00:15:45,696
First Davis, now... fuck!

255
00:15:45,698 --> 00:15:48,115
I can't... I can't...

256
00:15:48,117 --> 00:15:50,250
Jesus, he was...

257
00:15:52,672 --> 00:15:54,705
after everything else.

258
00:15:56,008 --> 00:15:58,926
Fuck.

259
00:16:07,770 --> 00:16:09,970
He was better than us.

260
00:16:12,808 --> 00:16:15,359
He saved our asses.

261
00:16:16,362 --> 00:16:18,145
Twice.

262
00:16:19,815 --> 00:16:21,482
Three times.

263
00:16:22,902 --> 00:16:25,735
Now.

264
00:16:30,242 --> 00:16:31,992
He deserved better.

265
00:16:37,133 --> 00:16:39,466
Who do we have now?

266
00:16:40,670 --> 00:16:43,587
The girl Erica, she's in the wind.

267
00:16:50,312 --> 00:16:51,762
There was two of them.

268
00:16:51,764 --> 00:16:54,815
- The kids... boy, girl.  - What?

269
00:16:54,817 --> 00:16:57,017
Field interviews, that movie set.

270
00:16:57,019 --> 00:17:00,404
We had a crew list. There was a guy there. Set photographer.

271
00:17:00,406 --> 00:17:03,190
She talked to him. The ages are right.

272
00:17:03,192 --> 00:17:05,743
Fuck, they even kind of looked alike.

273
00:17:05,745 --> 00:17:08,529
Set photographer. Lenny Tyler.

274
00:17:08,531 --> 00:17:11,331
That's the brother. Laura and Leonard.

275
00:17:11,333 --> 00:17:13,450
They might have the hard drive.

276
00:17:13,452 --> 00:17:14,918
Caspere's hidden camera.

277
00:17:14,920 --> 00:17:17,538
Caspere's murder, if it was them,

278
00:17:17,540 --> 00:17:19,540
it just opened up all this other stuff.

279
00:17:19,542 --> 00:17:22,292
We were always set up.

280
00:17:22,294 --> 00:17:23,594
So was Frank.

281
00:17:23,596 --> 00:17:24,762
Your gangster buddy.

282
00:17:24,764 --> 00:17:26,213
Yeah, he's actually not a bad guy,

283
00:17:26,215 --> 00:17:29,183
but, yeah, Caspere was playing him.

284
00:17:29,185 --> 00:17:31,885
So we find Osterman. Tyler.

285
00:17:31,887 --> 00:17:34,221
Says here Lenny's with the union.

286
00:17:34,223 --> 00:17:36,190
They'd have some kind of address.

287
00:17:42,782 --> 00:17:44,732
Unless you just want to take off.

288
00:17:47,119 --> 00:17:50,037
I'm pretty sure

289
00:17:50,039 --> 00:17:52,239
I can get us out of the country.

290
00:17:54,293 --> 00:17:57,911
If there's a chance to get them, I want to take it.

291
00:18:02,334 --> 00:18:05,252
I was never big on running myself.

292
00:18:07,840 --> 00:18:09,757
Woodrugh wasn't.

293
00:18:54,220 --> 00:18:56,270
Hello.

294
00:19:11,821 --> 00:19:13,453
Austin?

295
00:19:15,324 --> 00:19:17,491
Tony?

296
00:19:19,295 --> 00:19:21,745
Where is he? Tony.

297
00:19:21,747 --> 00:19:24,748
I don't know.

298
00:19:24,750 --> 00:19:26,667
What... what day is it?

299
00:19:28,304 --> 00:19:31,138
- There was yelling.  - Yelling about what?

300
00:19:31,140 --> 00:19:35,008
A Russian man. Tony's parties.

301
00:19:35,010 --> 00:19:37,344
His new business or something.

302
00:19:37,346 --> 00:19:38,645
Hard to remember.

303
00:19:38,647 --> 00:19:40,764
How did you meet Austin the mayor?

304
00:19:40,766 --> 00:19:43,400
Tony introduced us.

305
00:19:43,402 --> 00:19:46,820
He say his father lonely since mother got sick.

306
00:19:48,858 --> 00:19:50,858
But you were Tony's friend first?

307
00:20:08,093 --> 00:20:09,877
How did this...

308
00:20:09,879 --> 00:20:12,546
I... I don't... he kill himself?

309
00:20:12,548 --> 00:20:14,181
Where's the daughter Betty?

310
00:20:14,183 --> 00:20:17,718
Betty? She was there, I think.

311
00:20:17,720 --> 00:20:19,469
With the yelling.

312
00:20:19,471 --> 00:20:21,188
They talk about me. I hear them.

313
00:20:21,190 --> 00:20:23,807
She's sick like her mother.

314
00:20:23,809 --> 00:20:26,693
I can't believe Austin would do this.

315
00:20:26,695 --> 00:20:29,146
Are you fucking dense?

316
00:20:29,148 --> 00:20:31,231
This is your boy Tony.

317
00:20:31,233 --> 00:20:33,400
Made it look like some half-ass suicide.

318
00:20:33,402 --> 00:20:36,653
And my guess is you'll be taking the fall.

319
00:20:36,655 --> 00:20:39,122
Where's Tony now? Think.

320
00:20:39,124 --> 00:20:40,407
Where would he be?

321
00:20:40,409 --> 00:20:42,993
I... I don't know. He's cold to me now.

322
00:20:44,997 --> 00:20:46,747
Is there a safe in the house?

323
00:20:46,749 --> 00:20:48,632
Do you have access to bank accounts?

324
00:20:48,634 --> 00:20:50,167
Austin handles those things.

325
00:20:50,169 --> 00:20:52,502
I have allowance.

326
00:20:52,504 --> 00:20:55,222
Then I hope you saved some of that Miss Ukraine money.

327
00:22:46,001 --> 00:22:48,035
Len?

328
00:22:56,595 --> 00:22:58,261
Len?

329
00:23:08,390 --> 00:23:10,357
You?

330
00:23:20,569 --> 00:23:23,537
They split us up after.

331
00:23:23,539 --> 00:23:25,489
I had a foster family,

332
00:23:25,491 --> 00:23:27,741
but Len went into a group home.

333
00:23:29,128 --> 00:23:32,579
I ran away at 16.

334
00:23:32,581 --> 00:23:34,498
Started working the streets.

335
00:23:34,500 --> 00:23:36,967
How did you meet Caspere?

336
00:23:36,969 --> 00:23:39,469
Through Tascha.

337
00:23:39,471 --> 00:23:41,755
She introduced me to Tony.

338
00:23:41,757 --> 00:23:44,174
Brought me into the parties.

339
00:23:44,176 --> 00:23:47,094
Then she told me about his diamonds.

340
00:23:48,931 --> 00:23:50,931
Then I met him...

341
00:23:52,568 --> 00:23:54,434
and I knew.

342
00:23:54,436 --> 00:23:57,237
He used to visit my mother.

343
00:23:58,357 --> 00:24:00,273
I remembered him.

344
00:24:02,277 --> 00:24:05,112
And you got him to hire you?

345
00:24:05,114 --> 00:24:07,664
I changed my name.

346
00:24:07,666 --> 00:24:09,583
Dyed my hair red.

347
00:24:09,585 --> 00:24:12,119
He didn't recognize me from the parties.

348
00:24:12,121 --> 00:24:15,372
I started digging into all of his stuff.

349
00:24:15,374 --> 00:24:18,008
And Len, your brother?

350
00:24:18,010 --> 00:24:21,178
We found each other years back.

351
00:24:23,632 --> 00:24:25,966
He'd been through a lot.

352
00:24:25,968 --> 00:24:29,102
The places he grew up.

353
00:24:30,389 --> 00:24:32,472
I got him a job on the movie set.

354
00:24:33,642 --> 00:24:37,277
And what happened with Caspere exactly?

355
00:24:37,279 --> 00:24:39,229
I went to his place.

356
00:24:39,231 --> 00:24:42,449
His other place. I left the door unlocked.

357
00:24:42,451 --> 00:24:44,234
Put a pill in his drink.

358
00:24:44,236 --> 00:24:47,954
Len came in. He saw inside the house.

359
00:24:49,992 --> 00:24:52,492
He knew what I'd been doing.

360
00:24:52,494 --> 00:24:55,795
He went bad.

361
00:24:55,797 --> 00:24:59,499
He was gonna use the acid to get Ben to talk,

362
00:24:59,501 --> 00:25:01,384
to tell us who else had robbed us,

363
00:25:01,386 --> 00:25:05,255
who had killed our parents, but he got carried away.

364
00:25:05,257 --> 00:25:07,474
He was too angry.

365
00:25:09,011 --> 00:25:11,311
He put him out there on the road.

366
00:25:11,313 --> 00:25:13,346
- Why?  - I don't know.

367
00:25:14,600 --> 00:25:16,566
I think...

368
00:25:18,437 --> 00:25:20,353
he thought it was funny.

369
00:25:20,355 --> 00:25:23,073
Caspere was confessing everything.

370
00:25:23,075 --> 00:25:25,108
Begging.

371
00:25:25,110 --> 00:25:28,495
He told him about the rail corridor.

372
00:25:28,497 --> 00:25:32,365
He drove around with Ben's body through all those places.

373
00:25:32,367 --> 00:25:35,202
Why'd he leave you like this?

374
00:25:36,955 --> 00:25:39,506
Because I was trying to stop them.

375
00:25:39,508 --> 00:25:41,041
From what?

376
00:25:41,043 --> 00:25:44,044
He's gonna meet up with that chief, Holloway.

377
00:25:44,046 --> 00:25:45,845
He's gonna trade him the hard drive

378
00:25:45,847 --> 00:25:47,631
from Ben's place for the diamonds.

379
00:25:47,633 --> 00:25:48,715
What's on the hard drive?

380
00:25:48,717 --> 00:25:51,885
Would have been footage of important men.

381
00:25:51,887 --> 00:25:55,388
- You said would have.  - We didn't have the password.

382
00:25:56,558 --> 00:25:58,308
And the hard drive erased itself.

383
00:25:58,310 --> 00:26:00,944
Some kind of security feature.

384
00:26:00,946 --> 00:26:04,231
- It's blank.  - He's going there to kill Holloway.

385
00:26:05,867 --> 00:26:07,484
Where's he meeting Holloway?

386
00:26:07,486 --> 00:26:09,069
How long ago did he leave?

387
00:26:09,071 --> 00:26:11,738
A couple of hours. He wanted to get there early.

388
00:26:11,740 --> 00:26:13,823
- Where?  - The train station here.

389
00:26:13,825 --> 00:26:16,910
The big new one. He wanted a public place.

390
00:26:16,912 --> 00:26:20,413
We got her testimony. You stay with her until we can walk her into a precinct.

391
00:26:20,415 --> 00:26:22,132
Ray. Ray, wait.

392
00:26:37,349 --> 00:26:40,684
Saw the mayor went for a swim. Thought I should say good-bye.

393
00:26:40,686 --> 00:26:44,487
What are you doing, Frank? This was very unlike you.

394
00:26:44,489 --> 00:26:48,775
Lashing out, childish. Now I have to answer.

395
00:26:48,777 --> 00:26:51,778
Like I had to answer this, you patronizing old fuck?

396
00:26:51,780 --> 00:26:54,497
Are you still in LA, Frank?

397
00:26:54,499 --> 00:26:58,118
Oh, I'm long gone, cue ball.

398
00:26:58,120 --> 00:26:59,536
But we'll settle up later.

399
00:26:59,538 --> 00:27:01,621
We certainly will.

400
00:27:01,623 --> 00:27:05,125
Good luck with that, you KGB kike motherfucker.

401
00:27:05,127 --> 00:27:07,460
I'll only need the one bullet.

402
00:27:07,462 --> 00:27:09,796
Maybe not today and maybe not tomorrow,

403
00:27:09,798 --> 00:27:12,215
but, Osip, when the lights go out,

404
00:27:12,217 --> 00:27:14,434
that's me.

405
00:27:23,195 --> 00:27:25,362
Who is this?

406
00:27:25,364 --> 00:27:28,982
-  Velcoro.  - Ray.

407
00:27:28,984 --> 00:27:31,484
I was just thinking about you.

408
00:27:36,792 --> 00:27:38,458
Where are you taking me?

409
00:27:38,460 --> 00:27:40,043
Me? Nowhere.

410
00:27:40,045 --> 00:27:42,162
This bus goes to Seattle.

411
00:27:42,164 --> 00:27:44,497
Hits a couple stops in between.

412
00:27:44,499 --> 00:27:48,335
You get out of here. Forget this.

413
00:27:48,337 --> 00:27:49,803
Maybe it can blow over for you.

414
00:27:49,805 --> 00:27:53,139
This is never gonna blow over.

415
00:27:53,141 --> 00:27:55,008
My life ended that day.

416
00:27:55,010 --> 00:27:57,227
Except it didn't.

417
00:27:57,229 --> 00:28:00,597
You can lay it down. I'm giving you that.

418
00:28:01,983 --> 00:28:03,600
Why?

419
00:28:04,569 --> 00:28:07,737
Because...

420
00:28:07,739 --> 00:28:09,272
whatever debt there was,

421
00:28:09,274 --> 00:28:12,525
you're not the person who needs to be punished now.

422
00:28:12,527 --> 00:28:14,277
What about Len?

423
00:28:17,866 --> 00:28:19,366
Lay him to rest.

424
00:28:19,368 --> 00:28:21,584
Sounds like you lost him years ago.

425
00:28:25,374 --> 00:28:26,956
What am I supposed to do?

426
00:28:29,845 --> 00:28:31,878
I don't know.

427
00:29:07,082 --> 00:29:08,965
Nobody is here right now.

428
00:29:08,967 --> 00:29:11,167
I just move a group through.

429
00:29:11,169 --> 00:29:14,587
Anybody come around asking about me?

430
00:29:14,589 --> 00:29:16,389
No.

431
00:29:23,014 --> 00:29:24,981
What are you doing, Frank?

432
00:29:24,983 --> 00:29:26,182
Taking off soon.

433
00:29:26,184 --> 00:29:29,018
And I'm signing the place over to you.

434
00:29:29,020 --> 00:29:31,020
All the way.

435
00:29:31,022 --> 00:29:33,106
It's yours.

436
00:29:33,108 --> 00:29:34,774
Thank you.

437
00:29:34,776 --> 00:29:37,327
I was always grateful for your help.

438
00:29:41,416 --> 00:29:44,167
You heard about Ray?

439
00:29:45,337 --> 00:29:47,170
It's a frame-up.

440
00:29:47,172 --> 00:29:49,622
He'll be back here, everything goes all right.

441
00:29:49,624 --> 00:29:51,541
They're gonna need transport to Mexico.

442
00:29:52,711 --> 00:29:54,711
They?

443
00:29:54,713 --> 00:29:56,796
Him and a woman.

444
00:29:58,183 --> 00:30:00,717
What is going on? I heard about the poker room.

445
00:30:00,719 --> 00:30:03,686
Everything's ending.

446
00:30:03,688 --> 00:30:05,305
Time to wake up.

447
00:30:14,616 --> 00:30:20,320
# lately I'm not feeling like myself #

448
00:30:22,824 --> 00:30:26,326
# when I look into the glass #

449
00:30:26,328 --> 00:30:29,913
# I see someone else #

450
00:30:32,334 --> 00:30:36,503
# I hardly recognize this face I wear #

451
00:30:36,505 --> 00:30:41,474
# when I stare into her eyes, I see no one there #

452
00:30:41,476 --> 00:30:47,063
# lately I'm not feeling like myself #

453
00:30:54,856 --> 00:31:00,693
# lately I've been losing all my time #

454
00:31:03,865 --> 00:31:06,866
# all that mattered to me #

455
00:31:06,868 --> 00:31:09,669
# slips my mind #

456
00:31:13,375 --> 00:31:17,210
# every time I hit another town #

457
00:31:17,212 --> 00:31:21,514
# strangers appear to lock me down #

458
00:31:21,516 --> 00:31:27,136
# and lately I've been losing all my time #

459
00:32:06,428 --> 00:32:09,512
Don't turn around or I'll cut you in half before the show even starts.

460
00:32:09,514 --> 00:32:11,731
Just listen closely.

461
00:32:11,733 --> 00:32:13,316
You're fucking this up, kid.

462
00:32:13,318 --> 00:32:15,101
Who are you?

463
00:32:15,103 --> 00:32:17,437
The guy you blasted with a fucking shotgun

464
00:32:17,439 --> 00:32:18,988
in your little bird mask.

465
00:32:18,990 --> 00:32:21,941
That was Caspere's. Sick fuck.

466
00:32:21,943 --> 00:32:23,159
Could have killed you.

467
00:32:23,161 --> 00:32:25,278
Well, you don't need to worry about that right now.

468
00:32:27,115 --> 00:32:29,449
I know what they did.

469
00:32:29,451 --> 00:32:31,701
- Why you're here. - You know what they did?

470
00:32:33,371 --> 00:32:36,789
To my father? To me and my sister?

471
00:32:38,093 --> 00:32:40,126
Executed.

472
00:32:40,128 --> 00:32:42,679
Turned my sister into a whore.

473
00:32:42,681 --> 00:32:45,348
I know everything.

474
00:32:45,350 --> 00:32:46,933
I want them, too.

475
00:32:46,935 --> 00:32:49,469
But suicide ain't gonna get that.

476
00:32:49,471 --> 00:32:50,937
You want revenge?

477
00:32:50,939 --> 00:32:52,472
Drag their shit out into the light.

478
00:32:52,474 --> 00:32:54,974
They won't get punished.

479
00:32:54,976 --> 00:32:57,944
I am the blade and the bullet.

480
00:33:02,117 --> 00:33:04,150
Then listen carefully to me.

481
00:34:12,020 --> 00:34:14,554
The hard drive is in this bag.

482
00:34:14,556 --> 00:34:16,939
Lot of interesting things on there.

483
00:34:16,941 --> 00:34:21,728
A man with this, buy himself a lot of juice.

484
00:34:28,236 --> 00:34:30,203
What?

485
00:34:30,205 --> 00:34:32,238
What, a wire?

486
00:34:32,240 --> 00:34:33,706
See, I don't need a wire, Chief.

487
00:34:33,708 --> 00:34:35,291
I got plenty of insurance.

488
00:34:35,293 --> 00:34:38,377
What I need is a payout.

489
00:34:38,379 --> 00:34:40,413
The land documents.

490
00:34:40,415 --> 00:34:42,465
They're in the bag, too.

491
00:34:43,835 --> 00:34:46,085
The man who wanted to meet, he killed Caspere?

492
00:34:46,087 --> 00:34:47,587
Correct.

493
00:34:47,589 --> 00:34:49,672
One of the Osterman kids.

494
00:34:49,674 --> 00:34:51,891
All grown up.

495
00:34:51,893 --> 00:34:53,309
Where is he now?

496
00:34:53,311 --> 00:34:55,928
In a Vinci landfill.

497
00:34:57,065 --> 00:34:59,515
I got copies of everything.

498
00:34:59,517 --> 00:35:04,020
Something happens to me on the way out,

499
00:35:04,022 --> 00:35:05,521
that shit hits the cloud.

500
00:35:05,523 --> 00:35:08,241
News agencies.

501
00:35:08,243 --> 00:35:09,609
What do you want?

502
00:35:09,611 --> 00:35:12,111
Any chance you brought the stones?

503
00:35:16,451 --> 00:35:19,001
Plastic. Had I known you were coming,

504
00:35:19,003 --> 00:35:22,622
we could have made different arrangements.

505
00:35:22,624 --> 00:35:25,758
I want out from under.

506
00:35:25,760 --> 00:35:27,927
I want my name cleared.

507
00:35:29,097 --> 00:35:31,714
For the hard drive and land documents?

508
00:35:35,220 --> 00:35:36,969
And Bezzerides?

509
00:35:36,971 --> 00:35:38,638
Where is she?

510
00:35:38,640 --> 00:35:40,807
Fuck should I know?

511
00:35:40,809 --> 00:35:44,610
She and that Woodrugh guy both thought I did Davis.

512
00:35:44,612 --> 00:35:47,730
Think I've been working for you the whole time.

513
00:35:47,732 --> 00:35:50,032
Too bad you weren't.

514
00:35:50,034 --> 00:35:54,487
Honestly, Ray, nobody had an idea you were this competent.

515
00:35:55,874 --> 00:35:59,208
You all bought your way into Vinci with the stones.

516
00:35:59,210 --> 00:36:02,328
Caspere made a deal with Chessani.

517
00:36:02,330 --> 00:36:04,664
Ben had a talent for dissembling.

518
00:36:04,666 --> 00:36:05,798
And Dixon?

519
00:36:05,800 --> 00:36:07,717
He wasted his part of the take, yeah?

520
00:36:07,719 --> 00:36:10,169
He was looking to, what, blackmail you guys for a new piece?

521
00:36:10,171 --> 00:36:11,838
Where is this going, Ray?

522
00:36:11,840 --> 00:36:14,173
Amarilla. The shoot-out.

523
00:36:14,175 --> 00:36:15,675
How did that happen?

524
00:36:15,677 --> 00:36:18,561
He may have gotten a tip about the raid.

525
00:36:20,265 --> 00:36:22,932
Closed everything out, didn't it?

526
00:36:24,652 --> 00:36:27,353
Now you got a piece of that central corridor.

527
00:36:31,025 --> 00:36:33,693
You know Chessani's dead, right?

528
00:36:33,695 --> 00:36:35,778
Not the Chessani I work for.

529
00:36:37,115 --> 00:36:39,866
Cut the shit, Ray.

530
00:36:39,868 --> 00:36:42,702
Whatever happened in '92 isn't the issue.

531
00:36:42,704 --> 00:36:46,005
You want clear, we put this on Bezzerides.

532
00:36:46,007 --> 00:36:48,257
Geldof is already on board.

533
00:36:53,381 --> 00:36:55,381
No sudden movements, son.

534
00:36:55,383 --> 00:36:57,934
You're public enemy number one.

535
00:36:57,936 --> 00:37:00,853
Don't even need a reason to vaporize you.

536
00:37:06,945 --> 00:37:09,478
Couldn't you have just taken the stones?

537
00:37:09,480 --> 00:37:11,314
Way back?

538
00:37:12,817 --> 00:37:14,450
Did you have to kill those people?

539
00:37:14,452 --> 00:37:17,904
The Osterman woman had been seeing Ben for years.

540
00:37:17,906 --> 00:37:21,073
She was pregnant and she knew things.

541
00:37:21,075 --> 00:37:22,742
When he tried to break it off, she threatened him.

542
00:37:22,744 --> 00:37:25,828
Ben didn't even want the first kid, much less another one.

543
00:37:25,830 --> 00:37:27,630
The first one?

544
00:37:27,632 --> 00:37:29,382
The girl. The little one.

545
00:37:29,384 --> 00:37:32,001
That was Ben's illegitimate daughter.

546
00:37:55,360 --> 00:37:56,826
- Downstairs!  - Oh, my God! Go!

547
00:37:58,947 --> 00:38:01,414
- No!  - Move, move!

548
00:38:03,284 --> 00:38:05,251
Out of the way!

549
00:38:23,221 --> 00:38:25,438
# the mystery #

550
00:38:25,440 --> 00:38:28,357
# that no one knows #

551
00:38:32,480 --> 00:38:34,780
# where does love go #

552
00:38:34,782 --> 00:38:37,233
# when it goes? #

553
00:38:40,321 --> 00:38:43,572
# lately words are missing #

554
00:38:43,574 --> 00:38:46,409
# from now on #

555
00:38:49,914 --> 00:38:52,415
# vanished in the haze #

556
00:38:52,417 --> 00:38:55,167
# of love gone wrong #

557
00:38:58,840 --> 00:39:01,090
# there's no future #

558
00:39:01,092 --> 00:39:03,259
# there's no past #

559
00:39:03,261 --> 00:39:07,513
# in the present, nothing lasts #

560
00:39:07,515 --> 00:39:13,102
# lately someone's missing from now on... #

561
00:39:35,343 --> 00:39:37,126
We met?

562
00:39:41,716 --> 00:39:44,467
You're a cop, right?

563
00:39:44,469 --> 00:39:45,551
Lady cop.

564
00:39:45,553 --> 00:39:48,804
What gave me away? The tits?

565
00:39:50,691 --> 00:39:54,310
I meant you're a lady. You have dignity.

566
00:39:57,982 --> 00:39:59,231
You like Ray?

567
00:40:03,287 --> 00:40:04,737
I like Ray.

568
00:40:04,739 --> 00:40:07,323
Sure that means a lot to him.

569
00:40:07,325 --> 00:40:10,576
Relationships are important.

570
00:40:10,578 --> 00:40:12,461
Maybe you disagree.

571
00:40:18,836 --> 00:40:23,255
You take this Venezuela deal we're talking,

572
00:40:23,257 --> 00:40:25,724
you make it to Barquisimeto,

573
00:40:25,726 --> 00:40:29,562
there'll be this lady there in two weeks

574
00:40:29,564 --> 00:40:31,263
at this park.

575
00:40:31,265 --> 00:40:33,599
El Obelisco.

576
00:40:33,601 --> 00:40:35,651
Her name is Jordan.

577
00:40:35,653 --> 00:40:38,187
If she's there and I'm not,

578
00:40:38,189 --> 00:40:40,406
maybe you can give her a message.

579
00:40:43,744 --> 00:40:44,994
What's that?

580
00:40:51,869 --> 00:40:54,620
Tell her I wanted to be there.

581
00:40:54,622 --> 00:40:58,207
And that story we told, it's still true.

582
00:41:30,374 --> 00:41:32,875
Talk to you a minute?

583
00:41:38,833 --> 00:41:41,634
Venezuela works. Shit extradition.

584
00:41:41,636 --> 00:41:43,385
We could have good lives.

585
00:41:43,387 --> 00:41:46,805
Well, I don't have much choice at this point.

586
00:41:46,807 --> 00:41:50,092
Anaheim went to shit.

587
00:41:50,094 --> 00:41:52,561
Yeah, but a heist?

588
00:41:52,563 --> 00:41:54,230
You got money to run?

589
00:41:54,232 --> 00:41:57,516
Can't even access a bank. No credit cards.

590
00:41:57,518 --> 00:41:59,818
Even if retreat was my inclination,

591
00:41:59,820 --> 00:42:02,188
which it fucking is not,

592
00:42:02,190 --> 00:42:05,407
you want to stay alive, you and yours,

593
00:42:05,409 --> 00:42:07,826
you need money.

594
00:42:20,591 --> 00:42:23,542
You promised me the guy who set me up.

595
00:42:23,544 --> 00:42:26,212
It was Blake.

596
00:42:26,214 --> 00:42:29,048
The guy you clipped was some shit stain had it in for him.

597
00:42:29,050 --> 00:42:32,184
Blake's gone.

598
00:42:32,186 --> 00:42:34,136
He did not go nicely.

599
00:42:42,029 --> 00:42:44,029
Maybe I spared you that one.

600
00:42:47,985 --> 00:42:50,035
These fucks will never see it coming, man.

601
00:42:50,037 --> 00:42:52,288
Place is so far up the mountain,

602
00:42:52,290 --> 00:42:55,157
it'll be a day before anybody realizes what happened.

603
00:42:55,159 --> 00:42:57,576
This is just information, right?

604
00:42:59,247 --> 00:43:00,713
Shit in the air.

605
00:43:00,715 --> 00:43:03,249
That guy they're saying you killed,

606
00:43:03,251 --> 00:43:04,967
he was your buddy, right?

607
00:43:06,587 --> 00:43:08,254
Actually,

608
00:43:08,256 --> 00:43:11,257
I don't think I knew him that well.

609
00:43:11,259 --> 00:43:12,925
But...

610
00:43:14,345 --> 00:43:17,763
yeah, yeah, he was my friend.

611
00:43:17,765 --> 00:43:19,431
Maybe that means something.

612
00:43:19,433 --> 00:43:21,433
Call it what you want...

613
00:43:21,435 --> 00:43:24,603
revenge, justice,

614
00:43:24,605 --> 00:43:26,739
a retirement package.

615
00:43:26,741 --> 00:43:28,657
Men like this...

616
00:43:30,444 --> 00:43:32,611
they always skate.

617
00:43:32,613 --> 00:43:35,497
Not with me they don't.

618
00:43:35,499 --> 00:43:38,450
I did not live my life to go out like this.

619
00:43:39,370 --> 00:43:41,120
You?

620
00:43:48,796 --> 00:43:53,382
We use a short cruise, tourists to.

621
00:43:53,384 --> 00:43:56,218
From there, we go south to San Miguel.

622
00:43:56,220 --> 00:43:58,354
My people are there. We find someone.

623
00:43:58,356 --> 00:44:00,472
We get you all to Venezuela.

624
00:44:00,474 --> 00:44:02,274
You've done this a lot?

625
00:44:03,477 --> 00:44:06,612
Much easier to bring people in than out.

626
00:44:06,614 --> 00:44:09,481
I've been trying to get Ray to see San Miguel.

627
00:44:10,868 --> 00:44:12,401
How do you know them?

628
00:44:14,121 --> 00:44:17,239
The man that hurt me years ago,

629
00:44:17,241 --> 00:44:19,658
Ray took care of him.

630
00:44:19,660 --> 00:44:22,328
Put him in prison, I mean.

631
00:44:22,330 --> 00:44:23,912
Disabled wing.

632
00:44:25,082 --> 00:44:28,417
Frank gave me the money to buy this place.

633
00:44:28,419 --> 00:44:30,803
Never asked for it back.

634
00:44:37,011 --> 00:44:39,228
How do you know Ray?

635
00:44:44,485 --> 00:44:49,021
Well, I guess we saved each other's lives.

636
00:44:56,530 --> 00:45:01,450
Tony and Betty. Pitlor, I want him on the record.

637
00:45:01,452 --> 00:45:04,370
His files. We can get confessions.

638
00:45:04,372 --> 00:45:08,006
I've heard enough confessions today.

639
00:45:14,215 --> 00:45:15,714
Venezuela?

640
00:45:18,102 --> 00:45:19,852
We got nothing to run on.

641
00:45:22,723 --> 00:45:24,807
And I owe these filth.

642
00:45:27,728 --> 00:45:29,945
I owe Woodrugh.

643
00:45:43,744 --> 00:45:45,577
Would you run?

644
00:45:47,631 --> 00:45:49,965
Now?

645
00:45:49,967 --> 00:45:52,751
If I asked, would you?

646
00:45:52,753 --> 00:45:54,803
I might.

647
00:45:58,225 --> 00:46:00,259
I just might.

648
00:47:48,369 --> 00:47:52,788
A very strong foundation on which to build a future.

649
00:47:53,958 --> 00:47:56,508
There's a point to the waltzing in.

650
00:47:56,510 --> 00:48:00,462
I do not like beginning something unfinished.

651
00:48:00,464 --> 00:48:04,266
Mr. Agronov, have you ever heard of moderation?

652
00:49:27,885 --> 00:49:29,968
Guess I was wrong.

653
00:49:29,970 --> 00:49:31,520
It was today.

654
00:49:32,640 --> 00:49:34,723
Old times, Frank.

655
00:49:34,725 --> 00:49:37,526
I saved you.

656
00:49:37,528 --> 00:49:39,645
You're like my son.

657
00:50:57,307 --> 00:50:59,891
- Stay down south.  - Yeah.

658
00:51:02,029 --> 00:51:04,029
You're going, right? We got to get out.

659
00:51:04,031 --> 00:51:06,231
Yeah, that's the plan.

660
00:51:06,233 --> 00:51:08,400
Thinking about your boy?

661
00:51:10,738 --> 00:51:12,571
Now you can send him to Yale.

662
00:51:12,573 --> 00:51:14,906
Sure.

663
00:51:16,293 --> 00:51:17,909
You taking the boat?

664
00:51:17,911 --> 00:51:19,828
I made other arrangements.

665
00:51:19,830 --> 00:51:22,798
- But I'll be there.  - All right.

666
00:52:07,678 --> 00:52:10,095
They suicided Pitlor.

667
00:52:10,097 --> 00:52:12,430
Loose ends.

668
00:52:12,432 --> 00:52:14,266
No sign of Betty or Tony anywhere.

669
00:52:14,268 --> 00:52:16,051
Fuck it. Later for them.

670
00:52:16,053 --> 00:52:17,886
Maybe one day we get it to the press.

671
00:52:17,888 --> 00:52:21,857
Maybe that "Times" guy who wrote about Vinci.

672
00:52:21,859 --> 00:52:24,309
We got a hell of a retirement bonus.

673
00:52:24,311 --> 00:52:28,313
I'm on my way now. You understand?

674
00:52:28,315 --> 00:52:30,866
Yeah.

675
00:52:30,868 --> 00:52:32,234
I understand.

676
00:52:33,320 --> 00:52:35,153
All right. You packed?

677
00:52:35,155 --> 00:52:37,155
Yeah, I'm all set.

678
00:52:37,157 --> 00:52:38,540
Boat leaves at 3:00.

679
00:52:39,827 --> 00:52:43,078
All right. I'm 40 miles out. Plenty of time.

680
00:52:43,080 --> 00:52:45,497
Well, hurry anyway.

681
00:52:45,499 --> 00:52:48,416
All right.

682
00:52:48,418 --> 00:52:50,385
I, uh...

683
00:52:55,175 --> 00:52:57,509
I'll see you in a bit.

684
00:52:57,511 --> 00:52:59,594
Yeah.

685
00:53:00,814 --> 00:53:02,647
Yeah.

686
00:53:09,773 --> 00:53:12,357
He's okay. He's on his way.

687
00:53:24,588 --> 00:53:26,421
Thanks.

688
00:53:43,190 --> 00:53:47,225
They have a total valuation of $3.5 million.

689
00:53:47,227 --> 00:53:49,311
I will stand by their grading anywhere in the world.

690
00:54:32,856 --> 00:54:34,606
Meets your bio data.

691
00:54:34,608 --> 00:54:38,493
You're even a premium club member in United and American.

692
00:54:39,696 --> 00:54:42,530
That's your two plus five.

693
00:54:49,673 --> 00:54:52,958
Frank, you're full of surprises.

694
00:54:53,961 --> 00:54:55,710
The Russians?

695
00:54:55,712 --> 00:54:59,347
I wonder when we will hear about what you've done.

696
00:55:00,684 --> 00:55:04,386
Another 500 when I'm where I need to be.

697
00:55:22,239 --> 00:55:23,738
Safe travels.

698
00:56:52,412 --> 00:56:55,130
So Chad crossed the bridge and lost Calvin's farm.

699
00:57:02,889 --> 00:57:05,757
Under five, you're supposed to use the names.

700
00:57:05,759 --> 00:57:10,061
17, that's within your maximum power threshold.

701
00:57:21,775 --> 00:57:24,075
Under five, you need 18 or higher to use...

702
00:57:38,291 --> 00:57:41,876
Yeah.

703
00:57:41,878 --> 00:57:43,461
Yeah, all right.

704
01:00:57,540 --> 01:00:59,123
Why?

705
01:01:22,899 --> 01:01:24,649
Hey, cutting it a little close.

706
01:01:26,186 --> 01:01:28,403
I, uh... I'm gonna be late.

707
01:01:28,405 --> 01:01:30,738
The fuck are you talking about?

708
01:01:30,740 --> 01:01:32,273
Get on that boat.

709
01:01:33,360 --> 01:01:35,159
Wh... what?

710
01:01:35,161 --> 01:01:37,195
You hear me? You get on that boat.

711
01:01:37,197 --> 01:01:38,663
I'll catch up.

712
01:01:38,665 --> 01:01:40,748
Wait. What... what is...

713
01:01:40,750 --> 01:01:42,784
No, just get here.

714
01:01:42,786 --> 01:01:44,786
I just wanted...

715
01:01:47,374 --> 01:01:49,874
I thought we had time.

716
01:01:49,876 --> 01:01:51,376
What?

717
01:01:53,880 --> 01:01:56,547
I just wanted to see my boy again.

718
01:01:56,549 --> 01:01:57,715
What?

719
01:01:57,717 --> 01:02:00,351
There's a transponder on my car.

720
01:02:02,021 --> 01:02:05,022
Maybe they were watching from school.

721
01:02:05,024 --> 01:02:06,808
I don't know.

722
01:02:06,810 --> 01:02:08,893
Dump it.

723
01:02:08,895 --> 01:02:10,361
Come on, get rid of it.

724
01:02:10,363 --> 01:02:13,114
Put it on a truck headed north. Come on... shit, Ray.

725
01:02:13,116 --> 01:02:14,732
I can't.

726
01:02:14,734 --> 01:02:17,785
They could have already been watching, see?

727
01:02:17,787 --> 01:02:20,238
And if they got eyes on me,

728
01:02:20,240 --> 01:02:22,156
it won't matter what I do with the tracker.

729
01:02:22,158 --> 01:02:23,708
I'd just lead them to you.

730
01:02:23,710 --> 01:02:25,410
You understand?

731
01:02:25,412 --> 01:02:27,578
- So what... what are...  - You just get on the boat.

732
01:02:27,580 --> 01:02:30,748
Just take the files, take the recordings and get on that boat.

733
01:02:30,750 --> 01:02:33,634
Look, I'll ditch the car

734
01:02:33,636 --> 01:02:35,720
in a parking garage.

735
01:02:35,722 --> 01:02:37,505
I'll jack another one.

736
01:02:39,225 --> 01:02:41,008
I'll be right on your heels.

737
01:02:41,010 --> 01:02:43,344
Then I'll wait.

738
01:02:43,346 --> 01:02:45,313
You stick to the plan.

739
01:02:45,315 --> 01:02:47,064
Please.

740
01:02:48,268 --> 01:02:49,934
Please get onto the boat.

741
01:02:51,855 --> 01:02:53,404
Trust me.

742
01:02:53,406 --> 01:02:56,190
I can lose these assholes with a tricycle.

743
01:02:57,110 --> 01:02:59,277
Okay.

744
01:02:59,279 --> 01:03:01,612
Yeah.

745
01:03:01,614 --> 01:03:04,081
Listen, let me talk to Felicia.

746
01:03:04,083 --> 01:03:07,168
Please. All right? Just for a second.

747
01:03:07,170 --> 01:03:09,337
I'm gonna talk to you again, right?

748
01:03:09,339 --> 01:03:11,456
We're gonna see each other again?

749
01:03:13,343 --> 01:03:15,293
Are you kidding?

750
01:03:15,295 --> 01:03:17,595
You're gonna need a restraining order.

751
01:03:20,767 --> 01:03:23,351
No. No, I won't.

752
01:03:28,308 --> 01:03:29,807
Okay.

753
01:03:32,645 --> 01:03:34,946
- Hello.  - I'm not gonna make it.

754
01:03:36,366 --> 01:03:38,282
Don't ask, just listen to me.

755
01:03:38,284 --> 01:03:41,486
You owe me, right? You owe me.

756
01:03:41,488 --> 01:03:43,404
I don't care if you have to tie her up,

757
01:03:43,406 --> 01:03:46,374
you make sure she gets out.

758
01:03:46,376 --> 01:03:48,209
You get her out.

759
01:03:49,496 --> 01:03:52,046
Okay.

760
01:03:52,048 --> 01:03:54,131
I promise.

761
01:03:56,219 --> 01:03:57,835
What did he say?

762
01:03:59,472 --> 01:04:01,639
To make sure you get on that boat.

763
01:04:59,232 --> 01:05:01,983
You? What the fuck is this?

764
01:05:13,746 --> 01:05:18,082
A turn here, a turn there, and it goes on for years.

765
01:05:18,084 --> 01:05:20,384
Becomes something else.

766
01:05:23,423 --> 01:05:27,008
I'm sorry, you know,

767
01:05:27,010 --> 01:05:29,560
for the man I became...

768
01:05:31,097 --> 01:05:33,147
the father I was.

769
01:05:35,435 --> 01:05:38,069
I hope you got the strength to learn from that.

770
01:05:40,857 --> 01:05:44,325
And I hope you got no doubts how much I loved you, son.

771
01:05:51,084 --> 01:05:52,917
And you're better than me.

772
01:05:54,871 --> 01:05:56,621
If I had been stronger...

773
01:05:58,791 --> 01:06:01,125
I would have been more like you.

774
01:06:04,297 --> 01:06:05,880
Hell, son...

775
01:06:08,518 --> 01:06:11,302
if everyone was stronger, they'd be more like you.

776
01:06:34,210 --> 01:06:36,043
You taking me out?

777
01:06:36,045 --> 01:06:38,412
I was already gone.

778
01:06:41,551 --> 01:06:43,501
What the fuck did you come out to say?

779
01:06:43,503 --> 01:06:45,469
You made a deal.

780
01:06:45,471 --> 01:06:47,755
No clubs, no locations for us.

781
01:06:47,757 --> 01:06:51,475
The clubs burned down. What was I supposed to do?

782
01:06:51,477 --> 01:06:53,644
Armenians, Russians, this is their thing.

783
01:06:53,646 --> 01:06:55,763
Where do the Armenians get their supply,

784
01:06:55,765 --> 01:06:57,682
what they gave to you?

785
01:07:00,019 --> 01:07:01,686
You want to get square?

786
01:07:01,688 --> 01:07:03,821
There's a flat million in the suitcase.

787
01:07:03,823 --> 01:07:05,906
That's my trade.

788
01:07:34,020 --> 01:07:35,269
God damn it.

789
01:08:29,192 --> 01:08:31,192
We're square, then, our business?

790
01:08:33,830 --> 01:08:36,113
That'll buy you something.

791
01:08:41,621 --> 01:08:44,205
A million dollars doesn't buy me a ride back to town?

792
01:08:46,209 --> 01:08:48,509
Take his suit.

793
01:08:49,512 --> 01:08:51,545
He wants your suit.

794
01:08:51,547 --> 01:08:53,047
Give it to him.

795
01:09:07,563 --> 01:09:10,114
You want my suit?

796
01:09:10,116 --> 01:09:14,318
Hurry. Come on.

797
01:09:14,320 --> 01:09:15,903
All right.

798
01:09:17,623 --> 01:09:19,957
I didn't even wear a suit till I was 38.

799
01:09:28,000 --> 01:09:30,050
Stop, stop, stop!

800
01:09:32,004 --> 01:09:34,171
- We kill him?  - What for?

801
01:09:34,173 --> 01:09:36,757
Fuck!

802
01:09:38,177 --> 01:09:39,927
We made a nice bed for you.

803
01:09:39,929 --> 01:09:42,429
Lie down, Frank.

804
01:09:44,684 --> 01:09:46,684
Oh, fuck.

805
01:10:02,034 --> 01:10:03,584
Fuck.

806
01:10:06,706 --> 01:10:09,623
It's okay. It's okay.

807
01:11:35,261 --> 01:11:37,795
I don't know, boy.

808
01:11:37,797 --> 01:11:40,798
I don't think them other kids like you.

809
01:11:40,800 --> 01:11:43,801
I don't think anybody does.

810
01:11:43,803 --> 01:11:47,805
Who the fuck wants some lanky loudmouth

811
01:11:47,807 --> 01:11:49,974
pissing in their ear, huh?

812
01:11:49,976 --> 01:11:52,309
Your mother sure didn't.

813
01:11:52,311 --> 01:11:53,644
It's what made her sick.

814
01:11:53,646 --> 01:11:57,448
Your fucking whining, that's why she's gone.

815
01:11:57,450 --> 01:12:00,317
Shut up. Shut the fuck up.

816
01:12:01,320 --> 01:12:02,653
Faggot.

817
01:12:02,655 --> 01:12:04,738
Scared of the dark.

818
01:12:06,075 --> 01:12:08,242
Yeah, I never loved you.

819
01:12:08,244 --> 01:12:10,461
I never asked you to.

820
01:12:10,463 --> 01:12:12,463
Shut up.

821
01:12:12,465 --> 01:12:14,048
Shut the fuck up.

822
01:12:43,362 --> 01:12:45,029
Still got time, Ray.

823
01:12:45,031 --> 01:12:47,281
Where's the papers?

824
01:12:47,283 --> 01:12:49,283
Where's the woman?

825
01:13:58,320 --> 01:14:01,655
Yes, yes, gawky motherfucker.

826
01:14:03,109 --> 01:14:05,659
I told you not to come around here.

827
01:14:06,946 --> 01:14:08,862
You fucking retarded or something?

828
01:14:08,864 --> 01:14:10,280
Told you what would happen to you.

829
01:14:10,282 --> 01:14:11,999
Fuck your shit up, Larry Bird.

830
01:14:12,001 --> 01:14:14,168
Stop and lie down, you dumb motherfucker.

831
01:14:14,170 --> 01:14:16,503
Fuck you.

832
01:14:16,505 --> 01:14:18,122
Never lie down.

833
01:14:38,811 --> 01:14:40,477
Last time, Ray.

834
01:14:42,064 --> 01:14:43,730
Let me help you.

835
01:15:05,721 --> 01:15:07,421
Bezzerides.

836
01:15:10,342 --> 01:15:12,142
Where is she?

837
01:15:14,680 --> 01:15:16,680
In a better place.

838
01:16:57,616 --> 01:17:00,000
Please, Frank. They don't have to do this.

839
01:17:00,002 --> 01:17:02,953
Tell them. Tell them I'll make it up.

840
01:17:02,955 --> 01:17:05,756
I got stupid.

841
01:17:05,758 --> 01:17:07,291
Please.

842
01:17:07,293 --> 01:17:09,459
Frank, you could let me go.

843
01:17:09,461 --> 01:17:11,295
They'll never know.

844
01:17:11,297 --> 01:17:14,798
It's not me. I didn't put you here.

845
01:17:14,800 --> 01:17:16,850
But you could get me out.

846
01:17:16,852 --> 01:17:19,469
Please, Frank. I got a family.

847
01:17:19,471 --> 01:17:21,938
It isn't me.

848
01:17:35,070 --> 01:17:37,120
Hi there, handsome.

849
01:17:45,664 --> 01:17:46,830
You made it.

850
01:17:50,169 --> 01:17:51,335
You okay?

851
01:17:51,337 --> 01:17:54,171
I did.

852
01:17:54,173 --> 01:17:55,889
I'm fine.

853
01:17:55,891 --> 01:17:57,674
I'm safe.

854
01:17:57,676 --> 01:17:59,343
I'm coming.

855
01:18:00,763 --> 01:18:03,597
Hold on.

856
01:18:15,327 --> 01:18:18,912
What's a guy like you doing in a place like this?

857
01:18:27,256 --> 01:18:29,089
Just making my way, baby.

858
01:18:33,212 --> 01:18:36,213
I told you I'd make it.

859
01:18:36,215 --> 01:18:39,099
You did.

860
01:18:39,101 --> 01:18:41,051
You made it.

861
01:18:42,221 --> 01:18:44,054
You can rest now.

862
01:18:44,056 --> 01:18:46,473
No rest.

863
01:18:46,475 --> 01:18:48,275
Never stop moving.

864
01:18:48,277 --> 01:18:49,810
Babe...

865
01:18:50,863 --> 01:18:53,563
Oh, babe.

866
01:18:53,565 --> 01:18:56,950
You stopped moving way back there.

867
01:19:44,216 --> 01:19:47,701
The former sheriff's deputy and City of Vinci detective

868
01:19:47,703 --> 01:19:49,453
was the chief suspect in the murder

869
01:19:49,455 --> 01:19:52,339
of a state attorney and a state police investigator.

870
01:19:52,341 --> 01:19:54,458
He was employed as a security consultant

871
01:19:54,460 --> 01:19:57,511
at a Vinci casino, which recently burned down.

872
01:19:57,513 --> 01:20:00,263
After a lengthy pursuit, the fugitive engaged

873
01:20:00,265 --> 01:20:03,099
a tactical squad of state and city police

874
01:20:03,101 --> 01:20:06,052
in a firefight which resulted in his death.

875
01:20:14,858 --> 01:20:16,159


876
01:20:50,858 --> 01:20:54,159


877
01:20:59,858 --> 01:21:03,159
A lot of the rest was in the papers over the next year...

878
01:21:05,664 --> 01:21:07,581
if you know where to look.

879
01:21:12,537 --> 01:21:14,204


880
01:21:11,537 --> 01:21:14,204
These facts were paid for in blood...

881
01:21:16,208 --> 01:21:18,708
so honor that.

882
01:21:21,513 --> 01:21:24,514
I don't know if it'll make any difference,

883
01:21:24,516 --> 01:21:27,217
but it should

884
01:21:27,219 --> 01:21:29,853
because we deserve a better world.

885
01:21:52,327 --> 01:21:54,794
And I owe him that.

886
01:21:55,747 --> 01:21:57,797
I owe his sons that.

887
01:22:00,335 --> 01:22:02,419
Anyways...

888
01:22:04,756 --> 01:22:06,423
this is evidence.

889
01:22:06,425 --> 01:22:09,593
Most of it's here, some of it's not.

890
01:22:09,595 --> 01:22:11,561
The truth...

891
01:22:11,563 --> 01:22:13,897
is naked larceny,

892
01:22:13,899 --> 01:22:16,349
open murder,

893
01:22:16,351 --> 01:22:19,069
and cascading betrayals.

894
01:22:26,828 --> 01:22:28,328
Come with me.

895
01:22:28,330 --> 01:22:30,113
Testify.

896
01:22:30,115 --> 01:22:32,032
I can bring this to the "Times."

897
01:22:32,951 --> 01:22:35,619
It's your story now.

898
01:22:35,621 --> 01:22:37,203
I told it.

899
01:22:38,840 --> 01:22:41,174
- But wait, there's...  - Stay here.

900
01:22:41,176 --> 01:22:44,628
Don't leave this room until I've been gone for an hour.

901
01:22:44,630 --> 01:22:46,796
Understand?

902
01:23:02,898 --> 01:23:04,481
Oh!

903
01:23:04,483 --> 01:23:05,899
Yeah.

904
01:23:05,901 --> 01:23:08,652
Oh.

905
01:23:08,654 --> 01:23:10,320
I know.

906
01:23:10,322 --> 01:23:12,405
It's okay.

907
01:23:29,174 --> 01:23:30,557
Hi.

908
01:23:37,349 --> 01:23:39,149
He's restless.

909
01:23:40,819 --> 01:23:42,652
Long trip ahead.

910
01:23:43,689 --> 01:23:46,272
Ready? Okay.

911
01:23:48,827 --> 01:23:51,027
Mm-hmm, here we go.

912
01:23:57,369 --> 01:24:00,003
You okay?

913
01:24:27,315 --> 01:24:33,203
# lately words are missing from now on #

914
01:24:36,825 --> 01:24:42,128
# vanished in the haze of love gone wrong #

915
01:24:45,751 --> 01:24:50,470
# there's no future, there's no past #

916
01:24:50,472 --> 01:24:54,507
# in the present nothing lasts #

917
01:24:54,509 --> 01:25:00,263
# lately someone's missing from now on #

918
01:25:08,073 --> 01:25:13,660
# lately I'm not feeling like myself #

919
01:25:16,615 --> 01:25:19,749
# when I look into the glass #

920
01:25:19,751 --> 01:25:23,503
# I see someone else #

921
01:25:25,957 --> 01:25:30,260
# I hardly recognize this face I wear #

922
01:25:30,262 --> 01:25:35,265
# when I stare into her eyes, I see no one there #

923
01:25:35,267 --> 01:25:40,970
# lately I'm not feeling like myself #

924
01:25:54,252 --> 01:25:59,689
# the mystery that no one knows #

925
01:26:03,628 --> 01:26:08,765
# where does love go when it goes? #

926
01:26:12,137 --> 01:26:18,141
# the mystery that no one knows #

927
01:26:21,513 --> 01:26:27,000
# where does love go when it goes? #

