previously...
If you work, you see
society is unjust.
This time it's immigrants.
Here?
-He slept over.
Saga is my colleague and you're my son.
-I do what I want.
He has posted something new.
-Why only Henning?
Does he have Henning?
-I think so. He disappeared last night.
You have a letter.
I want my brother back.
What did you actually do at Charlotte's?
-I had to interrogate her.
Did you fuck her?
You get up, put on your stuff and then
clam up. I don't want it anymore.
I died last night.
I saw no tunnel. No light.
You can't just go inside.
Why is there blood in your bedroom?
-It's not me.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
-Still working, so late?
I'll find you.
I'm Stefan.
-Charlie walked down the street ...
Sonja, you know who poisoned you?
Did you see anyone?
I saw him.
How can a police car
be stolen for half a day?
It may not be stolen.
Maybe he's one of us.
Maybe he's in the police.
What next?
Mette. Now I can't talk now,
leave a message after the beep.
It's me.
I know you're angry and hurt.
But we must talk.
So will you call me back?
I'll try to get home tonight.
Good day.
Today.
It explains a lot
if he's in the police.
Such as?
-he never leaves traces.
Experienced criminals don't.
-They want to make money. He doesn't.
What's his motive?
-It's something personal.
He always chooses someone
he wants dead. In this case Henning.
Why a cop?
-Anja. He knew we were looking for her.
Only the police knew she
was in the garage.
He managed to get a police car
with no one raising an alarm.
He has access to riot gear.
The taser was in police possession.
The shots were
fired by a professional.
He is well organized, and
plans everything well.
He understands weapons and explosives.
He is military.
-A special police unit.
If we continue on this track,
we must be very careful.
Since he's a Dane, we want all the
material and to take the lead on it.
Why a Dane?
-Danish police car and equipment.
He spoke fluent Danish with Daniel.
I'll see who fits that profile.
Nobody would shoot his own colleagues.
Do you have a different theory, Martin?
Well?
I'll send what we have.
We still have to talk.
Shall we have breakfast?
-No, thank you.
Why not?
-Because I don't have time.
Martin has difficulty with the idea
it could be a colleague.
Or is there something else
I should know about?
He's a bit mad at me.
-Why?
Because his son slept with me.
Had he missed the train home?
-No, he likes me.
How old is Martin's son?
-18, So I don't understand his anger.
It's his son.
-August is mature.
That's not the point.
You can't have sex with your
colleagues' children.
We didn't have sex.
-You said ...
I just said he had slept with me.
-You must also say that to Martin.
Why?
-He probably thought the same as I.
That's not my problem.
-Can you do it for me.
A school bus just vanished.
Five children are missing.
BODY FOUND IN CONTAINER
I'm Stefan. Do you recognize me?
Charlie walked down the street
and found a bag.
He thought full of tobacco,
but it was gunpowder.
Are we in the past or the present?
-We're in the present now, sister.
Has she woken up.
-Yes, she's awake.
Don't go away.
-Listen to me.
I'll never leave you alone.
DOES A KILLER LIVE ON YOUR STREET?
I didn't think you'd come in  today.
-You were right.
It was a mistake to publish the
addresses of psychiatric patients.
I'm here to offer my apology.
You're a good man, Åke.
I didn't appreciate you.
I gotta go. A school bus has
disappeared with five children.
It's great.
-Congratulations.
Hey. Åke said you were sick.
-I'm better now.
He killed Henning.
-I heard.
Do you know anything about the fifth
problem? Have you checked your email?
Aren't you going to do it?
I don't think so.
It doesn't matter.
-What doesn't matter?
This. Everything I write.
Everything he sends me.
Ultimately, everything is meaningless.
There's actually nothing means anything.
-Daniel, what's wrong with you?
What does he say?
I have no idea.
Lillian sent these.
They match the criteria.
He died this winter.
He died years ago.
I don't know why
they hadn't checked.
I received new material from Copenhagen.
Martin, I didn't have sex with your son.
August and I didn't have sex.
You probably wanted to know.
Listen.
-What is that?
A conversation between a police
helicopter and the stolen car.
HK4 to vehicle 319. What's your status?
HK4, vehicle 319 here. Zebra Zulu. Zebra Zulu.
vehicle 319, repeat.
-Everything's under control. Nothing to report.
vehicle 319, understood.
Over and out.
Zebra Zulu means everything's quiet.
ZZ is a snore.
It's special forces police jargon
in America.
Does one of those persons fit the profile?
-They all received FBI training.
Can't he have learned 'Zebra Zulu'
from the internet?
I get no hits
on the major engines.
Is there anyone in Sweden
who meets the profile?
Johan? Swedish police officers?
-With the search criteria, I have seven.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Yes. Thank you.
Sonja's come out of the coma. Martin.
Wait. There are five children missing
and we have 15 people for investigation.
Sonja said she saw him.
We don't know what he intends.
-Can I get the photos of those seven Swedes?
She doesn't answer.
Who?
-Mette. I've called her all day.
Why do you call her?
She threw me out.
-Why?
She knows I've gone weird.
Didn't she know you don't
believe in monogamy?
What?
How do you figure? I don't believe.
-Why did you have sex with others?
Have you ever had a relationship?
-It depends how you define it.
I'm not talking about sex
with boys 20 years younger.
I'm 19 years older
and we didn't have sex.
What did you do all night with him?
Talked. Watched a movie. Slept.
-In the same bed?
Is it weird to spend the night
together without having sex?
In that case I understand your infidelity.
-Will you stop now?
Thank you.
Moreover, it is your fault. You stood
there waving my wallet.
Did you do it with
Charlotte Söringer?
Why was that?
Mette Rohde, here. I'll be right
down. Thank you.
Is Sebastian Sandstrod here?
-Yes, he's there.
Hello. Mette Rohde.
-Sebastian Sandstrod. Pleased to meet you.
You were in my calendar. Go ahead.
-I want to show our software.
That does make sense.
I don't buy IT systems.
But you use them right?
-I use what the company buys.
They think only in the interest
of the firm. I think of your interests.
Sellers always want
to improve my life.
But I really can do that.
-How?
Do you want the long or short version?
-The very short one.
Gain a clear overview, less
coordination, less overtime.
and more family time
for other things.
Too long?
-No, but is it true?
ln the short version is all true.
Sebastian Sandstrod,
I'll give you five minutes.
It's not long.
-You must earn more time.
We go up here.
Do you think it's my fault
Mette's mad at you?
You could've given
me my wallet at work.
So the problem isn't that you
comit adultery, but that Mette knows.
You said so.
-The problem is I want her back.
I love her and don't want to lose her.
-That has ...
Before? Thank you, Saga. I know.
What are you doing here?
I want to ask a few questions.
-She just woke up. Can't it wait?
I'm Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Look at these pictures.
Did you see who left
the wine bottles?
You said you recognized him.
Do you remember?
How are you?
-Good.
Fine.
Look at the pictures.
Sonja concentrate.
Look at each picture.
Can you concentrate?
-She's just woken up.
Do you have something to tell me?
-No.
Are you all right?
Sonja, it's okay.
It shows again we aren't equal
before the law. That's a problem.
Both the police and for society.
That deserves attention.
"As for the law."
-A serious problem.
Jesper Andersson, born in 1969,
bilingual, Danish mother.
Lived up to 12 in Denmark.
Gratuated from the police academy in 1995.
Between 1998 and 2000 trained
by the FBI at Quantico.
Assigned to the swat team until 2003,
two colleagues killed in an operation.
Sick-leave, divorced in 2005,
back to work in 2006.
Head of the team that monitored
recruitment for organized crime.
Doing good work among the youth.
Was well liked.
It can be him. Now find
the link to the dead persons.
One more thing. If we monitor him
nobody else must know.
Can't we talk to him?
-Do it.
Is Jesper Andersson here?
-No.
Do you know where he is?
-No. No idea.
What do you want?
-To talk to him.
I can say who was there?
He is a Swede.
-Who?
You said he was Danish.
-I said many things that could be.
But Jesper Andersson is a Swede.
What do you mean?
-Nothing.
He isn't there.
-He isn't at home.
Gry will search his house
with a team.
I'll go there.
-Wait.
If it's Andersson, he's now
working on something. Go to Johan.
Millions of children in the world
are abused and exploited every day.
If an item is very cheap,
there's another price to pay.
The problem is nothing we can
cure. It's not our children.
But these ones.
Where does this come from?
-Sanningnu.se, and on the Danish site.
Each child represents a type of business.
There are companies in our region
indirectly using child labor.
I want the companies set
afire before time runs out.
Each fire rescues a child. All of them can
stay alive, the choice is yours.
A list of the companies
will soon be made public.
Jesus Christ.
The list of companies.
That's not bad.
We assume this list is correct?
Can they be involved in child labor?
Up until now he was always right.
-Publishing it will have consequences.
Probably five fires.
What, insurance companies
make less profits ...
and five children's lives, or what?
So isn't that simple.
-It is that simple.
Or does it involve our advertisers?
You can't incite arson.
-We don't.
We just provide information.
As we've done all week.
We don't publish
this is to encourage crime.
You've already talked to the lawyers.
The list goes to the police.
This is a police matter.
Oh yes, now it concerns those
who pay our wages?
I've taken a lot of shit from you,
but be careful you don't go too far.
I didn't sign the death sentence
of the five children.
Now you've gone too far.
Thank you. These were five well-spent
minutes, or how long was it?
A half hour.
-But we also had coffee.
It sounds very interesting, the software.
I'll discuss it with my colleagues.
It's simple. Data systems are
metaphors for life.
Find out how everything is connected
and then create order.
And how do you do that,
bring order to your life?
If I knew, I'd now be an
extremely well-paid lecturer.
Do you need it? Order in your life?
Who doesn't?
Sorry. it's too private, too fast.
Pardon me.
Doesn't matter. Your five minutes
are definitely over.
I'll send the information,
you can give to your colleagues.
Thank you.
-I must thank you.
Navid?
What about Andersson
and the victims?
Kerstin Ekwall used to prosecute.
So they may have met.
Here is the list of companies.
We can't monitor all
their warehouses and shops.
We must try.
Pardon me.
Anne?
-Yes.
See if you can find a link
between the companies and the kids.
Please.
-Thank you.
Any chatter on the net?
-No noise.
What the hell did you do?
I suppose that's
a rhetorical question?
I said no.
-I have to press on.
Now, the list is all over the Internet,
if you want to get it off the site.
You're all done.
Get out within a minute.
You know the Labour code
doesn't quite work like that.
I want you to leave.
An update on Andersson.
His ex and he have no contact,
but she calls him a loner.
His mother doesn't want to see him
again. He has a house in Småland.
We'll talk to his colleagues,
but be careful.
Has Gry called?
-She didn't found anything at his house.
We haven't made any progress
since this morning.
Excuse me. We found
a body. Sören Holmgren.
His wife, Veronika Holmgren,
has disappeared.
Their social worker is Stefan Lindberg.
Have you've heard of him before?
He can't be found.
Do you know where he is?
He's in hospital. That's his sister.
-Nice. Thank you.
He did it.
-Excuse me?
Stefan Lindberg did it.
There is blood between the floor boards
in his bedroom. Check it out.
Saga, the school bus has been found
after an anonymous tip.
Five fires in two hours.
Otherwise he'll let the children die.
He wants people
to act instinctively.
Is it our instinct to start fires?
Children work on the people's
feelings, just like kittens.
Don't you think this is
the worst thing he's done?
He'll murder five children.
Five little people.
He's killed more homeless.
Little people?
-They don't know they're in danger.
It was worse for Björn Rasmusen.
He knew he was dying.
You don't really have
a maternal instinct, huh?
But why do you ask?
The windows are covered up.
No movement inside.
We will send the bomb expert
in first. Are you ready?
I'm ready.
-Then go.
They aren't on the bus.
We don't know that.
-He wasn't filmed on the bus.
He may have moved them.
-No.
It could be a video.
We'll take no risks.
We'll assume the worst.
Can you hear me, Milos?
Okay.
Here you can see it.
This is Milos' camera.
Whose warehouse is that?
-Unknown.
It's important.
We need to know whose warehouse that is?
Find out fast.
And, Milos?
-The exterior of the bus is fine.
Nothing on the outside.
Take it back a little.
-Milos, can you go back?
What is this?
Can you get a better image?
-Wait.
"Thanks for the help."
Thanks for the help?
Go ahead.
Thank you. It's a furniture company.
What's it called?
-Hulbos Furniture.
He must get out of there.
I got the door open.
-He's going in.
It's a company on the list.
He must leave now.
Come directly out.
-I'm going in.
Cease your operation immediately.
A fire broke out in the warehouse
where the school bus was parked.
The bomb expert just managed to get out
before the whole place caught fire.
We don't know if the five
children were in the bus.
Police think that isn't the case
because the perpetrator ...
left a note "Thanks for the help."
And next on TV1.
Five companies have to burn.
We don't know whether this warehouse
belongs to one of those companies.
The warehouse is now ablaze
and it will take time to ...
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
-Johan, here.
"Furniture" was removed from the list,
So one child will be saved.
Have you spoken to the police?
-What?
Those officers in uniform.
They asked about you.
Yes. Yes, we talked. Thank you.
You were very long.
-I know. Sorry.
We gotta go.
Where?
-I don't know. Just go.
Together?
-Of course. We'll always stay together.
Now?
-Yes, now.
We'll start a new life, Sonja.
We'll start again. We'll leave
all the misery behind us. Come.
Let's go the other way.
Wait, I need to sit down.
Sonja, listen to me.
I did something stupid.
Can you hear me? I'll take care of you
and ensure you get sorted out.
I love you.
Sonja, listen to me.
Remember what I said to you
the summer they took you from me?
I'd wait for you?
Can you promise me the same?
You wait for me?
Come with me.
-We want to stay together.
We'll do that too.
You just have to wait.
"Clothing" has also been removed.
Young people have
set fire to a clothing store.
Were they caught?
-Yes. The bystanders were heroes.
Indeed they are.
-Three to go.
Excuse me.
Is he a father?
-No idea.
He has a son
who's just turned two.
I'm sitting here with Erik and Anna,
the parents one of the kidnapped boys.
Some businesses were set on fire.
What do you think of that?
It's awful ...
but these are just things,
material things.
It's important
I get my son back.
They're insured, right?
I'll never get my son back.
I'd like the number of
Gladans Chocolate in Malmö.
Can you transfer me?
Hello, you're speaking with Daniel Ferbé.
Yes indeed, that Daniel Ferbé.
Your company is allegedly
associated with child labor.
I'd like to interview
for a nuanced story.
Who do I have to have to talk to?
Can you transfer me?
How's Andersson?
-I had him monitored.
Then he disappeared.
-He has already disappeared.
Do we know anything about him?
Found out anything about Andersson?
-I've seen his roster.
He often works nights. Travels
between Sweden and Denmark.
Nobody knows where he hangs out.
Gry, have you found a link
to the kids?
No, they seem to
be chosen at random.
In Copenhagen
a toy warehouse is on fire.
And another clothing store in Malmö.
Another three minutes and we have
two fires to go.
You want him to succeed?
-Yes. And you want that too.
"Sport" is gone.
How can this be personal? There should
be a connection to Andersson.
Maybe he knows one of the parents.
-Five companies have to burn.
The link between the companies.
Find the link between the companies.
Gladans headquarters
is on fire.
One minute and thirty seconds.
They were saved.
Everyone finds this a good thing?
-Because no children die, yes.
It's a good thing. But when
he pits people against each other?
Five disabled die for five children.
Or five immigrants.
-But he hasn't done that.
Everyone does what he says.
Isn't that scary?
Something new has appeared.
GPS coordinates.
Look where that is.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Is this man who you locked up?
-I don't know.
Did you see him?
-Yes.
Look at the picture. Concentrate.
Was it him?
Maybe. He had a beard and an
eye patch. He looked like a pirate.
I have found these. Are these them?
They all say the same thing.
Last problem. He has named
all five, so he's ready.
Maybe.
Get a search warrant.
He doesn't want us to look for him.
-It doesn't matter what he wants or not.
We won't issue a search warrant.
What are you doing here?
Change of clothes and look in on the kids.
-They're asleep.
And August?
-This isn't home.
Were the children saved?
-Yes.
So it's over?
-No, he's not caught. I want to...
Go get your clothes and then go away.
I love you, Mette.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
What? Now?
I just happened by.
Where were you going?
-Nowhere. I wanted to see you again.
You want to sleep with me.
If I may.
-No.
Your father doesn't approve.
Who cares what he thinks?
-Me.
Really?
I gotta get back to work.
Good night.
Thank you for a wonderful day
sleep well
I'll go back.
How long will it be like this?
I don't know.
-We need to talk.
I've just don't want to see you.
Lithium aluminum hydride.
-Excuse me?
That was on the floor around the bus.
It ignites in contact with water.
August slept over at your place.
Do you know if Andersson
knows anything about chemistry?
So you have a spare bed?
Don't you know or he doesn't
know anything about chemistry?
I don't know.
But do you have a spare bed?
Do you want to sleep with me?
-I don't. I was thinking of someone else.
Who then?
You can't touch that.
It is brand new, huh?
-Yes, it hasn't been used.
So August slept in your bed?
He came along at the office today.
-Who?   -August.
What did he want?
-He wanted to sleep with me.
Thank you.
-Please.
I'm going to eat. Do you want to?
Then I'll make something.
You call this 'what will do'?
-Isn't it hot?
Yes, it's hot. It's perfect.
Have you always lived alone?
-Except one time with my sister.
I referred to a friend.
A partner.
Why not?
-I'm no good as a friend.
You can't know
If you've never had a boy friend.
Do you live alone
because of your sister?
What do you mean?
-Are you afraid something will happen?
that you ought to have foreseen?
Many people commit suicide without
showing signs beforehand.
That's true.
Are you expecting a visitor?
Come in.
This is Martin Rohde,
of the Copenhagen police.
His wife has thrown him out.
This is Anton, I sometimes have sex with him.
Do you want to go to bed right now?
I won't stay.
Martin's sleeping on the guest bed.
But I thought ...
I'll come back another time, okay?
-Sure.
Good day.
-Good day. It was ... cozy.
Nice guy.
I had better leave you alone.
-No, we have work to do.
What then?
-Jesper Andersson.
Was it just you?
-Only me. What are you doing?
I'm copying things.
I've spent too much time here
for Carina to let me go now.
What are you writing?
-About the rescued children.
It has to be ready for tomorrow.
I know who set the fire
at Gladans Chocolate.
Do you? Who then?
Not all of it.
Just a small area in the office.
Have you lost your senses?
I have saved a child. And you can't
name me. Source protection.
I don't want to "out" you.
What'll you do now?
-I don't know.
It was so amazing
to save a child.
Or did I just find it normal
to set a building on fire?
I thought you'd changed.
-I have.
There seems no difference.
"So sue me."
I thought you were ready.
-I want to thank you for your cooperation.
I've got the sack because of you.
-Pity.
But you have helped me,
So I will help you.
Your newspaper will take you back, if you
get an exclusive interview with me.
Will we meet?
We'll meet, talk and then
can you turn me in to the police.
Is this a joke?
-Not at all.
I never wanted to escape punishment.
I want people to wake up.
Now I'm done. I'm
ready for my sentence.
How do we do that?
-I'll tell you when you're in your car.
I'm sitting in my car.
You are suddenly struck
by déjà vu?
It wasn't at all funny.
-You know what isn't funny?
People who hold their own interests
above everything else.
Journalists let themselves get bribed.
Cowardly people.
People like you, Daniel.
Okay, very good. You know what?
We're done with each other.
I agree.