The power is out.
The power is out on the bridge.
I'm going there now. The lights
were out for 45 seconds.
I'll go take a look.
- Okay. Over and out.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
- Copenhagen Police.
Do you know who she is?
- Yes.
Excuse me, Saga.
A woman is there to talk
with the person in charge.
Is she in Sweden or Denmark?
I don't know.
She is from Sweden and a Swede
brought her here. I have the lead.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID. Go ahead.
When can we go?
-Maybe in two hours.
Two hours? I don't have two hours.
-Is there someone in danger?
My husband is in the ambulance. He's getting
a heart transplant in Copenhagen.
He must wait a little longer.
I can't let anyone through.
Can I go through?
Traffic heading to Denmark on the
Øresund bridge is obstructed.
Police said it will continue ...
Stefan Lindberg.
-Hi, Veronika.
Sorry to call so late. Were you sleeping?
-No, you know. How are you?
I can't sleep. Pain in my belly.
-Understandable. How are the boys?
They're asleep. I don't think
they know what's happening.
What can I do for you?
Can we meet?
-Now?
Yes. If you can.
Of course I can.
Shall I come to you?
No.
It's better if I come to you.
-I can be in the office in one hour.
See you there.
I want everything on the car
that transported the body.
The recording was started manually.
Non-automaticly?
No, but maybe
my colleague recorded something.
Hey, there. Hold it. Hold it.
I've given permission.
But this is a crime scene.
-I know.
Why did you do that?
-One corpse is enough.
He wasn't dying.
-Are you also a doctor?
No. I'm a detective.
What's your name?
-Martin.
And beyond?
-Rohde. R-O-H-D-E.
Can you show
me some identification?
It was an ambulance.
We have the chair of Malmö city council.
She was probably murdered.
What evidence did I destroy
by letting him go?
Probably not. Thank you.
Finally.
Charlotte, I'm not going to operate on Göran.
I drank some wine at dinner.
When did you eat? Probably hours ago
already. Are you drunk?
We'd take this path together,
you said. So that wasn't true?
Morten Krag is a good surgeon.
-Better than you?
It's my husband, so I decide. I'll never
forgive you if someone else messes it up.
And if I were to blow it?
Then I'll never forgive myself,
as I gave you no choice.
We're ready. Can she go now?
-You can take her.
Holy shit.
The faction is committed to Kerstin
Ekwall. What about the videos?
They'll arrive in the morning.
How's the press?
They know we found the body of
a woman, but not who she is.
And her family?
-That's something I'll do.
Send Gry and Navid.
The family is still sleeping. She has children.
Go a bit cautiously.
What? I can really say. There
aren't many ways to say it.
Just do it gently.
Hans, wait a bit. She was sliced
in two. Above the hips.
What are you saying?
She had a conference in
Copenhagen tomorrow morning.
Do you have more computers in the house?
-No.
Please note that?
Those are the children's?
When did you speak to her last?
She called yesterday, when I was cooking.
Can you give an exact time of the call?
-I don't know.
Six thirty? We usually called
after breakfast.
Had she been threatened?
By whom?
I didn't say she was threatened,
I asked if she was threatened.
She was a politician. That includes
some phone calls and e-mails.
She kept herself in politics doing things
that didn't sit well with some people?
She wanted to introduce user fees
in libraries. Not everyone liked that.
No, that's stupid.
-Excuse me?
Then read a little elitist.
It increases the gap in society.
Do you think that has to do
with what happened?
We don't know why she was murdered,
but I don't think it was because of user fees.
Why would anyone do that?
Could the reason be personal?
Debts? Did she use drugs?
Was she unbalanced?
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Can't you call?
I'll be there in twenty
minutes. Thank you.
August.
Were you at the bridge?
-Yes.
What was it?
-A murder. The Swedes took control.
Have you looked in on August?
-Yes.
Is he asleep?
Really?
-Yes.
You promised to talk
to him about gambling.
You want me to wake him
so I can talk to him?
Today he was on for only three hours.
I'm going to talk to him tomorrow.
Does it hurt?
Do you know the cause of death?
-I have a suspicion.
But give me some time. I can already
say she's been dead for 6 to 8 hours.
That is true.
She called home at half past six and
was found after midnight on the bridge.
But there is something else.
That's why I asked you to come.
What then?
-But just look at her.
No body spots on the outer ear.
This is consistent with her bleeding.
Reddening in the white of the eyes.
Swelling of the face.
I'd say she was strangled
and split in half after her death.
And the other half?
The abdomen is much paler
then the upper body. Much paler.
This isn't explained by the
blood loss or the position of the corpse.
Brownish skin discoloration. Freezing?
It feels different.
Freezing?
-No freezing. She was frozen.
Approximately one year, I'd say.
I've never seen anything like it.
I don't know who's leg that is,
but it isn't Kerstin Ekwall.
All three of you have come then.
Hey, Sebastian.
I don't know what to do.
I just keep thinking about tomorrow.
I had to say.
You can't pay the rent?
Where are the children
to go, on the street?
They have their friends and everything.
I gave you money for the rent.
Where did you spent it?
Why did you bring the kids?
-Sören's not home.
I can't pay it.
Can't you make an exception?
Just once.
You know I can't.
-Please.
Rules are rules. I'm sorry.
Charlotte Söringer? Frederik Henriksen.
I'm in charge here.
Göran was given heart
defibrillation on arrival.
But that's been resolved.
-Göran is too weak for surgery.
Too weak? But there is
a new heart for him.
That's going to someone else.
I'm so sorry.
I know you are in need
of a new CT scanner.
My husband will donate a scanner to
the hospital that gives him a healthy heart.
We won't operate. He's too weak.
-Without a new heart, he'll die.
Everyone can be helped by my offer,
but if you refuse ...
can you ensure it helps
the right person?
Hello? Can I speak to Martin Rohde?
Saga Norén, here.
I met you on the bridge.
I remember, yes.
-Were you asleep?
It's half past three. Usually I lie down
dozing about that time.
There were two women on the bridge.
-Was there one?
The bottom half
wasn't the politician.
Did you find a half body
in Denmark?
I don't know.
The case is more than one year old.
The legs have been frozen.
Can you check it out?
Of course.
-Now?
I'll do it first thing tomorrow morning.
Give me a name of
someone who can do it now?
I'll call you back.
-When?
Are you going back out?
-Yes.
Missing woman, white, one year
or more ago. Do you know her age?
Adult.
In addition,  are you all right?
-Sure. And you?
Fine.
I hear you've had
a vasectomy.
Does the staff paper say that?
-Is everything as it should be?
It's probably succeed, yes.
But it's not cool, huh?
-What do you mean?
Think of a tom cat
who's lost his balls.
He changes from a wild predator
to a slow fat man. It happens very quickly.
Being castrated.
That's different.
Well, look what I can find.
Two women, murdered one year
apart. One has been frozen.
The parts were joined on the
Øresund bridge. Around midnight.
Someone wants to tell us something.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
-Martin, here.
The abdomen may be Monique
Brammer. She's been missing for 13 months.
Can you email me the info?
-I'm coming over to you now.
Over here? Why?
Because she is Danish
and I was first on the scene.
There's nothing to discuss.
Do you have something to give me?
Make sure I can get inside.
You have my data.
That was Martin Rohde.
He may know whose belly is.
Nice.
-He's coming here.
Have you got a problem with that?
If half of the body is Danish,
we must work together.
Logical.
I'll call his boss. We'll call a meeting
for half past five. Will that work?
Finally it's going to happen.
What was that paper
you signed?
A formality.
Whose is it?
What?
The heart. Whose is it?
-A man of 25 or 26. Motorcycle Accident.
What's his name?
-I don't know. Does it matter?
No, you know. It doesn't.
I'm scared.
It'll work out well.
Someone else will operate on you.
They're all so cleaver.
It will surely go well. I can't
imagine my life without you.
I'll take him.
Don't worry, honey. They know
what they do. You'll be saved.
Hello. An early breakfast.
-No, thank you.
It'd come quicker through e-mail.
-But this is more fun.
What are you going?
-Inside with you.
Why?
If the other half of
Monique Brammer appears to be ...
both you and me will take
the lead in this matter.
Then you have register first
at the reception.
Martin Rohde. I'm working with Saga on
the Øresund bridge case.
Then fill it in.
-I'd also like a pass.
My name is Felicia.
-Nice.
Good. Welcome.
-Thank you. Then you should like this.
Danish.
Goodbye.
-I hope so.
Where's Saga Norén?
-Right there.
Sit down.
-No, I don't want to.
You're making me nervous.
-Then I sit a moment.
Why can't you sit down?
-Because I have pain down here.
I was sterilized yesterday.
I have five children by three women,
So it is enough.
Do you have children?
-Why should I have?
What an original question.
I know a lot
who had to ask it.
Not you. You are undoubtedly
a great dad.
Why can't you sign off sick?
-I can't.
August is living with Mette and me again.
But it's not about the money.
It was a minor procedure
and it's better if I can work.
But you can't sit.
Well. I drove here
by car.
Pretend that's a car seat
and sit down.
Nobody wanted to resolve this matter, huh?
-What do you mean?
Monique was reported missing.
After interviewing two other
prostitutes, the investigation was closed.
The case ended up in a vacuum.
She was either killed or disappeared.
Because they never found a corpse ...
It was never seriously investigated.
I'd be surprised if it
lasted two weeks. Come.
Senior politician found dead
the Øresund bridge
The press now know who she is.
Hans, Saga will lead the investigation?
- Nice.
Together with the Danish police.
Does he know she is a bit unusual?
- Otherwise, he will find out.
Good morning.
This is Martin Rohde from Copenhagen.
It's Rohde.
As if you say 'road, toad, or flowed'.
Road. Flowed.
Have you read the material?
-Not the latest.
We have two half bodies.
One is Kerstin Ekwall.
The other, the one frozen
for a year ... Martin.
It's probably Monique
Brammer, 23 years old.
Prostitute and junkie. She disappeared
13 months ago without a trace.
Shall I repeat that?
- But just a bit slower?
Monique Brammer, 23 years.
Prostitute and junkie.
She disappeared 13 months
ago without a trace.
That came from the Danish
investigation, which was rather poor.
Don't you agree?
-Yes. It was pitiful.
But traces of blood were
found in her apartment.
Samples of those will be compared
with the lower body.
Someone remotely interrupted the power
to the bridge for 48 seconds.
The company wants to find the source
of the problem. Gry, can you help?
How was it done?
-Someone hacked into the computer.
Can you get pictures of it?
One, two, three and four.
Gry, here's Kerstin's mobile number.
Request a list of all calls.
And search the contents
from the work and home computers.
Anne, we have to find out
where she was kidnapped.
She left her work bu car
at half past six. Check it out.
Were the bodies transported in it?
-No, in a black Cadillac Escalade.
A picture from above.
The license plate is covered
with reflective tape ...
but John knows how we can
get the number. Can't we, John?
Sure.
-What are you doing?
I thought when I saw the picture. There was
an orange stripe where the corpse lay.
We know
exactly where they lay.
These are the coordinates
of the border.
One half is located in Sweden, the other in
Denmark. Almost down to the millimeter.
Gry, take a sample of the stripe.
Perhaps it'll give a lead on the paint.
Power failures, half bodies, a politician.
All eyes will be on us.
Good day, Sören.
ls Veronika home?
What is it?
-I just wanted to talk to her.
You can also talk to me.
-Not if you're under the influence.
I'm sober.
-Good day, Veronika.
What do you want?
To kick us out of our house?
I won't do it.
The homeowner will.
You're offering to help help?
-I've tried. Very often.
If you had taken a little
responsibility, this wouldn't happen.
That's pretty stupid of you, huh?
Let me go.
Hold it, asshole.
Come out, you.
Stop it.
-I hate that dirty bastard.
He's ruined everything
Since he came into our life.
Let me go.
You can go to hell,
bunch of idiots.
How's the surgery?
-It hasn't started yet.
He was preped hours ago.
I don't know what's happening.
Sorry, but I have to go.
Don't you know where he went?
-You know his actions better than me.
I'll let you know
when we find him.
Sorry for all this.
You must stop
making excuses for him.
He is grown up. He has to take
responsibility for his actions.
You have to too.
Sören's placed you in this situation.
I know you can manage,
but not if you have no money.
I know you take good
care of your children.
I know he hits you.
-Almost never the children.
Almost never. It is still too much.
He mustn't strike me at all,
and not even you.
You can put your life in order.
You and the children,
but only you and the kids.
You have to break with your husband,
otherwise nothing will ever change.
Think about it.
Anders, what's going on?
Why hasn't he had surgery?
We have a problem.
A nurse had a conversation
with the father of the donor.
He changed his mind. We
can't use the heart. That's Göran.
Shouldn't we turn off here?
Stefan, shouldn't we turn off here?
-No, not today.
Where are we going?
-You can still see it.
The old man named Johan
who used to lived there,
died one month ago.
No wife, no children,
no debts, no money.
The house was all he had.
It belongs to the community.
It's Sören.
Go inside.
And the children?
-They can stay out a bit.
Where are we? Tell me
in any case, why we are here.
I'll do so. Now go inside.
Crime scene and meeting place.
Have you worked here long?
-What's long?
More than ten years?
-Yes.
You come from here?
- From Malmö? No.
I'm from Copenhagen.
-I know.
No, I was born in Copenhagen.
- Yeah
It's not by accident
that Sweden ...
the land is lngmar Bergman
and Lars Norén.
Are you a member of the playwright
Lars Norén's family?   - No!
We have to find the place,
where the offender
met the victim.
I've talked to colleagues in Copenhagen.
You're heading this case together.
This is the protocol
of your rights in each country.
I know how it is in Denmark.
-Good.
Saga, can I talk to you?
That message you sent.
About Martin. On the bridge.
-I know what you're talking about.
What should I do about it?
-You must work together.
It may have an impact
on your collaboration?
Do you think so?
-It seems possible, yes.
So he will blame me.
-That's a risk.
That message shouldn't affect
the consideration of the case.
Not necessarily.
He had no urgent need
of an ambulance.
I had to mention it.
-I have to process your report.
Nice.
Saga, I have the license plate of the car.
He is Daniel Ferbé from Malmö.
-The journalist?
Yes, he is a journalist.
You know him?
-Yes.
I always read him.
He writes very entertaining.
I'm scared stiff.
I thought I was the first in.
I've worked through the night. I am
ready. Now Berlin and the blogging.
Work at night, partying in Berlin.
How do you keep up?
"Partying"? I have no ...
How many children do you have?
... two children who suck the life
out of me. I have no children.
And nowadays no one says
"partying" any more. No one.
Have fun.
-That'll be fine.
I downloaded
"Elephants in the Desert".
What do you want from me, Åke?
Do you want a hug? A prize?
Applause?
They are really good. I like them.
-Yes, they were good.
How is that possible? Two weeks ago
you thought they were super.
And now you like them.
My daughter ...
dancing all afternoon ...
-I really recording. Sorry.
I'll talk to you later.
You and your sons vanish.
Your papers have disappeared
and I resolved your debts.
You can start again.
Do you understand?
Here is start up money
and a new mobile.
But you have to break with your husband.
You can't ever see him again. Otherwise?
He's their father. What'll I say to them?
They need their father.
Why?
Why should they?
To continue to get beaten?
To always be afraid of a man
who spends all the money on drugs?
He'll ruin everything.
That's what he does. Ruin things.
You don't even know me.
Why are you doing this?
Because I can.
Here is my car.
-Could he be the man we're looking for?
A murderer who cuts power
on the bridge, doesn't use his own car.
Nice car.
-Yes.
Do you really deserve this?
-Just like you.
I don't have such a beautiful car.
You can't  draw conclusions
about my salary from my car.
I could've bought it, inherited it,
sure saved for it.
I hope you draw better
conclusions in the investigation.
Read this.
An article by Daniel Ferbé.
The man who writes well?
-I said he wrote entertainingly.
Are you coming?
What's up?
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
I have a guy in a Cadillac
and a bomb in the garage.
A black Escalade?
-Yes. Why?
It's involved in a double murder.
-And the man? Trying to commit suicide?
I think he's innocent,
but I'll ask.
You don't come inside.
You don't even come close.
Help.
Help. Help me anyway.
Get me out of here.
-Take it easy.
Help me.
Front and rear doors linked to
the bomb, the windows don't open.
Can we open them?
-We don't know what's in the doors.
There are wires everywhere.
We have his contact information.
What are you doing?
-My mobile.
Saga Norén , Malmö CID.
I'm standing outside the garage.
I want to know if you were driving
your car on the bridge at midnight.
What do you mean?
-Were you on the Øresund bridge.
No, I was up all night
Here at work.
How will you get me out of here?
No idea, I'm not involved in that.
Do you know Kerstin Ekwall?
Who?
-Kerstin Ekwall.
Did you do anything else
when you turned the key?
No. I turned it on and then
everything locked and the timer started.
I'm talking to the explosives man.
ls there's a connection between you and
Kerstin Ekwall? Have you written about her?
Talked to anyone about her? Has
anyone given you tips about her?
What is this? Get me out of here.
Please.
Do others have keys to your car?
Did someone just borrow it?
No, I don't know.
-Can you reach?
Can you think of anyone who's
used your car? It's important.
I don't want to die.
-Daniel, you have to talk to me.
It skipped.
What have you done?
It skipped. It stood at three
and then it skipped to two.
It was at three.
What are you doing?
Stay here. Please.
Please.
Come back. Where you going?
You should talk to me.
ls it a big bomb?
I think so.
I've read many of your pieces. You're
not religious. You're an atheist, right?
Then that's just.
Your body won't register the pain.
Are you sure?
-Don't look at the time, and listen to me.
Can you think why your car would
have been used to dump two bodies?
Think about it. Concentrate.
Who did this?
-I've written so much shit.
Daniel, are you still there?
No fingerprints.
Sorry for the drama. It is so difficult
to drown the noise of the media.
I suppose now I have
your full attention.
Our place on earth can be so beautiful,
but only if we solve our problems.
I point to five problems. The women
on the bridge are therefore only "the beginning".
This is an interesting time
for all of us.