previously...
That message about Martin
at the bridge ...
He had no good reason
to release the ambulance.
Can I take your gun?
-You can't carry arms.
What are all these for?
Back.
Knock, knock, knock.
What's the matter?
You must now go to the hospital.
The children are doing well
but you have kidney stones.
Children? As in twins?
Put your gun down.
They aren't our men.
We're back to square one.
The girl named Anja Björk, 14
years old. She ran away from home.
Saga Norén came along.
You always choose
the path of least resistance.
That's right.
That's how I hold it together.
A soldier.
-Special Unit.
This is Jens. His wife and child
died in a car accident.
They were killed on the bridge.
He committed suicide.
No fingerprints
or DNA samples were taken.
Saga thinks he's still alive.
-You can't believe it.
Do you want to sleep here again?
-Yes.
Fine. It would be bad if you don't
work it out. You're a good couple.
That we are, indeed!
Do you have to work?
-Yes, I'm off to Malmö.
I thought it was over.
We still need to try to catch him.
Saga also thinks he's alive.
What?
-I don't know.
When everything is quieter,
can we do something together?
Somewhere or something.
We'll work it out together?
-Yes.
Where should we go?
I don't know.
You think about it today?
Okay.
He can be recognized. He operates
both in Malmö and Copenhagen.
He's changed his appearance?
-Probably.
Bjørn knew him by his eyes.
Search the archives for things
about facial plastic surgery.
What should I focus on?
-Deaths and missing persons.
Hi, everyone.
Where were you? I thought you were
sleeping at my place.   -I slept at home.
I haven't got anything
going on with Saga, though.
Martin went strange and then
his wife threw him out.
That's right. Then you know that.
What was the name of Jens'wife?
-Mikaela. His wife was named Mikaela.
Why were they crossing the bridge?
-She was going to Sweden.
Jens said she went to her parents.
Two o'clock at night, in the
middle of the week.
Strange time to visit your parents.
-I'll check it out.
Can you pick up
the little ones today?
At what time?
-Around eleven.
Aren't they in school?
-They're out today.
We're also going to the zoo.
What did you before?
-Team meetings. Here at home.
Are you still sick?
-It's a presentation.
I can handle it.
I don't want the children running
around here, can you watch them?
No, I have to go to town.
I understand it's difficult for you
liveing in my house. Martin is almost never here.
I've never asked for anything, and
allowed you to use our house as a hotel.
But I need you now.
What's so important
you can't help me?
I have a job interview.
An interview? For a job?
-Yes. I can pay for the hotel.
I'll find something else.
Make a good job of it.
Good luck.
-Thank you.
Think out loud.
You were friends with Jens.
-Yes.
That's why he didn't shot you at Sorgenfri.
-Probably.
Was there anything between you two
that's relevant to our case?
I don't know. Jens was a good
cop and a good person.
He thought he could improve the world.
This is something quite different.
You were right. Jens' wife
wasn't on the way to her parents.
Where was she going?
They thought her friend,
Josefin Samuelsson, perhaps knew.
And did she?
-Mikaela was going to her.
Why was Mikaela coming to you?
She had a fight with Jens and asked
if she and Rasmus could sleep at my place.
What were they arguing about?
She wanted a divorce. She told him
she had met someone else.
Jens was furious and wanted her
say more. She didn't dare to stay.
Then she decided to come
with Rasmus to my place.
Did she tell you who she'd met?
-No.
Did she tell Jens?
-No. Only that she had met someone.
Are you sure?
-Yes.
I asked if she warned
him about Jens.
She said Jens didn't
know who he was.
Did she say anything else?
-No.
No, she called from the bridge
and said we'd see each other soon.
Why the questions?
It was years ago.
Their names has surfaced
in our investigation.
Jens committed suicide.
-Yeah, I know.
Why did you walk away?
The man, who Mikaela met, was me.
I wasn't married. It was long
Before I met Mette.
I was separated from Susanne.
She had left with Julie.
Mikaela had it hard,
and then it happened.
So you weren't married, but she was
to your best friend and colleague.
Can it stay between us?
I don't want the rest of
the team to know.
If it's important,
is unavoidable.
Did you know she wanted to tell Jens?
-No.
It must have been difficult
to see him every day.
How could you continue as colleagues
after what you had done?
Or wasn't that the intention?
I had certainly never
wanted to cause her death.
You didn't.
She wanted to tell.
Jens was so angry when she left.
Without me, there wouldn't have been
anything to say.
Without a bridge, there'd be no accident.
So you shouldn't think you're responsible.
But I do.
Come on.
Have you found anything?
It costs money
to perform this operation.
Maybe he owns property
and we can follow a transaction.
We looked at unresolved
robberies and burglaries.
That has yielded nothing.
But we'll go on checking.
Did your colleagues know about Jens?
-Lillian told a few of them.
What did the friends say?
Mikaela told Jens when she left
home, she was afraid to stay with him.
What was wrong?
-She had met another guy.
Do we know who he was?
She didn't say, and Jens didn't know.
So it isn't important.
I've got Karl-Erik Hermansson,
a plastic surgeon.
Killed in an accident in 2007.
He had a clinic near the Triangle.
Did he have any employees?
A nurse, Elsa Dahlberg.
Here's her address.
I just wanted to give you
a compliment. You're doing well.
If it leads somewhere ... You're deserving.
If someone is solving this, you are.
-I think so.
Do you ever tell the others
you appreciate their work?
Why not?
I just tell them what to do.
They do it well.
-It's their job to get it right.
Don't you like to be praised?
No, I don't need it.
Do you think it's important?
-Very. Most people find it important.
Do you want to praise me now?
It's okay to do that.
What do you want me to say?
-It doesn't work like that.
It's like wanting somebody to say he
loves you. It should come by itself.
Did you miss me yesterday?
When?
-Last night when I didn't.
A little.
Karl-Erik ... They said he
took his own life in his car.
But I never believed that.
-Why not?
I worked with him for eleven years.
I'd know if he was planning suicide.
Many people who commit suicide
show no signs beforehand.
And then there was the fire.
It was obvious something was wrong.
What fire?
-In the surgery.
Two weeks after his death.
The entire building almost burned down.
This man.
Was he a patient of yours?
Jens "What's his name". A Dane.
It wouldn't surprise me
if he had committed suicide.
Why not?
If you want to change your appearance
so much, there's a lot wrong with you.
What did he have done?
-Hairline, nose, mouth, teeth ...
changes in bone structure.
But he was very stylish.
Karl-Erik was good at his job.
Do you have records from that time?
They were there.
And backups on the computer.
Unfortunately, everything was
destroyed in the fire.
Can you describe
what he looked like for an artist?
I think I have a picture of him.
Him? After the surgery fire?
I had paper copies of some
patients' files.
I sometimes worked from home.
My husband was ill.
So you may now have
something at home?
In the attic.
Do you remember where they were
placed?
They're in a box.
What's marked on it?
I don't remember anymore, but they
lie slightly further in.
How far?
-Go further that way.
Maybe somewhere near a typewriter.
There.
It says 'office' on it.
Is 'office' written on it?
-Yes, that's it.
There.
Sorry I'm late.
Flowers for your recovery.
Come inside.
Thi is what he looks like now.
What do we do now?
-I try to find a name.
What about the picture?
Do we distribute it?
He doesn't know we know
what he looks like.
If no one but us knows,
he can't be recognized.
If we want to catch him,
Everyone should know what he looks like.
If we do that, he'll disappear.
-If we have a leak.
He always knows the information
we distribute.
Okay, we'll leave it
a moment for us.
How long?
If we have anything tomorrow morning,
I'll issue an alarm. Europol Interpol, everywhere.
Martin. I won't lie to Hans.
-What are you lying about then?
I haven't told him
you had a thing with Mikaela.
You haven't told everything.
That's not lying.
Not tell the truth
is the same as lying.
But has he asked you about it?
if he'd asked,
would you conceal anything?
Then you haven't lied.
-He'll come to know sooner or later.
You say you knew, but
you didn't think it was important.
But then I lied.
Is it important?
Until now, no.
What a beautiful house you have.
-Thank you. We are very happy with it.
What does your husband do?
Martin works for the police.
Exciting. What kind of police
work does he do?
He's a detective.
He's working on the bridge murder
case or the TT ...
or whatever they call the crazy guy.
Then he's busy. It seems
they can't catch him.
I wouldn't say so.
They're close to solving it.
Mommy, when are we leaving?
When I finish work.
If I can handle it.
You promised.
-Before I became ill.
You can work.
The more you disturb me, the longer
it'll take and I'm tired now.
Where were you going?
-To the zoo.
Now it'll be a movie and candy.
The zoo sounds like more fun.
-They think so too.
Do you want company?
No, I'll manage.
You do this for sure, but I can
help with the kids, if you want.
It isn't necessary.
I haven't been in ages.
It would be nice.
Thank you. Nice.
Thank you for coming.
You'll hear from us.
"Thank you for your interest,
but the job is already taken."
Excuse me?
-If you want help with the formulation.
As I mentioned, you'll be hearing from us.
What are you doing here already?
-What do you mean?
You said you could only come this afternoon?
-Afternoon?
We decided to see each other?
-Did we?
We agreed.
When did we agree?
-The day before yesterday. In the chat room.
We don't chat.
-Quit kidding.
It's true.
Are you taking the piss? We chatted
for more than one week, every night.
No we don't, you know. Someone
must be playing a joke on you.
I hope you haven't revealed too much.
Did you say anything
you'd regret?
No, not directly.
I don't know.
I thought I was talking to you.
In any case we have met each other again.
Am I interrupting?
-What is it?
Where's Martin?
-Coffee Break. I'll get him.
Don't. I want to tell you
before the others hear.
I've asked for a transfer.
-Yes, to Gothenburg.
It's going to happen.
-When?
I don't know.
First I want to close this case.
And they must find a replacement.
-How long will that take?
I don't know. A month maybe.
Do you know who it's going to be?
-No.
You'll do just fine.
You're a great police officer.
Not everone agrees.
-They'll see their mistake.
Not everyone is as understanding as you.
I just wanted you to know.
A cession with Johan.
We have a name.
Sebastian Sandstrod.
There was a link between him
and Jens' bank account.
He has a IT-consulting firm.
-Where?
There's only a PO Box
and a mobile phone.
When we discovered his name,
we have everything. Credit card, address ...
Where does he live?
-Outside Copenhagen. In Hellerup.
Did Jens live there?
-No.
Well done. You have
all done very well.
Thank you.
-No thanks.
Will you come with me?
No, I'm going along with Martin.
Who are you calling?
-Mette.
Did she know Mikaela?
-No.
Tell her now you've deceived her.
Because even though you didn't know her yet,
when you knew Mikaela, when you were with ...
Go and wait outside.
That's my husband.
I'll call him later.
Where's your hat?
-I don't know.
Have you told your husband about us?
-What then?
I came today and wanted to
go to the zoo?
I'll leave him a note.
Then we're done.
you don't regret it?
-No, I'm excited.
Nobody in the house.
We'll go in.
Downstairs.
I had Gry, Navid and Anne come.
They know what to look for.
We also have police.
-There's no time for political stuff.
Easily said.
You haven't anything to lose.
I'm going to talk to someone who knew Jens.
-You knew him.
Not in the last few years.
-I want to leave the team.
I have withdrawn the report.
For the bridge?
-Yes. I thought you should know.
But you were wrong however.
-Thanks anyway.
Has she been talking to you
about me on the way here?
No. Was she supposed to?
No, you know. But I'm quitting.
I'm moving.
I know.
Now it's certain, I wonder
how she'll handle it.
Saga never says how she feels.
-If anyone knows, it's you.
You think so?
-You might ask her about it.
Of course.
-It'll mean a lot to me.
You mean a lot to her.
Remember my old colleague. Jens?
-He lived here.
Were there places
where he felt safe?
He didn't talk very much.
He was very self contained.
Do your best, I need something.
He bought the caravan, in which he
committed suicide. All I know.
Why?
It wasn't suicide.
Was he killed?
-No, he's still alive.
What are you saying?
-His name is Sebastian Sandstrod. Know him?
Think carefully. Can you
think of anything?
Yeah, hold on. Just before he
left here, he got a package.
What was it?
-His family had a house in Sweden.
In Höllviken.
-Yes you're right.
When they sold it,
they sent his things to Mikaela.
What things?
-I don't know exactly.
Notebooks, some letters
personal things.
But there was something
that infuriated him.
What?
-I don't know.
But he cried
someone had to die.
He broke furniture. He was
out of control. I had to throw him out.
When he bought the caravan in which he ...
He never came back.
Saga, here. He knows it was you.
Come on, now. Just pick up.
It's August.
-It's me. Is Mette home?
No. I'm home alone.
Where'd she go?
-She said she went to the zoo.
I thought she wasn't going.
-There's a note.
She is gone. With someone.
-Who?
Sebastian Sandstrod.
His photograph's been distributed
and there's an APB on him and his car.
Gry, Navid and Anne are searching his
cellar. He must have planned this too.
You said he has succeeded
in everything else?
Does that mean ...
-Stop it. I can't think.
The zoo's been searched completely.
They're not there.
Why's he out to get you?
You were friends.
How do I know what he thinks?
And Mette's mobile?
-Barbara's working on it.
Just move it.
I've got him. He's in that area.
Can you define it more precisely?
-No. But he doesn't seem to be moving.
What is that?
-The Zoo.
They're still there.
How's that possible?
It doesn't make sense.
-Perhaps the ring tone is off.
He gives his name for Mette to write down.
He trusts we'll learn
who he is and where they are.
But that's the best we have.
Can't you say "thanks"?
The first team is about 5 minutes away.
-No uniforms.
Okay, we're now on our way.
Should we go?
What is it?
That way.
Saga Norén.
-He used his credit card.
Where?
-Just now. In the zoo café.
He used his credit card. Where?
-In a kiosk called the Proviant.
Police. I want to see your credit card.
-I've got it.
Can I see him?
-He said I had to use it here.
Are you Martin?
-Yes.
He said you'd duck.
Relax. Here's the point.
He said I had to give it to you.
Do you have children?
I had one. One son.
What happened?
Auto accident.
That's really terrible. I'm sorry.
It took a while ...
but I recovered.
The worst was the rage.
You need to vent your anger.
I worked at it every day.
I don't know what I'd do if
something happened to the children.
And your wife? Is she ...
-She met another guy.
She wanted a divorce. I let her go.
So I lost her already before the accident.
Pardon me.
I rooting around in your life.
It doesn't matter.
Martin deceived me.
I mean, I know
what you've been through.
It hurts.
We'd better ...
Children.
We're leaving.
Thanks for today. It was fun.
-I want to show you one thing, okay?
We must go home. They're tired.
It'll only take a minute.
You won't regret it.
The door is open.
Go inside.
There's a surprise for you.
The light switch is next to the door.
Whose is this?
-It belongs to a friend of mine.
What animal is that? A rat?
-I think so.
Rats aren't so small.
These are slightly larger.
What is it?
Pardon me.
-I didn't know. That was ...
I'll get the kids.
-That is the best.
Come on, kids.
-Look, a hamster.
I have something for you.
Close your eyes.
Close your eyes. Give me your hand.
Hold down here.
-What is it?
I'm almost done.
Good pinch.
Now you can watch.
What's that, mommy?
What is that?
Sit down. Listen to me. Sit down.
Help.
I've talked with my dad.
Was it good?
-Better than expected.
Have you already found her?
-No.
I found something.
-What then?
Remember that Frida
with whom I chatted? My ex-girlfriend.
What about her?
It wasn't Frida.
Saga, come on.
I met her today.
We didn't chat at all.
When did she contact you?
-A week ago.
It is Jens. You write here
we're looking for Anja. So he did.
Did it matter?
Is there more?
He doesn't know August is on to "Frida".
We'll make contact with him.
He hasn't answered.
I've written to him today.
What is there today?
I'd agreed with Frida,
rather the alleged Frida,
to meet in Fælledparken,
in about a half hour?
Do you have a hoodie?
-Yes. Why? Do you think he'll come?
So far, he's fulfilled its promises.
-I'm going.
I stay here with August
and monitor everything.
I'm in position.
Roger. Can I get your status
units 1 to 4?
Unit 1 is ready.
I see the object clearly.
Unit two in place.
Unit three in position. I see the object.
Unit four in position. I see the object.
-Roger. Standby.
A man approaches the object.
What's happening?
A man with a dog
approaching the object.
All units,
walk slowly toward the object.
It isn't him. We'll restart the operation.
Everyone to his old position.
I want to report
strange noises.
It sounds like a woman
and children screaming.
You write a lot about me.
Maybe.
-MlLF?
That was a joke.
It means ...
-I know, but I have no children.
Did it matter, you
told me about Anja?
He didn't know we were looking for her
until you mentioned it.
So it's my fault she's dead?
We didn't have to talk about her.
That was unprofessional.
I saw no harm in it.
I didn't know it was him.
I know. He is smart and dangerous.
Will he murder Mette
and the children?
Give me an honest answer.
Probably.
If he hasn't done so already.
Still nothing. What do we do now?
-Just a minute.
He was twenty minutes late, so ...
He's not coming. Abort.
He's not coming, damn.
We'll abort the operation.
We'll meet in the office.
The office called. Someone reported hearing
a woman and children crying for help.
Morten, you drive.
Why does he do this?
His wife and child died
in a car accident.
He thinks mistakes were made in the
investigation. Now he wants to avenge himself.
So all this talk of his
about opening people's eyes ...
was just talk?
What mistake did my father make?
You must ask him.
-But you know?
Did he let him down?
Like he did me
and my mother ...
and my half sister and her mother,
and Mette.
He has done so.
Wait here.
Martin, what 's happening?
Lillian will take you outside.
There's a grenade. Get them out of here.
I stay here with Mom.
Take the children away.
I'll stay with mom.
Help me.
-I'm with you. I'll take it now.
I will help you. Come on honey, you've
so well done. Now we do it together.
Martin, you can get.
To the left. To the ruins.
I'm with you.
At three you release.
Okay? On three. Raise your hand.
In three open your hand
and let it go. Ready?
One, two, three.
Thank you. Good day.
Johan couldn't continue
with that chat.
Who is Johan?
-He is the specialist of my IT team.
You'll always hear, huh?
When it starts going well ...
Frida let me ...
Or the man I mistook for Frida ...
He showed me a different side
of my father.
Because of him, I talked to him.
He said really good things
and then turns out to be a psychopath.
Do you hear me?
-The park.
Do you know anything?
He had already lost Mikaela.
Why did he never see her again.
And so he lost a son.
-Who?
As Martin and you come closer
together, it will hurt him even more.
What are you talking about?
He's not after Mette
and the children, he's after you.
Saga Norén. Can you hear me? Over.
What is it?
This is Saga-Norén. Can you hear me? Over.
Why don't they answer?
-This is Saga. Can you hear me?
What are you doing?
He's here.
Don't you have a gun on you?
-No. Come on.
Stay here.
Turn around.
Hands behind your back.