previously...
Daniel Ferbé.
-What a sad front page.
I try make people
aware of problems.
According to Daniel Ferbé, the TT
said he's behind it.
Due to budget cuts
in psychiatry.
You need to talk.
You committed a murder for him.
Look at me when I talk to you.
Don't take him into custody.
There. She turns when she
sees the officer. Is that his roommate?
I want to talk about Anja.
She stayed with you.
The man you killed for,
did this.
And this.
He'll do the same to Anja
if we don't find. Do you want that?
That's him. We need to find her.
We've sighted Anja Björk, at
the corner of Adelgata and Östergata.
Stefan? I see you're home.
Open up.
What did Lindberg say?
-Nothing.
But there's something about him.
-We'll monitor him.
Soon I'll get fired.
-I'll do my best to prevent it.
The four officers were acquitted.
The verdict called for resistance.
Last year, four immigrants
were convicted of assault ...
even if it wasn't clear
who the culprit was.
We must take action.
Where are you going?
Stay home.
Henning?
Are you here?
Good morning.
And goodnight. I'll go to sleep.
Did you just come home or going away?
-So you can ask that, yes.
I'm leaving.
Can you help out at home today?
-What?
With everything that has to be done
when Mette comes home with the kids.
She never asked for help.
-That shouldn't have been necessary.
That's good.
Will you see Saga today?
-Yes.
Do you enjoy working together?
-Nice ...
She is an amazing
good detective ...
but fun?
Yes, we like it.
We have fun,
but she's pretty special.
In what way?
-All ways.
Is she single?
What?
-I just asked.
What do you ask?
-Whether she's single.
Yes, she's single.
No one would be
able to stand her.
See you later.
Sorry to bother you,
but I'm really worried.
Perhaps it's about revenge.
You hear a lot about their gangs.
But you've seen nothing in the house
that's amiss?
He's just never
disappeared in this way.
He was determined to be alone.
That trial had ground him down.
I'll ask if anyone here knows anything.
I'll call you when I know more.
That's good, thank you.
Maybe he's already home.
-Maybe.
And wondering where I am.
Thank you for your time.
-No thanks necessary.
Where were you?
-In the cemetery.
Why?
-That's my sister.
How did he know Anja? She was
never connected to this investigation.
We were the only ones who knew
why we were looking for her.
Would anyone leak the information?
-I don't know.
Take a look.
How good they look together?
-Good. Look at the look.
He ducks all the time.
He was home all evening
When Anja was shot.
As it is, let's see him alone and
what he wants us to see.
It isn't enough.
Then let's look further.
Come on.
We need a search warrant.
Do you want to arrested me for burglary?
No, I'm just saying we
need a search warrant.
Only a Sweden would
be as upstanding as that.
Did you regret it?
The prosecution gave permission.
-Good. Where do you start?
I'll do the kitchen and you the bedroom.
-Agreed.
In the bedroom.
This is a great first aid station.
Does he play doctor?
This is as big as the needle
that drained Bjørn's blood.
This certainly isn't
destined for Africa.
This isn't enough.
Is there a connection or something?
You're late.
What did you do tonight?
-Nothing. I just hung around.
For four hours?
I hung around.
Who were you with?
Yassir and the others?
Listen. You can stay out
as long as you want.
You can go wherever you want.
But promise me one thing.
I won't gett called by the
hospital or the police. Got it?
Do we have a deal?
There was a letter for you at the door.
Did you see
who left it there?
What's in it?
-Nothing.
What are you going to do?
What do you mean? Today?
-No, he no longer calls.
If you are a journalist again
like everyone else here.
That will never happen.
-Oh, no?
I'll always be the man who had
direct contact with a horrible killer.
People forget quickly.
-I'll keep reminding them.
I think I'll write a book.
Maybe two or three.
What are you thinking?
You look really like shit. I'm
worried about you, is that so strange?
So is he.
Someone's been arrested who may
know him. Should I check this?
Did they find someone?
-A social worker.
Do we know his name?
I'm not him.
What do you do with all those drugs
and first aid stuff?
You've been to my home.
-That was me, yes.
It isn't forbidden to do that.
-What do you do with it?
If someone gets hurt.
-That often happens in your neighborhood?
Just in case.
Do you know who this is?
Should I know?
Where were you last night between 10 and 12?
- In the evening?
In the evening, yes.
-I was home watching TV.
What did you watch?
-Nothing special. I was channel surfing.
So you can't name a specific
program you watched.
No, I can't remember anything.
-Do you speak Danish?
I'm not the man you're looking for.
These are wine boxes
from a crime scene.
And this comes from your apartment.
Same type of wine.
Yes, I see it.
Why is all this blood
in your bedroom?
What blood?
We'll come back for a blood sample.
-That is okay.
Can I go?
-That you can't. You stay here.
Please. Good day and goodbye.
-Goodbye.
"Closed"
What is this?
What do you want? What is your purpose?
The thing with your brother, that's not ...
-Shut up about my brother.
I can explain about your brother ...
Shut up about my brother.
-Listen ...
What are you doing here in the basement?
How did you get here?
What do you mean?
-What do you mean?
You've dragged me here?
Will you release me?
Will you untie me?
-Why should I release you?
Then we'll rectify
that thing with your brother.
Upstairs we'll explain
how it all went.
Then we'll explain what happened?
I didn't do it. I'm very sad about
what happened to your brother ...
You won't get your brother
back by doing this.
That's exactly what I won't get.
I won't get my brother back.
When did your sister died?
Fifteen years ago.
-Your parents?
I was younger. 7 years old. She was 14.
-Just like Anja.
How did she die?
-Suicide.
Were you close?
I guess so. She lived with me.
Why not with her parents?
-She didn't want to.
Suicide?
She jumped in front of a train.
Was she depressed?
Did she show signs?
I'm not good at signs.
He asked for you.
I help people.
-We know.
It's almost more than a job.
Our society leaves many weak
people in the lurch. I help them.
You can do that with food, cash, clothes,
drugs, sometimes with housing.
How do you pay for that?
Have you inherited money?
There are many ways
you can fool the system.
Give a name of someone
you helped this week.
I can't, and you know it.
There is a priest
who can confirm it.
The blood in your apartment?
The only thing I can think of ...
I had a refugee visiting
who had to leave the country.
He cut himself. I stopped
the bleeding and bandaged him.
Where is that refugee now?
-I don't know.
Do we know anything
about the blood in the apartment?
It isn't the victim's
or Stefan's.
An unknown death?
Our perpetrator won't kill in his own
house. Then he'd erase all traces.
I don't believe the story of the refugee.
-Stefan isn't the man we're looking for.
At least the priest confirms
the story about the refugee.
Our culprit is socially disengaged.
-No. He wants to pick certain people.
Do we spend more time and energy on
Lindberg? Then I'll to release him.
Wait a bit.
I want to talk with Daniel Ferbé first.
Gry, I need your help. Come on.
Just go to my boss if you want
to say anything about the publication of his name.
It isn't him.
Stefan Lindberg isn't the man we're
looking for. He's been released now.
Have you already published?
-No. I don't begrudge you a scoop.
Why?
-It can help our investigation.
You can quote an anonymous source and
add that he doesn't speak Danish.
Stefan doesn't speak Danish?
-No.
Well?
What should I do?
-Write that we were mistaken.
I'm giving this to you alone
because Saga likes the articles you write.
Damn.
Damn, say. Pardon me.
There's a toilet outside.
How is it?
-It looks like I peed chocolate.
In my opinion
it'll wash out.
When do you explain to the press?
-How long do you need?
One hour.
-You'll get two.
What is that?
-Daniel's SIM card.
Why?
-It's from his mobile.
Did he give it to you?
-Not at all.
If our killer calls, you answer.
Initiative: 1, insight: 0.
Misconduct.
You don't want to do it?
He's posted something new.
Why just Henning and not the rest?
-I don't know.
Have you seen it?
-Yes.
Does he have Henning?
I think so. His wife said
he disappeared last night .
I'll deploy the whole force.
-That'll lead to riots.
Do you have a better idea?
-No.
Saif, why did you close up?
I had to do something.
Did you hear?
One of those officers was kidnapped.
They think he's here in Nørrebro.
There'll be fighting in the streets.
Saif, here. We need to see each other.
Has something happened there?
-I can't talk about it now.
Do you have that cop?
I want to talk to you about it.
-I 'm on the square.
Hi, Danne. Want to go out drinking this evening?
-No, he'll call you later.
Daniel?
-No, Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Why don't you talk to us directly?
Hello? Are you still there?
-Yes. Where do you want to talk?
Why did Anja die?
How did you know we were looking for her?
I'll skip lunch.
-It's for you.
It's for you.
What are you up to?
-Excuse me?
I wonder what you're up to.
-Nothing.
What is it?
-Why do the police answer when I call you?
Why would they do that?
-Saga Norén has your phone.
But I have it here.
I'll check ...
Damn it.
He stole my SIM card. That Dane.
We know that. Now we can
continue our cooperation.
Police made a mistake
and will release the man in question.
You have something of mine.
-Hi. I was just reading your article.
Cool action. I didn't expect that.
-Me neither.
My boss Carina will see red
when she hears.
I am a journalist. She attaches great
importance to source protection.
She'll cut all your heads off.
I'll be nice. I don't say anything, but
you guys are in debt to me.
And give it back. I need it.
-Yes, many people have called.
You haven't made note
of the names, huh?
He called me at the office.
Now it's about immigrants.
I'll forward it.
How's it going?
Have either of you seen Yassir?
No.
-Okay. I'll see you later.
Hey, Yassir. What's up?
-There you are. Where have you been?
I had to help. You gotta see something.
-Not now. Come.
I got him. That fucking cop.
That fucking cop's sitting in my basement.
-Are you serious?
Will you help me?
-Of course. Come.
Okay. You're not the man we're after.
But you've something to do with it.
I'm going to compare the blood
of every corpse that turns up this week.
And if I find out
whose blood it is, I'll nab you.
In Copenhagen 17
people were arrested.
Three policemen were injured
in skirmishes.
Henning Tholstrup, the kidnapped officer
still has not been found.
We know the fourth problem.
-Immigrants?
Or rather their failure to integrate.
He says we have failed them.
Because integration doesn't happen.
"Those in power,
don't want to share with others."
Then there's free speech
of your Danish colleagues ...
figures that indicate immigrants
are punished harder than natives.
Pia Kjaersgaard, crime statistics,
The Swedish Democrats ...
and a proposal
for a burqa ban.
All that plays no role.
This is personal.
This is about Henning.
As in the other cases.
He tells the police where Henning is.
Henning must die.
He's making it easier
for the force to find him.
Where does the victim's family live?
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
This is my colleague, Martin Rohde.
Is Saif here?
-No.
Do you know where he is?
Do you know that one of
these officers has disappeared?
My son's out.
How do you know? You don't know where he is.
-Because he is my son.
It doesn't matter.
Violence and revenge aren't hereditary.
What is behind this?
-The stairs.
One to our house
and one to the basement.
Can we take a look?
Stop it.
Silence. Keep your damn ...
Shut up.
What's in there?
-The heating cellar.
Others who aren't ours.
They're all locked.
I don't have the key.
Then we're done.
He wants Henning to die. It must be in
the area the force searched.
We can't do anything more here.
-You can always do more.
Feel like talking?
About what?
-About your sister.
What do you want to know?
-I want to know everything.
I don't want to talk about it.
-Maybe you need to.
Why should I?
-Because you couldn't save Anja.
She was the same age as your sister,
so you might recall something.
Sometimes it's totally empty without her.
But she's gone now.
Will you be okay?
-Yes.
See you tomorrow.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
-So you're still working?
What do you want?
-What do you want?
So you want to talk
if you take the initiative.
You were surprised
When I took Daniel's mobile.
You don't like surprises, huh?
Order and control
are your stability in the world.
You talk like you know me.
-I understand you.
Knowledge of others is rooted in
self-knowledge.
How did you know
we were looking Anja?
I will find you.
Perhaps, yes. You still want to know
how I knew you were looking for Anja?
Do you feel guilty about her death?
-No.
I couldn't do anything.
Awful, isn't it? The feeling
you've missed the mark.
How did you know?
-You should know that.
Me as a person or as the
head of an investigation?
You're intelligent. You'll find out.
Are you awake?
What were you actually doing at Charlotte's?
-I had to interrogate her.
I keep thinking about your wallet.
-my wallet?
Yesterday it slipped out of your pocket
when you took your pants off.
What about it?
-Did you use the toilet at her place?
I can't remember.
You don't remember?
-Yes ...
It's so, yes.
I went to the bathroom at her place.
Did you fuck her?
I really don't know why ...
Perhaps it has something
to do with the vasectomy. I don't know ...
I'm not sure if I have something to prove.
To prove?
-Yes.
Or something to do with me ...
Or that I still can. Or ...
Or something to do with my
manhood. I have no idea.
You got me pregnant.
-I know.
Isn't that evidence?
I don't know what to say.
-You say nothing.
You get up and grab your stuff.
And then you clam up.
I don't want it anymore.
Tired, tired.
What do you want?
Thirsty?
If you let me go, I'll tell everything.
There'll be a new trial.
It was Bo who did it.
Bo and Luffe. I'll tell everything.
You should have to spoken sooner.
-I can testify. Will get you sorted out.
It's too late. D'you understand.
It isn't too late. I will testify.
There will be a new trial.
Listen to me. It's not ...
-Shut up.
The unrest is now declining. The police
reported major riots.
Several persons were wounded
and cars set on fire.
There is still no trace of Henning
Tholstrup the missing officer ...
You're up early.
-I couldn't sleep.
Me neither.
Why not?
-I dreamed.
What did you dream about?
-I was with your brother.
We met these officers.
They started beating him.
I couldn't do anything.
I was just watching.
Then they went away.
I went to him and turned him around.
It wasn't him.
He had your face.
-My face?
Was there blood in the dream?
No? It was just a silly dream.
You shouldn't fret about it.
Why do you feed me?
-Rats must eat, right?
What's it?
What's going on here? What are you doing?
What is he doing here?
-I found him here.
You found him here?
We'll take it to the court.
I'll testify, I promise.
What are you talking about? All that grief
because you and your nasty colleagues.
I can testify.
If I testify, everything will be fine.
Fine? What can you fix?
I've lost my son.
Can you give me my son back?
-No.
Let me go. Then we'll make it right.
We make anything okay. You don't understand.
Tell the truth to the court.
You've killed my son.
He's not coming back.
Calm down. Calm down.
Help him.
Martin.
What do you want?
-Open the door.
I was hoping for a cup of coffee.
I've brought croissants.
Have you brought for August?
-August Who?
My August?
Can I borrow a towel.
-Fine.
What the hell are you doing?
-What does it look like?
He slept here.
I'll wait downstairs in the car.
What was that?
-None of your business.
Saga is my colleague and you're my son.
-I'll do what I want.
No. You don't. As long as you live
with me, You obey my rules.
How do I know your rules if
you've never told me?
So this is revenge because
I've been a bad father to you?
Not everything revolves
around you, you know.
Saga ... exactly why Saga?
Are you jealous or something?
-Give me a break.
Are you going home?
You've come here yourself,
So you can create your own home.
Very mature.
Henning's been found. He's dead.
-Damn.
What's wrong?
You and my son. That's what's wrong.
He's 18.
He doesn't need your permission.
You shouldn't. It isn't right.
-Why not?
You're a little weird, but still ...
I don't see the problem.
-We'll talk no more about it.
I don't want to hear anything more.
You must keep quiet for a while.
You found him in the basement,
let him go after one day ...
and then saw he was wounded?
By an officer?
What did he look like?
-I don't know.
How tall was he? Height.
I can't remember.
He was in combat uniform.
There must be something you
remember. Think carefully.
Yes?
I got a letter with a key
for where he was.
Where's the key?
-Here.
What else?
Actually, no.
What is it?
-It is so typical.
What's so typical?
-You know.
I don't know.
My brother was murdered. I ask for
justice. You let me rot.
If one of you is killed,
suddenly it's a very different matter.
You saw chaos everywhere,
turning everything upside down. No?
That's how the Danish police work.
-Shut your face. Shut your face.
What did he look like?
-I don't remember.
Eye color. Hair color.
-He looked like a cop.
Was he as big as Martin?
He had a uniform.
He was as big as Martin,
or slightly larger. He was slim.
I remember no more.
How did you know where I was?
-I read the morning the police reports.
Young man. Overdose.
Your favourite nightclub.
And you weren't at work. You don't
need to ne called Einstein.
That must be the
highlight of your morning.
Not at all.
How are you?
-Okay.
I spent the whole time sleeping.
You haven't heard
what happened last night.
Henning Tholstrup
was shot in Copenhagen.
I'm going to work,
but first I'll take you home if you want.
I died last night.
I laid lifeless on the ground
for 2 minutes 33 seconds.
I saw no tunnel. No light.
-I'll take you home.
It was just dark, Åke.
Very dark.
The preliminary investigation confirms
Henning was in the basement.
Saif had something to say
when we were there.
His confidence in the police
isn't very large.
It can still be him. He killed Henning
and invented the story of the officer.
No gunpowder residue
on his hands or clothes.
Maybe a gang member?
Can someone be abducted
without a trace?
It sounds more like our perpetrator.
What do you think, Saga?
-That it was him.
He wasn't sure Henning would
be killed, so he stayed nearby.
But why Henning?
-I don't know.
But there is a connection
among the victims.
The car's been found.
The car comes from Helsingör.
Only Saif saw him
getting into the car.
How can a police car
be stolen for half day?
It may not have been stolen.
-What do you mean?
Maybe he's one of us.
Maybe he's in the police.