previously...
The power is out on the bridge.
The women on the bridge
are the beginning.
He identifies five specific problems.
The first problem is inequality
before the law followed by four more.
He wants to kill the homeless.
-He doing that.
Is he a psychopath?
He sacrifices people when necessary.
Is it the same man as on the bridge?
-Absolutely.
Two women and nine homeless persons.
-Ten, they've found another one.
In our studio is Daniel Ferbé,
who's had contact with the perpetrator.
Or the perpetrators.
Why is that, Daniel?
We don't know.
I've had contact with one man.
He's done more for them
than the politicians.
He kills them.
-Now they're news.
Stefan. Stefan was there.
Stefan. Is he someone you know?
Do you know who brought the bottle?
Who's your poisoner?
We have no place for you, Anja.
I'm having a cup of tea. Want some?
What do you want?
Has he contacted you?
-He wants 20 million.
From those four. Then he'll stop
everything.
His heart won't stop immediately.
We have five, six hours to
find out where he broadcasts from.
We'll contact those four.
He's doing something, with his eyes?
-The blinks?
Wasn't he in the merchant marine?
It's Morse Code.
Good morning.
-Did you sleep well?
I'm fine. And you?
I dream a lot.
About Dad?
-About anything and everything.
Was he happy?
Yes. Why do you ask?
We got along very
well together. Why?
I want to see him.
Is that wise?
-I don't know, but I want to see him.
Want to go?
The police. They want to talk to you.
Charlotte Söringer's coming.
-And the Danes?
Both are coming. Reluctantly.
I won't care. Tell me when
they're there.
How are you?
This is Kjell-Åke Jönsson.
He was a telegrapher.
He has found "recognize the eyes"
and "not true, when".
He knows him?
-Apparently.
From the merchant marine?
-No, because TT has no Morse.
TT?
He's called that on the Internet.
The truth terrorist.
-This is new.
The ...
man ...
lives ...
ist ...
istedgade.
The man lives on the Istedgade.
I'll go there.
August, damn.
I got milk on the stove.
Keep any eye on it.
How are you, twerps?
We're not twerps.
-Yes. All three of you.
What happened to Mommy?
-She has eaten something wrong.
What then?
-I don't know. A car?
She did it yesterday.
-Eat a car?
No, throw up.
The officers are acquitted
of the abuse charges.
Mistreatment by the police
couldn't be proven.
It couldn't be determined
who did what ...
Hadi Hurani was seriously injured
resisting when he was arrested.
That's why experts think ...
I don't give a hoot
what they say on the radio.
Good coffee.
What are you doing?
-Did I wake you?
Nope.
What time is it?
What are you doing here?
I came here yesterday
and then I slept over.
Don't you remember?
I had a fight with my mother,
and it was raining outside.
Then you let me in.
Do you have bread or something?
A samurai must always fast
the day before the battle.
Tomorrow I need to do
a difficult task.
Do you mind if I eat something?
-Okay.
Bread is in the other box.
Why are you so cranky?
-I am afraid of my wife.
Former sailor. Nasty guy.
He can't come here anymore.
Why not?
-We got complaints.
He was aggressive. Uncontrolable.
The clincher was
he hit someone.
Have you looked in "O5"?
-He had enemies.
Absolutely.
-Where did he go?
I know nothing more.
I need to know who was here
when Bjørn came here.
Jesus. Do you know how many there were?
What do you mean?
We think Bjorn
knows his kidnapper.
Stefan Lindberg.
What a coincidence.
I work here.
-what as?
As Swedish contact person in Malmö.
Then maybe you know Bjørn.
-Bjørn Who?
The Bjørn currently bleeding to death
in front of the camera.
Were you here when Bjørn
was kicked out?
I don't know Bjørn, so I
don't think so.
How's your sister?
Still unconscious.
When will you be in Malmö?
Sometime in the afternoon.
-Come along to the police station.
We want to ask you some questions.
-What?
You hear them this afternoon.
Glad you could come here so soon.
We had a choice?
I was ordered to come.
What are we doing here?
-You must go into his claim.
Why?
-He doesn't improvise.
If he does,
he can make a mistake.
So he thinks we won't pay?
-Of course.
It is well known you four are
not philanthropists.
We need to discuss the next step.
After your public refusal
he has to react. That gives us time.
Then we can save Bjørn.
-So what?
No idea.
-We understand what's intended.
But we need some time to
discuss this together.
Of course.
Is there anything to discuss.
Well?
Would you give 20 million
to a fool?
We could agree,
and then withdraw the money.
We shouldn't pay on principle.
On the Internet, there's a group:
"They can save Bjørn".
Which so far has 9,454 members.
And this is there too.
they can save Bjørn
I agree with Charlotte.
Bjørn knows his kidnapper.
He knows these people.
-I'll have it checked out.
There is more.
-Is it something personal?
No idea.
-Is he in Denmark?
I really don't know.
-Jesus, Martin.
Tomorrow we'll get hit hard.
-I heard they got acquitted.
The press'll make a
connection to the case of the gang.
Four immigrants were wrongly
convicted of complicity.
And this is the same?
-Yes.
Is this really the same? Do you think?
Now it's all about officers?
-Yes, now the cops.
I'm going to Malmö.
Martin, good luck.
Hello, Henning.
How are you?
-Good.
That lawsuit has
really bogged  you down.
It's acquittal.
-I heard.
Can I bum a butt?
Why did you protect them?
I don't.
He fell.
-Broke his arm and hurt his eye?
You weren't there. He fell.
You're wekk out of it. How can you
be so sure the affair is finally over?
He's dead.
Hold on.
-Let me go.
Otherwise I'm gonna come
to an unhappy end too?
I see it still bothers you.
Don't let them
bring you down.
What were you talking about?
-Nothing.
One day.
You need to keep quiet
only one more day.
Got it?
It'll be fine, Henning.
There is no news
from the property owners ...
at the police station in Malmö
to discuss whether they'll agree.
It's becoming urgent. According to experts
the kidnapped Bjørn Rasmusen ...
will lose consciousness
in the next hour.
Then he has about
one hour to live.
Back to the studio.
Thank you, Karin. She is
at the police station in Malmö.
Now to Daniel Ferbé ...
the journalist from the 'Aftonpost'
in contact with the bridge killer.
How are you here?
We don't know how Bjørn is
if that's what you mean.
The homeless didn't reveal anything.
I ran into Stefan Lindberg.
What was he doing?
-He works there.
I asked him to come here.
-Why?
I think he pops up too often.
They won't pay.
Haven't they listened to us?
-No idea.
Are they calling the shots?
-Leave it now.
They don't.
-Stop it, Saga.
Wait a minute. He's saying something new.
He says A, 1, ...
and then three letters: A, J, B.
And then he repeats A, 1, ...
-Maybe a code.
Why? It's probably something he sees.
-He sees the camera.
Maybe.
Gry, Navid, look after all details
on A1AJB.
Production number, serial number,
property register ...
Have them do the same in Copenhagen.
If any info comes, we'll hear it.
What if it doesn't work.
He'll lose consciousness.
they'll murder Björn
Can you see it?
-You wrote it?
It's true.
-So isn't that simple.
To negotiate with terrorists ...
-Write about it yourself.
Have you seen the competition?
It's about feelings.
-That is exactly what he wants.
How'd you know?
Have you ever had contact with him?
-No.
There you go. You're just jealous.
-That's not the case with me at all.
The four property owners
asked to pay the ransom ...
decided not to pay 20 million.
Have you changed your mind?
-No, not yet.
We can go back too.
-No, I want to see him.
Are you okay?
Who are you?
Sorry, I'm going.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
I'm Emilie Hanson. I was
a good friend of Göran.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't be here.
Em?
Are you Em?
Did you have a relationship?
Condolences, Maya.
I didn't know she'd be here.
Think out loud.
He hasn't made a single mistake.
He didn't know Bjorn
could communicate.
It doesn't matter to him
what's behind the camera.
It looks like an abandoned factory.
What's in an abandoned factory?
-Machines.
Then he had said
what kind of machine.
Pipes, doors ...
A door with a number.
A container with a chemical.
-Behind a camera that films ...
Films ...
Bjørn sees an electricity meter.
-Do you know what?
Two digits are missing.
ln Malmö we have a letter, a number,
three letters and two digits.
Probably he can't see
the last two digits.
There are certainly 99 possible?
-Hundred. 00 is also possible.
We have found it.
-It's a meter. And further?
Not everything one is in use.
There are 89 active numbers.
That is 88 too many.
-There are 67 residential.
He isn't in a house.
-Another 22 posibilities.
Martin, Saga?
I'll pay.
I'll pay everything.
-Why? By yourself?
We can pretend
the others paid too.
You said your husband wouldn't do it.
-He'd burst into a rage.
Are you sure? It's a lot of money.
I'm quite sure.
Then he must go to Bjørn.
-I'll notify the media.
Please come with me.
Why have you changed his mind?
Revenge.
Sorry.
No lofty motives,
and no moral dilemma.
Just out of revenge.
-On your husband?
I've found I wasted 19 years
of my life.
I feel that to.
It doesn't matter.
I can collapse or turn back.
I'll turn back.
Are you married?
Married?
Good.
I'd like to drive you home,
but I have to work.
Doesn't matter. I have my own car
and I'm in no rush.
Maya gets the chance
to leave the house.
My stepdaughter.
Now who inherits 20 million less.
They'll pay 20 million.
-In order to save the Swede?
Some good news.
-Have you?
I'm not issuing a press release.
Give it to Åke.
What is he doing now?
-Åke now is picking his nose.
No, the killer bridge. TT.
-He'll stop bleeding when he gets the money.
Then he is going to.
But nobody knows where "there" is.
There are three meters of interest
in the port area, all in the same building.
One of these meters
is now being used illegally.
The SWAT team is about 20 minutes
away. We'll get him.
If he's keeps his word.
-He does.
You think he's dead?
Are you expecting someone?
-Open it.
The door's locked.
Lasse Jönsson?
-Yes, he lives here. Let us in.
I want a signature.
Thank you.
I don't like the door locked.
Why not?
-Then I'm trapped.
I don't lock you in.
I just lock out the outside world.
But for me the same result.
Yet?
Here's the keys.
How's that?
-Yes.
But don't let anyone in.
-No.
Won't you open the package?
-I don't want to.
Not yet.
-Who from?
From no one.
I want to call my mom.
She must be worried.
Well, she deserved it.
Dad is much cooler.
But he has
a great, new family.
So he has no time.
Who are you?
Are you kidding?
Anja.
I came yesterday.
I slept over.
The rain.
I'm going out.
-Will you be back?
Does that suit you?
-Of course.
Knock just three times.
They are about ten minutes away.
Then we'll go inside.
The meters are in three different
places. Ten minutes is a long time.
9.47.
What are you doing?
-I'm going to work.
We have to wait
on the arrest team.
It is important
an officer protects his colleague.
For the record:
I am your colleague.
To the left.
This is one.
Saga, it's Hans. Where are you?
Saga, come in.
What is she doing now?
Police. Halt.
Stop.
Don't kill me.
The other meter is a little further.
Calm down.
Take it easy.
I'm with the police,
so calm down.
What's your name?
-Mange.
And beyond?
-I live here.
Have you seen anyone here today?
-No, there's no one else.
I'll go to the other meters.
You bring him up?
Are you okay?
-Yes.
Hans, it's Saga.
We've found someone.
What are you doing?
He wasn't there?
Who's that?
-A Swede.
He wasn't at Sorgenfri or Dalvik.
-What are they?
Industrial areas with meters with
the same number. But nothing.
I was so sure.
- He put a stop to the bleeding.
We need to know where they are.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
With Gry. We've discovered something.
Some meters have
a sort of twin numbers.
What does that mean?
- On Sorgenfri there's new construction.
These meters have the same numbers
as the meters in the demolition area.
But those are still there.
The meters are thus in two places.
And we were in the building.
-Exactly.
Give me the information.
Send everyone back there.
Can I have your gun?
-You mustn't carry arms in Sweden.
I don't care.
-I can shoot well.
Okay. That way.
We must follow this course.
You okay?
-Yes.
Are you okay?
Bjørn, can you hear me?
Hans, it's Saga.
I've found the victim.
TT escape through the roof.
He is armed.
How are you?
-Am I? Well.
What did he look like?
-He was taller than me ...
well trained, fit ...
He can fight well. Nothing more.
-That's all?
We really mean:
How are you?
I'm back together.
How's Bjørn?
He was alive when we arrived,
but he died in the ambulance.
He had put stop to the bleeding.
He kept his word.
But you didn't catch him.
He knew how to flee.
-He shot two officers.
How are they?
One dead and the other has
life-threatening injuries.
Damn it.
-Have you seen anything?
What then?
-It was something I felt.
I don't know what it was.
Unfortunately.
Today I don't work,
but I'll come back tomorrow.
Are you sure?
-Certainly.
Your wife is waiting.
I'll send her to you.
Are you Mette Rohde? Your husband is there.
Saga Norén Malmö CID.
-Nice to meet you.
Martin has said a lot about you.
-What then?
You two are working together.
-No more?
You don't work together?
-No.
What do you mean?
-Mette leave it.
I am Hans.
I had called you. Would you go inside?
-Please.
Hopefully I'll see you soon
under more pleasant circumstances.
Come.
I want a kiss from you.
Go sit down.
Ouch, damn.
-Sorry.
It doesn't still hurt.
That bastard kicked me hard.
It hurt so much.
Just as bad as childbirth.
What is it?
-Nothing.
Tell me.
Was it this guy?
Why didn't you shoot him down?
How could he come so close to you?
I can't carry weapons in Sweden.
So you're unarmed
behind a madman?
Saga is armed.
-And what did they do?
She was also knocked down.
Will you stop it?
Why not?
-I can't.
Of course.
You lie in the fucking hospital.
I can't. I gotta find him.
There is no difference between this job
and my other jobs.
In addition, you can defend yourself.
That's a big difference.
How are the twins
and Nicholai?
August's taking care of them.
He's been very big help.
Now it's good.
Maybe.
Saga Norén isn't here.
She'll return tomorrow.
And Martin Rohde?
-The same. Coming back tomorrow.
Where is the punch?
-Will you say Stefan Lindberg stopped by?
I will.
-This isn't one.
What was your name again?
-Stefan Lindberg.
Got it.
-Thank you.
Stefan Lindberg?
-Where is Veronica?
Veronika what?
-They can't just run away.
I'll really find her.
And if I don't find her, I'll find you.
Jesus Mina.
I can do it myself.
-Sorry.
What is it?
Are you back home?
I might as well be home in bed.
Thanks for looking after the little ones.
Really fine.
Have you seen the TT?
-Yes.
How did he look like?
-No idea. But he kicks hard.
I'm going to bed. Are you going too?
Maybe I make an account.
-Why?
To maintain contact with others.
Yes, you can do that.
Who is that?
-Frida.
Pretty girl.
You got a girlfriend?
Is she a girlfriend?
-That you should know.
Who is she?
-She's my ex.
She was my girlfriend
in high school.
Do you remember something
of my high school?
He said, leaving his son alone.
Good night.
-From the same.
Damn it.
What is it?
What are you thinking?
Is there something wrong?
What is it?
I'm pregnant.
I was operated on for you.
It's yours, do you doubt.
-No, no.
We wanted no more children.
But?
We can't?
I don't know.
-And if it's twins?
It could be twins again.
Then we have five children.
We don't have ...
We don't have room for.
Can we handle it?
Or, we can handle?
Come here.
We don't need to decide anything now.
I'm going home.
Hans, what's the main task
an officer?
Solve crime? Catch perpetrators?
Protect your colleague.
That's Martin.
You couldn't help it
Martin was injured.
I thought Bjørn was important.
The important thing is
to save lives.
Martin is still alive.
Save a life is more important.
-I say anyway.
They are equal
on the priority list.
We have the same rules
throughout Scandinavia.
There is no difference.
You handled it properly.
Why are you in the dark?
Honey?
We wanted to search him,
but he resisted.
Bo gave him a knee in his face.
Then his eye got damaged.
Luffe wanted him to quit
screaming and broke his arm.
He had so much pain.
He tried to stand.
They went down on him,
until he calmed down.
He lost consciousness.
I watched. I watched,
and when I left.
You must tell this to other people.
I think so.
Sorry.
Hi, I am.
Did you met anyone?
Some one who just left?
How can I meet anyone?
-So he called. A real master.
If you say so ...
-He has revealed the truth.
Good night, Anja.
You're crazy.
But in a good way.
Do you? I have called my mom.
I thought she would cry
and would ask me to come home.
Like mothers do.
But she was well into the red wine.
So I'll stay another night
if you don't mind.
Fine. You can stay as long as you want.
From tomorrow, the apartment is yours.
What? Why is it mine?
-Good night.
Don't forget to lock the door.
Nope.
Hi, Saga.
-How are your balls?
Small talk isn't
your forte. What is it?
There was something inside me.
About what happened.
He focused on you, but he didn't fire.
Why didn't he shot you down?
No idea.
Later, he shot down two policemen.
I was no threat.
-Maybe not.
Whether he wants to make something clear.
What then?
-Maybe he needs you.
Why?
-I don't know.
Think about it.
Good night.