previously...
The power is out on the bridge.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Two women were killed.
They were placed on the Øresund bridge.
Someone wants to leave us a message.
Can you understand my Danish, Daniel?
-Fine. Who are you?
Someone who stands up for the truth.
Why are you calling me?
It's so hard to hear your voice.
The women on the bridge were the beginning.
When I heard the message, I was shocked.
I narrated it 3.5 years ago.
Where do you work?
-The police. That's a corpse.
Can I turn on the lights?
Martin, one of the dogs smells something.
When I thought I was going to die,
I thought I can't and won't go on.
Do you want a divorce?
What's happening?
He's contacted Daniel again.
Homeless. The homeless.
Six people were admitted to
hospital in serious condition.
Everything points to poisoning.
They were hospitalized.
Sonja, I am.
He wants to murder the homeless.
-He's already begun.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Do you know anything about the poisoning?
Come. There.
Inside?
Go there, over there.
I'm going to Malmö.
-Is it the same case?
Yes, that's for sure.
Two murdered women, a car bomb,
nine dead and homeless.
Ten. They've found another.
Is your Swedish colleague good?
-Saga Norén?
They do tremendous things
to solve crimes.
She is very effective.
-She's filed a complaint against you.
I love you too. But try
her to persuade her to withdraw it.
I'll try.
-Keep it neat.
Neat? Why?
That means you're only
colleagues. And nothing more.
Did you bring me here for that?
-No.
This is a growing region. We're trying
to attract businesses and families.
We feed the homeless.
But to murder ...
We'll do our best to solve this problem.
Then there's Monique Brammer
and the trial of five policemen.
I wasn't on the Brammer case.
I had nothing to do with it.
I know.
-What do you mean?
My first priority is to fix this.
-And your second priority?
Danish police can use
some good PR. Sometime?
It seemed to go well. He woke
and we talked. And then ...
I wasn't there when Mom died.
Your father loved you very much, Maya.
A lot.
Can I help you?
-Stefan Lindberg.
Come with me.
We don't know
what she ingested.
There wasn't much life in her.
Should we notify anyone?
No. She's just got me.
Thank you.
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Sonja.
That's mine.
Let go.
What are you doing?
They've come to pick us up.
-Who?
Social workers.
There is a bus outside.
Won't you join?
-I'll save myself.
Come on.
What do you want?
Are there any survivors?
-Two in Denmark, one in Sweden.
It doesn't look good.
Nobody knows who passed out the wine?
-Apparently not.
We don't know what poison it is.
We haven't heards anything
from forensics.
Severe cramps and tightness
indicates an alkaloid.
It would be strychnine.
But the bleeding
not consistent with that.
You have to find a hobby.
-What?
Nothing on the bottles and boxes?
-Of course not.
So we haven't anything?
-He's like a fucking ghost.
We'll review everything again.
ln the studio is Daniel Ferbé, a
journalist with the 'Aftonpost' in Malmö ...
he's had contact with the perpetrator.
Or perpetrators. What about it, Daniel?
We don't know.
I've had contact with one man.
Twelve were killed in one day.
What does he want?
He wants, if he wishes,
to high light five problems.
Five truths about our society.
He's a kind of truth terrorist.
It started with the question
whether we are equal before the law.
What is this offensive?
Actually it's crazy
we're so worry about it.
Every year as many people
die from the cold.
But that doesn't agitate anyone.
Those are his words.
Why did he decide to contact you?
-He has faith in me.
What are the three other problems
he wants to point out?
No idea. He'll get back in touch
if anything new happens.
He determines what you write?
-A journalist should be independent.
You know it.
I decide what I write.
The circulation of the 'Aftonpost' ...
Saga? Gry, congratulations.
-Thank you.
He's back on air.
He uses the same addresses,
but hides them better.
Can you find him?
-I can only find the server.
What does he want with that man?
Is it live on the site?
-No.
Do you know who it is?
Check the background.
-It may be a recording.
Martin, here.
We're just looking at it.
Who? Are you sure?
We're coming.
We know who it is.
I have a talk
with my boss. She's under pressure.
The sloppy investigation of
Monique Brammer ...
Five colleagues are
standing trial for murder.
Are you listening?
Is it so hard to acknowledge
by saying the occasional 'yes' or 'um'?
I sit next to you in the car.
I have to listen to you.
She could use some good PR.
She wants to show the police do
a good job. You know what I mean?
If we solve this together, she wants it to
appear as if it's especially due to my work.
I just wanted to say that.
And we should share the honor.
Fine. If that's important to you.
For me?
Don't you think that's important?
Give me a break.
You know you'll also get
a promotion if we solve this?
Yes.
These cases can move
your career forward.
It doesn't matter.
-Oh, no?
I don't want a promotion.
Why not?
-I am not a leader.
Who said that?
-Nobody.
I thought you should know this.
Thank you.
-No thanks.
Excuse me.
Hold it.
Let me go.
-Just calm down. Come on.
Stop it.
Let me see your bag.
-I don't want.
Let's see your bag.
-Let me go.
Stand still and let me look at your bag.
Please let me go.
What is wrong with you? Stand still.
-Let me go.
Let me see your bag. Hello?
I want to see what's in your bag.
-It wasn't on purpose.
Not on purpose?
I want it to look in your bag.
I'm sorry.
Do they have their own beds?
-First come, first served.
Except Bjørn.
-Well ...
He gets violent
if someone swipes his bed.
And that worked?
-He was thrown out.
Eventually he got his own way.
Who's that girl?
-His daughter.
He took that picture during his last visit.
Was he a sailor?
-He sailed in the merchant navy.
Do you know if he fought with anyone?
Besides neighbors, shopkeepers, policemen
and all other people on earth?
I can't help you.
But there are enough people
angry at Bjørn.
I know where Bjørn is.
Or, where he was, in any case.
It's a pin from a taser.
ln the cartridge are strips of paper
with a serial number.
They flying out when it's fired.
You can identify who fired,
how long and how often.
To prevent abuse.
A strip of paper?
-Small strips of paper.
We need people to come
and find them.
I'm sorry.
That's it.
What are you thinking?
-Why is he there?
Bjørn?
-What's the offender doing?
He'll tell us later.
He isn't stingy with information.
Lilian told me something else.
You've filed a complaint against me.
What can I do so you'll withdraw it?
Nothing.
What did you do yesterday?
-I was at the slaughterhouse, with you.
Yes, but?
-Why do you want to know?
No idea. If you work together,
you just talk to each other.
I'm having a conversation with you.
-I even had sex.
How did you succeed?
It doesn't take so long?
What was his name?
-I don't remember.
He shoots ... Bjørn down with a taser
and binds him to a chair.
And puts it on the Internet.
Why?
He killed the others instantly.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
We will go there immediately.
She woken up.
She was very awake.
How's she doing?
-From time to time she's conscious.
Conscious.
-What?
It's 'conscious'.
-Thank you.
Okay.
Shall we take a look?
Then we didn't come for nothing.
Sonja, d'you hear me?
I'll get a doctor.
-Wait.
Sonja, d'you hear me?
Stefan.
-I'm Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Stefan was there.
-Is Stefan someone you know?
Everything is good.
-Did you see someone with the bottles?
Stefan.
-Did Stefan have the bottles?
Sonja, do your best.
Stay awake.
Do your best to stay awake.
Do you know who has poisoned you?
Did you see anyone?
I've seen him.
-Did you know him? What did he look like?
Who are you?
-And who are you?
I'm her brother.
Is she awake?
No. Saga Norén,
Malmö CID.
This is Martin Rohde
of the Danish police.
Who are you?
-Stefan Lindberg.
What are you doing here?
Can you show some ID?
So you've found her
and brought here.
How long has your sister been homeless?
I don't know.
We lost contact with each other
when I was fifteen.
We ended up in
separate foster homes.
I just found her yesterday. I didn't
even know if she was still alive.
So you just find your sister
and then apparently she gets poisoned.
Yes. Is that so strange?
That's bad luck.
-Where were you before?
I had to arrange things.
And you left
your dying sister behind.
I can show you where she was.
No, you don't.
We know where she was.
Tell me if I can help you with
anything. Can I go to Sonya?
We have to buy flowers for Gry.
-Why?
It's her birthday.
-Oh yeah?
Did you know?
-Go ahead. I'll wait here.
Do you have some Swedish money?
Can I borrow some?
Aren't you going back to work?
Mommy?
I said I was sorry?
Take an aspirin.
-I took one an hour ago.
From a taser.
See if you can identify it.
Do you know which brand?
I'll start immediately.
-Please.
Congratulations from Saga and me.
I didn't buy flowers.
You said they were from both of us.
It doesn't matter. She was delighted.
What does that have to do with it?
-Something's happening to the feed.
Yes, but I can't come.
We need to do it over the phone.
For three hours. lt's okay.
But call me later.
You were really good on TV today.
-Thank you, Åke.
I'm really glad you liked it.
No, you mean that ironically.
-No.
lronie is dead, Åke.
Really?
But you were right.
It's all here.
I know.
This man is my Sankara Stones.
What are they?
Daniel Ferbé.
-Nice, the bit about "truth terrorist".
I don't care what you think.
-Shall I call someone else?
No, you don't.
-Good.
I've seen your broadcast.
Have you seen mine?
I'm looking now.
You're not alone.
And the pictures?
-Are you now a journalist?
I can figure out who they are,
but it's easier if you tell me.
Who are they?
What's this?
Dad's on TV.
Bjørn Rasmusen is in the video.
Two property owners from Malmö
and two from Copenhagen ...
are also on the site.
-I'll get it.
Daniel Ferbé, the journalist
who had contact with the killer ...
says these four have to save
Rasmusen. How is unknown.
Chosen to save Bjørn.
How?
-No idea.
What is the common denominator?
-Real Estate.
But the link to Bjørn?
-No idea.
No lead on the spot where
Bjørn is being held.
In the video, you can't see where he is.
-Why not?
Or else he wasn't there.
The police are going to Lorentzen
and Beckgård.
You and I go to Söringer.
Anne and Navid to Hodell.
What has it to do with Sonja?
-She saw someone.
They'll get protection.
-Saga, Martin?
He's dead.
-Who?
Söringer died last night
in Copenhagen.
Whose business is it now?
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
I'd like to speak to you.
Remember me?
I don't want to talk to you.
I want to help you,
but I will only talk with you.
Do you have a name?
Martin Rohde.
Come inside.
Aren't you coming in?
Haven't you heard what she said?
Can't you just listen?
-Yeah.
Hold it.
Get out.
Stupid drunk.
What do you want doing?
What do you want?
I get hungry too.
But you know that yourself.
Every officer in Malmö and Copenhagen
are actively looking for him.
The camera turns off
and the image disappears.
He'll come to us.
-You hope.
How long ago was this?
-Approximately one hour.
None of the Danish
property owners know Bjorn ...
or know how to save him.
No Bjørn Rasmusen
rents his house ...
or has anything to do
with Hodells real estate.
Charlotte Söringer didn't know him.
He didn't pick up those four.
-But he doesn't have Bjørn anymore.
We don't have him either.
Such a psychological profile is useful.
But we don't know if there is only one perpetrator.
There's only one.
-How do you know?
From the way
when he speaks to us.
Hello, Salvatore.
This is Martin Rohde from Denmark.
I suppose no one can pronounce
your last name properly?
Sounds like a classic case
of manipulation.
Hear that, Saga?
-Good.
I am Martin Rohde.
Salvatore Johansson,.
It's not much to go on.
I have little evidence.
But this is someone on the edge
of a psychotic condition.
Saga, we have a ...
-You'll have to wait.
This person focuses on a project
and shuts out all the other things.
He is single.
He is successful or was successful
in his profession or otherwise.
I think a traumatic
event has taken place.
Which has turned his world
up side down.
In this way he tries make the world
understandable again.
Are we talking
about a psychopath?
You could say that.
He has a clear goal.
He wants to impose
his worldview on us.
If he has people to sacrifice,
he will do so.
A psychopath, I think.
-Does he have a weakness?
Everything he does,
is carefully planned and executed.
He worked on it for over three years.
-That doesn't surprise me.
But that's his weak spot.
If someone or something upsets his plans
and it isn't the way he wants ...
everything will collapse.
In short: He doesn't improvise.
Daniel Ferbé.
- Who's that woman?
What woman?
The photo-.
lnstead of Goran Söringer.
-He is deceased.
He died yesterday.
That's his wife.
Maybe you should
just read the whole article.
Should I find someone else?
What happens now?
To Bjørn.
We have been in contact with Taser.
The gun was known to us.
It was in 2001 handed over.
-To us?
In April 19. It was supposed
to be destroyed on May 8.
Then it disappeared.
-Why?
It was legally
removed from the registry.
By?
-Lennart Fransson.
An officer. He's retired.
Four years ago. He has
an apartment in the city.
How was he as an officer?
He was good, accurate,
never went wrong, well liked.
And this?
-We still know nothing.
Anne, Navid, go to the rear.
Gry, stay here.
Police, Lennart.
Lennart, this is Hans of CID.
I'll come back.
ls daddy home?
-He just left.
We're having visitors
for Oscar's birthday.
My brother and my parents are coming.
-Nice.
Can I wait for daddy?
Here?
It may take a while.
He just left.
That's okay.
I can wait.
You may sit there.
Does Mommy know you're here?
No. I thought you'd call
to say I'm asleep.
Yeah, but ...
There's something happening at home.
I can't go home. Because ...
You can't stay.
I'm sorry, but you can't.
You can't come unexpectedly.
-Why not?
Filippa's brother's coming with his family.
Her parents and neighbors what a piece of ...
There is no place.
-I won't come to the party.
I'm looking for a place to sleep.
-It's okay to come to the party.
But we have
no place for you to sleep.
Everyone, except the
neighbors, will stay overnight.
But I can surely ...
Another time.
You're always welcome.
You know that.
I have no time to take
you all the way home.
I can bring you to the train.
-Doesn't matter .
Are we okay?
There are no traces
at Fransson's house.
That doesn't happen.
-Still nothing?
What happened to Bjørn?
-He got to him.
He needed Bjørn for something.
Why Bjørn?
-Why not?
He is big, strong and aggressive.
-He had a taser.
But why Bjørn?
-Maybe he was just in his way.
Then I'd pick somebody
weaker. It's easier.
Say Hans ...
Are you going to move?
-Why? Do you want to get rid of me?
There's still nothing decided.
Karen's looking at houses on the internet.
We're homesick.
It doesn't go away.
Do you want to replace me?
-No.
Whoever succeeds me,
will be glad you're on the team.
Extremely concentrated,
single, successful employee ...
clear objectives, organized.
-There you go.
What?
That's the psychological profile
of the perpetrator.
You have to go home and sleep.
How was your day?
Well.
The children are in our bed.
Why?
Ask your eldest son.
What has he done?
He showed them the tied up
man on the computer.
Now they don't dare
sleep in their own beds.
Why does it start again now?
What is it?
-How about you?
The little ones are in our bed
because you've shown them that misery.
That's the reality.
-That's too intense.
What it means.
Nobody wants to see reality.
What do you mean?
Him. The truth terrorist.
He does more for the homeless than politicians.
-He kills them.
Everyone talks about it.
At least now they have shelter.
Should I worry about you're doing?
-No, why?
You don't go to school,
don't work, sleep all day ...
What's your plan?
-The plan is to have no plan.
That doesn't work.
You can't think only of yourself.
Don't you do that?
You need to help more.
Yes, yes.
You need to help Mette more.
I mean it.
I said yes?
-We want you ...
Why do they call him
the truth terrorist?
A Swedish reporter called him that.
It's on the Internet.
TT.
Turn it off. And act mature.
-Yes, I will.
Who was that?
-My father.
I don't know him, right?
I don't either.
-Why do you live with him then?
Do you come here to find someone?
No, but ...
But it's raining outside.
I know.
I just put the waste out.
I'm having a cup of tea.
There's a cup for you if you want.
Okay.
Come on up.
I only have green tea.
-That's fine.
Nice apartment.
-Thank you.
Sit down.
Where are you from?
-From Copenhagen.
What are you doing here?
It sounds terribly childish,
but I ran away from home.
Why?
Quarrel with my mother.
You do that sometimes.
Can I stay a while?
Fine. You can stay as long as you want.
That's nice of you.
I'll stay a while.
Dad, you should see something.
What time is it?
-Five o'clock.
Come on.
-What is it?
Hello?
-He has Bjørn back on air again.
What happened? Is he dead?
Not yet.
I'm coming.
-Good.
Saga Norén.
-He called again.
Have you heard from him?
He wants to have 20 million.
-Who?
From those four. Five million each.
If he gets it, he'll put
a stop to everything.
If they don't, we know
how much a person is worth.
How much time do we have?
-He started at 5 am, it's now about 6.
He's lost a pint of blood.
He weighs 80 kilos.
7 % is more than 5 liters.
At 40 % blood loss
he'll loose consciousness.
Half a liter per hour.
We have four hours.
His heart won't stop immediately.
-Five, six hours.
Do we know where he's broadcasting from?
We'll contact those four.
He's doing something, with those eyes?
-The blink?
Wasn't he in the merchant marine?
It's Morse Code.