previously...
TT?
-They call him the truth-terrorist.
Go to his demands.
-Why?
He doesn't improvise. When he
does, he makes mistakes.
We don't know
if the property owners ...
who the police are
consultating, will meet his demands.
He says: A, 1 ...
and then three letters.
A J-B.
-Bjørn's seeing an electricity meter.
There are three meters correspond.
They're in an abandoned building.
Bjørn, can you hear me?
He shot two men,
then disappeared.
How are they?
One died on the spot,
the other is seriously injured.
Sören, stop it.
You don't even know me.
Why are you doing that?
Because I can.
Hold it.
-Let me go.
Otherwise I'll also meet
an unhappy end?
Then he was unconscious.
I watched
and then I ran off.
Won't you open the package?
I shouldn't. Not yet.
A samurai fasts the day
before he fights.
Lasse Jönsson?
Hello. I'm Emil.
Have you ever come here before?
No problems
coming here?
Come on.
Thank you.
We can best honour our colleague,
Mats from the SWAT team ...
by catching the bastard.
How are you?
-Fine, as long as I swallow painkillers.
Good.
Was there something found with Bjørn?
-A shoe print, size 43.
I don't know
what brand the sole is.
Now you must bring in
all men with size 43 feet.
That was a joke.
-I know too.
Hello, Lillian.
-What time are you in court?
In one hour.
-Then we have plenty of time.
What are you doing now?
I don't know.
-Don't you know?
I think you'll tell who did what,
and that you watched.
And when I say ...
what happened?
-Then you have to testify.
Some colleagues will spit at you,
others will support you.
Will I be prosecuted for perjury?
-There's a small risk.
But the risk's there.
And then I'll be fired.
I'll do my best
to prevent that.
That's not good enough.
-Henning, that boy is dead.
Today the decision is expected in the case
against the four Copenhagen officers.
The 24-year-old Hadi Hurani died after he
was arrested. The prosecutor has ...
Saif, let's go.
Why aren't you ready yet?
-I don't want to go.
We've already discussed it.
It's important you're there.
For your brother.
I already know what will happen.
-They'll make the right choice.
Do you believe that yourself?
I have to. I've no choice.
Come on.
We're being made fools.
You know it.
Two murders this morning.
A postman and a psychologist.
In the case of the postman,
the perpetrator committed suicide.
Is that for me?
-Don't you want it?
Yes, this is great.
Make sure it looks good.
-Of course.
I just need ...
He is so sweet when he works hard.
Like throwing a ball to a puppy.
Daniel Ferbé.
-What a sad front page.
I try to make people
aware of problems.
This diverts their attention.
Then you shouldn't shoot cops.
They came too close.
-Are you careless?
Are you trying to irritate me?
-No, sorry.
We will focus on
the third problem.
And that is?
Psychiatric patients must make
do with pills and a pat on the back.
Åke, let Daniel read everything
you have. He'll decide what we use.
It was my job.
-Not any more. There's what's happening.
Several murders were committed,
in three cases, followed by suicide.
In Malmö a postman was
murdered with a machete.
Someone cut up rough at a
psychiatrist's with a sword.
In Copenhagen someone
on a bus was hit with an ax...
and there someone was stabbed
in a doorwaywith a knife.
According to Daniel Ferbé, the TT
says he's behind it.
Due to budget cuts
in psychiatry.
It's probably the same in Denmark?
-Unfortunately, yes.
This is the third problem.
-How did he do this?
Both Swedish offenders
suffer from paranoid schizophrenia.
Confirme for the Dane too.
He worked here for months.
So four murders,
and only three suicides?
The killer of the psychiatrist
was captured ...
before he could commit suicide.
Is he here?
-The first interrogation yielded nothing.
It's 9.55 am.
The second interview with Lasse Jönsson.
Interrogator: Saga Norén. Present:
Martin Rohde of the Danish police.
You killed Emil Fernskog.
It wasn't your idea.
Who did you do that for?
Did you meet him?
What did he look like?
Can you describe him?
Lasse?
Look at us, Lasse.
Lasse, try to look at us.
How do you feel?
What?
I don't know.
Are you thirsty, hungry? Do you smoke?
A cup of green tea.
-Green tea?
You'll get a green tea
if you do something for me.
What then?
-You have to answer some questions.
Not about him.
-Who?
About whom?
No one.
Lasse, are you afraid of him?
He isn't here.
He can't come here.
Besides, you should be
more afraid of me than of him.
Do you understand me?
You have to talk.
You've committed murder for him.
I'll get angrier if you keep
sitting there without saying anything.
Lasse, you know what I'm saying?
Look at me when I talk to you.
Don't keep him in protection.
Martin?
-Yes?
You shouldn't protect him.
The hearing ended at 9.57 hours.
Don't say anything.
-What?
About this.
-About what you heard?
If I tell you here to keep
your mouth shut, I mean really ...
you should keep quiet
about this. Will you?
But that's not true.
-Thank you.
What are you doing?
-He is always one step ahead of us.
So I don't see. I don't see it
if we were after him.
How do you see it?
-We are at various locations.
With the right information
we'll get there together.
This is the same.
-No.
If we sit waiting for him,
he determines the route.
Martin, Stefan Lindberg
stopped by.
Yesterday?
-I forgot to tell you.
And now you tell us.
Didn't you have our mobile numbers?
He may have had
important information.
I asked him to come.
-She don't know.
Good day.
He needs help few days a week.
I don't know.
I'm going around some time
this afternoon to see how he's doing.
Absolutely.
No, it doesn't matter.
Hold on.
Sorry.
I will tell you just know
how it went. Thanks alot.
Were you talking to Veronika?
No, a colleague.
I want Veronika
and the kids back.
Yes, of course.
At the office, do they know where she is.
-No, you tell me now.
Where are they?
Stefan Lindberg, this is Martin Rohde.
I know you're home.
Open up.
What were you doing?
-I was in bed. I had night shift.
I just wanted to come in.
Sure. Come in.
What ...
What do you actually do?
-We run into each other a little too often.
In several places.
Now we're both
in the same place.
Are you nervous?
-No.
Without the murder of Kerstin Ekwall or
another celebrity I wouldn't know you now.
Celebrity. Do you have some
against promenant people?
I don't mean that.
-Why did you say it?
What do you mean?
-If you're working ...
I see society is unjust.
But you can't solve that by force.
-How then?
I don't know.
Are you OK?
-Yeah. Why do you ask?
Is this someone you know?
Are they homeless?
Addicts?
Why would I know them?
-Maybe you met them.
I want Lasse Jönsson's file.
-This was his first visit.
But he did have an appointment?
He made it two months ago.
How many psychiatrists work here?
-Five. But they're never all here.
So it was a coincidence
he came to see Fernskog.
No, he specifically wanted have
an appointment with Emil today.
I remember because Emil
previously had two cancellations.
Then I called Lasse Jönsson ...
to say he could come earlier.
But he insisted on today.
Martin.
-Saga, here. Are you in the office?
I'm with Stefan.
-See you in fifteen minutes?
I'll be there.
-Good.
Until then.
We must talk again later.
Will you stay in town?
-What?
You won't be travelling around
the world or anything?   -No.
My sister is sick, so I'll stay here.
See ya.
What did Stefan Lindberg say?
Nothing, but there's something about him.
We'll monitor him.
You have to see this.
These two schizophrenics in Copenhagen
lived here and there.
The murders were
respectively here and there.
The postman was killed
in the vestibule of the perpetrator.
Lasse lived here ...
walked to the bus stop, took the bus ...
got out, walked through
the park to practice ...
sat waiting in the waiting room and
killed Fernskog in the consulting room.
He made the appointment
with Fernskog eight weeks ago.
It was planned.
-Or worse.
Bjørn announced
he knew his kidnapper.
Maybe Brammer and Ekwall
weren't symbols.
You mean
he chose them?
Gry see if there is a connection
among the victims.
Have they found Lasse' apartment?
-It is being investigated.
The four officers were acquitted.
The statement called for restraint.
Last year, four immigrants
were convicted of assault ...
although wasn't certain
who the perpetrator was.
Jesper Anderson, you follow
the growth of organized crime.
What does this sentence mean?
-This is a serious matter.
This sends the wrong signal.
-Explain.
We work with young people
and try to build trust.
But after such a verdict
there isn't anthing left.
This is compared with the trial
of the four immigrants last year.
I understand it happens.
It appears again
we aren't equal before the law.
That's a problem.
Both for the police and for society
deserving of our attention.
Thank you, Jesper Anderson.
Lucky, I wasn't there.
-We're going to appeal.
It doesn't help.
-It's all we can do.
Not you, no. If something's gonna happen,
you have to do it yourself.
Where you going?
-On the street, with my friends.
Stay away from them.
Saif, stay home.
We're urging the sender
of the package to contact us.
That does nothing. Anything else?
-Navid?
He swallowed clozapine.
Looks like he followed the dosage.
Get it analysed.
It was in his apartment.
Properly signed.
-But not by him.
The pen in the flat has
various fingerprints.
Do you know who?
-Not yet.
It's a small hand.
Not an adult.
Someone with the initials AB.
Charlotte Söringer. Am I interrupting?
-No.
I have found something in Göran's belongings.
-What have you found?
An archive.
It's easier if you just look.
I'll come right away.
-Great.
Charlotte Söringer found something.
-What then?
An archive. I'm going there now.
-Great.
This he called his black archive.
With all complaints
that were filed against him.
Legal correspondence.
Tenants Associations, the environmental service.
People who had a case against him.
There is also a folder of hate mail.
Can you do something with?
-I'll have someone look at it.
Do you have to go right back?
-Yes.
He's leaving. We'll follow him.
Martin.
-Where are you?
At Charlotte Söringer's.
-Still? Why?
I'll be there in about twenty minutes.
-Did she have any news for us?
I've got an archive.
-Did it take so long to get that?
I'm coming. See you soon.
How does it feel to cheat on your wife?
I remember what Göran did.
This isn't the first time, right?
It's some time ago.
Take care of yourself.
Did I miss something?
-No.
The cameras at Lasse' apartment
haven't yielded anything.
We don't need to see Lasse.
I think he never went out the door.
Our man also avoided the cameras.
He didn't stand in front of it.
Stop. Stop. Go back.
There. She turns around
when she sees the officer.
That might be his roommate.
-Lasse said nothing about a roommate.
According to the lab, the drugs of
all four are placebos.
They didn't swallow anything
for schizophrenia for months.
Thank you.
The Göran Söringer archive.
Go through them with Navid and see if
you find a name in the investigation.
Can I see her again?
See that sign?
-Yes.
Ellborns' Fur.
The windows were smashed three times.
Red paint splashed everywhere.
And what did the police do?
Vandalism isn't a priority.
-For me it is.
But I'm talking about us.
Is that all?
The images are
kept only for 48 hours.
I'll send someone to issue a citation.
-Why?
The camera in the window is illegal.
-No way.
Wasn't that a joke?
-She never makes jokes.
I'll see what I can do.
Are there any rules you don't follow?
-Why?
I'm just wondering.
Rules are there to be followed.
You mean the camera?
That's illegal.
He's helping us.
-Maybe.
He wants to help us.
He was helpful.
And then you'd
condone anything?
I don't mean that.
If anyone wants to help us, you'd
prosecute him for something else.
Why not?
You just don't.
These are unwritten rules.
I don't know.
It's me. I'm on my way home.
Can we eat together?
Yes, all together. For a change.
That would be great.
I'm coming home.
Saga sends her greetings.
Why did you say that?
I didn't send greetings to her.
But I had to do it.
Is that an unwritten rule?
I'm going home. Call me if Johan
finds something on the video.
A murderer lives near you?
-Nice, right?
The addresses of psychiatric patients.
What is wrong with you? Is that legal?
I asked just one question.
He just wants people to be afraid.
He just wants to identify
what the problems are.
Not every psychiatric patient
is a potential killer.
That was so this morning
in four cases.
The parents of the boy
who killed the postman ...
have been trying for weeks
to get their son committed.
We need to write about that.
You don't decide what we write.
-No, the TT does.
You are a dork
he's making use of.
That's better than being
an ordinary fool. Or is it?
Please delet my name
if you update this nonsense.
Glad you're here.
This is the fur shop's video.
Lasse Jönsson is nowhere to be seen.
But his potential roommate
is there three times.
Here.
That's all.
We must know who that is.
-This is Anja Björk.
She disappeared two days ago
in Copenhagen.
Anja Björk.
-Are we going to find her?
Keep it quiet that she's involved in
this investigation. Otherwise she's at risk.
This had already been cleaned.
-I know.
Is it so difficult to ask
him to do something ?
He finds it difficult
to adapt.
And so must we adapt?
You don't notice he's here.
-Exactly.
The twins help more than him.
What would happen if you
placed damands on him?
No idea.
Give him some time.
And as long as we
still keep "Hotel Rohde" open?
For me it's new too.
Give him a chance.
Is dinner ready?
August, the door bell.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Does Martin Rohde live here?
Is he home?
What is it?
-I know who the girl is.
Her name is Anja Björk, 14 years old,
ran away from home.
We're about to eat. Do
you want to eat here?
We have no time.
-Yes.
And this is faster than just going to
the supermarket. We're eating 'biksemad'.
Hash.
This is Carl, Johanne and Nikolai.
The young man staring
at you is August.
Mette know already.
Aren't you going to greet
my colleague here?
Charlotte Söringer gave me this.
-That was nice of her.
Sit down.
You can get the recipe.
-No, it wasn't good.
Just leave it on the plate.
I also want to leave it.
-You just eat what's on your plate.
Why are you looking at me like that?
-I'm not.
August is a fan of the TT.
Not because of what he does.
The murders and stuff.
But he highlights important
problems. He's a genius.
He has planned
everything extremely well.
He's no genius.
-That is just what you see.
I know nobody like him.
Exactly. He's Michelangelo,
while the others work with finger paints.
That's a good comparison.
So you're a fan?
I understand him.
I understand how he thinks.
We're coming.
Anja Björk's mother
is en route to the office.
Nice to meet you, Saga.
Too bad you didn't like it.
Thanks for the food.
See you later.
That's all I can do for you.
She can still come home?
-Yes, I promise.
You can't promise. We'll do
our best, but we can't promise anything.
Will you make further contact?
You know sometimes what you say?
-What?
Do you know what you say?
We can't promise
she'll come back. She may be dead.
Eight days ago she was alive.
-Therefore, she can now be dead.
30 percent of all people
who disappear, don't come back.
I know.
And I think they
know that too.
But sometimes you have to tell people
what they want to hear ...
even if it isn't true.
Martin, wait. So people
sometimes want to be lied to?
Yes sometimes people want
to be told a lie.
What do we say
if she is dead? You promised.
Now you're getting on my nerves.
-Oh yeah?
But Anja ...
-What about her?
She isn't the only one who knows him.
-No, but he doesn't says anything.
Maybe we'e asking
the wrong questions.
I want to talk about Anja.
She stayed with you.
Did you like her?
She signed for you.
The man you killed for
has done this.
And this.
He'll do the same to Anja
if we don't catch him.
Do you want that?
If we catch him, Anja is safe.
But we need to know
what he looks like. What does he look like?
Lasse, what does he look like?
He is tall, with blue eyes, plaid
coat, hat, scarf and gloves.
What did you say?
Tall, blue eyes, plaid jacket ...
hat, scarf and gloves.
You must speak louder.
-Tall, blue eyes, plaid jacket ...
and gloves.
-But ...
He's tall, he has brown hair,
he wears one scarf and gloves.
He is tall, with blue eyes, he wears
a plaid jacket and gloves.
That's him. She has seen him.
-He isn't on the other videos.
He avoids the cameras.
No. He doesn't know Anja's a
threat. We need to find her.
Every officer in the region
is looking for her.
Does Anja's father where she is?
-He had no idea.
We need to find her.
-You can't look everywhere.
You can't, and you can't go
everywhere. Do you hear me?
Are you Daniel?
Daniel Ferbé?
-Yes.
What the hell is that?
The stone was thrown through my window.
I'm Mark Bolin.
Perhaps you recognize my name.
You have just published my address.
Relax, I won't hit you.
I wanted to tell you
the problems your articles cause.
That's sad.
But I just write.
I'm not responsible
for what people do.
Jesus, that's pretty easy.
You don't care about the consequences.
Good luck in life.
Good luck.
One more. Do you want another one?
-Don't you want something stronger?
You recognize me?
Oh yes. We had sex.
Right.
Anton Cederlund.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Do you want a drink?
-I gotta eat something first.
First?
-If we are going to have sex.
I haven't eaten all day.
That was Saga Norén,
Malmö CID.
She is special.
Occasionally I want to shake her.
But she has something special.
We're a good team.
Nice of her to bring your wallet.
Didn't you not notice
you lost it?
No, so.
Who is Charlotte?
Charlotte is one of
the property owners.
She paid the twenty million.
Do you know you're super sexy?
We see Anja Björk on corner
of Adelgata and Östergata. Over.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Well. I'm coming.
I've got to go.
Henning?
Are you drunk?
Yes, a little.
How'd you know?
I heard the verdict.
Did you speak to Lillian?
Yes, I have spoken to her.
What did she say?
No. Nothing I want to hear.
Let go but, Saif.
It's late.
I understand you're disappointed.
We did what was right.
-You, yes. I didn't.
We'll file in appeal. We will go
to the media, talk with journalists.
That doesn't help.
Yes. We live Denmark.
Here it's better.
You are lost your son
and they weren't punished.
Listen. You solve nothing
with hatred and revenge.
I want you behind this.
You mean everything to me, Saif.
I suppose so.
Your brother didn't listen. He went
his own way and now we've lost him.
You won't get rid of me.
I feel I've already lost you.
That's how it feels sometimes.
Saif?
-I gotta go.
Remember him?
Did he shoot you?
If you draw, I'll pick him up.
Will I die?
No.
Anything else?
We found nothing in the garage.
How's Anja?
She died 20 minutes ago.
Did she?
-Yes.
Really?
-She drew that.
D'you see who it is?
It's Stefan Lindberg.
Don't you see?
His eyes.