previously...
Thanks for your cooperation.
-I'm done with you.
I agree.
Each fire rescues a child.
All of them can survive.
"Thanks for the help."
-Milos, come right out.
I haven't had sex with your son.
August and I haven't had sex.
You don't work. What are your plans?
-The plan isn't to have a plan.
I'm pregnant.
-Come here.
Have you done it with Charlotte?
Why was that?
Do you need it? Order in your life?
Sorry. It's too private.
I love you, Mette.
Have you never lived with
a boyfriend? Why not?
I'm no good as a friend.
-You can't know that.
I am Emil.
It explains a lot
if he is in the police.
He could get riot gear
and a police car.
The taser came from police storage.
He has knowledge of explosives.
Did you see who put down the wine?
You said you recognized him.
Look at the pictures.
Be careful of the car.
Why did he kill Daniel?
-He didn't need him anymore.
That isn't enough. Kerstin, Monique,
Emil Henning, Bjørn and Daniel.
A link between them.
Andersson's been home 20 minutes now.
We can go inside.
Why am I here?
-Why do you think?
No idea, but I know
what happened at those times.
Because you were there?
As I'm in the police. And I know
what you two are working on.
Do you need DNA?
Fingerprints? It's fine by me.
I want you to fill out the form.
Anderson's alibis. Check them out.
-I'll get on it right away.
Double check everything.
If it's him, it will likely agree.
Have Johan search
Daniel's computer.
"If it's him"? Aren't you sure?
-You must always remain objective.
Andersson went to therapy after
the death of his two colleagues.
Emil Fernskog.
He relieved him of his position.
-See if he knows the other victims.
We'll check out Jesper's
psychological dossier. Ready?
Does Mette like you living with me?
-Probably, okay.
Does she think you're having sex with me?
-No.
Why not?
-You're not my type.
Do you have a type? Charlotte and Mette
are quite different. Do you want to separate?
No. It'll be okay.
-Have you reconciled?
So you've been unfaithful?
-What are you doing?
Talking.
As colleagues do.
You have no talent for it,
So don't.
Do I irritate you now?
-No.
But sometimes?
-Sometimes you're very annoying, yes.
More than other people?
-Now and then.
You don't care anyway
what other people think of you?
Well. It's important to me
how you feel about me.
Is Mette unfaithful to you too?
-No.
I read, in unhappy relationships both
parties often seek solace outside.
We aren't unhappy.
-Why are you weird?
Does it really matter to you
what I think about you?
Then you must stop now. Thank you.
I have hardly slept
since it happened.
I keep seeing all that blood,
and him and the sword ...
I don't know how I can work here.
-We want a file.
We don't have one.
It was his first visit.
Not Lasse Jönsson's.
But Jesper Andersson's.
That name means nothing to me.
It was a while ago.
Jesper Andersson. His last session
with Emil was five years ago.
I didn't work here then.
-We want his file.
I can't give it to you.
-Yes, you can.
I may not.
For offenses punishable by more than 1 year
imprisonment voids privacy protection.
You know that
as a medical secretary?
You still doubt whether it's him?
-I won't say.
Because you want to be 100% sure?
-I want to be sure only when there is certainty.
If it's him, he knows we have no DNA
or fingerprints. He's good.
We now know his relationship
to Emil and Henning.
Three more.
Maybe he knows Ekwall from work.
Andersson's back in the
interrogation room. His lawyer too.
Our subject has complete control.
Why does he need help?
Because we are super good.
-Not in his world. Not according to him.
Why would he murder a homeless
person, a politician and a whore ...
manipulate schizophrenics
and threaten the lives of children?
Talk about the death of your colleagues.
-I'd like to talk about that.
It was a joint Danish-Swedish operation
against a motorcycle gang.
We had the building surrounded
and waited for a signal.
The Danes didn't search the building
from the other side.
We were shot at
and two of my colleagues were killed.
You hold the Danish police
responsible for their death.
You mean they actually
had to die?
I never said that.
You said that on August 23
to your psychologist.
That was less than a month
after they were shot.
Jesper was going to a psychologist
because of just those types of thoughts.
You are then transferred.
-That was the right decision.
That wasn't your opinion at the time.
-Now yes, now I've put it in perspective.
What do you think about your divorce
Now you've put it in perspective?
I understand why Maria left. I was
angry, I was full of hate.
I was selfish, unsympathetic.
Now you're a considerably self-aware,
middle aged man.
Do you live with someone?
-No.
Why not?
-Sorry, but where is this going?
Tholstrup Henning was one of the
Danes who participated in the operation.
Wasn't the same Henning Tholstrup
just acquitted of negligence?
I know. I was there.
-Then you know ...
Then you know Henning was shot
day before yesterday.
You spoke on TV about the verdict.
In Danish.
-Yes.
I am bilingual. It's very useful
in my work.
You said we aren't equal
before the law.
That's what the perpetrator wanted
to show with his first victims.
Is that a problem?
There are editors who've written
the same thing. Are they sitting here?
Then do you have anything else to present.
Such a motive, or evidence.
Three of his alibis are confirmed.
Ekwall was kidnapped when he was at
an information evening in Copenhagen.
When the bottles were distributed,
he was in a youth club in Rosengård.
The staff confirms that.
When Bjørn was kidnapped,
he was working in a school.
We don't know what time Bjørn was
kidnapped, but he was there at 7:30 pm.
Bjørn was alone a little after 7:00pm.
Jesper worked with Lennart Fransson
during the 2001 weapons amnesty.
Fransson registered the taser. We
don't know if he passed it to him.
And Ferbé's computer?
-It's still missing.
The lock was forced. Break-in.
-Have we asked to arrest him?
True to his profile.
Extremely focused on a project.
No relationship. Successful in his work.
Experienced a traumatic event.
This gets us no further.
-We try it again.
Sonja Lindberg has pointed you out.
How do you explain that?
I don't know Sonja Lindberg.
She is one of the homeless who
was poisoned. She has pointed you out.
She's mistaken.
-She viewed 15 pictures.
She wasn't mistaken.
She picked you out immediately.
She recognized you and you know her.
Is that the woman in a comma?
Until yesterday, yes.
And is she trustworthy?
-There isn't anyhing wrong with her eyes.
I've heard
she was homeless for a long time ...
and that, sorry to say,
not entirely reliable.
And, Jesper has an alibi for
the time the wine was deposited.
But have you
already checked.
Hans gives up.
-Why?
He wants to go back to Gothenburg.
Closer to the children.
I can understand that.
It is one hour by plane and three
by train. How close do you have to get?
You'll miss him.
-I don't know.
The prosecutor authorized remand.
-On what grounds?
Think about what you'd prefer
to do in the next 72 hours.
The prosecutor has given us three days.
Three days root into your life.
And we will find out
what you're hiding.
No district court in the world
would you hold on to those grounds.
You also said no
prosecutor would do that?
It's difficult to clear my name.
The press will devour me.
In 72 hours you'll befree. Then we'll see
how we cope with the press.
Three days. They'll tear me apart.
If you have something to say,
it is good to do so now.
No, nothing.
Thanks for the help.
Say, can I go to the bathroom?
Open it.
Get in.
Get back.
Drive.
How could he have escaped?
-He received help.
He used a key card.
Where did the gun come from?
-He went to the bathroom before he escaped.
Dis someone leave
a weapon there for him?
Check everything. Bank accounts, emails,
phone calls, ex-wife, family.
Leave everything else
and make sure you find the car.
Knock, knock, knock.
Am I interrupting?
-No.
Or rather a little bit, yes.
I was going to send the information, but then
I wanted to make sure you were around.
What beautiful flowers.
-They are for my mother.
I'm kidding. They are for you.
As I pass by unannounced.
I'll get a vase. Do you want coffee?
-Please.
No traces of blood or violence.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Jesper has a foundation for young people
that fights crime.
The foundation is registered
to Jesper's address.
It is his foundation, so ...
-They rent a room in the Frihamnen.
What do all these proposals have in common?
-They were filmed.
No computer, no camera, nothing.
We must search his apartment again.
Isn't it strange the photos are
of his ex-wife?
I don't have any of mine.
Look.
Look who's the best man.
Kent Hammar.
Look. This is the garage
Jesper comes in a few seconds.
We thought Kent arrived at that
moment. But look.
This is three minutes earlier.
He is waiting for someone.
-They work together. Anne?
Hammar Kent, born in 1975,
joined the police in 2000.
He rented a room from Jesper.
They knew each other.
When Jesper was in the special unit,
he recommended Kent twice.
He failed the test both times.
-He was best man at Jesper's wedding.
Colleagues confirm
they're good friends.
That explains Jesper's alibis.
-We'll look at Kent's roster.
So we had the right man.
Now you know something more of it.
Call me if you're interested.
Thank you. It looks fascinating.
I must thank you.
If only for your company.
Are you okay?
What's going on?
I've got cramps.
-Have you had them previously?
I'm pregnant.
Then it's clear.
You must go to the hospital. Now.
My car is downstairs.
Hammar used his credit card.
-Where?
Statoil Bunkeflostrand.
He rented a car.
Do they know the license plate?
-There's a GPS tracking system.
Do you know where they are?
-Yes.
Hi, honey.
Where are you? I'll be right there.
Mette's gone to the hospital.
There's something to do with the child.
She's pregnant. I have to go.
Good luck.
Wasn't he neutered?
They're in the third row.
Third car from the front.
There is little space. Lots of people.
We'll wait for a while.
I gotta pee.
Hammar's left the car.
Anne and Navid, pick him up.
Jesper will wonder why he stays.
-We'll get him.
Put your weapon down.
Feel a pulse?
-He's alive. Take him to the car.
Police. Relax.
There's an ambulance.
How are you?
-I'm in a lot of pain.
What happened?
We had lunch and suddenly I got
bad cramps twice. It hurts so much.
And what about ...
-I don't know.
I'm here with you,
So it'll be okay, okay?
Who are you?
-Martin. Mette's husband.
Hi, I'm Tom.
I'm her doctor here in the hospital.
The ultrasound has told us two things.
As far as we can see the children
are okay. And you have kidney stones.
Children?
You mean like twins?
There are two of each.
Two children and two stones.
What do we do with the stones?
Sometimes you can fix it
by drinking a lot of water.
Then peeing them out.
We can't crush them now.
If necessary, we go inside
with a tube and we can fish them out.
But first we start drinking and
urination, take painkillers and thumbs up.
Shall we meet again? Good.
Two there.
How can we save?
-Just now I have too much pain to talk.
Of course.
How old can they be?
-Sixteen, maybe seventeen.
Jesper received a youth award
two years ago.
He's done a good job.
He didn't work with young people
to search for more victims.
It was intended as a counterweight.
Both are active. Sadistic.
Jesper over Hammar.
The man we seek, didn't enjoy
hurting people.
They aren't him.
Are we really sure?
Then we're back to square one.
-I 'm going to tell the others.
Jesper Andersson and Kent Hammar
aren't the men we're seeking.
Andersson didn't know all the victims.
And his profile is wrong.
Maybe they know Hammar.
-What is wrong then?
Our offender has no partner.
A partner poses a risk.
But Sonja Lindberg identified him?
She was on their videos.
They sexually abused her.
So we're not finished with the case.
Why are you sitting?
We have a break.
A coffee-break.
What are you talking about?
About nothing in particular.
Just small talk.
I'm not feeling well.
How's Mette?
Better.
She'll stay for some more monitoring.
But she'll come home tonight.
Fine.
How's it this gone?
Well. The two older ones are watching TV
and Nikolai is asleep.
Nice. Thanks for your help.
There is bread and coffee in the kitchen.
Are you getting divorced?
It started that way with mom.
You no longer slept at home.
I don't know if you didn't want
to or if she didn't allow you.
I was one year younger
than the twins when you left.
You came back on my
tenth birthday with a bicycle.
I did occasionally stop by.
Not that I can remember.
It seemed better to keep a distance.
You were very angry,
and your mother was angry.
Then I met Julie and began a new life.
I felt ...
I could no longer
interfere with you.
That would be for me to decide.
You know why you stayed away?
Because you always chose
the path of least resistance.
You get used to in.
And you stay that way.
That's how I understand it.
Would you have preferred I was there?
-Yes. For a while then.
But after all I care about you.
I threw the bike into the canal.
-Did you really do that?
The next day.
If you love Mette and you don't
want a divorce, why are you acting weird?
Because ...
I thought ...
I really thought I needed it.
And I had to prove something.
And I wanted to make sure
I'd made the right choice.
And you're back there now?
-Yes.
In some respects you are
the dumbest man I know.
Why do you live here?
-To see if I really mean nothing to you.
Was that it?
-What was I supposed to think?
You just went away.
I'm glad you came here
to live. I am happy.
I've talked about it with Frida.
on the Internet.
She said I had to talk to you about it.
That is a wise girl.
Saga. Kerstin Ekwall was a prosecutor
before she went into local politics.
I've reviewed at her won, lost and discontinued cases.
One is very interesting.
Are you listening?
In 2001 there was a collision on the bridge.
A woman and her son were killed.
The other car drove away.
Later it appeared it had been
reported stolen.
There was no evidence
the owner drove it that night.
I remember. She suspected
Sixten Rockstad. But he wasn't prosecuted.
Ekwall ordered an investigation.
The husband of dead woman was a policeman.
The Danish elite police.
Where are you?
-Home.
You shouldn't be. It's not Andersson.
But we are on to something.
Mette is doing well.
She has kidney stones.
You probably wanted to know.
I wanted to know, yes. Thank you.
When can you come in?
Now. Soon. At once.
-Nice.
Was that Saga ?
-Yes.
About Saga and me ...
-I already know.
She said nothing happened.
So everything's fine.
Okay.
Are you saying 'okay'? You sound surprised.
No, you know. I wanted to tell you
yesterday I was working at Saga's.
I know.
-She threw me out.
Because you didn't like
how we treated each other.
I gotta go. Can we continue talking?
I thought you should know.
Saga, you have a visitor.
Who then?
-Anton "What's his name".
What are you doing?
How are you?
-Good.
What are you doing?
-These are for you.
Why?
We started in the wrong way.
With sex.
And I want to ...
I want to turn back time.
Get to know you.
Why?
Because I feel you're worthwhile
to get to know.
Can we go out one more time together
to eat? Just food.
You mean without sex?
-Yes. Without sex.
Didn't you like it?
-Yes. That's not it.
I want to see if it can be more.
There you are again. Hello.
Think about it.
What are you to think about?
-Listen. Do you know this man?
This is Jens. I've worked
with him for years.
Was he a good cop?
-The best.
He could have gone far.
What happened?
-His wife and child were killed.
He never got over that.
He was fired and lost everything.
Why are we talking about Jens?
Would he be able to commit a murder
without leaving a trace?
Freezing a woman's body?
Provoking a riot?
It isn't him, Saga.
Ekwall didn't prosecute anyone
after the accident.
That may well be, but he's dead.
He blew out his brains.
He's in Charlotte Söringer's archive.
In 2004, he was put in one of their
homes. Then he threatened them.
Gry didn't look further because he's dead.
-Logical.
Are you serious about this now?
-Why shouldn't I be?
Because he's dead. He blew out
his brains in his caravan.
I've seen him.
You mean he literally
he shot his head off?
Why?
-Didn't he have a face anymore?
It's someone taking vengeance on
Jens' behalf.
After five years? Maybe it looked bad
or because he was a policeman, but ...
I see no fingerprints
or DNA samples were taken.
He sat in his caravan.
He had blown out his brains.
There was a farewell letter
in his own handwriting.
Isn't there an autopsy report?
-There was no investigation.
Why not?
-The cause of death was obvious, right?
Don't you do an investigation for a suicide?
-Yes, but this was a colleague.
Let the poor man rest in peace.
I'll take it with me.
I've talked with August.
I'd a feeling more went on
when he was with you.
Do you remember the conversation
with Anja's mother?
That you sometimes say what people
want to hear? Are you doing that now?
And now neither.
You'll learn Jens' wife was
Swedish.
She wanted to visit her parents
with her child.
They were on the bridge
when they were hit by a car.
There was no evidence
it was Rockstad.
But when Jens wants revenge ...
Or, someone else.
Why didn't he kill
Rockstad?
Thank you.
Rockstad died in Monaco.
Drunk driving.
Well, do you call that poetic justice.
Jens asked if he could
investigate the accident.
To us in any case.
Sweden refused each time.
A note about Jens.
Is always tardy, places colleagues
in danger, suspected of drug use ...
requirement for transfer to desk duty,
psychological evaluation.
Signed by police union representative.
Do you know who that was?
-Yes.
Henning Tholstrup.
Daniel was investigating the accident.
He was at the same festival too.
As who?
-Sixten Rockstad. In Copenhagen.
He asked the staff how drinks
Rockstad had.
And whether he got in to his car
behind the wheel.
Did he complete his research?
-I don't know.
He suddenly got an offer from
Stockholm. Good job, good income.
He left immediately.
-Bribery.
It isn't inconceivable
what you have about Daniel.
As far as I know, he was completely
lacked moral scruples.
I'll miss him.
Thanks for your help.
Saga, Martin, I
read the information on Jens.
There was a report recommending he
be relieved from his duties ...
and even doubts about his fitness
as an officer.
But the report is missing.
Do you know the name of his psychologist?
-When was that?
Late autumn 2003.
Lately he had completely given
up trying at work.
His imminent dismissal is again
referred to in the report.
But there's no indication
who drafted the report.
What did Emil Fernskog do in 2003?
He had a practice in Copenhagen and
transferred to Sweden the following year.
Andersson went there see to him.
Did Fernskog sometimes work
with traumatized officers?
Sonja Lindberg was found.
She'll be here in about five minutes.
I will put them in a vase?
What did Anton want?
He wants to take me out to dinner.
He gives you flowers
and asks you to dinner?
Yes. Weird, right?
Why do you find that weird?
I read men do that when they
want sex. But we already had sex.
Where did you read that?
-Isn't it so?
No. Or yes. Sometimes.
What are you doing?
As Sonja Lindberg is ...
-I'm talking about Anton.
I don't know.
You should do it. He likes you.
-How is it possible? He doesn't know me.
No, that's true.
Do you know who that is?
He was like my brother.
Stefan saved me.
My brother is.
I wait for him where I live now.
This man ...
Where did he save you?
Someone picked up my stuff.
He picked up my stuff all the time.
He told him to stop,
and when he hit him.
So Jens hit the man who picked up
your stuff?
Later he hit him. Very, much
worse than I got. Repeatedly.
Remember the man's name?
His name was Bjørn. Like the animal.
Is this him?
He hit him.
He hit everyone.
Thank you.
You have helped us a lot.
Where is my brother?
You know, unfortunately.
She can go.
Do you have a name?
The business where the fire broke
out is connected to a group: Pica.
Do you know who is the CEO?
No idea.
Ida Rockstad. Sixten's mother.
I've talked with my dad.
-Was it good?
Better than I expected.
-Does he feel guilty?
Not really. But it was good. Thank you.
-Take me out to dinner.
Deal. Say where and when.
-You can bet it'll be expensive.
I thought you were asleep.
I'm looking after the children
I'm stuck.
Are you all right?
Remember Jens?
-Yes. What happened to him?
Saga thinks he's still alive.
You can't.
I know it sounds crazy,
but there's every indication he is.
I'll go.
-You may as well stay.
Are you serious?
Today I thought I was going to lose
the child, I was almost relieved.
I'm not sure I want more children.
Now I felt like I didn't have
the right to take that decision.
Can we handle it, more kids?
If we can manage each other,
it can work.
Can we do it together?
We need to spread out the photos.
The whole area is full of them.
He must have changed his appearance.
-I know.
You know what's worse?
-No. What then?
Five years ago he staged his suicide,
his plans have been long in the works.
Do you think he is finished now, after Daniel?
-Why not?
It isn't enough. He isn't finished.