previously...
Working so late?
-I'll find you.
This is Jens. He was my colleague.
He committed suicide.
His wife and child died
in a car accident.
I read no fingerprints
or DNA were taken.
Saga thinks he's still alive.
His wife and son were killed. He thinks
mistakes were made in the investigation.
So all this talk of his about opening
people's eyes doesn't mean anything?
Sometimes you tell people what
they want to hear. Even if it isn't true.
So sometimes people want you to lie to them?
-Yes, Saga, sometimes they want you to lie.
Sebastian Sandstrod.
-Do you have children?
I've had one. One son.
I'm back on top come.
Her name was Mikaela.
Mikaela wanted a divorce.
She met another guy.
The other man was me.
He knows it was you.
Help.
I wouldn't lie to Hans. I haven't
told him about you and Mikaela.
When was that?
-The day before yesterday. In the chat room.
We haven't chatted.
The "Frida" who I chatted to,
wasn't Frida.
Saga, come on.
-It is Jens.
He's not after Mette and the children,
he's after you.
Wait here.
-What is it?
Where are the guards?
-Perhaps inside.
That wasn't the intention.
-Call them. You go inside.
Martin? Come here.
The ambulance is on its way.
Don't talk.
He's got August.
Y E. ..
-Y, E.
Five, seven.
-Five, seven.
Yes. Y, E, five, seven.
Dark blue.
-Dark blue.
Y, E, five, seven. Dark blue.
All cars, we looking for his dark blue
car. The license plate starts with YE 57.
I repeat: YE 57.
What happened?
-He ... He's got August.
Where are we going?
What are you doing?
My son would've been seventeen now.
His name was Rasmus.
How old are you?
-I'll be twenty soon.
You could've been friends.
Just like your father and me.
Everything was different.
What are you doing?
With you?
What has Martin done?
You call him that?
Not 'Daddy'?
Does it matter?
Haven't you ever felt everything turned
out to be different than you thought?
That the people supposed to help you,
aren't there.
Authorities and agencies that are
supposed to protect you, don't.
That friends ...
people you consider
as friends, cheat you.
It is a shocking experience.
A real revelation.
What has he done?
Is he a good father?
He wants to be..
And is he ideal?
He knows he's not perfect ...
but he's as good as he can be.
That's a wise observation.
-What did he do?
Here we are.
Can you let me go?
I don't understand.
It looks okay. The bullet in your side
didn't hit any vital organs.
And your blood levels
are almost back to normal.
You were lucky.
Can you squeeze my fingers?
Can you squeeze harder?
The nerve and muscle damage
should be investigated further.
I can't.
What do you say?
-I need to work.
You've lost a lot of blood.
-You said my levels were normal.
That they were almost normal.
Your body has had a big hit.
I feel good.
Thanks to your adrenaline
and my painkillers. You stay right here.
Europol and Interpol were informed. His photo
is in the media. We'll do everything.
Martin, are you listening to me?
Yes. What about you and your team?
Anything found in the basement?
No. Everything is now in Malmö.
They're working as fast as they can.
And the license plate?
-We're working on them. Excuse me.
I gotta do something.
-What?
No idea. I'm going crazy waiting.
-Your judgment wouldn't be objective.
You put me on the investigation. Or
I'll quit and find the bastard anyway.
That was Saga.
How is she?
-Pretty good. She wants me to come.
How are you?
-Good.
I have nerve and muscle damage in my arm,
but my vital organs are intact.
But how are you?
-Good.
I've got clothes from Mette.
Nice. Can you help me with the stockings?
Have the doctors actually said
you could in your condition?
They said you had to stay?
-Yes. How is the license plate?
They are working on it. You better stay.
-He has August.
Have you any idea where he can be?
-No, but he's still alive.
How do you know?
-He wants Martin to suffer as he suffers.
That's why he doesn't kill August.
Why should Martin suffer?
-Put the zipper closed.
You think he wants to kill August?
-In the end. Are you here with the car?
Why does he do this?
You were friends.
Why is he doing this to us?
Because I went to bed
with Mikaela.
With his wife?
You slept with his wife?
She wanted to leave him.
They had a fight.
She ran away. So she was on the bridge.
When they are killed.
-After that, you practically lived with him.
He didn't know then.
He found out only much later ...
I'm so sorry, Mette.
I am so sorry for what you all
had to endure. I'm so sorry.
Now it's just about August.
Are you okay?
-I've been given painkillers and blood.
I feel some pain, but
otherwise I feel good.
It could have ended much worse.
-Shall we go?
You're bleeding.
-I know.
Everything's gone wrong and it's all my fault.
-Yes, you seem to think that.
I think she'll leave me.
-Mette?
You should have seen her when I
told her about Mikaela and me.
You hadn't already.
-I haven't.
She sees sides of me
she didn't know.
Why did you tell her?
-I had to.
He locked her and the children in the house
in with a grenade. She had to know why.
I've been thinking.
I imagine that Jens
decided to do everything ...
when he read the notebooks.
You don't know.
-Even I had abandoned him.
Can you check on this? That too
isn't connected to this.
Hey, how are you?
-Good. How are you?
I'm okay, but there's a lot.
What have you found so far?
-The link isn't always clear.
All this is related to the bridge,
the outage and the women.
There are the homeless,
The cards and poison ...
the schizophrenics,
Here is the gang in Nørrebro ...
the bus companies and
companies who used child labour.
The things here we haven't
linked to the five problems.
It's all over the map ...
as well as print-outs, schedules,
pictures, formulas, drawings ...
We don't know whether all this
is related to anything.
He has something planned for August,
So among all this, we should find something.
There are 103 cars that begin
with YE 57 and are dark blue.
82 are registered
in Jutland and Fynen.
None are reported stolen. Then there are
21 on Zealand and 15 in Copenhagen.
And none reported as stolen?
-We'll start in Copenhagen.
Wait a minute. I have to check.
Anne, that parking ticket?
Here. This is a parking ticket on the day
before everything began on the bridge.
Let's see.
There. Margrethe Helstad.
Bakkegårds Allée, Copenhagen.
I know where that is.
Yes. He was here
a few weeks ago.
To Margrethe Helstad?
-He comes several times a year.
Why?
To visit her.
I think he's her cousin.
I know it's early,
but we have to talk to her.
Of course. She doesn't sleep much.
Good morning Margrethe,
You have a visitor.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
They are the police.
They want to ask you something.
Do you know this man?
He's here sometimes. He comes to visit.
We know,
but why is he here?
He's my father.
No, he's not.
-Who are you?
It's a home
for the demented elderly?
Is there anyone else
who knows anything about her?
I'm sorry, but I don't think so.
I think Jens plans a special vengeance.
How exactly did his son die?
He died in the collision
on the bridge and then drowned.
With Saga. It's the car.
Trace it.
We need to trace that car.
Okay. Saga, we're going.
We go straight along the road.
They found the car.
Beside Bispebjerg Cemetery.
Mikaela is buried here.
-And the son?
He was never found.
-But he was declared dead?
Did you find anything?
-No.
WAs the trunk checked?
-Not yet.
Martin, Saga, come HERE.
Lillian, yes.
What is this?
-There is a gravedigger.
Nothing there.
Someone tried to get into Sandstrod's home .
-Who?
We don't know, but he was arrested.
Here I am again.
There is no point in going.
He knows we know his new name
and follow every clue.
We can ask that person.
-He can't help us.
He makes us run from pillar to post,
so he can work peacefully.
What do we do?
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
That's his mother, Margrethe.
Say that again.
-Margrethe is his mother.
Of whom?
Of Jens. Or Sebastian.
His parents are dead.
His adoptive parents. ln 1991, he reestablished
contact via the adoption agency.
Where did they used to?
-Engmosevej 22 .
Who's the owner there now?
-Hold on.
They are still there.
But I think nobody lives there.
What are you doing?
Suppose we find nothing.
Then we'll continue the search. Come.
-But where to?
I haven't talked to him in years
and then he came to me.
You know I left him when he was little?
We wanted to do something together.
Just him and me. I never thought
that it would turn out like this.
Jens thought of that.
-I know.
And now I'm close to loosing him.
You can't say now
we won't find him.
What should I do if he isn't there?
Where are you?
-We're checking out some information.
Are you alone?
-No, Saga is with me.
I want him to be tried.
I want him dead.
Have you checked on the man at the house?
-Did you hear me? You're a policeman.
If you can't handle this,
you must withdraw.
I can handle it.
If you think you've found something, then call
in and wait for reinforcements, okay?
Jens gave the man 500 DKK
to go to his home.
I'll call you back when we know something.
-Do that.
It looks empty.
Take this.
-I can't.
I'll say nothing.
And if I have to shoot?
-Then we'll invent something.
Do it for me.
Police. Is there anybody home?
Monique Brammer.
It's me.
Jens, damn ...
That was long ago.
It's good you went, I understand.
You should let August go, do you hear me?
You have to punish me.
I'm still to do that?
-I'd like to talk to August.
You can't.
-Why not?
He isn't here.
-What have you done?
He's alive.
I believe we must meet.
Why?
-Because you're right.
I'm mad at you.
I only kidnapped August to get
you to speak to me. Alone.
Where?
-Where are you now?
Engmosevej 22.
Hello, are you still there?
I'm impressed. Monique
Brammer is in the freezer in the garage.
We found her, yes.
-You aren't alone?
Saga is with me.
-Oh yeah? How is she?
Where will we meet?
-I'll call you back in about one minute.
Get in your car,
I'll give you directions.
And perhaps for the sake ...
to avoid any misunderstandings:
you really should just come alone.
One minute.
You don't want to go?
There is no reason to believe
he'll let August go.
His son is dead. He wants to punish you.
He wants to kill August, whatever you do.
I gotta believe I have a chance.
Call in and tell Lillian
we've found Monique.
And don't say anything about my
conversation with Jens. It's important.
You must promise you won't say anything
about my conversation with Jens.
Someone called me and then I left.
You don't know who called me.
I know.
-It's important.
Promise me you'll say nothing, okay?
He's killed everyone
who let him down.
I'm going now.
I'm on my way to the car.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
I want to speak to Lillian.
Where are you?
-On Jagtvej in the direction of Nørrebro.
Go to the roundabout at Skt. Kjeld Plads.
Don't hang up, I want to keep listening to you.
Have you thought about me ...
since my suicide?
I haven't thought about you, no.
-I think about you.
What went through your head
when you went to bed with my wife?
What was your intention?
-I had no intention to do it.
Did you think I'd congratulate you?
My wife and my best friend.
Did you think I'd be happy for you?
No, I didn't.
-Was it easy?
To get her into bed?
Does it go well between you and Mette?
-Why do you ask?
She was very open ...
and responsive, in the last few days.
If things were going well between you, she
probably wouldn't have gone to bed with me.
I'm at the roundabout.
-Take Bryggervang.
Can you see me?
-Maybe.
Park the car on the side.
Across the street is a Toyota.
The key is on the left front tire.
Leave your mobile behind,
There is a new one in the Toyota.
So you don't know where Martin is?
-No.
What about the material
from the basement?
It's Lillian. Saga Norén, here.
May I talk to Martin? He doesn't answer.
-He isn't here.
Where is he?
-I don't know. He left.
Where did he go?
-No idea.
He received a phone call and then
he left. I don't know where he is.
If anything happens, it's your fault.
You can't lie very well.
-I can always do better?
Yes.
How are you?
Where is Martin?
-There isn't here. How are you?
There is still a lot we can't associated
to bring his 'problems'.
Then we need more context.
He has August.
Jens' son died.
Think out loud. Say what comes into your mind.
-His son drowned.
Or was already dead.
-He fell into the water.
Nothing here is related to water.
-He was never found.
Does this help us?
-But how?
The first event was the accident
on the bridge on April 13.
Is there anything
related to April 13?
I checked but found nothing.
Wrong date, wrong month.
Saga, you're bleeding. With Johan.
The trial. Of Henning.
He had no influence,
So he had to plan around it.
The encounter with August in the park.
That was scheduled for a specific time.
Is there anything related to today?
With today? With something recent?
No, nothing.
What are we overlooking?
-Maybe it's nothing about August.
It's here. It must be.
Continue to search.
I know where he is.
I know where August is. Come on.
Have you been inside?
-Yes.
You haven't checked well.
One more time.
Tell me about your colleague,
Saga Norén.    -No
Why not?
-Because I don't want to.
I am so tired of this. I want no more,
Do you understand? You're sick.
You're awfully sick.
Where are you now?
-What do you want?
Go to the Central Station
and go inside.
We couldn't find anything.
-We looked everywhere.
Then we'll look through everything
again. He must be here.
He isn't here. You're mistaken.
Don't you really know where Martin is?
Did he meet with Jens?
Saga, did he meet Jens?
-I think so.
Now what?
-Go to platform two.
There is the Øresundtrein.
Get on it.
Now what? Do I have to go to Sweden?
Are you holding August in Sweden?
Mikaela was on her way to Sweden.
On the bridge. Are you going to throw
him from the bridge, you sick bastard?
Can you hear me?
-Yes.
Sit down.
Well done, Martin.
Relax and enjoy the ride.
I found it.
There's a false wall.
We went
to the dedication of the bridge.
Mikaela ...
Rasmus and I.
Were you there?
We can keep quiet,
if you want.
Why? I need to know why.
Was it because they chose me?
ls it all because they chose me?
-In some ways perhaps.
Did you kill all those people
because your wife left you?
Because my wife left me, I lost
my son, my job and my friends.
How much do you need?
Other people experience loss,
and don't go killing.
I have contemplated suicide.
I stood with the gun in my mouth.
But it wasn't my fault.
Nothing was my fault.
So I decided to hit back.
Is August dead?
You get one chance to save him.
That's more than I received.
Stay sitting.
Good. There too.
Damn it.
No sound. Everyone stay sitting.
We'll get out here. She comes too.
She's not coming.
-You take her.
I am Martin Rohde
of the Danish police.
I want to ask you to sit
and you come along.
Everyone stay. Quiet and calm.
Handcuff her.
She isn't going anywhere.
Do it.
What's this?
Saga Norén, here.
-He's broadcasting again.
Who?
-He, from the bridge.
On sanningnu.se.
Martin is there too.
He must know
we've found August .
He has to know. Call Martin.
Draw your gun.
Where is August?
-It'll cost you to save your son.
Your gun. You don't have much time.
I want you to shoot her.
I won't.
Lillian.
Martin's on the bridge.
Yes. We're heading to Peberholm.
The bridge is closed. We'll detemine
what we can do. Where are you?
The clock is ticking. The chance, August
will survive, isn't increasing.
I won't shot her.
-You don't have to murder her.
You'll be dismissed. Maybe you
be in prison for a few months.
Infliction of injury. Abuse.
Maybe they'll conduct a
trial. It'll cost you something.
But you have to, to save August.
I promise, I'll tell you where he is.
You can find out from me
what you want and what I've done ...
but I've always kept my word.
I told you where Mette
and the children were.
You can still save him.
Isn't it worth it?
Please. Don't shoot, please.
Don't do it, please.
Unfortunately, I have to do.
-Please. Don't shoot.
Martin shot the hostage.
-We have to go there.
Three people are on the working platform,
the train isn't empty ...
No one can go there. Sorry.
I have to go.
-The bridge is closed.
Order it, otherwise you'll lose Martin.
Did you find August ?
She's in shock.
-I see.
You've done exactly what I asked.
Every time.
You deserve to know ...
I lied.
Where is he? Where is August?
He's gone.
What's he doing?
-He put down the detonator.
You'll never know if he suffered ...
if he was afraid, if he cried,
or had a long and painful death.
You will never have a body to
bury, a grave to visit ...
Shut up.
-You 'll always live in uncertainty.
Shut up. Shut up.
A group, ready to pick them up.
Martin, don't.
We've found August.
-That isn't true.
We found him in the garage,
at Engmosevej. Behind the wall.
No, he's not dead. She's lying.
Remember when he called?
When he heard we were there?
He went silent and then he told
us Monique Brammer was there.
So we wouldn't look any further.
-He isn't there. She's lying.
He died somewhere else.
Slowly and painfully.
He's unarmed, this is being
broadcast. Everybody's watching this.
Whatever he did,
You can't shoot him.
If she found him,
why isn't he here?
I was in a hurry
and he had to go to the hospital.
Call him.
Martin wants to talk to him.
You have his mobile.
-He's with people you can call.
He's not there.
You can't talk to him.
Do you really think she's
telling you the truth?
I found him.
-Are you lying?
Are you saying what I want to hear?
-We've found him.
Maybe they found him,
but he still alive?
Yes.
Is he alive?
August is still alive?
Can you say to me
August is really still alive? Can you all
honestly say August is still alive?
Can I come in?
I'll wait outside.
How are you?
I should never have
given you that gun.
Are you serious?
He deserved to die.
He would have won.
You'd be fired from the police,
and end up in jail.
I probably wanted to do it.
I don't know what to say.
-You don't have to say anything. It's okay.
I'm sorry I was late.
You did everything you could.
It wasn't enough.
I let you down.
When is the funeral?
That hasn't been finalized.
Call me when you know.
-I will.
It was nice working with you.
-I liked that too.
Anton here.
-Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
Hey, Saga. How are you?
-Good.
The dinner you
wanted to treat me to. How about now.
Now?
-Yes, now. I've got time.
Where'll we meet?