Presiously...
The power on the bridge failed.
The lights were
out for 45 seconds.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
She is in Sweden or Denmark?
Two women were killed.
The parts were placed on the Øresund
bridge. Someone wants to say something.
May I know whose heart it is.
-There's a problem.
The father's changed his mind.
We can't use the heart.
I got the license plate of the car.
He is Daniel Ferbé from Malmö .
-Journalist?
Do you know Kerstin Ekwall?
-Who?
It skipped.
Please.
Come back. Where you going?
Daniel, are you still there?
Sorry for the drama. It's so difficult
to drown the noise of the media.
I suppose
I now have your full attention.
The women on the bridge
were just the beginning.
This is an exciting time
for all of us.
What are you doing?
Can it wait?
We're on our way.
What is the address? Okay, thanks.
There is information on www.sanningnu.se.
What's that?
-A web address.
Someone knows more than us
about what happened on the bridge.
What'd you have done
if you had a bomb in the car ...
and you knew you had
only five minutes to live?
That wasn't the case.
Let's pretend you thought
you had only five minutes.
I'd try to get out.
-Then it would've exploded.
Five minutes more or less ...
-You know what I'd have done?
I got it.
"Equality before the law, a myth."
in the Danish and Swedish.
"Equality  before the law, a myth."
"The women on the bridge"...
'Women'. Did we announce
there were more than one?
"The women on the bridge
were just the beginning."
"A message to the police.
Listen here."
Sorry for the drama. It is so difficult
to drown the noise of the media.
I guess I ...
You don't eat breakfast?
-Sometimes.
Have you eaten today?
-I eat if I am hungry.
There's a website.
-Two. www.Sandhednu.dk. Same content.
This is from Daniel Ferbé's car.
Look what's on it.
Can't we eat before we
interrogate Daniel?
We won't.
-Why not?
We have special people.
Interrogation experts.
So you don't talk to him?
You don't know what he
has to say? What room is he in?
Room 3.
- Come on.
Hello.
-What am I doing here?
Your car was used last night
for a murder.
I was working all night.
Call my editors.
-We've done that.
We don't believe your car was involved
with what happened. That's why you're here.
I don't know anything about Kerstin Ekwall
or what happened at the bridge.
Maybe you don't think you know.
Sorry, but I can't help you.
I got a ticket to Berlin ...
You're not going anywhere
without our permission.
Is that a joke?
-No, that's no joke.
Come on.
I almost died in that car.
You didn't.
But there was dynamite in the back seat.
Go grab the person who did it.
That's precisely what we doing.
-I don't know anything.
I just want to leave. Please.
If a fool steals my car,
It isn't my problem.
Your problem is the stuff
we found at your home.
Private use.
-What?
For private use.
-It is still allowed.
We want to know why your car
was used in a double murder.
I have no idea.
Shall we try to find
out together?
Interrogators never lie.
-They don't, no.
He'll never confide in us again.
-He doesn't trust us anyway.
How do you know?
-I know the type.
From the article you read in the car?
-I'm just fine.
Have I irritated you?
-No, not yet. Why?
I want a search warrant request.
Or, we'll just take a look now?
You'll get ten minutes in the cafeteria.
Pardon me. Room 32-34?
Christian?
I'm Charlotte Söringer.
-I 'm Ole. Are you a psychologist?
No, but my husband is very ill.
He is in another department.
Without a new heart, he'll die.
The heart of your son.
My son still breathes.
His heart still beats. You can see.
I understand you very well ...
-I want to keep him here. Do you understand?
I understand very well.
But he isn't here anymore. Everything
that made your son who he was, is gone.
You can't use his heart.
It is dramatic for you
to lose a child, but I love my husband.
Unless he gets your son's heart,
he's also dies.
So be it.
Hey, come here.
Listen to this. Johan.
Jørgen, I have a question for you.
Actually, my name isn't Jørgen.
Have you heard, two half
bodies were found on the bridge?
One of them was Monique Brammer,
junkie and prostitute.
I killed her.
The police dropped the case after two
weeks. Does it go so easily in Sweden?
This isn't the right forum ...
You know what the right forum is?
www.sandhednu.dk. Wake up.
This just aired on Danish radio.
Was it tracked?
-Prepaid card.
The voice on the CD sounded different.
-Is it a group?
He keeps saying 'I '
"I killed them."
A group claims they're more than
one, because it increases the terror.
I'm going to reopen
Monique's case.
Daniel Ferbé is allowed to leave
after the search of his house.
We're going to shadow him.
And the websites?
We try to locate the server,
but it doesn't even show an lP address.
Both links are available
on the websites of most newspapers.
There are things
only the killer could know.
Does he brag?
On the radio, he had
a clear message:
"Not everyone is equal before the law."
-That is correct.
You won't repeat that.
-That doesn't make it any less true.
What do we think?
He says those women
were just the beginning.
And he will point out five problems.
If inequality was the first,
there are four left. The question is what.
According to a website the other corpse
on the bridge was a Danish prostitute.
The police have confirmed this.
The motive for the murder, according to
the website is "Inequality before the law".
You've talked to the donor's father.
He had to know
his son could save my husband.
That wasn't a good idea.
-Do you think I liked it?
Nothing happened.
He is brain dead.
Just pull the plug out.
Your husband isn't the only patient.
Suppose it was your son.
Hypothetical situations
don't interest me.
I have no children. I have Göran
and I don't want to lose him.
The coroner wants
to be ready today.
And I'll see how Daniel's
car is. Do you have an address?
Hi, honey. I'm in Malmö ,
but I'll be right back.
That's tonight, because I still
in the office. Can you help August.
Because it was already after midnight,
so go in and wake him.
I promise tonight
I'll talk to him.
Hi, honey.
Sending greetings from Saga.
That was my wife. Do you have a boyfriend?
-No. Do you have an address?
It's August.
He lives back home with Mette and me.
I know where the server is.
ln Copenhagen. Here's the address.
That can't be good.
-Yes.
With the lP address you can track
the server. It really is good.
What happens at that address?
-It's the police headquarters.
But that's impossible.
It can't be.
That's what I said,
but the Swedes are certain.
He shut the power on the bridge.
-That's true.
God's Holy shit.
-What is it?
He does use our server.
-Why?
Via a Trojan horse, or he can
change the code.
And even if I knew,
you still wouldn't understand.
Can we track him?
-I can try.
He's gone.
Saga Norén. Have you closed him down?
-He did that himself.
Can you still trace him?
-Can we still find him?
Maybe, but even if I
find the computer, he'll be gone.
We can find the computer ...
-I heard it.
He wanted us to come so far, huh?
-He was certainly aware.
To close the site
before we could trace it ...
he works towards his goal.
He wants to bring out everything .
-That's already happened.
Everything's already on the net.
He needed no sources.
Saga, a visitor. He says he
narrated the message on the net.
Turn around
and up against the wall.
Why? I just come here to ...
-Against the wall.
I didn't do anything.
When I heard the message on the radio,
it scared me badly. I narrated that.
Why is that?
-I work sometimes for Ljudgrottan.
I do voices for radio ads
and cartoons.
I also work in the City Theatre.
Are you an actor?
-Perhaps you may have seen me.
No. Recording so ...
-Ljudgrottan called me.
A customer had a job for someone
who speaks Standard Swedish.
Did you meet the client?
-No. The text came in the mail.
The cassette had to be
sent to a mailbox address.
We joked
it was for a spy movie.
Wasn't it strange
for something to say?
Actually, no. I thought it for a
play or one part or something.
It had a sinister sound, but I didn't know
it'd be used for this.
Do you have the text?
-No.
The studio would have
the mailbox number?
You can always call
but it'd surprise me.
Why?
I recorded it three and a half years ago.
You stay here with my son.
I've never seen you before.
It is important
to take good care of yourself.
It's damned important
make a good impression.
Last year I
got two new teeth.
A beautiful smile
opens most doors.
Charlie walked down the street and found ...
What do you say?
-Charlie walked down the street and found ...
Charlie?
In any case, you have nice legs.
May I say that?
It was fun,
but now I must go.
Charlie walked down the street and found ...
Did you sell her dope?
Look again to do your best.
May have. Long time ago.
Who did it?
-I don't know.
You know.
-I can't remember.
I'm tired, I'm hungry
and I have pain in my dick.
So I have a short fuse.
I wish I could help.
-My fuse is getting shorter.
Her name is Monique.
She disappeared one year ago.
And then you now?
Did she say anything to you
before she disappeared?
She is dead.
Did she take customers home?
That would be stupid of her, right?
We suspect
she was murdered in her home.
Did a customer threaten
or abuse her?
Not that I know of.
Where did she work?
-On Absalonsgade.
ls there someone I can talk?
-Pernille. I'll call her.
How old are you?
-She's old enough. Want her to blow you?
Thanks for the help.
I care about her,
So let me know how it goes.
You get all my attention
when I'm done with this case.
I know you're going to Berlin ...
-I 'm not. The police don't like it.
He called Danish Radio, and confessed
to the murders. The man of the bridge.
It is a great story. With you
We'll have a unique perspective.
I've finally got time off.
-We can talk about that.
Daniel's negotiating his salary.
Can I call back?
Who is this?
Can you understand my Danish, Daniel?
-Prima. Who are you?
Someone who stands up for truth.
Why are you calling me?
-We need each other, Daniel.
Oh yeah? I don't need anyone
a bomb in my car plant.
I have one voice. They want
to silence me all the time.
Why do I need you?
-Don't you want higher wages?
I'm not for sale.
-No?
What do you mean?
-I give you facts. Do with it what you want.
What facts?
What is this?
-Those are crime statistics.
"How different crimes
are solved ...
depending on where they are committed."
"Social Groups."
"Percent Solution."
"Distribution police budget."
What are we talking about?
What do you do?
This is to protect Veronika
Holmgrens' identity. Do you approve it?
Super. Thank you.
She was here a lot. She needed the money.
She was on speed.
-I know.
Was that the reason?
What?
Why she was murdered?
Because she owed them money?
That wasn't the reason.
She wanted to quit. She had
met a man she loved.
Who was he?
Jørgen-something. He came here.
And this was her room?
-No, that was there.
But I had her things removed.
-What stuff was that?
This is her diary.
Why wasn't it taken by the police?
-They never came here.
Thank you.
I'll make sure everything gets back.
Only the owner's fingerprints.
-Have other people never been in it?
No idea. It was completely clean.
Too little fiber and other materials.
Someone has already cleaned it.
-Very thoroughly. I think with steam.
Have you really gone
all the way through it?
Well?
Who are you?
-Someone who stands up for the truth.
Why are you calling me?
-We need each other, Daniel.
I don't need anyone
who puts a bomb in my car.
What is that?
-He's a reporter called. Listen.
Why do I need you?
-Don't you want higher wages?
I'm not for sale.
-No?
Why didn't you call?
-No idea.
He is a criminal.
-I just got busy.
If he contacts you again,
call us immediately.
What is that?
-The law on the subject.
Possible prosecution
for violation thereof.
I said I'd call you.
-I don't believe you.
Where is your boss?
I gave her a copy.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
-We have Ekwall's car.
It was in the garage
in town.
He avoids the cameras.
Is there only one camera in the garage?
-Two, but on the other one, you see nothing.
The window is covered.
And when he drove in?
-He backed in to the parking garage.
Can there be another way?
Do you know this woman?
I'll pay anyone
who knows something about her.
The guy there knows where she is.
The surgery went well. A few
complications, but he's fine.
He's in the recovery room. We
let you know if you can see him.
Thank you, Anders.
Ekwall was indeed smuthered
and then cut in half.
The cause of death of the other
woman can't be determined.
We have traces of amphetamines,
but not in lethal doses.
She was cut in half
too after her death.
They were both cut in half using
great force, I don't think, manually.
The cut is basically perfect.
-A saw?
Probably the blade wasn't used
to cut wood.
You can see the fine tooth marks.
I think he has the right tool
for the job. A meat saw.
So a slaughterhouse.
-Maybe. ln any case, a meat saw.
Watch out. Come inside
to eat. Take a bag each.
Very clever, yes.
No, not that. Hi, honey.
Did you see August?
-Where is he?
He's pruning the hedge.
We're eating. Thanks.
It is important to eat well
if you exercise so much.
August, pack it in. Food's on the table.
We're all waiting for you.
I want to eat together as a family.
Is that asking too much?
I haven't eaten with a family for 15 years.
What's this all about? Your comment?
You're coming with me.
Turn that thing off.
Stop it now. Come on.
But we aren't equal before
the law. That's a lie.
So you stand behind him.
-Of course not. He has that point right ...
It is increasing.
If one thing's been planned
for 3.5 years, it must be noted.
Ekwall's computers and
telephones yielded nothing.
The websites are not traceable.
He has his voice is distorted.
Johan can't do anything with it.
Martin has
Monique Brammer's diary.
She had met a guy named Jørgen.
That's the name he used on the radio.
How is Martin?
-Good.
Do you ever call Karin?
-On occasion, yes. Why?
Martin's wife called today.
She wanted nothing from him.
She called just to hear his voice.
Want a ride?
-I have my car.
"Equality Before the Law"
Are you waiting for someone?
-No.
Do you want some of my drink?
No.
Hello. Why did you go away?
I only said
I wanted something to drink.
Do you want to make love
with me at my place?
You bet.
What are you reading?
-A diary.
Do you regret it?
It was a long day.
And there is something in that case ...
The women on the bridge
and the man who called.
What then?
-I don't know.
It's just a feeling.
Now go to sleep. It was a long day.
Tomorrow's another day.
Hi, sweetheart.
We did it.
So the father changed his mind?
The son was in the donor registry.
It didn't matter what the father wanted.
It didn't matter.
As I lay there ...
and thought I was going to die ...
I told myself
if I survived ...
I'd have more life
to enjoy.
We'll fix it together.
I can't any longer and I won't any longer.
It hasn't been good since ...
It's been so bad for so long.
Life is too short
not to be happy.
I am happy.
But I'm not.
Very long time.
Do you want a divorce?
But I love you.
-I know.
Don't you realize what I've
done for you? For us?
What's happening? What's happening?
Sonja?
Listen to me.
I'm. Stefan.
Charlie walked down the street and found ...
A bag. He thought filled with tobacco,
but it was gunpowder.
When Charlie lit his pipe, it exploded,
This story was out.
We sang that the whole summer.
Remember, little sister?
Do you remember?
It hadn't rained for days.
You and I killed him
again and again.
But he came back,
because he lives here inside.
Did you talk?
We talked about the future.
About the time we had together.
How happy we were together.
He really loved me, Anders.
I know.
What is that?
My work.
Where do you work?
-The police. Malmö CID.
Do you want me to go?
Do you want to stay?
Do you want me to stay?
Go back to sleep.
What the hell is that thing?
That's a corpse.
-Okay. I think I'll have ...
Well ... See you then.
Thank you.
S-T-E-A-B.
Does "Staeb" mean anything in Danish?
-Jesus.
When the coroner examined
Monique for a tattoo ...
I believe it is a print
or a stamp or something.
Maybe her body
pressed against something.
Doesn't "staeb" mean anything to you?
It's not a word, but part of the word.
Think ...
an autopsy room, meat ...
-Kødbyen.
What's that?
-It's an abattoir in Vesterbro.
There's a large abattoir on
Staebogade. I'm going there right away.
I'll see you there.
Can you let us in?
Turn on the lights?
Martin.
One of the dogs smells something.
No one.
I want a list of everyone
here in the evening.
Do you have a camera?
A surveillance camera.
-No.
Do you have an alarm system? I want
a list of everyone who has the code.
And the access logs for yesterday.
No one.
info@sandhednu.dk
visible but invisible
What have you found?
-The other half. The abdomen.
Ekwall.
-This was on the body.
"... There were no casualties."
He knew we'd find the mark.
He knew we'd find it.
Saga Norén, Malmö CID.
-Daniel Ferbé, here.
He emailed me back.
-What did he want?
ln the subject line state
'Visible but invisible.
The email only reads:
If you were concerned about youself.
"Then there were
no victims."
What did you say?
-Nothing. Go on.
It's a lot of attachments.
Just like last time.
What are they?
-Weather statistics.
The increase last year
in Copenhagen and Malmö.
What has increased?
"Low budget ..."
definition of homelessness
Homeless.
These are the homeless.
He contacted Daniel again.
Six people were admitted to the
hospital in life-threatening condition.
He wants to kill the homeless.
-He's already begun.