1
00:00:05,289 --> 00:00:07,056
# The war was lost #

2
00:00:07,324 --> 00:00:09,592
# The treaty signed #

3
00:00:07,889 --> 00:00:09,990


4
00:00:09,826 --> 00:00:11,693
# I was not caught #

5
00:00:11,960 --> 00:00:13,695
# I crossed the line #

6
00:00:13,889 --> 00:00:15,690


7
00:00:13,962 --> 00:00:15,997
# I was not caught #

8
00:00:16,265 --> 00:00:18,266
# Though many tried #

9
00:00:18,189 --> 00:00:20,190


10
00:00:18,501 --> 00:00:20,602
# I live among you #

11
00:00:20,836 --> 00:00:22,637
# Well disguised #

12
00:00:22,871 --> 00:00:24,906
# I had to leave #

13
00:00:22,989 --> 00:00:24,790


14
00:00:25,140 --> 00:00:27,075
# My life behind #

15
00:00:27,089 --> 00:00:29,190


16
00:00:27,343 --> 00:00:29,376
# I dug some graves #

17
00:00:29,539 --> 00:00:31,390


18
00:00:29,644 --> 00:00:31,645
# You'll never find #

19
00:00:31,689 --> 00:00:33,990


20
00:00:31,880 --> 00:00:33,715
# The story's told #

21
00:00:33,982 --> 00:00:36,117
# With facts and lies #

22
00:00:34,539 --> 00:00:36,540


23
00:00:36,351 --> 00:00:38,152
# I have a name #

24
00:00:38,289 --> 00:00:40,440


25
00:00:38,386 --> 00:00:40,554
# But never mind #

26
00:00:40,789 --> 00:00:42,590
# Never mind #

27
00:00:42,825 --> 00:00:44,925
# Never mind #

28
00:00:42,989 --> 00:00:44,690


29
00:00:45,227 --> 00:00:48,895
# I had to leave my life behind #

30
00:00:47,089 --> 00:00:49,190


31
00:00:49,163 --> 00:00:50,831
# The story's told #

32
00:00:51,065 --> 00:00:53,800
# With facts and lies #

33
00:00:54,135 --> 00:00:58,105
# You own the world, so never mind #

34
00:00:55,889 --> 00:00:57,890


35
00:00:58,473 --> 00:01:02,809
# I could not kill the way you kill #

36
00:01:03,044 --> 00:01:04,745
# I could not hate #

37
00:01:05,012 --> 00:01:07,013
# I tried, I failed #

38
00:01:07,248 --> 00:01:09,349
# You turned me in #

39
00:01:09,583 --> 00:01:11,517
# At least you tried #

40
00:01:11,886 --> 00:01:16,056
# You side with them whom you despise #

41
00:01:16,323 --> 00:01:18,157
# But never mind #

42
00:01:18,392 --> 00:01:20,159
# Never mind #

43
00:01:20,494 --> 00:01:24,764
# I live the life I left behind #

44
00:01:25,065 --> 00:01:27,133
# There's truth that lives #

45
00:01:25,992 --> 00:01:28,877


46
00:01:27,401 --> 00:01:29,235
# And truth that dies #

47
00:01:29,570 --> 00:01:33,506
# I don't know which, so never mind #

48
00:01:50,190 --> 00:01:52,323
How'd a water stain get there?

49
00:01:52,624 --> 00:01:55,726
It rained maybe twice this last year.

50
00:01:57,263 --> 00:01:59,230
It's like everything's papier-mache.

51
00:02:02,802 --> 00:02:04,936
Stop thinking.

52
00:02:06,471 --> 00:02:08,272
I don't like being on a ledge.

53
00:02:08,573 --> 00:02:11,475
Nobody gets rich on their own money.

54
00:02:12,711 --> 00:02:14,712
I never really knew what to do with it.

55
00:02:15,914 --> 00:02:18,282
Money.

56
00:02:20,118 --> 00:02:21,919
I see that about myself.

57
00:02:25,556 --> 00:02:28,926
You always said you want lots of land.

58
00:02:29,093 --> 00:02:31,228
Yes,

59
00:02:31,562 --> 00:02:33,596
but you need children to leave it to.

60
00:02:35,300 --> 00:02:37,467
It's never really yours.

61
00:02:37,768 --> 00:02:39,136
You don't take it with you.

62
00:02:39,270 --> 00:02:41,638
You don't take anything with you.

63
00:02:41,939 --> 00:02:45,308
Just yourself, whatever that was.

64
00:02:45,643 --> 00:02:49,479
I've worked my whole life, same as you.

65
00:02:49,847 --> 00:02:53,149
And not being poor is better than the opposite.

66
00:02:58,788 --> 00:03:00,823
My old man back in Chicago,

67
00:03:01,124 --> 00:03:03,960
when I was a kid...

68
00:03:04,361 --> 00:03:07,263
he used to lock me in the basement when he'd go on a bender.

69
00:03:09,132 --> 00:03:10,666
Usually last the night.

70
00:03:10,934 --> 00:03:12,902
Let me out the next day.

71
00:03:13,270 --> 00:03:15,436
Thought he was keeping me safe, I guess.

72
00:03:17,340 --> 00:03:19,941
This one time, I was six...

73
00:03:21,477 --> 00:03:23,678
he puts me down there

74
00:03:23,880 --> 00:03:26,381
and I wake up

75
00:03:26,615 --> 00:03:29,184
and it's locked.

76
00:03:29,451 --> 00:03:31,552
It had happened before.

77
00:03:33,021 --> 00:03:36,624
Anyways, I guess he ended up arrested.

78
00:03:36,825 --> 00:03:37,825
I guess.

79
00:03:38,026 --> 00:03:39,527
God, baby.

80
00:03:39,795 --> 00:03:42,096
Well...

81
00:03:42,330 --> 00:03:44,331
by the second morning...

82
00:03:46,167 --> 00:03:47,734
I was out of food.

83
00:03:49,504 --> 00:03:53,007
The third day, the lightbulb burned out.

84
00:03:55,010 --> 00:03:56,643
Pitch-black in there.

85
00:03:58,846 --> 00:04:00,881
That's when the rats started coming out.

86
00:04:03,018 --> 00:04:04,750
I dozed off and...

87
00:04:06,520 --> 00:04:10,056
I felt the thing, you know, nibbling my finger.

88
00:04:16,330 --> 00:04:18,231
I woke up.

89
00:04:18,532 --> 00:04:21,066
It was, you know, chewing my finger.

90
00:04:23,702 --> 00:04:25,904
What did you do?

91
00:04:26,205 --> 00:04:28,873
I grabbed it in the dark with my hands

92
00:04:29,108 --> 00:04:30,875
and I started smashing it.

93
00:04:32,745 --> 00:04:34,913
And I just kept smashing it...

94
00:04:36,950 --> 00:04:39,450
till it was nothing but goo in my hands.

95
00:04:47,859 --> 00:04:49,726
Two more days I was in there...

96
00:04:51,363 --> 00:04:52,863
in the dark...

97
00:04:55,199 --> 00:04:57,067
till my dad comes home.

98
00:05:09,113 --> 00:05:12,448
Sometimes I wonder how many things you have like that...

99
00:05:15,385 --> 00:05:17,419
that I don't know about.

100
00:05:18,588 --> 00:05:20,755
Ever since, I wondered

101
00:05:21,057 --> 00:05:23,292
what if he never comes home?

102
00:05:28,131 --> 00:05:29,498
What if I'm...

103
00:05:31,934 --> 00:05:35,036
still in that basement

104
00:05:35,237 --> 00:05:36,738
in the dark?

105
00:05:45,947 --> 00:05:47,515
What if I died there?

106
00:05:56,825 --> 00:05:58,326
That's what that reminds me of.

107
00:05:58,494 --> 00:06:00,161
What?

108
00:06:03,164 --> 00:06:04,864
That water stain.

109
00:06:07,668 --> 00:06:11,438
Something's trying to tell me that

110
00:06:11,672 --> 00:06:13,673
it's all papier-mache.

111
00:06:15,609 --> 00:06:17,610
Something's telling me to wake up.

112
00:06:19,846 --> 00:06:21,480
Like...

113
00:06:25,885 --> 00:06:27,520
like I'm not real.

114
00:06:29,722 --> 00:06:31,657
Like I'm only dreaming.

115
00:06:35,828 --> 00:06:39,031
TOD between 4:00 and 9:00 am morning of the 26th.

116
00:06:39,298 --> 00:06:42,000
Tox shows Xanax, alcohol,

117
00:06:42,334 --> 00:06:45,037
also had gonorrhea, for what it's worth.

118
00:06:45,337 --> 00:06:46,939
Hydrochloric acid on his eyes.

119
00:06:47,306 --> 00:06:49,441
Burn pattern tells us he was on his back.

120
00:06:49,742 --> 00:06:51,076
Lack of spray around the orbital cavity

121
00:06:51,310 --> 00:06:52,444
indicates precision.

122
00:06:52,744 --> 00:06:55,213
Some kind of glass eyedropper, maybe.

123
00:06:55,514 --> 00:06:57,014
He's our body.

124
00:06:57,449 --> 00:06:59,850
I don't see that changing, so why don't you all fill me in?

125
00:07:00,186 --> 00:07:02,353
Victim is a key figure in a State's investigation.

126
00:07:02,754 --> 00:07:04,489
- What state investigation?  - Newly formed.

127
00:07:04,790 --> 00:07:06,391
We're looking into various allegations

128
00:07:06,659 --> 00:07:08,492
made against Vinci in the papers.

129
00:07:08,627 --> 00:07:12,262
Vinci detectives have been on Caspere as a missing person for two days.

130
00:07:12,330 --> 00:07:14,665
We have the man's house which was burglarized.

131
00:07:14,933 --> 00:07:16,133
You want to shut us out,

132
00:07:16,501 --> 00:07:18,635
we'll continue our investigation autonomously.

133
00:07:18,870 --> 00:07:21,772
In Vinci, so everybody can keep their little corners to themselves,

134
00:07:22,140 --> 00:07:25,042
but, ladies and gentlemen, PD is solving this case.

135
00:07:25,476 --> 00:07:29,346
I understand Ventura. How does the state have any claim here?

136
00:07:29,647 --> 00:07:32,482
Our officer found the body.

137
00:07:32,983 --> 00:07:35,519
This could get you out from under, Woodrugh. That actress bullshit.

138
00:07:35,853 --> 00:07:37,287
You'd be detailed as a state's investigator.

139
00:07:37,722 --> 00:07:40,324
The Caspere homicide is your public investigation.

140
00:07:40,725 --> 00:07:42,759
Looking into Vinci PD is your confidential mandate.

141
00:07:43,060 --> 00:07:45,361
Gathering intel for a grand jury.

142
00:07:45,796 --> 00:07:48,331
This probe is very important to the governor's office.

143
00:07:48,565 --> 00:07:50,200
Say this goes your way.

144
00:07:50,567 --> 00:07:52,535
How's it play for my boy here once the dust settles?

145
00:07:52,803 --> 00:07:54,804
Everything shakes out,

146
00:07:55,172 --> 00:07:57,540
you'll be offered a chance to remain investigator.

147
00:07:57,875 --> 00:07:59,775
In line for a state detective shield.

148
00:08:00,076 --> 00:08:02,645
We can wipe away all that admin hassle.

149
00:08:02,879 --> 00:08:06,148
When this is over,

150
00:08:06,483 --> 00:08:09,385
can I just go back to being on the bike?

151
00:08:09,819 --> 00:08:12,455
You can see abrasions on his wrists and ankles,

152
00:08:12,689 --> 00:08:14,590
lividity on his torso.

153
00:08:14,858 --> 00:08:17,325
He was bound upside down.

154
00:08:17,560 --> 00:08:19,795
Or close to it.

155
00:08:20,196 --> 00:08:22,131
Attorney General's office has concerns

156
00:08:22,498 --> 00:08:24,466
about obfuscation on the part of Vinci PD.

157
00:08:24,934 --> 00:08:27,335
Detective Bezzerides, you'll be primary commander of the detail.

158
00:08:27,703 --> 00:08:29,872
Secondary is gonna be a Vinci guy, Velcoro.

159
00:08:30,206 --> 00:08:32,407
Your DB was into a lot of LA County money.

160
00:08:32,775 --> 00:08:35,610
His house was broken into, so you're going to Vinci.

161
00:08:35,944 --> 00:08:37,979
Vinci detective with you, word is he's bent.

162
00:08:38,347 --> 00:08:40,715
Work him. Leverage something to turn him.

163
00:08:41,083 --> 00:08:42,817
We'll have a full state probe up inside a week.

164
00:08:43,185 --> 00:08:45,553
Caspere's death is a window into everything.

165
00:08:45,854 --> 00:08:47,756
And what is everything exactly?

166
00:08:48,090 --> 00:08:49,690
You know anything about the city of Vinci?

167
00:08:54,963 --> 00:08:58,632
It started out as a vice haven early 1900s.

168
00:08:58,934 --> 00:09:01,269
Went industrial in the '20s.

169
00:09:01,636 --> 00:09:04,405
Pushed out residents from manufacturing zones.

170
00:09:06,908 --> 00:09:09,042
Worse air polluter in the state.

171
00:09:09,477 --> 00:09:13,814
Annually emits or processes 27 million pounds of toxic waste.

172
00:09:18,052 --> 00:09:19,953
Reds tries to stop my grandfather

173
00:09:20,221 --> 00:09:22,122
from industrial rezoning.

174
00:09:22,323 --> 00:09:25,225
Same thing.

175
00:09:25,659 --> 00:09:28,728
Geldof's been after us since we won the last EPA suit.

176
00:09:29,063 --> 00:09:31,898
It's about money, Detective Velcoro.

177
00:09:32,266 --> 00:09:33,099
Caspere was one of the architects

178
00:09:33,467 --> 00:09:34,500
of the community renewal initiative.

179
00:09:34,836 --> 00:09:36,903
Passing legislature, our city gets to keep

180
00:09:37,271 --> 00:09:40,840
75% of its county tax revenue for eight years.

181
00:09:41,174 --> 00:09:42,908
- And what's that worth? - About $900 million.

182
00:09:43,243 --> 00:09:44,610
Being kept from the county general fund.

183
00:09:44,945 --> 00:09:46,078
Hell, Ernst, it's our money.

184
00:09:46,480 --> 00:09:49,449
Vinci's a goddamn success story in a depressed economy.

185
00:09:49,950 --> 00:09:51,984
State's gonna use the homicide to dig into whatever they can, Ray.

186
00:09:52,419 --> 00:09:55,254
Wherever the Caspere case goes, we need you running point.

187
00:09:55,655 --> 00:09:58,324
Control the sprawl. Control the flow of information.

188
00:09:58,658 --> 00:10:01,327
Dixon is secondary to you staging out of Vinci.

189
00:10:01,828 --> 00:10:05,597
You'll be working under a Ventura detective commanding the task force.

190
00:10:08,601 --> 00:10:10,069
That clear to you, Detective?

191
00:10:10,370 --> 00:10:12,738
10-4, Lieutenant. Just one question.

192
00:10:13,038 --> 00:10:15,374
Am I supposed to solve this or not?

193
00:10:19,144 --> 00:10:21,413
Just no surprises, Detective Velcoro.

194
00:10:21,714 --> 00:10:24,349
Ray accepts dualities must be effected

195
00:10:24,617 --> 00:10:28,253
to serve public interests.

196
00:10:28,453 --> 00:10:30,121
I really do.

197
00:10:32,191 --> 00:10:34,092
- Bound?  - Vinyl fabric.

198
00:10:34,493 --> 00:10:36,627
You can see the edge of the buckle's imprint on both wrists.

199
00:10:36,828 --> 00:10:38,196
Tape residue.

200
00:10:38,563 --> 00:10:41,132
Pelvic wounds are from a 12-gauge at point-blank range.

201
00:10:41,466 --> 00:10:43,567
Some kind of Super-X heavy load.

202
00:10:44,002 --> 00:10:46,737
Came after the eye stuff. Official COD is heart attack.

203
00:10:47,038 --> 00:10:48,972
- Trauma-induced.  - A coup de grace.

204
00:10:49,340 --> 00:10:50,641
Lividity indicates he was placed

205
00:10:50,975 --> 00:10:52,276
in upright position after death.

206
00:10:52,577 --> 00:10:53,611
Spent a few hours that way.

207
00:10:53,912 --> 00:10:56,246
Nothing under his nails, no prints.

208
00:10:56,481 --> 00:10:59,249
No trace at all?

209
00:11:07,491 --> 00:11:10,394
His eyes? What the fuck kind of modus operandi is that?

210
00:11:10,694 --> 00:11:11,795
Doc said it was hydrochloric acid.

211
00:11:12,063 --> 00:11:14,731
And a shotgun blast happened.

212
00:11:15,066 --> 00:11:17,567
Torture. Somebody wanted to know something.

213
00:11:17,868 --> 00:11:18,668
Yeah, his house was tossed.

214
00:11:18,903 --> 00:11:21,538
Somebody's making a move.

215
00:11:21,839 --> 00:11:24,474
What? What does that mean?

216
00:11:24,708 --> 00:11:26,108
You knew Caspere?

217
00:11:26,410 --> 00:11:28,478
There's deals being done upstate.

218
00:11:28,846 --> 00:11:31,714
- A lot of money moving around.  - What deals?

219
00:11:32,182 --> 00:11:34,951
- You pull my string? Is that how this works?  - Jesus, Frank.

220
00:11:35,285 --> 00:11:36,718
The more I know, the better I can deal with this.

221
00:11:36,954 --> 00:11:37,987
This is what you deal with.

222
00:11:38,388 --> 00:11:40,489
Caspere was important to this thing I have going on.

223
00:11:40,757 --> 00:11:42,224
I've got to clean it up now.

224
00:11:42,592 --> 00:11:44,994
So you beat the bushes until you figure it out.

225
00:11:45,395 --> 00:11:46,895
You ain't no sheriff's brownie. You're a detective.

226
00:11:47,197 --> 00:11:48,864
Who's your best informant?

227
00:11:49,066 --> 00:11:50,298
Are you serious?

228
00:11:51,734 --> 00:11:52,935
Fucking hell, Raymond.

229
00:12:07,483 --> 00:12:10,352
Leave!

230
00:12:10,552 --> 00:12:11,252
Leave!

231
00:12:11,454 --> 00:12:13,588
Danger!

232
00:12:18,094 --> 00:12:20,428
Yeah, yeah, that's right. Fuck me.

233
00:12:43,651 --> 00:12:46,553
So good to see you.

234
00:12:46,821 --> 00:12:48,655
Why don't you visit me more?

235
00:12:48,923 --> 00:12:51,058
Just busy. The job.

236
00:12:51,426 --> 00:12:54,361
The job. We haven't had dinner in ages.

237
00:12:54,662 --> 00:12:56,162
That's why I brought you this, Ma.

238
00:12:56,497 --> 00:12:57,864
Don't give me that Ma shit.

239
00:12:58,198 --> 00:12:59,866
It's too late for us to start all that now.

240
00:13:00,167 --> 00:13:02,268
Well, you ought to eat something.

241
00:13:03,838 --> 00:13:05,171
Oh, I don't touch bread.

242
00:13:05,472 --> 00:13:07,306
Peel that skin off for me, Paulie.

243
00:13:10,044 --> 00:13:12,111
So strong.

244
00:13:14,781 --> 00:13:17,517
I saw your old prom date the other day.

245
00:13:17,717 --> 00:13:19,385
She got fat.

246
00:13:19,619 --> 00:13:20,753
I remember her.

247
00:13:21,055 --> 00:13:22,855
Couldn't wait to have somebody's baby.

248
00:13:23,157 --> 00:13:26,159
She was nice. She was nice to me.

249
00:13:28,162 --> 00:13:31,063
All the girls are nice to you, Paulie.

250
00:13:31,364 --> 00:13:33,498
You haven't figured that out by now?

251
00:13:37,671 --> 00:13:39,137
Want to stay tonight?

252
00:13:39,405 --> 00:13:40,773


253
00:13:39,405 --> 00:13:40,773
We can watch a Clint movie.

254
00:13:41,041 --> 00:13:43,576
You can have your old room.

255
00:13:43,843 --> 00:13:45,544
I'm working on something.

256
00:13:45,878 --> 00:13:48,780
- Just came to see...  - Who is she, you scamp?

257
00:13:48,981 --> 00:13:51,616
You rake.

258
00:13:51,984 --> 00:13:54,252
You got hound's blood just like your daddy.

259
00:13:54,554 --> 00:13:56,688
I'm not gonna be around for a while.

260
00:13:57,022 --> 00:13:59,091
I've got to work around LA and the coast.

261
00:14:01,060 --> 00:14:03,861
- Special detail.  - Mm.

262
00:14:04,162 --> 00:14:06,864
Then stay. We can play cards.

263
00:14:07,165 --> 00:14:08,833
You can have your old room.

264
00:14:13,238 --> 00:14:15,106
You been getting any more shifts at the restaurant lately?

265
00:14:18,043 --> 00:14:19,843
Not with my carpal tunnel.

266
00:14:20,112 --> 00:14:22,279
I'd lose my state check anyway.

267
00:14:22,680 --> 00:14:24,915
I thought Bill was letting you work off the books.

268
00:14:25,283 --> 00:14:28,385
Oh, Bill? Don't talk to me about that motherfucker.

269
00:14:32,190 --> 00:14:33,591
Are you gonna give yourself up...

270
00:14:33,858 --> 00:14:35,892
or do this the hard way?

271
00:14:36,227 --> 00:14:37,828
There ain't no easy with me.

272
00:14:38,062 --> 00:14:39,162
You know that.

273
00:14:39,463 --> 00:14:42,232
Damn. I so hate making a mess.

274
00:14:42,533 --> 00:14:44,134
A lot of paperwork, you know.

275
00:14:44,368 --> 00:14:46,103
It messes with you.

276
00:14:46,437 --> 00:14:49,239
Screw you. I did my time in prison.

277
00:15:21,604 --> 00:15:23,873
We're listing contents against insurance audits.

278
00:15:24,107 --> 00:15:25,774
See what was stolen.

279
00:15:27,977 --> 00:15:31,180
Well, somebody was looking for something. Would explain the torture.

280
00:15:31,514 --> 00:15:34,283
Maybe. Guy really thought about fucking a lot.

281
00:15:46,662 --> 00:15:48,296
Do you mind?

282
00:15:53,102 --> 00:15:54,769
Psychiatrist appointments.

283
00:15:55,004 --> 00:15:56,437
He was seeing a shrink.

284
00:15:56,839 --> 00:15:58,673
We need to call every appointment in that calendar.

285
00:15:59,040 --> 00:16:02,510
Should check all those circled dates against his GPS.

286
00:16:02,811 --> 00:16:05,479
Yeah.

287
00:16:11,653 --> 00:16:14,822
You pull off that e-cig. Not a lot of people do.

288
00:16:15,156 --> 00:16:16,757
This place gets a day-to-day influx

289
00:16:16,991 --> 00:16:19,126
of 70,000 people, right?

290
00:16:19,360 --> 00:16:20,660
Where do they live?

291
00:16:21,029 --> 00:16:23,563
I tried one once. It felt like it was smoking me.

292
00:16:25,466 --> 00:16:27,300
A real cigarette wouldn't make you feel like that.

293
00:16:30,071 --> 00:16:32,071
Maybe it was just a little too close

294
00:16:32,406 --> 00:16:35,308
to sucking a robot's dick. I don't know.

295
00:16:51,892 --> 00:16:53,592
Caspere was my bank on this thing.

296
00:16:53,894 --> 00:16:55,494
My disposal company set this up.

297
00:16:55,829 --> 00:16:57,496
Chemical runoff. We took the risk.

298
00:16:57,931 --> 00:17:00,266
And that risk afforded you the chance to buy into the corridor.

299
00:17:00,600 --> 00:17:02,468
But I'm telling you, that buy was never made.

300
00:17:02,836 --> 00:17:05,371
Caspere had me down for 12 parcels below Monterey.

301
00:17:05,772 --> 00:17:08,340
Frank, I can only account for what purchases Caspere completed.

302
00:17:08,708 --> 00:17:10,842
- Are you saying that I...  - Mr. McCandless,

303
00:17:11,244 --> 00:17:14,212
Mr. Caspere had effectively sold Mr. Semyon the land

304
00:17:14,581 --> 00:17:16,348
while acting as a short-term holding company.

305
00:17:16,750 --> 00:17:19,885
All we're trying to do is ensure the deal for our parcel

306
00:17:20,219 --> 00:17:21,853
goes through despite Caspere's tragedy.

307
00:17:22,221 --> 00:17:24,055
If you got this transaction legally documented,

308
00:17:24,423 --> 00:17:26,291
- it shouldn't be hard.  - You know we have issues.

309
00:17:26,759 --> 00:17:28,827
If we had a fucking paper trail, we'd be doing this through banks.

310
00:17:29,228 --> 00:17:31,429
Well, otherwise I'd say you're in the unenviable position

311
00:17:31,730 --> 00:17:33,131
of being owed money by a dead man.

312
00:17:33,432 --> 00:17:35,133
That's $5 million of my money.

313
00:17:35,467 --> 00:17:37,101
Hold it, we were given to understand

314
00:17:37,436 --> 00:17:39,069
that our partnership was with Catalast.

315
00:17:39,438 --> 00:17:41,172
Had Mr. Caspere made payment, it would have been.

316
00:17:41,640 --> 00:17:44,208
And your name would have been added to the corporate charter for the development.

317
00:17:44,543 --> 00:17:46,377
- But he didn't.  - How do I know that?

318
00:17:46,645 --> 00:17:48,279
We're not gangsters, Frank.

319
00:17:48,547 --> 00:17:50,348
This is unacceptable.

320
00:17:50,749 --> 00:17:52,950
Since Caspere's remaining interests have been voided,

321
00:17:53,318 --> 00:17:55,286
I can provide you the same parcel, same price.

322
00:17:55,553 --> 00:17:57,788
- Seven million. - The same?

323
00:17:57,989 --> 00:17:59,023
We were quoted 10.

324
00:17:59,224 --> 00:18:00,324
Not by me.

325
00:18:05,063 --> 00:18:07,064
Motherfuck.

326
00:18:07,265 --> 00:18:08,933
Motherfuck me.

327
00:18:10,668 --> 00:18:14,170
We sold off our Vinci assets to put in with Caspere and...

328
00:18:17,308 --> 00:18:18,342
I went liquid for this deal.

329
00:18:18,743 --> 00:18:20,577
What can I tell you, Frank? It sounds like Mr. Caspere

330
00:18:20,911 --> 00:18:22,412
was playing fast and loose with your capital.

331
00:18:22,680 --> 00:18:24,381
I can offer you the buy-in again,

332
00:18:24,649 --> 00:18:26,182
but it sounds like you're short.

333
00:18:26,416 --> 00:18:27,683
I can get it back.

334
00:18:28,018 --> 00:18:30,419
Find another stake, it'd be worth your while.

335
00:18:30,620 --> 00:18:32,288
Excuse me.

336
00:18:37,828 --> 00:18:39,996
Shit. Seven he says?

337
00:18:40,331 --> 00:18:42,098
Seven's the same as 10 to me at this point.

338
00:18:42,333 --> 00:18:44,266
Can't round off zero.

339
00:18:55,044 --> 00:18:57,380
Am I diminished?

340
00:18:57,681 --> 00:18:59,514
Is that my message to the goddamn...

341
00:19:03,519 --> 00:19:06,088
My business partner takes my money,

342
00:19:06,356 --> 00:19:08,823
gets tortured and murdered,

343
00:19:09,025 --> 00:19:11,326
and what?

344
00:19:11,727 --> 00:19:14,396


345
00:19:11,727 --> 00:19:14,396
I'm waiting on this Velcoro burnout to make like Rockford?

346
00:19:17,299 --> 00:19:19,868
Get everybody.

347
00:19:20,202 --> 00:19:23,471
Stan, Ivar, his cousins, our Glendale people.

348
00:19:23,839 --> 00:19:25,640
Fucking Blake, wherever the fuck he's been.

349
00:19:26,008 --> 00:19:27,742
Frank, we can look at your remaining assets.

350
00:19:28,043 --> 00:19:30,478
I don't have any fucking assets.

351
00:19:30,846 --> 00:19:33,314
The house and the poker room were double mortgaged.

352
00:19:36,351 --> 00:19:38,052
This was fucking everything.

353
00:19:38,387 --> 00:19:41,122
That's what you meant. Frank, why did you...

354
00:19:41,390 --> 00:19:43,557
Leave it. I'll get it back.

355
00:19:45,827 --> 00:19:47,395
Every dime.

356
00:19:49,263 --> 00:19:52,999
That was maybe a month ago.

357
00:19:53,200 --> 00:19:54,802
September.

358
00:19:55,202 --> 00:19:57,638
Celebrated breaking ground on the Red Line extension

359
00:19:58,039 --> 00:20:02,476
and the imminent production of a major Hollywood movie.

360
00:20:02,844 --> 00:20:06,146
Big news for the city. And Ben had a hand...

361
00:20:06,580 --> 00:20:09,316
Could you tell us anything about Mr. Caspere's demeanor at the party?

362
00:20:09,583 --> 00:20:12,385
Was he with someone? A date?

363
00:20:15,622 --> 00:20:18,425
A woman he had been seeing.

364
00:20:20,127 --> 00:20:22,728
I think.

365
00:20:23,029 --> 00:20:25,331
Can't quite recall her name.

366
00:20:25,699 --> 00:20:30,035
- Ernst? - A Miss Tascha, I believe, sir.

367
00:20:30,437 --> 00:20:32,972
He see a lot of girls? Enough you wouldn't know her name?

368
00:20:33,306 --> 00:20:36,576
I believe Ben maintained an active social life.

369
00:20:36,910 --> 00:20:40,712
We didn't often cross paths that way.

370
00:20:40,981 --> 00:20:43,715
We only met over business.

371
00:20:44,117 --> 00:20:46,418
You wouldn't have any pictures from the party, sir,

372
00:20:46,619 --> 00:20:48,620
by any chance?

373
00:20:48,955 --> 00:20:51,256
Something to help us identify the girl.

374
00:20:56,228 --> 00:20:57,696
Mr. Caspere was dedicated to his community.

375
00:20:57,964 --> 00:21:00,665
A community of 95 residents.

376
00:21:01,066 --> 00:21:04,068
He didn't seem distressed by anything last you saw him?

377
00:21:04,336 --> 00:21:07,005
No, just the usual headaches.

378
00:21:08,574 --> 00:21:10,842
County can't forgive our independence.

379
00:21:11,143 --> 00:21:13,144
And you didn't talk to him much

380
00:21:13,445 --> 00:21:14,778
outside of business get-togethers?

381
00:21:15,080 --> 00:21:17,848
And cabinet meetings occasionally.

382
00:21:18,017 --> 00:21:20,118
Well...

383
00:21:20,452 --> 00:21:22,086
Thank you, your Honor. That'll do us.

384
00:21:22,587 --> 00:21:25,256
Do you recall what time Mr. Caspere left your house night of the party?

385
00:21:25,590 --> 00:21:28,659
I believe around 11:00, maybe 12:00.

386
00:21:29,093 --> 00:21:31,194
- Around the time things broke up. - With Miss Tascha?

387
00:21:31,462 --> 00:21:33,363
Thank you, your Honor.

388
00:21:33,632 --> 00:21:35,132
Thank you, detective.

389
00:21:35,500 --> 00:21:38,301
I'd like to see this solved as soon as possible.

390
00:21:44,375 --> 00:21:46,643
Got his bank records, phone calls.

391
00:21:47,011 --> 00:21:48,412
Don't know if he had any of the lines, though.

392
00:21:48,812 --> 00:21:50,447
Starting to think he must have kept other accounts.

393
00:21:50,781 --> 00:21:53,950
Hey, kid, just save it for the debrief.

394
00:21:54,185 --> 00:21:55,952
Why are you here?

395
00:21:56,287 --> 00:21:57,854
You're not even an investigator, right?

396
00:21:59,557 --> 00:22:01,758
Special detail. State owns the case.

397
00:22:02,192 --> 00:22:05,227
Found his lawyer, too. Had to hump all over LA for this shit.

398
00:22:05,529 --> 00:22:08,297
Oh, and this one fag at the bank

399
00:22:08,566 --> 00:22:10,700
tried, like, hitting on me.

400
00:22:10,968 --> 00:22:12,301
Almost clocked the guy.

401
00:22:12,570 --> 00:22:14,170
Yeah? Why would you do that?

402
00:22:15,706 --> 00:22:16,973
Hey, I'm not trouble here, stud.

403
00:22:17,307 --> 00:22:19,175
Just leave me out of it, all right?

404
00:22:41,097 --> 00:22:42,497
His insurance had these forms.

405
00:22:42,832 --> 00:22:45,166
Items likely stolen from Caspere's place,

406
00:22:45,434 --> 00:22:47,035
we can put out pawn sheets on them.

407
00:22:48,905 --> 00:22:49,905
What'd you guys get?

408
00:22:50,272 --> 00:22:53,741
The young man here, he got a dynamite anecdote.

409
00:22:56,579 --> 00:22:57,878
Last withdrawal was five days ago.

410
00:22:58,180 --> 00:22:59,747
Nothing jumps except this.

411
00:23:00,082 --> 00:23:02,950
Once a month, $4,000 cash withdrawal.

412
00:23:08,389 --> 00:23:10,591
Let me see this.

413
00:23:15,964 --> 00:23:17,732
The withdrawals seem to come around the time

414
00:23:18,066 --> 00:23:19,600
of these blank days in his calendar.

415
00:23:21,770 --> 00:23:23,604
- Did you get his GPS? - Yeah.

416
00:23:26,207 --> 00:23:27,774
Here.

417
00:23:29,710 --> 00:23:31,178
There's nothing on those dates.

418
00:23:31,579 --> 00:23:34,348
Car didn't go anywhere. Says his Mercedes was a lease.

419
00:23:34,749 --> 00:23:37,484
- Well, that makes sense. - Not city. Catalast Group.

420
00:23:37,785 --> 00:23:38,952
Why'd Catalast lease him a car?

421
00:23:44,091 --> 00:23:45,825
Maybe somebody should call them.

422
00:23:54,434 --> 00:23:55,969
You tight with him?

423
00:23:56,270 --> 00:23:57,703
I'm not tight with anybody.

424
00:24:01,575 --> 00:24:04,410
Can I pick up here tomorrow?

425
00:24:05,512 --> 00:24:06,779
Sure.

426
00:24:23,797 --> 00:24:25,630
I gotta go.

427
00:24:34,807 --> 00:24:36,841
- What?  - These coordinates.

428
00:24:37,042 --> 00:24:38,343
They're up north.

429
00:24:38,644 --> 00:24:41,346
Monterey County, Fresno, Gilroy.

430
00:24:41,614 --> 00:24:43,348
A lot of them on weekends.

431
00:24:56,161 --> 00:24:58,429
Hey.

432
00:24:58,630 --> 00:24:59,997
Where's Chad?

433
00:25:03,801 --> 00:25:05,902
He's not coming.

434
00:25:06,070 --> 00:25:08,305
What? Why?

435
00:25:08,640 --> 00:25:11,041
You're gonna ask me why? Really?

436
00:25:11,243 --> 00:25:12,409
You fucking prick.

437
00:25:12,677 --> 00:25:14,010
What, that thing at the school?

438
00:25:14,379 --> 00:25:16,012
I apologized to Chad and it's between me and him.

439
00:25:16,381 --> 00:25:18,048
That's not the end of the story and you know it.

440
00:25:18,516 --> 00:25:20,516
- How's that? - The police said that someone beat up Wit Conroy.

441
00:25:20,918 --> 00:25:23,720
Said it had something to do with a schoolyard altercation.

442
00:25:24,055 --> 00:25:25,088
Well, I don't know anything about that,

443
00:25:25,489 --> 00:25:27,824
but sometimes a good beating provokes personal growth.

444
00:25:28,192 --> 00:25:30,060
It's not like you know any other way, right?

445
00:25:30,261 --> 00:25:32,695
God damn it.

446
00:25:33,064 --> 00:25:35,898
Chad gets anxious when he has to be around you.

447
00:25:36,199 --> 00:25:38,100
Do you get that? Do you even see it?

448
00:25:38,369 --> 00:25:40,503
That's bullshit. I... we talk,

449
00:25:40,904 --> 00:25:43,506
we build models, we write letters, I got him this recorder.

450
00:25:43,840 --> 00:25:44,840
And how many times has he written you back?

451
00:25:45,208 --> 00:25:47,443
He needs me, all right, even if he doesn't know it.

452
00:25:47,844 --> 00:25:49,712
And if he gets anxious, it's probably because he knows

453
00:25:50,113 --> 00:25:51,614
he's gonna have to listen to his mom talk shit about his dad.

454
00:25:51,882 --> 00:25:55,384
Yeah. You're bad, Ray.

455
00:25:55,618 --> 00:25:56,952
You're a bad person.

456
00:25:57,287 --> 00:26:00,222
- And you're bad for my son.  - Don't say that.

457
00:26:00,423 --> 00:26:03,159
You know me.

458
00:26:03,393 --> 00:26:06,395
We had something and...

459
00:26:06,797 --> 00:26:08,664
What I done for you, things started to slip away from me...

460
00:26:08,964 --> 00:26:10,098
No, you didn't do that for me, Ray.

461
00:26:10,433 --> 00:26:12,701
Don't you dare say that you did that for me.

462
00:26:13,035 --> 00:26:14,202
I had a right by any natural law.

463
00:26:14,404 --> 00:26:15,970
I had a right.

464
00:26:23,045 --> 00:26:24,946
I came to tell you this in person.

465
00:26:25,214 --> 00:26:27,015
Richard didn't want me to.

466
00:26:27,416 --> 00:26:29,083
I'm getting an emergency writ for supervised visits.

467
00:26:29,285 --> 00:26:31,652
What? No.

468
00:26:31,954 --> 00:26:34,388
We're petitioning for sole custody.

469
00:26:34,556 --> 00:26:36,424
What?

470
00:26:36,591 --> 00:26:37,692
No, why?

471
00:26:37,960 --> 00:26:40,161
Because this can't go on.
457 

472
00:26:40,329 --> 00:26:42,530
It can't.

473
00:26:42,798 --> 00:26:44,932
I mean, look at yourself.

474
00:26:45,266 --> 00:26:47,635
You will not... no. Please, please, don't.

475
00:26:47,969 --> 00:26:50,571
You used to have something, a decency.

476
00:26:50,839 --> 00:26:53,207
You were good at being decent

477
00:26:53,475 --> 00:26:55,576
until something happened.

478
00:26:55,977 --> 00:26:58,378
You were fine as long as everything else was fine.

479
00:26:58,847 --> 00:27:01,748
But then something happened and you weren't strong enough to stay decent.

480
00:27:02,116 --> 00:27:03,650
- And now...  - You won't get away with it.

481
00:27:04,085 --> 00:27:06,820
I will burn this entire fucking city to the ground first.

482
00:27:09,290 --> 00:27:11,225
I'll petition for a paternity test, too, Ray.

483
00:27:11,625 --> 00:27:14,294
- If you make me.  - Don't. Please. Please, don't.

484
00:27:14,528 --> 00:27:16,463
Don't do that, please.

485
00:27:16,797 --> 00:27:19,265
God damn it, look, he's... he's all I...

486
00:27:19,533 --> 00:27:21,000
all right, I'm a piece of shit,

487
00:27:21,369 --> 00:27:23,302
but that boy is all I have in my entire shitty life.

488
00:27:23,504 --> 00:27:25,705
No, babe.

489
00:27:26,006 --> 00:27:28,441
Then don't you know he deserves better?

490
00:28:08,915 --> 00:28:11,482
Oh, fuck. Son of a bitch.

491
00:28:11,884 --> 00:28:14,286
Some asshole just rear-ended my car. Look, you mother... ah!

492
00:28:16,755 --> 00:28:18,589
Fuck.

493
00:28:18,857 --> 00:28:22,092
Son of...

494
00:28:22,260 --> 00:28:23,928
Oh, fuck.

495
00:28:26,364 --> 00:28:29,066
Next time, we put you in trunk.

496
00:28:37,542 --> 00:28:39,943
Oh, fuck!

497
00:28:40,244 --> 00:28:42,779
Jesus, buddy. What was that about?

498
00:28:43,080 --> 00:28:45,381
Oh, God, thank you. Fuckin' me...

499
00:28:47,251 --> 00:28:48,718
Why would somebody come after you like that, guy?

500
00:28:49,019 --> 00:28:50,386
I mean, that was crazy, right?

501
00:28:50,688 --> 00:28:52,655
I don't know. They just...

502
00:28:52,957 --> 00:28:54,257
What did you do to piss somebody off?

503
00:28:54,624 --> 00:28:56,259
- Can you think of anything?  - What does that mean?

504
00:28:56,626 --> 00:28:58,027
I don't know what that means. I'm asking you.

505
00:28:58,429 --> 00:29:00,896
What you might have did to get guys like that after you.

506
00:29:01,131 --> 00:29:03,032
Wait, do I know you?

507
00:29:03,434 --> 00:29:05,368
I've never seen you before, but I saw the whole thing.

508
00:29:05,735 --> 00:29:07,403
And I wish we could figure out what you did.

509
00:29:07,871 --> 00:29:10,272
Like some kind of behavior that guys like that would have issue with.

510
00:29:10,574 --> 00:29:12,508
Like mouthed off or made a gesture

511
00:29:12,809 --> 00:29:14,710
or you run a book in Vinci sweatshops.

512
00:29:14,978 --> 00:29:17,045
What? Is that what this is?

513
00:29:17,447 --> 00:29:20,148
Is what what what is? Is that what you think this is?

514
00:29:20,584 --> 00:29:23,786
It just seems to me like you pissed off some serious people.

515
00:29:24,087 --> 00:29:27,222
Maybe you ought to take more care.

516
00:29:27,457 --> 00:29:28,890
Just a thought, pal.

517
00:29:48,644 --> 00:29:51,513
Velcoro and Bezzerides to see Dr. Pitlor. We called ahead.

518
00:30:16,370 --> 00:30:17,604
You do surgeries here?

519
00:30:17,805 --> 00:30:19,272
Only cosmetic.

520
00:30:19,674 --> 00:30:21,775
The clinic employs a small group of medical professionals

521
00:30:22,043 --> 00:30:23,977
who cover a variety of services.

522
00:30:27,114 --> 00:30:28,615
This is quite a shock.

523
00:30:30,217 --> 00:30:32,618
Anything he might have told you that indicated

524
00:30:32,853 --> 00:30:35,221
trouble, enemies?

525
00:30:37,191 --> 00:30:41,194
The reputation of this clinic rests on its discretion, Officers.

526
00:30:41,395 --> 00:30:43,696
Confidentiality.

527
00:30:43,964 --> 00:30:46,132
Your patient was murdered.

528
00:30:46,367 --> 00:30:48,000
He's got no living family.

529
00:30:53,406 --> 00:30:55,641
Somebody burned out his eyes with acid, Doc.

530
00:31:04,350 --> 00:31:08,853
Well, of course I am willing to help.

531
00:31:09,155 --> 00:31:10,755
I would hope I can, at least.

532
00:31:11,057 --> 00:31:12,624
What were you treating him for?

533
00:31:12,925 --> 00:31:16,061
A number of things. Neuroses, anxiety,

534
00:31:16,329 --> 00:31:18,897
a painful past like many.

535
00:31:20,400 --> 00:31:21,432
Guilt.

536
00:31:21,667 --> 00:31:22,968
Guilt over what?

537
00:31:23,268 --> 00:31:25,637
Ben had a weakness for young women.

538
00:31:25,938 --> 00:31:28,139
Paying for them, more specifically.

539
00:31:28,507 --> 00:31:31,076
He frequented escorts, although it ignited in him

540
00:31:31,376 --> 00:31:33,211
tremendous shame and self-loathing,

541
00:31:33,545 --> 00:31:37,348
which resulted in further damaging tendencies.

542
00:31:39,351 --> 00:31:41,352
- Old cycles.  - How long had he been seeing you?

543
00:31:42,921 --> 00:31:43,854
About three years.

544
00:31:44,256 --> 00:31:46,724
Was he making any progress, his therapy?

545
00:31:46,958 --> 00:31:47,925
I like to think so.

546
00:31:48,227 --> 00:31:49,594
His relapses were less frequent

547
00:31:50,028 --> 00:31:52,096
and he didn't compound them with further damaging behavior.

548
00:31:52,464 --> 00:31:54,999
His habit, did he ever mention any girls by name?

549
00:31:55,299 --> 00:31:57,701
Favorite service? Favorite girl?

550
00:31:58,136 --> 00:32:01,138
No, not that I recall, but I'd be willing to go back over my notes.

551
00:32:01,472 --> 00:32:04,975
What about the name Tascha? He ever mention her?

552
00:32:06,711 --> 00:32:09,479
Did he ever mention violence? Trouble with a girl, a pimp?

553
00:32:09,881 --> 00:32:13,283
He was sexually obsessed, but he was not aggressive.

554
00:32:13,484 --> 00:32:16,886
More... passive.

555
00:32:20,057 --> 00:32:23,593
That's about as detailed as I'll get airing Ben's personal issues.

556
00:32:25,729 --> 00:32:27,997
This was helpful. Thank you.

557
00:32:31,135 --> 00:32:34,403
Your ID said Antigone Bezzerides.

558
00:32:34,805 --> 00:32:38,207
Are you related to Elliot Bezzerides by any chance?

559
00:32:38,608 --> 00:32:40,877
- You know him?  - I used to a bit a long time ago.

560
00:32:41,244 --> 00:32:42,945
I did some social theory with the Good People.

561
00:32:43,246 --> 00:32:45,347
He had a daughter, I remember.

562
00:32:46,650 --> 00:32:47,849
Good Lord, was that you?

563
00:32:48,117 --> 00:32:50,452
I left all that behind.

564
00:32:50,687 --> 00:32:52,421
It was a fucked-up place.

565
00:32:52,755 --> 00:32:55,224
Well, all kinds of secrets in the world.

566
00:32:55,458 --> 00:32:57,092
All kinds of truth.

567
00:32:57,460 --> 00:32:59,961
Five kids living there when I was growing up.

568
00:33:00,296 --> 00:33:02,230
Two are in jail now, two committed suicide.

569
00:33:02,498 --> 00:33:03,899
How's that for social theory?

570
00:33:04,266 --> 00:33:07,169
- And the fifth?  - She became a detective.

571
00:33:26,888 --> 00:33:29,890
To curb public speculation in this homicide,

572
00:33:30,292 --> 00:33:32,493
it's become necessary to announce that our offices

573
00:33:32,961 --> 00:33:35,462


574
00:33:32,961 --> 00:33:35,462
are conducting a criminal probe into the incorporated city

575
00:33:35,697 --> 00:33:38,099
of Vinci in LA County.

576
00:33:38,533 --> 00:33:40,634
This investigation is long overdue.

577
00:33:40,869 --> 00:33:43,137
And we ask all state

578
00:33:43,471 --> 00:33:46,140
and city officials to cooperate...

579
00:33:46,474 --> 00:33:48,843
Attorney general just announced a shakedown.

580
00:33:53,514 --> 00:33:54,881
You're not supposed to bring that here.

581
00:33:55,082 --> 00:33:57,718
It's short 10.

582
00:33:58,018 --> 00:34:00,420
When you took over from Gene Slattery,

583
00:34:00,655 --> 00:34:02,055
we established terms.

584
00:34:02,357 --> 00:34:05,024
Short wasn't part of it, Frank.

585
00:34:05,326 --> 00:34:06,659
I'm pulling some stuff together.

586
00:34:06,894 --> 00:34:08,261
Adding revenue streams.

587
00:34:08,528 --> 00:34:09,562
I just need a couple of weeks.

588
00:34:09,930 --> 00:34:12,165
I sold the rent farms and waste disposal business

589
00:34:12,532 --> 00:34:14,134
to pull together the corridor money. You know that.

590
00:34:14,434 --> 00:34:15,969
You still owe the poker room kickback.

591
00:34:16,270 --> 00:34:18,071
Sell some of that land if you need to.

592
00:34:18,405 --> 00:34:20,706
Caspere died with my money in his pocket.

593
00:34:21,075 --> 00:34:25,244
I've had outside interest re: the poker room.

594
00:34:25,545 --> 00:34:27,313
Think they can turn a higher gross.

595
00:34:27,614 --> 00:34:30,149
- Higher vig.  - What outside interest?

596
00:34:30,450 --> 00:34:33,352
Just so you know, it's a seller's market.

597
00:34:35,889 --> 00:34:38,724
You seriously gonna bust my balls over 10 Gs?

598
00:34:39,092 --> 00:34:41,393
I kept this place tight as a drum six years.

599
00:34:41,795 --> 00:34:44,830
Who squashed the undocumented workers alliance?

600
00:34:45,064 --> 00:34:46,131
That hit and run?

601
00:34:46,432 --> 00:34:48,000
Your son's face was so coke-dusted

602
00:34:48,234 --> 00:34:49,434
he looked like a clown.

603
00:34:49,702 --> 00:34:51,970
Tony, yeah.

604
00:34:54,307 --> 00:34:56,641
My son, I fear,

605
00:34:56,909 --> 00:34:59,611
is losing his fucking mind.

606
00:34:59,878 --> 00:35:02,514
Like his departed mother.

607
00:35:02,815 --> 00:35:06,518
Some people can't handle the deep trip.

608
00:35:06,786 --> 00:35:08,787
I fear he is a destroyer.

609
00:35:09,254 --> 00:35:12,423
In my day, you understand, it was about consciousness expansion,

610
00:35:12,657 --> 00:35:15,126
tracing the unseen web.

611
00:35:15,427 --> 00:35:18,429
Children are a disappointment.

612
00:35:18,663 --> 00:35:21,299
Remain unfettered, Frank.

613
00:35:23,168 --> 00:35:24,802
They closer on who killed Caspere?

614
00:35:28,673 --> 00:35:31,408
Catalast is taking over his action.

615
00:35:31,643 --> 00:35:33,677
Everything's happening.

616
00:35:34,111 --> 00:35:37,214
My farkakte offspring I will set up with a club in Oakland.

617
00:35:37,515 --> 00:35:39,650
Let him be a boy prince elsewhere.

618
00:35:39,984 --> 00:35:42,152
Whoever killed Caspere, they have my money.

619
00:35:42,520 --> 00:35:44,621
- How's that?  - The holding company is empty.

620
00:35:45,089 --> 00:35:47,958
The land was never purchased and I'm fucked out of my life's work.

621
00:35:48,292 --> 00:35:50,393
Now I need a direction to turn, Austin.

622
00:35:50,694 --> 00:35:52,829
Or I may just start pulling down walls.

623
00:35:55,299 --> 00:35:58,168
That doesn't sound like a smart play, gever.

624
00:35:58,435 --> 00:36:00,603
Innuendo is nobody's friend.

625
00:36:01,105 --> 00:36:04,306
You're not worried whoever did Caspere might be part of something bigger?

626
00:36:04,708 --> 00:36:07,076
Muscling in on the corridor, secret handshakes and whatnot.

627
00:36:07,478 --> 00:36:10,613
Ben had his own charity and what punched his ticket

628
00:36:10,947 --> 00:36:13,949
could have come from some personal pocket.

629
00:36:16,219 --> 00:36:19,355
Nobody muscles me, Frank.

630
00:36:19,689 --> 00:36:22,091
State attorney will get his piece,

631
00:36:22,458 --> 00:36:24,826
Caspere will get closed, the world will turn

632
00:36:25,061 --> 00:36:27,062
uncaring of our struggles.

633
00:36:32,502 --> 00:36:36,304
They close Caspere, I want a tip.

634
00:36:36,672 --> 00:36:38,473
I want time alone with the guy that did it.

635
00:36:41,511 --> 00:36:43,978
You are industrious, Frank.

636
00:36:44,313 --> 00:36:46,548
I want to see you make it through this.

637
00:36:48,250 --> 00:36:49,684
Who wants to move on the poker room?

638
00:36:50,019 --> 00:36:52,320
Kickback's an extra 15 next week, Frank.

639
00:36:52,554 --> 00:36:54,355
22.50 the week after.

640
00:36:54,656 --> 00:36:56,490
You don't come through then,

641
00:36:56,825 --> 00:36:58,927
I have to entertain other interests.

642
00:36:59,161 --> 00:37:00,929
It's business.

643
00:37:02,064 --> 00:37:03,431
Sure.

644
00:37:16,678 --> 00:37:19,146
Now this is making some sense, right?

645
00:37:19,414 --> 00:37:20,848
It explains his home decor.

646
00:37:21,282 --> 00:37:24,151
Nine to one the cash withdrawal every month was a hooker blowout.

647
00:37:24,518 --> 00:37:26,619
Guy's regularly in touch with criminal elements.

648
00:37:28,957 --> 00:37:31,091
Pimps,

649
00:37:31,426 --> 00:37:32,725
they break in, tortured him somewhere.

650
00:37:33,061 --> 00:37:34,428
Probably trying to get access to assets.

651
00:37:34,728 --> 00:37:36,496
I think it's more twisted than that.

652
00:37:36,864 --> 00:37:38,565
What was done to him, that shit in his house.

653
00:37:38,933 --> 00:37:41,400
He's into a lot of stuff we're just scratching.

654
00:37:41,802 --> 00:37:45,304
Well, we can have Woodrugh work prosts, escort services.

655
00:37:45,573 --> 00:37:46,940
He'd be smooth for that.

656
00:37:49,209 --> 00:37:50,643
Sure.

657
00:37:54,548 --> 00:37:57,183
You know that expression about flies and honey?

658
00:37:57,550 --> 00:38:00,119
Mmm. The fuck do I want with a bunch of flies?

659
00:38:00,487 --> 00:38:02,154
Well, you don't have flies, you can't fly-fish.

660
00:38:16,469 --> 00:38:18,303
What is this fucking place?

661
00:38:19,639 --> 00:38:21,707
Suburban flight,

662
00:38:22,074 --> 00:38:24,576
heavy manufacturing moves inland or overseas,

663
00:38:24,777 --> 00:38:26,411
plants close.

664
00:38:26,746 --> 00:38:28,413
Except here, a bunch of good capitalists

665
00:38:28,748 --> 00:38:30,348
ran in for cheap leases, tax incentives,

666
00:38:30,682 --> 00:38:33,318
immigrant labor, sweatshop economics.

667
00:38:33,619 --> 00:38:34,652
You don't have a problem with that?

668
00:38:35,021 --> 00:38:38,755
No, my strong suspicion is we get the world we deserve.

669
00:38:43,361 --> 00:38:45,662
Why are you here? This place?

670
00:38:47,265 --> 00:38:50,434
I did time in the LA Sheriff's.

671
00:38:50,668 --> 00:38:52,869
I just needed better pay.

672
00:38:53,103 --> 00:38:55,906
Regular hours.

673
00:38:56,106 --> 00:38:58,474
I had a son.

674
00:39:03,380 --> 00:39:04,915
They told you about me, I'm sure.

675
00:39:05,282 --> 00:39:07,551
Yeah, bosses said you're a solid investigator.

676
00:39:07,952 --> 00:39:11,120
I know you wouldn't think it, but I don't bullshit.

677
00:39:11,388 --> 00:39:12,621
What would you say if you did?

678
00:39:12,989 --> 00:39:14,424
Can I tell you what you may or may not have heard,

679
00:39:14,824 --> 00:39:16,959
but almost definitely will hear about my busted marriage?

680
00:39:17,361 --> 00:39:19,662
Rumors have me killing this piece of filth hurt my wife.

681
00:39:19,996 --> 00:39:21,764
Same rumors put me in hock to a Southland mob.

682
00:39:22,166 --> 00:39:23,466
And if you know who to ask, you might hear I like to wet

683
00:39:23,800 --> 00:39:25,034
now and then from a number of bad habits.

684
00:39:25,335 --> 00:39:26,969
- Any of that true?  - Oh, yeah.

685
00:39:27,236 --> 00:39:29,872
- Which parts?  - Bad habits.

686
00:39:32,141 --> 00:39:33,576
Never lost one yet.

687
00:39:35,344 --> 00:39:36,679
You?

688
00:39:37,047 --> 00:39:39,715
Oh, I don't distinguish between good and bad habits.

689
00:39:41,150 --> 00:39:42,250
What's with all the knives?

690
00:39:42,651 --> 00:39:44,619
Could you do this job if everyone you encountered

691
00:39:44,887 --> 00:39:47,355
could physically overpower you?

692
00:39:47,656 --> 00:39:48,890
I mean, forget police work.

693
00:39:49,258 --> 00:39:51,126
No man could walk around like that without going nuts.

694
00:39:51,427 --> 00:39:53,528
So they're equalizers. Makes sense.

695
00:39:53,896 --> 00:39:56,098
No, I'd still wear them if I wasn't on the job.

696
00:39:56,399 --> 00:39:58,733
Fundamental difference between the sexes

697
00:39:59,167 --> 00:40:02,403
is that one of them can kill the other with their bare hands.

698
00:40:02,705 --> 00:40:04,872
Man of any size lays hands on me,

699
00:40:05,207 --> 00:40:06,774
he's gonna bleed out in under a minute.

700
00:40:08,844 --> 00:40:11,613
Well, just so you know, I support feminism.

701
00:40:11,914 --> 00:40:14,548


702
00:40:11,914 --> 00:40:14,548
Mostly by having body image issues.

703
00:40:21,356 --> 00:40:23,857
What's that thing Pitlor mentioned?

704
00:40:24,126 --> 00:40:25,826
Your dad, the Good People?

705
00:40:26,194 --> 00:40:29,896
It was this, like, commune around Guerneville

706
00:40:30,132 --> 00:40:32,032
in the late '70s, '80s.

707
00:40:32,233 --> 00:40:34,501


708
00:40:32,233 --> 00:40:34,501
Hippie shit.

709
00:40:34,802 --> 00:40:36,603
You had to look out for yourself, huh?

710
00:40:45,146 --> 00:40:46,947
That's you.

711
00:41:03,597 --> 00:41:07,599
Look, I'm trying to effect transparency between us.

712
00:41:07,834 --> 00:41:09,434
The reason being...

713
00:41:11,838 --> 00:41:13,372
I don't know if you know this,

714
00:41:13,640 --> 00:41:16,508
but us, the investigation,

715
00:41:16,810 --> 00:41:18,410
I don't think it's supposed to work.

716
00:41:18,611 --> 00:41:20,412
Why is that?

717
00:41:20,747 --> 00:41:22,113
State attorney's investigation.

718
00:41:22,482 --> 00:41:25,350
They must have tapped you. You know, the kid, too.

719
00:41:25,785 --> 00:41:27,786
Why wouldn't they have a team of state grand jury investigators

720
00:41:28,154 --> 00:41:30,322
working Vinci instead of just you and the kid?

721
00:41:30,690 --> 00:41:33,525
Why wouldn't the SA do a full-court press on this?

722
00:41:36,962 --> 00:41:39,964
You want honest?

723
00:41:40,299 --> 00:41:42,667
Tell me, how compromised are you?

724
00:41:52,845 --> 00:41:55,846
Anyways, good night.

725
00:42:30,648 --> 00:42:33,250
What is that? Why didn't you tell me?

726
00:42:35,519 --> 00:42:37,721
- What the fuck?  - Hmm?

727
00:42:36,000 --> 00:42:38,300


728
00:42:41,359 --> 00:42:43,426
'Cause that right there is a bunch of unbridled horseshit.

729
00:42:43,694 --> 00:42:46,129
You read about the girl.

730
00:42:46,396 --> 00:42:47,730
Goes to jail for one more fuckup,

731
00:42:48,065 --> 00:42:51,067
tries to say I did something wrong. That's it.

732
00:42:51,334 --> 00:42:52,701
Then why didn't you tell me?

733
00:42:53,036 --> 00:42:54,436
'Cause I don't want to think about it.

734
00:42:54,738 --> 00:42:56,239
- Are you gonna lose your job?  - No.

735
00:42:56,606 --> 00:42:58,241
I got a new assignment through the state attorney.

736
00:42:58,541 --> 00:43:00,309
I'm gonna be a detective after.

737
00:43:00,610 --> 00:43:02,578
Listen, this paper talks about you

738
00:43:02,912 --> 00:43:04,380
being in this Black Mountain Security thing.

739
00:43:04,748 --> 00:43:07,949
I told you, I don't talk about the desert.

740
00:43:08,351 --> 00:43:10,786
But this Black Mountain Security, they did things, bad...

741
00:43:22,265 --> 00:43:24,699
So that's it? You're just taking off?

742
00:43:24,967 --> 00:43:26,902
Come on, I just told you.

743
00:43:27,236 --> 00:43:29,771
I got to go to LA to work for a while.

744
00:43:30,106 --> 00:43:32,674
Special detail. Special investigator.

745
00:43:33,042 --> 00:43:34,742
- That's it.  - God, you smell like a bar rag.

746
00:43:35,110 --> 00:43:37,645
They say vodka don't smell, but that's bullshit.

747
00:43:37,946 --> 00:43:39,714
You smell just like my uncle.

748
00:43:40,048 --> 00:43:41,616
I'm just going down south a while.

749
00:43:41,883 --> 00:43:44,319
- Mm-hmm.  - That's it.

750
00:43:44,653 --> 00:43:46,887
- And your apartment?  - Still there, Em.

751
00:43:50,258 --> 00:43:52,392
What are you doing?

752
00:43:57,332 --> 00:44:00,434
I can't do this anymore. I tried.

753
00:44:04,239 --> 00:44:06,307
It's work.

754
00:44:06,574 --> 00:44:08,542
It's a good thing, Em.

755
00:44:08,676 --> 00:44:11,345
No.

756
00:44:11,579 --> 00:44:13,747
You barely talk.

757
00:44:14,148 --> 00:44:16,115
I don't know your family. You don't want to know mine.

758
00:44:16,417 --> 00:44:17,651
- Who are you?  - Oh, fuck off.

759
00:44:17,952 --> 00:44:19,353
Who the fuck am I supposed to be?

760
00:44:19,754 --> 00:44:21,521
- I don't know who you're supposed to be.  - Jesus Christ.

761
00:44:21,756 --> 00:44:24,290
Yeah, fuck off. Go.

762
00:44:24,658 --> 00:44:27,827
God, whatever happened to you, I can't fix it.

763
00:44:29,429 --> 00:44:30,830
There's nothing wrong with me.

764
00:44:33,367 --> 00:44:35,434
I'll call you this weekend.

765
00:44:35,802 --> 00:44:38,537
Don't. I don't want to hear from you, Paul.

766
00:44:38,839 --> 00:44:40,873
You can't give me more than this.

767
00:44:41,140 --> 00:44:43,442
You're not... you're not right.

768
00:44:43,810 --> 00:44:47,012
Sometimes I'm with you and I can tell that...

769
00:44:49,850 --> 00:44:51,316
Fuck it.

770
00:44:51,518 --> 00:44:52,685
I gotta go.

771
00:44:52,886 --> 00:44:54,620
Don't come back.

772
00:44:54,855 --> 00:44:57,990
It's on you, not me.

773
00:44:59,325 --> 00:45:00,993
I can't see you again, Paul.

774
00:45:01,227 --> 00:45:03,028
You hurt me seeing you.

775
00:45:05,965 --> 00:45:08,133
You're doing this.

776
00:45:08,401 --> 00:45:10,969
This isn't me doing this.

777
00:45:11,170 --> 00:45:12,871
This isn't me.

778
00:45:43,936 --> 00:45:46,236
# Are you gonna leave me? #

779
00:45:46,504 --> 00:45:48,472
# Are you, now? #

780
00:45:48,773 --> 00:45:52,810
# Do you think that's okay? #

781
00:45:53,210 --> 00:45:57,781
# To leave it all to drown in this violent swell #

782
00:45:58,082 --> 00:46:01,184
# Never gonna see you again #

783
00:46:02,586 --> 00:46:05,088
# Never gonna see you again #

784
00:46:07,191 --> 00:46:10,793
# Never gonna see you again #

785
00:46:15,399 --> 00:46:17,033
Frank.

786
00:46:17,435 --> 00:46:19,469
Surprised you're visiting this pit you stuck me with.

787
00:46:19,736 --> 00:46:22,572
It's hard work up in here.

788
00:46:22,940 --> 00:46:25,875
I gotta say, being back in here, I don't miss it.

789
00:46:26,209 --> 00:46:27,409
Seems like a headache looking back.

790
00:46:27,711 --> 00:46:28,744
Fucking right it's a headache.

791
00:46:29,045 --> 00:46:32,348
Vendors, purchase orders, licenses.

792
00:46:32,749 --> 00:46:35,050
Every one of these bitches think this is "Pretty Woman."

793
00:46:38,321 --> 00:46:40,389
I need to know if any of your girls knew a guy

794
00:46:40,623 --> 00:46:42,257
liked young trim.

795
00:46:42,558 --> 00:46:45,827
Maybe, like, a few months ago.

796
00:46:46,096 --> 00:46:49,064
He booked a date at his place.

797
00:46:50,100 --> 00:46:52,801
In Vinci? The big house?

798
00:46:54,269 --> 00:46:57,238
No, this place small. In Hollywood.

799
00:46:57,439 --> 00:46:58,607
Took-over home.

800
00:46:58,908 --> 00:46:59,808
You remember where it was?

801
00:47:00,075 --> 00:47:02,811
Go ahead, girl, speak.

802
00:47:05,815 --> 00:47:07,348
I write them down.

803
00:47:07,650 --> 00:47:10,451
Danny says you pay attention to streets,

804
00:47:10,685 --> 00:47:11,986
always know where you are.

805
00:47:14,356 --> 00:47:17,625
This guy, he do anything scary?

806
00:47:17,959 --> 00:47:19,527
Anything might have pissed somebody off?

807
00:47:19,761 --> 00:47:21,429
No. He kind of...

808
00:47:21,630 --> 00:47:23,898
weak, you say?

809
00:47:24,133 --> 00:47:26,667
Just want to watch.

810
00:47:26,968 --> 00:47:28,468
Write it down where you met him.

811
00:47:33,642 --> 00:47:36,577
I hope this goodwill does not go unnoticed on your end, Frank.

812
00:47:36,845 --> 00:47:39,112
Everybody needs friends, see?

813
00:47:39,045 --> 00:47:39,912


814
00:47:45,653 --> 00:47:47,921
This is Hollywood Division Vice Squad.

815
00:47:48,389 --> 00:47:50,690
Please leave your message after the beep and we'll get back to you.

816
00:47:51,059 --> 00:47:53,160
This is Detective Bezzerides

817
00:47:53,461 --> 00:47:56,296
with state police detail 93009.

818
00:47:56,730 --> 00:47:58,819
I was hoping to speak with a vice detective...

819
00:47:59,633 --> 00:48:02,035
If you are satisfied with your message, press one.

820
00:48:16,233 --> 00:48:22,435


821
00:49:10,101 --> 00:49:12,335
- Yeah.  - Yo, you remember that missing girl?

822
00:49:12,603 --> 00:49:13,870
I talked to her old roommate.

823
00:49:14,238 --> 00:49:16,172
Said Vera last called her a couple months ago.

824
00:49:16,540 --> 00:49:18,074
Asked if anybody'd come around looking for her.

825
00:49:18,575 --> 00:49:22,445
I checked her phone records and a call came from a Guerneville address.

826
00:49:22,713 --> 00:49:23,813
How's it going down there?

827
00:49:24,115 --> 00:49:25,515
It's a pain in the ass, you know?

828
00:49:25,750 --> 00:49:27,216
Not much so far.

829
00:49:27,584 --> 00:49:29,718
It's... might be a hooker job, some pimp.

830
00:49:30,053 --> 00:49:32,821
Let me let you go. Catch up tomorrow?

831
00:49:32,989 --> 00:49:34,457
Sure.

832
00:49:34,625 --> 00:49:36,125
Bye.

833
00:49:58,014 --> 00:49:59,581
Wait for me!

834
00:50:31,613 --> 00:50:33,414
# You were a loner #

835
00:50:33,648 --> 00:50:36,917
# You were alive #

836
00:50:37,185 --> 00:50:40,654
# among the walking dead #

837
00:50:42,990 --> 00:50:45,593
# He was a liar #

838
00:50:45,827 --> 00:50:48,762
# would not atone #

839
00:50:49,030 --> 00:50:52,799
# still leaving tonight... #

840
00:50:59,673 --> 00:51:01,474
How's that for detecting?

841
00:51:01,843 --> 00:51:04,344
Caspere had another house. Place he brought girls.

842
00:51:04,746 --> 00:51:07,347
- You check it out?  - No, I don't want to go near it.

843
00:51:07,748 --> 00:51:10,483
And my people ain't exactly proficient in evidence handling.

844
00:51:10,817 --> 00:51:12,218
Figured you'd go in as police,

845
00:51:12,653 --> 00:51:14,120
see what you can, see what I might need to know.

846
00:51:14,655 --> 00:51:17,223
Grab anything that pushed towards Caspere's dealing with land purchases.

847
00:51:17,524 --> 00:51:19,259
Yeah, what's going on with that?

848
00:51:19,660 --> 00:51:22,027
Money. Place is about to be worth a whole lot more.

849
00:51:22,328 --> 00:51:25,164
- This is Hollywood.  - So?

850
00:51:25,498 --> 00:51:29,001
Listen, I've been wanting to ask you,

851
00:51:29,269 --> 00:51:30,702
things shake out like I expect,

852
00:51:31,071 --> 00:51:35,574
this time next year, might be Chief of PD... Vinci.

853
00:51:35,776 --> 00:51:37,476
How'd that be?

854
00:51:37,744 --> 00:51:40,078
Chief? I don't want that, Frank.

855
00:51:40,513 --> 00:51:42,481
Did I ask you if you want that? What's up with you, huh?

856
00:51:42,782 --> 00:51:44,716
I'm lining stuff up for you here.

857
00:51:45,017 --> 00:51:46,652
That job pays 300K a year.

858
00:51:47,019 --> 00:51:49,788
You could hire a hell of a family lawyer for that.

859
00:51:50,055 --> 00:51:53,525
That right there.

860
00:51:55,761 --> 00:52:00,564
You... you remember how we got together?

861
00:52:00,866 --> 00:52:02,133
I remember you dumping a body.

862
00:52:02,434 --> 00:52:06,171
The reasons for all this, all that,

863
00:52:06,438 --> 00:52:08,606
might not exist for me anymore.

864
00:52:08,774 --> 00:52:11,375
You see?

865
00:52:11,643 --> 00:52:14,444
I got no reason to keep at this.

866
00:52:14,779 --> 00:52:17,414
Meaning you'd consider life in prison, what,

867
00:52:17,615 --> 00:52:18,748
a positive?

868
00:52:19,050 --> 00:52:20,483
No, I ain't saying that either.

869
00:52:20,885 --> 00:52:22,986
What, you have other options here I'm not privy to?

870
00:52:23,288 --> 00:52:25,923
Everybody's got the one option,

871
00:52:26,157 --> 00:52:27,991
you want it bad enough.

872
00:52:29,493 --> 00:52:30,694
You used to be a hard man.

873
00:52:30,994 --> 00:52:33,262
- I'm tired.  - Then get some sleep.

874
00:52:33,564 --> 00:52:36,599
After you check the place out.

875
00:52:36,801 --> 00:52:38,768
Get back to me.

876
00:52:38,969 --> 00:52:40,637
And, Ray...

877
00:52:44,408 --> 00:52:46,342
I don't want to hear you talk like that again.

878
00:53:00,123 --> 00:53:01,757
You want another beer, Ray?

879
00:53:02,024 --> 00:53:05,494
No, I... I gotta take off, I guess.

880
00:53:05,762 --> 00:53:08,230
He's keeping you busy.

881
00:53:08,431 --> 00:53:10,098
Yes, ma'am.

882
00:53:19,441 --> 00:53:21,209
You ought to take some time.

883
00:53:21,377 --> 00:53:23,278
A vacation.

884
00:53:23,612 --> 00:53:25,247
Have you ever been to San Miguel de Allende?

885
00:53:25,514 --> 00:53:27,215
- No.  - That's where I'm from.

886
00:53:27,516 --> 00:53:32,020
Mountains, waterfalls, this plaza.

887
00:53:32,321 --> 00:53:34,555
Well, that sounds really nice.

888
00:53:34,857 --> 00:53:37,525
Maybe I could show it to you sometime.

889
00:53:37,893 --> 00:53:41,228
I think the only way I get a vacation is if I croak.

890
00:53:41,530 --> 00:53:43,163
You should get another job, then.

891
00:53:43,465 --> 00:53:45,366
It's too late for that, darlin'.

892
00:53:47,503 --> 00:53:49,036
That and about a million other things.

893
00:53:55,743 --> 00:53:57,244
Your money.

894
00:53:59,915 --> 00:54:01,681
That's not mine.

895
00:54:04,185 --> 00:54:05,119
# He said #

896
00:54:05,486 --> 00:54:10,557
# "I love you, baby, like a miner loves gold #

897
00:54:10,892 --> 00:54:14,561
# and this way you'll never grow old" #

898
00:54:16,931 --> 00:54:18,932
# the noose recovered #

899
00:54:19,199 --> 00:54:22,402
# church and worms #

900
00:55:13,858 --> 00:55:16,726
# I pity the fool #

901
00:55:19,296 --> 00:55:22,799
# I said I pity the fool #

902
00:55:24,802 --> 00:55:31,707
# whoa, I pity the fool, yeah #

903
00:55:32,009 --> 00:55:36,578
# I said I pity the fool, yeah #

904
00:55:40,183 --> 00:55:43,218
# that falls in love with you #

905
00:55:43,520 --> 00:55:45,554
# and expect you to be true #

906
00:55:45,822 --> 00:55:48,189
# oh, I pity the fool #

907
00:55:52,028 --> 00:55:55,531
# look at the people #

908
00:55:55,899 --> 00:55:58,866
# I know you're wondering what they're doing #

909
00:55:59,201 --> 00:56:02,237
# they're just standing there #

910
00:56:02,571 --> 00:56:05,073
# watching you make a fool of me #

911
00:56:05,341 --> 00:56:08,143
# look at the people #

912
00:56:08,544 --> 00:56:11,646
# I know you're wondering what they're doing #

913
00:56:11,948 --> 00:56:14,749
# they're just standing there #

914
00:56:15,083 --> 00:56:17,718
# watching you make a fool of me #

915
00:56:17,953 --> 00:56:19,921
# oh, I pity the fool #

916
00:56:23,258 --> 00:56:24,358
# I pity the fool #

917
00:56:24,693 --> 00:56:26,928
# that falls in love with you... #

918
00:56:35,470 --> 00:56:38,738
# I pity the fool that falls in love with you #

919
00:56:43,711 --> 00:56:46,480
# she'll break your heart one day #

920
00:56:46,814 --> 00:56:49,616
# and then she'll laugh and walk away... #

921
00:56:55,623 --> 00:56:59,425
# look at the people #

922
00:56:59,794 --> 00:57:02,496
# I know you're wondering what they're doing #

923
00:57:02,830 --> 00:57:04,597
# they're just standing there... #

924
00:57:06,299 --> 00:57:09,087
# watching you make a fool of me #

925
00:57:42,897 --> 00:57:45,932
# what a wonderful day #

926
00:57:49,769 --> 00:57:53,605
# to lose it all #

927
00:57:56,843 --> 00:57:59,945
# lose it all #

928
00:58:04,050 --> 00:58:08,086
# what a wonderful way #

929
00:58:11,623 --> 00:58:15,593
# to choose to fall #

930
00:58:18,730 --> 00:58:21,966
# choose to fall #

