1
00:00:08,295 --> 00:00:10,396
{\an8}圣城家园SCG字幕组

2
00:00:14,295 --> 00:00:16,096
{\an8}http://hdscg.com/

3
00:00:18,595 --> 00:00:20,596
{\an8}仅供翻译交流使用

4
00:00:23,395 --> 00:00:25,196
{\an8}禁止用于商业用途

5
00:00:27,495 --> 00:00:29,596
{\an8}协调: 影子

6
00:00:29,945 --> 00:00:31,796
{\an8}翻译: 酱油影

7
00:00:32,095 --> 00:00:34,396
{\an8}翻译: 飘飘行天下

8
00:00:34,945 --> 00:00:36,946
{\an8}翻译: Morning

9
00:00:38,695 --> 00:00:40,846
{\an8}翻译: 鸟生鱼汤

10
00:00:43,395 --> 00:00:45,096
{\an8}翻译: 捞小盐

11
00:00:47,495 --> 00:00:49,596
{\an8}校对: 假探UU

12
00:00:05,513 --> 00:00:07,447
# 输了战争 #
# The war was lost #

13
00:00:07,449 --> 00:00:09,866
# 签了条约 #
# The treaty signed #

14
00:00:09,918 --> 00:00:11,918
# 犯了禁忌 #
# I was not caught #

15
00:00:11,953 --> 00:00:14,170
# 却未被抓 #
# I crossed the line #

16
00:00:14,205 --> 00:00:16,205
# 纵然前赴后继 #
# I was not caught #

17
00:00:16,258 --> 00:00:18,508
# 依旧未果 #
# Though many tried #

18
00:00:18,543 --> 00:00:20,710
# 我巧妙伪装 #
# I live among you #

19
00:00:20,762 --> 00:00:23,046
# 混迹其中 #
# Well disguised #

20
00:00:23,098 --> 00:00:25,465
# 无所谓 #
# Never mind #

21
00:00:25,517 --> 00:00:27,433
# 无所谓 #
# Never mind #

22
00:00:27,469 --> 00:00:31,220
# 我却还过着 旧的生活 #
# I live the life I left behind #

23
00:00:31,273 --> 00:00:36,309
# 真相会永存 也会泯灭 #
# There's truth that lives and truth that dies #

24
00:00:36,361 --> 00:00:41,064
# 我分不清 所以无所谓 #
# I don't know which, so never mind #

25
00:00:43,068 --> 00:00:47,320
# 你已大获全胜 #
# Your victory was so complete #

26
00:00:47,372 --> 00:00:52,075
# 你们有些人想要 #
# Some among you thought to keep #

27
00:00:52,127 --> 00:00:56,496
# 留下生活的纪念 #
# A record of our little lives #

28
00:00:56,498 --> 00:01:00,633
# 穿过的衣服 勺子和刀子 #
# The clothes we wore, our spoons, our knives #

29
00:01:00,669 --> 00:01:04,346
# 以及诸如此类的一切 #
# And all of this expressions of #

30
00:01:04,381 --> 00:01:09,286
# 甜蜜的冷漠 叫爱情 #
# The sweet indifference some call love #

31
00:01:09,784 --> 00:01:14,003
# 高冷的漠然 叫命运 #
# The high indifference some call fate #

32
00:01:14,038 --> 00:01:18,791
# 但我们有 更亲密的名字 #
# But we had names more intimate #

33
00:01:18,793 --> 00:01:23,179
# 这些名字 至深至爱 #
# Names so deep and names so true #

34
00:01:23,214 --> 00:01:26,849
# 于我如血亲 于你如尘土 #
# They're blood to me, they're dust to you #

35
00:01:26,884 --> 00:01:31,971
# 真相会永存 也会泯灭 #
# There's truth that lives and truth that dies #

36
00:01:32,023 --> 00:01:36,509
# 我分不清 所以无所谓 #
# I don't know which, so never mind #

37
00:01:25,692 --> 00:01:28,877
{\an8}真探 第二季第5集

38
00:01:56,264 --> 00:01:57,963
六十六天前
It's been 66 days

39
00:01:57,999 --> 00:02:01,567
警方与涉嫌谋杀Vinci市市政官的嫌疑犯交火
since the alleged murderers of Vinci City Manager Ben Caspere

40
00:02:01,602 --> 00:02:05,838
这也是本州历史上伤亡最严重的火拼之一
engaged police in one of the deadliest shoot-outs in state history.

41
00:02:05,873 --> 00:02:07,707
人称"Vinci大屠杀"的事件
The so-called Vinci Massacre

42
00:02:07,742 --> 00:02:10,743
由Geldof首席检察官画上了句点
was determined closed by Attorney General Geldof,

43
00:02:10,778 --> 00:02:14,113
他利用发布会宣布将参选州长
who used the conference to announce his candidacy for Governor.

44
00:02:14,148 --> 00:02:17,850
Benjamin Caspere是个腐败的人
Benjamin Caspere was a corrupt individual

45
00:02:17,885 --> 00:02:20,486
他被在Vinci制造惨剧的
and he was killed by the dangerous psychopaths

46
00:02:20,521 --> 00:02:22,405
危险分子和变态所杀
who engineered the tragedy in Vinci.

47
00:02:22,440 --> 00:02:24,990
我研究该如何保护
In examining how to protect

48
00:02:25,026 --> 00:02:27,243
本州最为人忽视的地方
the state's most overlooked places,

49
00:02:27,278 --> 00:02:30,279
最终只能得出一个结论
I can finally only come to one conclusion.

50
00:03:11,506 --> 00:03:13,489
州长还未发表任何评论
No comment yet from the Governor.

51
00:03:13,541 --> 00:03:17,243
其它新闻 州际中央铁路走廊工程
In other news, construction is expected to break ground

52
00:03:17,245 --> 00:03:20,329
将于下周开始动工
next week on the state's central rail line.

53
00:03:23,554 --> 00:03:24,903
Vinci花园赌场保安
Velcoro

54
00:03:25,954 --> 00:03:27,503
有什么需要帮忙的?
Help you with something?

55
00:03:28,957 --> 00:03:30,590
做保安?
Security, hmm?

56
00:03:30,625 --> 00:03:32,341
给Frank Semyon打工
Frank Semyon.

57
00:03:34,045 --> 00:03:35,678
别想探听更多
Stick with what you know.

58
00:03:35,713 --> 00:03:38,848
你不必辞职的 我跟你说了
You didn't have to quit. I told you that.

59
00:03:38,883 --> 00:03:42,218
那件事完全不对头
None of that went down right.

60
00:03:42,270 --> 00:03:44,687
州警局插手了
State came in.

61
00:03:44,722 --> 00:03:46,689
最好在他们动手前默默走开
Better to walk before they make you run.

62
00:03:46,724 --> 00:03:48,808
我们可以帮你解决的
We'd have helped you with that.

63
00:03:48,810 --> 00:03:50,776
Geldof结了案 你安全了
Geldof closed the case. You're clear.

64
00:03:50,812 --> 00:03:53,145
他说是那些墨西哥人杀了Caspere?
He's saying the Mexicans did Caspere?

65
00:03:55,483 --> 00:03:58,451
有人来找你问这些事吗?
Anybody come to you asking about that?

66
00:03:58,486 --> 00:04:00,119
Caspere和墨西哥人的事?
Caspere, the Mexicans?

67
00:04:00,154 --> 00:04:03,289
你和Teague共事的时候 他会和你交流吗?
You and Teague, he talk to you much when you were working together?

68
00:04:03,324 --> 00:04:05,324
你来这里做什么 副队?
What did you come here for, Lieutenant?

69
00:04:05,376 --> 00:04:07,877
我想查点有关Dixon的情报
Learned some things about Dixon.

70
00:04:07,912 --> 00:04:09,161
问问你知不知道
Wondered if you knew anything.

71
00:04:09,163 --> 00:04:11,631
知不知道什么?
Anything about what things?

72
00:04:11,666 --> 00:04:15,418
他有很多照片 还有些其它东西
He had a lot of photographs, some other stuff.

73
00:04:15,470 --> 00:04:18,170
可能查了某些人很久
Might've been into some people.

74
00:04:25,313 --> 00:04:27,430
你又买了辆道奇
Bought another Charger.

75
00:04:27,482 --> 00:04:29,098
对
Yeah.

76
00:04:29,150 --> 00:04:32,685
我喜欢好车
I appreciate a good rut.

77
00:04:32,737 --> 00:04:35,571
我得告诉你... 真的很抱歉...
Well, I gotta tell you... sorry about this...

78
00:04:35,607 --> 00:04:37,657
但这些联排式住宅
but these row houses

79
00:04:37,692 --> 00:04:40,276
是供市政公务员住的
are reserved for municipal employees.

80
00:04:40,328 --> 00:04:43,195
既然你现在已经不...
And now that you're not one...

81
00:04:43,197 --> 00:04:45,081
你要驱逐我?
You fucking evicting me?

82
00:04:45,116 --> 00:04:47,416
我让他们给你六十天宽限
Hey, I got them to give you 60 days.

83
00:04:47,452 --> 00:04:49,502
我想自己来跟你说
And I wanted to come tell you myself.

84
00:04:49,537 --> 00:04:50,786
拜托 Ray
Come on, Ray,

85
00:04:50,838 --> 00:04:53,422
你不会想在这里住下去的
you don't want to live here anymore.

86
00:04:59,964 --> 00:05:01,764
我得去上班了
I gotta go to work.

87
00:05:01,799 --> 00:05:03,215
当然
Sure.

88
00:05:17,982 --> 00:05:19,782
谢谢
Thank you.

89
00:05:35,583 --> 00:05:37,249
少了两百
This is short 200.

90
00:05:37,251 --> 00:05:41,459
我跟你说过的 你让我怎么跟Frank先生交代?
I told you about this. What do I tell Mr. Frank?

91
00:05:45,143 --> 00:05:47,570
他买得起啤酒 就能付得起房租
He can buy beer, he can pay the rent.

92
00:05:54,402 --> 00:05:57,770
让他明天准备好钱 不然就要把你交给移民局
Tell him to have it tomorrow or I'll put you on an ICE bus.

93
00:05:57,822 --> 00:05:59,939
移民局 懂吗?
Immigration, do you understand?

94
00:05:59,941 --> 00:06:01,941
就这样
Okay.

95
00:06:07,115 --> 00:06:09,365
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.

96
00:06:12,837 --> 00:06:14,787
性骚扰是种政治手段
Sexual harassment's a political tool.

97
00:06:14,789 --> 00:06:17,123
你表扬她一下 妹子就会请律师
You pay a compliment, a chick lawyers up.

98
00:06:17,175 --> 00:06:19,208
这破事还关乎外表
That shit's about looks, too.

99
00:06:19,293 --> 00:06:22,044
来这里受教育和调情间的区别
Difference between something like what I'm here for and flirting

100
00:06:22,096 --> 00:06:23,379
就是一个男人有多帅
is how good-looking a dude is.

101
00:06:23,431 --> 00:06:25,014
这他妈哪里公平了?
How's that fucking fair?

102
00:06:25,049 --> 00:06:28,634
听着 这种怪罪受害者的本能反应
Now, this reflex to project blame upon the victim

103
00:06:28,686 --> 00:06:32,605
阻碍了我们养成良好的习惯
is going against the sorts of habits we want to encourage.

104
00:06:32,640 --> 00:06:36,776
Bezzerides警探 你对自己的行为有何感受?
Detective Bezzerides, how do you feel about your actions?

105
00:06:36,811 --> 00:06:40,529
我就问一句 你来这里干什么?
Can I just ask, what the fuck are you doing here?

106
00:06:42,150 --> 00:06:44,200
有谁不想被她性骚扰的? 我说得没错吧?
Who wouldn't want her sexually harassing you? Am I right?

107
00:06:44,235 --> 00:06:46,318
听着 你的这种说法
See, that kind of thing there

108
00:06:46,371 --> 00:06:48,704
非常不妥当
could be considered inappropriate.

109
00:06:48,740 --> 00:06:50,906
怎么? 这是在夸她
What? It was a compliment.

110
00:06:50,958 --> 00:06:53,376
没关系 完全没关系
Oh, it's all right. It's all right.

111
00:06:53,411 --> 00:06:56,379
我理解
I understand.

112
00:06:56,414 --> 00:06:58,831
但我不明白
But I don't know.

113
00:07:00,218 --> 00:07:01,417
我能说什么?
I mean, what can I say?

114
00:07:01,469 --> 00:07:03,836
我...
I...

115
00:07:03,888 --> 00:07:07,640
只是很喜欢大肉棒
just really like big dicks.

116
00:07:09,260 --> 00:07:10,893
对
Yeah.

117
00:07:10,928 --> 00:07:12,561
不能光有长度
It's not just length.

118
00:07:12,597 --> 00:07:16,148
人人都讲要够长 但是... 长是很好
Everybody's always talking length, but... it's fine.

119
00:07:17,351 --> 00:07:20,436
但粗也很重要
I mean, girth, too.

120
00:07:20,488 --> 00:07:24,323
我特别想要那种手铐铐不住的那种
I really want to have trouble handcuffing the thing, like.

121
00:07:24,358 --> 00:07:26,776
唔 我不确定...
Um, I'm not sure...

122
00:07:26,828 --> 00:07:29,195
这可能会被认为...
you know, that might be taken...

123
00:07:29,197 --> 00:07:31,163
认为什么?
What?

124
00:07:31,199 --> 00:07:33,199
我以为你想让我跟大家分享
I thought you wanted me to share.

125
00:07:33,251 --> 00:07:35,785
在这里讲很安全 对吧?
This is a safe circle, right?

126
00:07:35,837 --> 00:07:37,787
- 当然安全  - 嘿 让她继续分享
- Hell, yes, it is.  - Hey, let her share, man.

127
00:07:37,839 --> 00:07:39,455
- 对  - 对
- Yeah.  - Yeah.

128
00:07:42,627 --> 00:07:45,511
这个人刚刚在洛杉矶区史上最惨烈的
This man just received a commendation for bravery

129
00:07:45,546 --> 00:07:47,797
枪战中获得英勇的殊荣
for one of the worst firefights in LA County history.

130
00:07:47,849 --> 00:07:51,434
我想没人会质疑Woodrugh先生的杀人才能
I don't think anyone would argue Mr. Woodrugh's facility for killing.

131
00:07:51,469 --> 00:07:52,388
够了 该死...
All right, damn it...

132
00:07:52,389 --> 00:07:54,746
我们都想尽快把这件事解决
We're amenable to putting this entire matter behind us.

133
00:07:54,806 --> 00:07:58,057
我想忘掉这个可怕的事情
I just want to forget that this terrible thing ever happened

134
00:07:58,109 --> 00:08:00,025
继续回归正常生活
and get on with getting my life back.

135
00:08:00,061 --> 00:08:03,863
我什么都没做
I did not do anything.

136
00:08:03,898 --> 00:08:06,031
我是无辜的
And I am innocent.

137
00:08:06,067 --> 00:08:09,151
黑山 潘达哈村
Black Mountain. Pandhar Village.

138
00:08:09,203 --> 00:08:12,071
我不在那
I wasn't there.

139
00:08:12,073 --> 00:08:13,739
我不在潘达哈
I wasn't at Pandhar.

140
00:08:13,825 --> 00:08:15,825
你那时候杀了多少人?
How many men did you kill then?

141
00:08:15,877 --> 00:08:18,577
在Vinci市又杀了多少?
How many at Vinci?

142
00:08:18,579 --> 00:08:22,414
我们希望撤销所有涉及这一事件的指控
We want any violation involving this incident dropped.

143
00:08:22,416 --> 00:08:26,418
我们还要删除Lindel小姐早前的假释违规记录
And we want Miss Lindel's earlier probation violation expunged.

144
00:08:26,471 --> 00:08:28,587
是你的公关做的 对吧?
That was your publicist, right?

145
00:08:28,589 --> 00:08:31,841
收买小报想要中伤他?
Got the tabloids to try smearing him?

146
00:08:31,893 --> 00:08:34,927
现在你倒同意撤销指控了?
And now you feel okay about dropping the allegation?

147
00:08:34,979 --> 00:08:37,596
我在治疗中学到很多
I've learned a lot in therapy.

148
00:08:37,598 --> 00:08:39,265
听从内心更高能量的声音
I'm listening to my higher power.

149
00:08:39,317 --> 00:08:41,267
我在Vinci市救过人
I saved lives in Vinci.

150
00:08:41,269 --> 00:08:43,769
哦 能抵消
Oh, and did they fully account

151
00:08:43,771 --> 00:08:46,188
无辜中枪死去的市民吗?
for whose bullets killed those civilians?

152
00:08:46,240 --> 00:08:49,158
是 可以
Yeah, they did.

153
00:08:49,193 --> 00:08:52,495
我只是不想发生在我身上的事情再发生在别人身上
I just don't want what happened to me to happen to anybody else.

154
00:08:52,530 --> 00:08:55,498
Woodrugh警探现在负责保险欺诈案
Detective Woodrugh works insurance fraud now.

155
00:08:55,533 --> 00:08:57,833
你成功让他远离公路了
So you got him off the street.

156
00:08:57,869 --> 00:08:59,418
恭喜你
Congratulations.

157
00:08:59,453 --> 00:09:01,670
我们还要谈吗?
Are we still talking?

158
00:09:01,706 --> 00:09:03,789
你想和解 那就和解
You're going for the deal, so take it.

159
00:09:03,841 --> 00:09:05,424
她他妈的是个谎话精
She is a fucking liar.

160
00:09:05,459 --> 00:09:08,210
骂人的话我们都已经说过了
I think we're past all the name-calling.

161
00:09:08,262 --> 00:09:12,381
我们本来可以再提起民事诉讼的 Woodrugh先生
We could still pursue a civil case, Mr. Woodrugh.

162
00:09:12,433 --> 00:09:15,718
是Woodrugh警探
Detective Woodrugh.

163
00:09:17,305 --> 00:09:18,938
价格变了
Rate's changed.

164
00:09:18,973 --> 00:09:21,473
看在多年情份上 给个友情价吧
I need you to offer me an old-times'-sake price.

165
00:09:21,475 --> 00:09:24,143
Frank 拜托 就这经济形势?
Frank, man, this economy?

166
00:09:24,195 --> 00:09:26,028
{\an8}美国喝酒一般会让酒保开单子 最后喝完一起结

167
00:09:24,195 --> 00:09:26,028
给我开个单子 Lloyd
Start me a tab, Lloyd.

168
00:09:33,204 --> 00:09:34,787
你是Frank Semyon?
Frank Semyon?

169
00:09:35,706 --> 00:09:37,456
你们是谁?
Who are you?

170
00:09:37,491 --> 00:09:40,659
我们叫Gonzales 在这工作的
Our name is Gonzales. We work here.

171
00:09:44,298 --> 00:09:46,131
怎么可能 朋友?
How's that, friend?

172
00:09:46,167 --> 00:09:48,884
我们跟Santos有协议
We had an arrangement with Santos.

173
00:09:50,504 --> 00:09:52,838
没人见过他
Nobody's seen him.

174
00:09:52,890 --> 00:09:54,506
挺长时间了
Long time now.

175
00:09:54,559 --> 00:09:57,259
我们听说了
We heard.

176
00:09:57,311 --> 00:09:59,345
是时候敲定一下你我之间的协议了
So it is time to ratify our arrangement.

177
00:10:04,652 --> 00:10:06,268
我们从来没什么协议
We never had one.

178
00:10:09,023 --> 00:10:10,990
我也不需要跟人合作
And I don't need partners.

179
00:10:14,278 --> 00:10:16,445
从哪个门进就哪个门出吧 朋友
Door's in the same place, amigo.

180
00:10:26,707 --> 00:10:28,540
你还有事吗 Cisco Kid?
Can I help you, Cisco Kid?

181
00:10:26,707 --> 00:10:29,540
{/an8}Cisco Kid是头戴宽沿草帽的墨西哥骑士虚拟形象

182
00:10:44,108 --> 00:10:46,442
操?
The fuck?

183
00:10:46,477 --> 00:10:48,894
Frank 你他妈在这干什么?
Frank, what the fuck are you doing in here?

184
00:10:48,896 --> 00:10:51,113
你今天很放松嘛
Ship seems a little loose today.

185
00:10:52,566 --> 00:10:55,034
小睡片刻而已 Frank
Micro naps, Frank.

186
00:10:55,069 --> 00:10:56,869
米开朗基罗也午睡的
Michelangelo took 'em.

187
00:10:58,122 --> 00:11:00,205
你记得Archeron废物管理公司吗?
You remember Archeron Waste Management?

188
00:11:00,241 --> 00:11:01,740
你把它抛售了
You sold it off.

189
00:11:01,792 --> 00:11:05,077
因为我们把沿走廊的山谷都用重金属污染了遍
After we sprinkled that corridor valley with heavy metals.

190
00:11:05,079 --> 00:11:06,712
所以?
So?

191
00:11:06,747 --> 00:11:09,715
所以倒闭了
So it's closed.

192
00:11:09,750 --> 00:11:12,751
我卖给的那个人 Ali Komunyakaa
The guy I sold it to, Ali Komunyakaa,

193
00:11:12,753 --> 00:11:15,337
我从没见他喝完一杯啤酒
who I never saw finish a beer,

194
00:11:15,389 --> 00:11:19,091
他喝醉了 在Ventura市跌下山崖
gets drunk and drives off a hillside in Ventura.

195
00:11:19,143 --> 00:11:22,695
事出突然
All of a sudden.

196
00:11:22,731 --> 00:11:25,771
不是人人都有我们一样强健的体魄 Frank
Not everyone has our physical fortitude, Frank.

197
00:11:25,772 --> 00:11:27,252
比如Caspere就没有
Like Caspere.

198
00:11:29,288 --> 00:11:31,821
Ben可是他妈的纵欲过度
Ben was king fuck of pad pulling.

199
00:11:31,823 --> 00:11:33,907
你跟拉皮条的打交道
You deal with pimps,

200
00:11:33,959 --> 00:11:36,826
就会惹一身骚 Frank
you get pimpish results, Frank.

201
00:11:38,547 --> 00:11:40,747
几个月前
Couple months back,

202
00:11:40,799 --> 00:11:44,501
你说有外围资金对赌场感兴趣
you said that there were outside interests looking at the poker room.

203
00:11:45,754 --> 00:11:47,337
是谁?
Who?

204
00:11:47,339 --> 00:11:49,339
国外的资金
Foreign interests.

205
00:11:51,226 --> 00:11:54,010
什么鸟人 我不记得了
Some fuck. I don't remember.

206
00:11:54,012 --> 00:11:57,514
那之后没再联系
I haven't been in touch since.

207
00:11:57,516 --> 00:11:59,682
你儿子没搬去Oakland
Your boy hasn't moved to Oakland.

208
00:11:59,684 --> 00:12:00,934
我注意到了
I've noticed.

209
00:12:00,986 --> 00:12:02,936
是没有
No.

210
00:12:02,988 --> 00:12:05,021
但你搬去Glendale了
But you moved to Glendale.

211
00:12:05,023 --> 00:12:06,523
可惜啊
Shame, that.

212
00:12:06,575 --> 00:12:08,358
唔
Mm-hmm.

213
00:12:09,361 --> 00:12:10,527
你儿子Tony也可惜了
And your kid Tony.

214
00:12:10,579 --> 00:12:14,197
我家里人不关你的事 小子
My family ain't your concern, boychik.

215
00:12:14,249 --> 00:12:17,333
你一直通过赌场组织妓女
You've been running girls through the poker room.

216
00:12:17,369 --> 00:12:20,203
我也可以睁一只眼闭一只眼
Not so much as a heads up to me.

217
00:12:22,290 --> 00:12:25,425
不过你每月得再多付百分之五
Penance is an extra five a month.

218
00:12:25,460 --> 00:12:27,927
出去吧 Frank
Get out of my office, Frank.

219
00:12:27,963 --> 00:12:30,180
下回等我请你来你再来
Next time, wait for an invitation.

220
00:12:31,800 --> 00:12:33,850
请继续你的"工作"吧
I'll let you get back to your process, then,

221
00:12:33,885 --> 00:12:35,718
米开朗基罗
Michelangelo.

222
00:12:37,439 --> 00:12:40,023
Semyon先生
Mr. Semyon.

223
00:12:40,058 --> 00:12:43,276
别对我指手画脚 溪生战役狗
You don't direct me, Khe Sanh motherfucker.

224
00:12:40,058 --> 00:12:43,276
{/an8}越南战争中的一场战役 此处指其为越南人

225
00:12:43,277 --> 00:12:44,766
我是中国人
I'm Chinese.

226
00:12:44,801 --> 00:12:47,530
{\an8}暗指天安门事件

227
00:12:44,801 --> 00:12:47,530
那你他妈的倒是站到坦克前去啊
Then, go stand in front of the fucking tank.

228
00:12:47,566 --> 00:12:49,699
Velcoro先生是州里反腐调查中
Mr. Velcoro was a person of interest

229
00:12:49,734 --> 00:12:51,568
的利害关系人
in a state investigation into corruption.
213 

230
00:12:51,620 --> 00:12:53,069
调查最终毫无结果
Which yielded nothing.

231
00:12:53,071 --> 00:12:55,321
在Vinci枪战之后 他离职了
And after the firefight in Vinci, he resigned

232
00:12:55,373 --> 00:12:57,657
然而还处在审查中 还有一项药物滥用指控
under scrutiny and pending a charge on substance abuse.

233
00:12:57,742 --> 00:12:59,375
那是毫无根据的谣传
That's anecdotal hearsay.

234
00:12:59,411 --> 00:13:02,412
没有记录显示我的客户使用毒品
There's no record of my client being reprimanded for drug use.

235
00:13:02,414 --> 00:13:04,609
你可以提交一份血液检测报告吗 Velcoro先生?
Would you submit to a blood test, Mr. Velcoro?

236
00:13:04,610 --> 00:13:06,179
当然可以 大人
Absolutely, Your Honor.

237
00:13:06,214 --> 00:13:07,133
最后 大人
Finally, Your Honor,

238
00:13:07,169 --> 00:13:09,636
我们对Velcoro先生的父权提出质疑
we are contesting Mr. Velcoro's paternity

239
00:13:09,671 --> 00:13:12,505
希望能确定他是否实属亲生父亲
and wish to establish whether he even qualifies for father's rights.

240
00:13:12,557 --> 00:13:14,307
- 反对  - 操你妈的
- Objection.  - Fucking assholes.

241
00:13:14,342 --> 00:13:15,842
Velcoro先生 你这么做对本案毫无益处
You're not helping your case, Mr. Velcoro.

242
00:13:15,894 --> 00:13:17,010
Brune太太在怀孕前
Mrs. Brune was the victim of an assault

243
00:13:17,062 --> 00:13:18,678
曾遭受性侵害
during the period of conception.

244
00:13:18,730 --> 00:13:21,514
她相信强奸者才是她儿子的亲生父亲
She believes the rapist to be the biological father of her child.

245
00:13:21,566 --> 00:13:24,517
我抚养那孩子长大 现在还在养
I raised that boy. I'm raising him.

246
00:13:24,569 --> 00:13:26,319
他是谁的无关紧要...
It doesn't matter where he comes...

247
00:13:26,354 --> 00:13:28,104
我们的立场是这至关重要
Our position is that it matters a great deal.

248
00:13:30,942 --> 00:13:32,192
我那么信任你
I trusted you.

249
00:13:32,244 --> 00:13:34,327
- 我那么信任你  - 你什么意思?
- I trusted you.  - What does that mean?

250
00:13:34,362 --> 00:13:37,363
双方当事人请勿互相交谈
I'll instruct the parties to refrain from addressing one another.

251
00:13:37,415 --> 00:13:38,998
结束
Period.

252
00:13:39,034 --> 00:13:41,751
现在我会申请亲子鉴定和药物检测
Now, I'm going to order a paternity and toxicology test.

253
00:13:41,786 --> 00:13:43,253
在两项结果出来之前
I'm ordering supervised visitation

254
00:13:43,288 --> 00:13:46,289
我决定给予监督探视权
until both the paternity and toxicology results are in.

255
00:13:46,291 --> 00:13:48,958
等等 等一下
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.

256
00:13:49,010 --> 00:13:51,127
怎么 我去看自己儿子还要陌生人在场?
What, I gotta get a stranger to chaperone me and my son?

257
00:13:51,129 --> 00:13:54,347
我已经做了裁决 别逼我 Velcoro先生
I've delivered my verdict. Don't push me, Mr. Velcoro.

258
00:13:54,382 --> 00:13:57,634
在这节骨眼上任何裁决修改都不会对你有利
Any revision at this point would not be in your favor.

259
00:14:14,035 --> 00:14:16,736
她从来没那么看过我
She never looked at me like that before.

260
00:14:16,788 --> 00:14:18,705
充满恨意
Like she hated me.

261
00:14:18,740 --> 00:14:20,373
你真的能通过测试?
You really gonna test clean?

262
00:14:20,408 --> 00:14:22,075
是
Yeah.

263
00:14:22,127 --> 00:14:24,494
是 已经戒了60天了
Yeah, 60 days now.

264
00:14:24,496 --> 00:14:27,964
这一仗我要竭尽全力
I want to fight this however I can.

265
00:14:27,999 --> 00:14:30,250
那就多筹点现金
Then pull some more cash together.

266
00:14:30,302 --> 00:14:33,169
不管你哪来的钱 肯定要花上大价钱
Tax-free or not, this is gonna get expensive.

267
00:14:42,230 --> 00:14:44,314
你急需用钱?
You need more money?

268
00:14:45,433 --> 00:14:47,183
我也急需用钱
I need more money.

269
00:14:47,235 --> 00:14:49,185
我们现在可是战时配资
We're war rationing.

270
00:14:49,237 --> 00:14:50,987
那我多做点工作
More work, then.

271
00:14:51,022 --> 00:14:54,023
我可以在勒克斯多上一个班次
I can, you know, do double shifts at the Lux.

272
00:14:54,075 --> 00:14:55,858
是为了你孩子吗?
This is for your kid?

273
00:14:57,529 --> 00:15:00,780
我倒有个工作适合你
I might have a job for you.

274
00:15:00,832 --> 00:15:02,615
买了废物管理公司那个人死了
The guy who bought the waste company

275
00:15:02,667 --> 00:15:05,118
就是铁路走廊工程里的公司
we used in the corridor died.

276
00:15:05,170 --> 00:15:07,704
地方已经清理出来了
Place has been cleaned out.

277
00:15:07,706 --> 00:15:09,789
我要开始听从我的直觉
I'm gonna start listening to the hot feeling

278
00:15:09,841 --> 00:15:12,592
这种不详的感觉
I got in the back of my neck.

279
00:15:12,627 --> 00:15:14,043
我要你去跟踪Blake
I want you to tail Blake.

280
00:15:14,045 --> 00:15:16,262
我想知道他不在我身边时的生活
I want to know what his life is outside of me.

281
00:15:16,298 --> 00:15:18,598
我没问题
I can do that.

282
00:15:20,468 --> 00:15:22,302
你怎么会有这种感觉?
What's your feeling?

283
00:15:22,354 --> 00:15:24,053
店里的妓女?
Running girls?

284
00:15:25,140 --> 00:15:26,939
我是在忏悔吗?
Am I in confession?

285
00:15:26,975 --> 00:15:28,808
不是
No.

286
00:15:28,860 --> 00:15:31,361
只是没见过你这样
Just, um, never seemed like you.

287
00:15:31,396 --> 00:15:33,313
可能只是你观察力不够
Maybe you're just not very perceptive.

288
00:15:35,700 --> 00:15:37,617
问你点事儿?
Ask you something?

289
00:15:38,787 --> 00:15:41,954
你真觉得是那些墨西哥人杀了Caspere?
You think those Mexes really did Caspere?

290
00:15:44,159 --> 00:15:46,075
我不知道
I don't know.

291
00:15:46,077 --> 00:15:49,495
什么监视...
It was bullshit surveillance and...

292
00:15:50,832 --> 00:15:53,966
那破房子竟然是他妈的毒品工厂
the crash pad was a fucking meth factory.

293
00:16:02,227 --> 00:16:04,761
Caspere死了
Caspere died

294
00:16:04,763 --> 00:16:07,930
拉了我五百万美元现金陪葬
with five million of my dollars cash.

295
00:16:09,651 --> 00:16:12,268
Stan被人杀了
Stan's killed.

296
00:16:12,320 --> 00:16:15,071
我被挤出了铁路走廊工程
I'm squeezed out of the rail corridor.

297
00:16:16,324 --> 00:16:18,608
敌人不肯揭下面纱 Raymond
The enemy won't reveal itself, Raymond.

298
00:16:19,778 --> 00:16:22,945
让我更加难以报复
Stymies my retribution.

299
00:16:22,947 --> 00:16:25,915
就好像...
It's like, uh...

300
00:16:25,950 --> 00:16:28,785
勾起欲火又不让人发泄
blue balls in your heart.

301
00:16:31,623 --> 00:16:34,340
我看看勒克斯还有没有多余的班次
I'll see about some shifts at the Lux.

302
00:16:34,376 --> 00:16:35,958
但你跟着Blake
But follow Blake.

303
00:16:36,010 --> 00:16:38,511
为了让我安心 他有点太平静了
He's gotten too smooth for my peace of mind.

304
00:16:53,228 --> 00:16:56,479
哦 Paulie 不
Oh, Paulie. Oh, no.

305
00:16:56,531 --> 00:16:58,948
我要结婚了
I'm getting married.

306
00:16:58,983 --> 00:17:01,150
我爱她
I love her.

307
00:17:11,413 --> 00:17:12,745
她的名字叫Emily
Her name is Emily.

308
00:17:12,797 --> 00:17:14,580
她怀孕几个月了?
How pregnant is she?

309
00:17:14,632 --> 00:17:16,666
差不多四个月了
Almost four months.

310
00:17:18,052 --> 00:17:20,052
老天啊
Mother of God.

311
00:17:24,309 --> 00:17:26,759
那么多蠢事你偏偏...
Of all the stupid...

312
00:17:29,013 --> 00:17:32,181
你是个帅哥白人小伙儿
You're a good-looking white man.

313
00:17:32,233 --> 00:17:35,184
而你却偏偏要去混混火拼...
And you want to get in shoot-outs and...

314
00:17:35,186 --> 00:17:38,187
偏偏要做别人的丈夫
become somebody's husband.

315
00:17:38,189 --> 00:17:40,523
你本该大有作为
You could do anything you want.

316
00:17:41,993 --> 00:17:43,493
好吧
Okay.

317
00:17:47,031 --> 00:17:50,917
要是我是个男人 我早有了全世界
If I was a man, I'd have had the world.

318
00:17:52,287 --> 00:17:54,370
蠢货
Dumb bastard.

319
00:18:09,938 --> 00:18:12,188
不 不
No, no.

320
00:18:12,223 --> 00:18:14,056
不不不
No, no, no.

321
00:18:14,058 --> 00:18:16,025
不 妈的
No. Fuck.

322
00:18:21,533 --> 00:18:23,616
你拿走了
You took it.

323
00:18:23,651 --> 00:18:25,368
你怎么能这样?
How the fuck could you?

324
00:18:25,403 --> 00:18:27,069
拿了什么 Paulie?
Took what, Paulie?

325
00:18:27,956 --> 00:18:29,572
你知道的!
You know what!

326
00:18:31,075 --> 00:18:32,575
钱啊!
The money!

327
00:18:32,627 --> 00:18:35,077
我从阿富汗带回来的钱啊
The money I brought back from Afghanistan.

328
00:18:35,079 --> 00:18:38,080
他妈的两万美金 Cynthia
20 fucking thousand dollars, Cynthia.

329
00:18:38,082 --> 00:18:42,251
那个袋子? 哦 Paulie
That bag? Oh, Paulie.

330
00:18:42,253 --> 00:18:44,837
你已经回来四年了
You've been back four years.

331
00:18:44,889 --> 00:18:46,639
我以为那是你留给我的东西
I thought that was something you left for me.

332
00:18:46,674 --> 00:18:50,476
什么... 我藏着是等你来找吗?
Something I... I hid for, what, you to find?

333
00:18:51,813 --> 00:18:53,763
那是我的资金
That's my stake.

334
00:18:53,765 --> 00:18:55,348
我要有个孩子了
I'm having a kid.

335
00:18:55,400 --> 00:18:57,316
这我怎么会知道?
Well, how would I know that?

336
00:18:58,269 --> 00:19:00,653
我他妈为了这笔钱拼死拼活
I fucking bled for that money.

337
00:19:00,688 --> 00:19:03,439
你把钱花哪儿去了 赌博吗?
What did you do with it, slots?

338
00:19:03,441 --> 00:19:06,526
听我说
Now listen.

339
00:19:06,578 --> 00:19:08,744
你知道我失业了
You knew I was out of work.

340
00:19:08,780 --> 00:19:11,364
我完全有理由期望得到一点帮助
I had every reason to expect a little help.

341
00:19:11,416 --> 00:19:13,032
我正在组建一个家庭
I'm making a family.

342
00:19:13,084 --> 00:19:14,917
我知道那对你这种人来说 屁都不是
I know that don't mean shit to somebody like you,

343
00:19:14,953 --> 00:19:16,786
可它对我很重要!
but it fucking matters to me!

344
00:19:16,788 --> 00:19:21,007
你他妈别跟我说 我不在乎家庭
Don't you fucking tell me I don't care about family.

345
00:19:21,042 --> 00:19:23,042
我曾经是个舞者
I was a dancer,

346
00:19:23,094 --> 00:19:25,211
但我怀了你
but I carried you.

347
00:19:25,263 --> 00:19:28,965
我一个人把你养大
And I brought you up alone.

348
00:19:30,018 --> 00:19:32,184
我本来完全可以把你打掉
You could have been a scrape job.

349
00:19:32,220 --> 00:19:35,021
你根本就不知道是谁的
You wouldn't even know whose it was.

350
00:19:38,393 --> 00:19:41,110
你毁了我的事业
You ruined my career,

351
00:19:41,145 --> 00:19:44,480
你个忘恩负义的混蛋
you ungrateful asshole.

352
00:19:46,701 --> 00:19:49,318
我怀了你九个月
I carried you for nine months

353
00:19:49,370 --> 00:19:52,822
你变成这个怪胎以后
and I've been carrying you ever since

354
00:19:52,824 --> 00:19:54,874
我还一直养着你
with your weirdness.

355
00:19:56,327 --> 00:19:58,628
你个怪人
You're strange.

356
00:19:58,663 --> 00:20:01,797
你所有的好朋友 都是男孩
All your good friends, the boys.

357
00:20:03,134 --> 00:20:06,385
是 我了解你 Paulie
Yeah, I know about you, Paulie.

358
00:20:06,421 --> 00:20:08,220
是 我知道
Yeah, I know.

359
00:20:09,674 --> 00:20:12,508
闭上你的臭嘴
You shut your fucking mouth.

360
00:20:12,510 --> 00:20:16,562
你个蛇蝎毒妇
You fucking poisoned cooze.

361
00:20:21,936 --> 00:20:24,987
Paul啊
Paul.

362
00:20:25,023 --> 00:20:28,024
喂 Paulie?
Paulie?

363
00:20:28,026 --> 00:20:30,276
等等
Wait.

364
00:20:31,913 --> 00:20:36,332
我上周拿到的 警察一直就没有收获
I got this last week. The police never found anything.

365
00:20:36,367 --> 00:20:39,285
你... 你说你会调查它
And you... you said you'd look into it.

366
00:20:39,337 --> 00:20:42,338
她把这个留在邮政信箱?
She left this, what, at a PO box?

367
00:20:42,373 --> 00:20:44,206
寄到我的旧地址去了
Attached to my old address.

368
00:20:44,258 --> 00:20:46,208
过了一段时间 我们才收到账单
The bill took a while to find us here.

369
00:20:46,260 --> 00:20:49,211
等我付了钱 他们就给了我这些
When I paid it, they gave me the contents.

370
00:20:49,213 --> 00:20:51,297
你安顿好了吗?
You settling in okay?

371
00:20:58,306 --> 00:21:00,022
这是什么意思?
What's it mean?

372
00:21:00,058 --> 00:21:01,474
看起来像是个派对
Looks like a party.

373
00:21:01,526 --> 00:21:03,359
你有跟警局说吗?
Did you follow up with Sheriff's?

374
00:21:03,394 --> 00:21:07,947
他们一无所获 我什么都没听到
They got nothing. I hear nothing.

375
00:21:07,982 --> 00:21:10,533
我不想把这个交上去
I didn't want to hand this over.

376
00:21:10,568 --> 00:21:13,569
我觉得... 我们谈话的时候
I thought... when we talked,

377
00:21:13,571 --> 00:21:16,455
我觉得我可以信任你
I thought I could trust you.

378
00:21:24,582 --> 00:21:26,632
我去
Shit.

379
00:21:46,320 --> 00:21:47,853
我操
Fuck me.

380
00:21:47,905 --> 00:21:49,405
你不是因爆粗口而被警告了吗?
Ain't you been warned about that kind of talk?

381
00:21:58,783 --> 00:22:00,366
抱歉让你待这下面
Sorry you're down here.

382
00:22:00,418 --> 00:22:04,120
虽然我知道你不相信 但告发你的不是我
And I know you don't believe it, but I never put you under that bus.

383
00:22:04,122 --> 00:22:06,505
警长已经知道我们的事了
Sheriff already knew about you and me.

384
00:22:06,541 --> 00:22:08,124
我担了全部的责任
I took full responsibility.

385
00:22:08,126 --> 00:22:10,843
是 没错 你是个白马王子
Yeah, sure. You're a real prince.

386
00:22:10,878 --> 00:22:13,295
过几个月 你就会离开这里的
You'll be out of here in a few months.

387
00:22:15,600 --> 00:22:18,017
听着 有人一直想搞你 妹子
Look, somebody was trying to do you, girl.

388
00:22:18,052 --> 00:22:20,886
要是你再多几个朋友 可能就没那么容易被搞垮
And if you had a few more friends, it might have been harder to get done.

389
00:22:23,858 --> 00:22:26,142
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.

390
00:22:26,144 --> 00:22:29,729
你还记得我们几个月前去收的房子吗?
You remember that foreclosure we served a couple months back?

391
00:22:29,781 --> 00:22:31,647
那个失踪的女孩 Vera
The missing girl, Vera.

392
00:22:31,649 --> 00:22:33,149
记得
Yeah.

393
00:22:33,151 --> 00:22:35,868
你说你调查过她原来室友的通话记录
You said you had looked into her old roommate's phone records,

394
00:22:35,903 --> 00:22:38,320
发现了Vera最后打电话的地址
found an address where Vera last called from?

395
00:22:38,372 --> 00:22:41,624
对 是在北边
Yeah, it was up north.

396
00:22:41,659 --> 00:22:43,993
能把那个给我吗?
Could you get me that?

397
00:22:44,045 --> 00:22:46,378
你已经在这里了
You're here now.

398
00:22:48,800 --> 00:22:50,916
这件事你帮我 我答应
Help me out with this and I promise

399
00:22:50,968 --> 00:22:54,053
做一次彻底的发自内心的反省
to do a fearless and searching moral inventory.

400
00:22:57,008 --> 00:22:58,974
好吧
All right.

401
00:23:31,292 --> 00:23:32,958
忠诚很重要
Loyalty's important

402
00:23:33,010 --> 00:23:35,711
通常也很痛苦
and usually painful.

403
00:23:35,713 --> 00:23:39,682
也许有天你会想问问自己
One day you might find cause to ask yourself

404
00:23:39,717 --> 00:23:42,852
你正在经历的痛苦还有没有尽头
what the limit is to some pain you're experiencing

405
00:23:42,887 --> 00:23:45,304
然后...
and...

406
00:23:45,356 --> 00:23:48,307
你会发现根本没有尽头
you'll find out there is no limit at all.

407
00:23:49,393 --> 00:23:52,228
苦海 无边
Pain is inexhaustible.

408
00:23:54,315 --> 00:23:56,732
败下阵来的终究是人
It's only people that get exhausted.

409
00:25:43,841 --> 00:25:45,307
- Tony 你好吗?  - Osip
- Tony, how are you?  - Osip.

410
00:25:45,343 --> 00:25:47,476
随时恭候
Always a pleasure.

411
00:25:47,511 --> 00:25:49,845
支持是最重要的
Approval is most essential.

412
00:25:49,897 --> 00:25:51,897
让我看看
Let me see.

413
00:26:51,075 --> 00:26:52,708
这些书全是扯淡
These books are bullshit.

414
00:26:52,743 --> 00:26:56,045
不管他们到底在这儿搞什么 我都想不明白
Whatever they were actually making here, I can't figure it out.

415
00:26:56,080 --> 00:26:59,081
这不奇怪 我们可以让事情水落石出
That's expected. We can wipe that clear.

416
00:27:00,167 --> 00:27:02,668
你呢? 你过得怎样?
How about you? How are you doing?

417
00:27:02,720 --> 00:27:04,920
这个Santos在哪里?
Where is this Santos character?

418
00:27:04,922 --> 00:27:06,422
这地方曾经的主人
Used to own the place.

419
00:27:06,424 --> 00:27:08,640
不论他在哪儿 他都不会回来的
Wherever he is, he ain't coming back.

420
00:27:08,676 --> 00:27:11,510
这是堕落之都 Frank
This is backslide city, Frank.

421
00:27:11,562 --> 00:27:15,564
我知道赌场里在发生什么
I know what's going on out there in the poker room now.

422
00:27:15,599 --> 00:27:17,733
我们不只是运营夜店 对吧
We're not just running some club. Come on.

423
00:27:17,768 --> 00:27:22,488
现在是 我们在谋生
What's happening now is we are surviving.

424
00:27:23,491 --> 00:27:25,107
知道吗? 我们在重建
All right? We are rebuilding.

425
00:27:25,109 --> 00:27:28,160
我们相遇的时候 你几乎脱离这一切了
You were almost out of this kind of thing when we met.

426
00:27:28,195 --> 00:27:30,412
你是有规划的
It was like you had a design.

427
00:27:30,448 --> 00:27:34,283
一旦有人偷走了我们所有钱
That design does not work

428
00:27:34,285 --> 00:27:38,370
那个规划就实施不了了
once someone has stolen all of our money.

429
00:27:38,422 --> 00:27:41,924
当我深陷泥潭时 规划也实施不了
The design does not work when I am knee-deep in dirt.

430
00:27:41,959 --> 00:27:44,343
你不会想把一个孩子带到这种环境中来
You don't bring a kid into a situation like this.

431
00:27:44,378 --> 00:27:47,129
什么环境? 这是什么意思?
To what? Where is this going?

432
00:27:47,181 --> 00:27:49,214
打断一下
Excuse me?

433
00:27:49,266 --> 00:27:51,633
首先 我认为这是我们俩的事
I thought this was a you and me thing, first off.

434
00:27:51,685 --> 00:27:54,803
没错 但肯定有不止于此的事情
It is, but it has to be about something more than this.

435
00:27:54,805 --> 00:27:56,388
天啊 Frank 我是帮了你
God, Frank, I helped, I know,

436
00:27:56,440 --> 00:27:58,807
但我不想成为一个街头混混的妻子
but I don't want to be some fucking gangster's wife.

437
00:27:58,809 --> 00:28:01,443
你知道那个词会让我不高兴
You know that word bothers me.

438
00:28:01,479 --> 00:28:04,229
因为我没有向这个世界索求什么
Because, me, I didn't ask for this world.

439
00:28:04,281 --> 00:28:08,233
我拿到了就是... "混混"吗?
I took it as... "gangster"?

440
00:28:09,703 --> 00:28:12,654
我生来就处在阶级斗争的错误那一方
I was born drafted on the wrong side of a class war.

441
00:28:12,706 --> 00:28:14,706
所以别说混混这种词
So fuck that gangster shit.

442
00:28:14,742 --> 00:28:18,043
你现在是个拉皮条的 Frank 交易者
You're a pimp now, Frank. A dealer.

443
00:28:18,079 --> 00:28:19,878
我不会跟那些人混在一起
I don't mix with those people.

444
00:28:19,914 --> 00:28:21,880
你知道的
You know that.

445
00:28:21,916 --> 00:28:25,334
我一直都在努力挣扎 好让我们可以...
I'm trying to stay above water long enough so that we can...

446
00:28:25,336 --> 00:28:28,670
那些人 他们做的一切 不管怎样都会做
those people, everything they do, they would do anyway.

447
00:28:28,722 --> 00:28:31,673
犯罪是存在于人类欲望之上的
Crime exists contingent on human desire.

448
00:28:31,675 --> 00:28:33,725
这是给我留的活路
These were the avenues left me.

449
00:28:33,761 --> 00:28:36,178
那这一切的有效期呢?
And what's the expiration date for all this?

450
00:28:36,180 --> 00:28:37,513
我们的孩子?
Our child?

451
00:28:37,515 --> 00:28:39,314
我们的孩子是规划的一部分
Our child is part of the design.

452
00:28:39,350 --> 00:28:41,517
正当合法也是规划的一部分
And being legitimate is part of the design.

453
00:28:41,569 --> 00:28:44,353
先不说这个 你爱我吗?
Right now it's on hold. You love me?

454
00:28:45,356 --> 00:28:46,822
那你跟我同心协力
Then you're with me.

455
00:28:46,857 --> 00:28:50,075
又或许...
And maybe...

456
00:28:50,111 --> 00:28:52,778
你爱我 但不想支持我
you love me if you're not with me.

457
00:28:52,830 --> 00:28:55,864
我理解
I understand.

458
00:28:55,866 --> 00:28:58,033
但说出来
But say so

459
00:28:58,035 --> 00:29:00,786
这样我们就不必提心吊胆
so we don't have to be on these goddamn eggshells.

460
00:29:00,838 --> 00:29:03,589
仿佛我不是我 你不是你
Like I'm not me and you're not you.

461
00:29:11,849 --> 00:29:13,799
我觉得我不会有孩子了 Frank
I don't think I can have kids, Frank.

462
00:29:13,851 --> 00:29:17,386
我一直假装 骗自己不是那样的
I've been pretending that it might not be that way.

463
00:29:17,438 --> 00:29:19,605
我以为有可能...
I thought maybe...

464
00:29:19,640 --> 00:29:23,559
但我独自找过医生
but I went to the doctor alone.

465
00:29:23,561 --> 00:29:25,561
我做过不止一次
I had more than one.

466
00:29:25,563 --> 00:29:27,863
我做过不止一次手术
I had more than one operation, I mean.

467
00:29:27,898 --> 00:29:29,565
- 我做过三次  - 三次?
- I had three.  - Three?

468
00:29:29,567 --> 00:29:31,066
- 你他妈...  - 在我20岁的时候
- The fuck are you...  - In my 20s.

469
00:29:31,118 --> 00:29:34,953
我们都认为我不会有孩子了 我生育不了
We don't think I can have one, a child. I can't.

470
00:29:34,989 --> 00:29:37,322
你...
You...

471
00:29:37,374 --> 00:29:40,459
你 可为什么现在告诉我?
You. But why now, huh?

472
00:29:40,494 --> 00:29:43,996
也许我现在没那么有魅力了
Maybe I'm less appealing in current circumstances.

473
00:29:44,048 --> 00:29:46,915
为什么不在我当时最得意的时候告诉我这个?
Why not tell me this when I'm on top of the world?

474
00:29:46,917 --> 00:29:49,251
现在 我是我
Well, now I'm me.

475
00:29:49,303 --> 00:29:52,054
你是你了
And you're you.

476
00:29:52,089 --> 00:29:55,257
现在我们都打开天窗说亮话了
And here we both are out in the open.

477
00:29:55,259 --> 00:29:57,092
所以谁爱谁?
So who loves who?

478
00:30:06,820 --> 00:30:08,403
这只鸡看起来不错
This chicken looks good.

479
00:30:08,439 --> 00:30:10,689
你用了那本食谱还是...?
Did you use that recipe or...?

480
00:30:10,741 --> 00:30:13,108
- 是的  - Carlotta的食谱?
- I did, yeah.  - Carlotta's recipe?

481
00:30:13,160 --> 00:30:16,828
是的 我希望成品跟她做的一样好
I did. I hope it comes out as well as she makes it.

482
00:30:16,864 --> 00:30:18,614
- 给  - 非常好
- Here.  - Very nice.

483
00:30:18,616 --> 00:30:21,250
- 哦  - 谢谢
- Oh.  - Thank you.

484
00:30:21,285 --> 00:30:22,951
谢谢
Thank you.

485
00:30:23,003 --> 00:30:26,205
我们在说 生完孩子后
You know, we were just saying that it'd be a good idea

486
00:30:26,257 --> 00:30:28,924
让妈咪来住段时间是个好主意
for Mami to come stay with us a while after the baby comes.

487
00:30:28,959 --> 00:30:31,843
婚礼呢? 赶紧啊 我说
And the wedding? Speed up, I say.

488
00:30:31,879 --> 00:30:33,712
你正在筹备 要加快速度啊
You're doing it, get on with it.

489
00:30:33,764 --> 00:30:35,464
你会希望我在这里的
And you're gonna want me here.

490
00:30:35,466 --> 00:30:37,266
你不知道自己面对的是什么
You have no idea what you're in for.

491
00:30:37,301 --> 00:30:39,468
夜长梦多啊
Long nights. No sleep.

492
00:30:39,520 --> 00:30:41,303
也许会有点挤
Might get kind of cramped.

493
00:30:41,305 --> 00:30:44,389
我睡客厅的沙发 我不会抱怨的
I'll take the sofa in the living room. I don't complain.

494
00:30:44,441 --> 00:30:48,310
我四岁时 在船上待了一整个星期 我都没抱怨
An entire week on a boat, I'm four. I don't complain.

495
00:30:48,312 --> 00:30:51,063
在船体下层八天
Down in the hull eight days.

496
00:30:51,115 --> 00:30:52,898
- 妈妈  - 什么?
- Mama.  - What?

497
00:30:52,950 --> 00:30:54,866
他会逮捕我吗?
Is he gonna arrest me?

498
00:30:54,902 --> 00:30:57,986
感谢上苍 你不用骑摩托车了
Thank Jesus they got you off that motorcycle.

499
00:30:57,988 --> 00:31:01,156
好多了 现在你穿西装了
Much better. And you wear a suit now.

500
00:31:01,158 --> 00:31:03,158
他很帅
He's very handsome.

501
00:31:12,469 --> 00:31:14,503
几个月前
A couple of months back.

502
00:31:14,505 --> 00:31:16,838
我说起领养的事情
When I talked about adoption.

503
00:31:16,840 --> 00:31:18,006
Jordan 我不想...
Jordan, I don't want...

504
00:31:18,058 --> 00:31:20,842
我一直在想 你还小的时候
I was thinking about you as a kid,

505
00:31:20,894 --> 00:31:23,395
要是有人照顾你
what it would have meant

506
00:31:23,430 --> 00:31:25,647
那会怎么样呢?
if somebody had looked out for you.

507
00:31:25,683 --> 00:31:28,317
要是有人照顾你
If somebody had taken care of you.

508
00:31:28,352 --> 00:31:29,985
现在说已经晚了
There's no bandwidth for that right now.

509
00:31:30,020 --> 00:31:32,354
我跟你一起 Frank
I'm with you, Frank.

510
00:31:32,406 --> 00:31:34,356
我爱你
I love you.

511
00:31:34,408 --> 00:31:38,026
但我不想看见你迷失现在的自己
But I don't want to see you lose who you've become.

512
00:31:38,078 --> 00:31:40,028
我说的不是钱
And I don't mean the money.

513
00:31:42,032 --> 00:31:44,333
我想谢谢你这样看待我
And I want to thank you for seeing me like that.

514
00:31:44,368 --> 00:31:47,202
你现在一定要这么活着 让我崩溃
It fucking tears me up the way you're having to live now.

515
00:31:47,204 --> 00:31:49,338
我的问题是 你不上床
My problem is with you not coming to bed.

516
00:31:49,373 --> 00:31:53,625
我们俩每天晚上都喝得烂醉
With both of us being half in the bag each night.

517
00:31:53,677 --> 00:31:55,794
我会找到解决方式
I will find a way out.

518
00:31:55,846 --> 00:31:59,548
领养的事 你态度很明确
The adoption, you were so definite.

519
00:31:59,600 --> 00:32:04,386
我想你是在跟曾经孩童时的自己说不
I think you were saying no to the kid that you once were.

520
00:32:04,438 --> 00:32:07,389
你当时说是别人的问题
You were saying he was somebody else's problem.

521
00:32:17,151 --> 00:32:19,568
我要回家了
I'm going home.

522
00:32:22,623 --> 00:32:25,290
你应该花点时间跟我在一起
You should make some time to join me.

523
00:32:51,235 --> 00:32:53,652
# 很难醒来... #
# waking up is harder... #

524
00:32:53,687 --> 00:32:56,855
在证物室查了一整天
Spent all day in state's evidence control.

525
00:32:56,907 --> 00:32:59,574
然后去了Vinci警局
Then Vinci PD.

526
00:32:59,610 --> 00:33:01,443
没有人知道
Nobody had an answer.

527
00:33:01,495 --> 00:33:03,245
凭空消失了
They just vanished.

528
00:33:03,280 --> 00:33:05,781
好吧 看着很像
Well, looks like them.

529
00:33:05,833 --> 00:33:08,617
但这些可以在Caspere死之前就被拿走的
But these would have to be taken before Caspere died.

530
00:33:10,120 --> 00:33:12,454
最近怎么样?
How you been?

531
00:33:12,456 --> 00:33:14,423
酒喝得更多了
Drinking more.

532
00:33:15,626 --> 00:33:18,627
我的手已经废了
My hands get fucked up.

533
00:33:18,679 --> 00:33:21,046
不停颤抖 你呢?
Shake, like. You?

534
00:33:21,098 --> 00:33:23,215
跟自己说了很多
Talking to myself a lot.

535
00:33:23,267 --> 00:33:25,851
又开始嗜酒 算是个变化吧
Sticking to booze, though. That's new.

536
00:33:31,291 --> 00:33:34,426
那么Caspere保险箱里的钻石不在证物室了
So the diamonds from Caspere's safe deposit went missing from evidence.

537
00:33:34,461 --> 00:33:37,796
也不是不可能发生的
It ain't exactly unheard of.

538
00:33:39,049 --> 00:33:40,932
这个女孩消失了
This girl's missing.

539
00:33:40,968 --> 00:33:44,803
就在Caspere的尸体出现之前不久
Disappeared shortly before Caspere's body turned up.

540
00:33:44,805 --> 00:33:47,389
那些援交聚会 我们听说的都是?
What did we keep hearing about escort parties?

541
00:33:47,441 --> 00:33:49,474
有势力的人
Powerful men.

542
00:33:49,476 --> 00:33:52,861
我不能找出所有人 但这是州参议员
I couldn't make them all, but that's a state senator.

543
00:33:52,896 --> 00:33:54,730
看这个
Look at this one.

544
00:33:54,782 --> 00:33:56,531
是Caspere
Caspere.

545
00:33:56,567 --> 00:33:58,734
这种聚会肯定不许拍照的
This ain't the type of party allows cameras.

546
00:33:58,786 --> 00:34:01,286
你怎么看? 用来勒索的?
What do you think? Some kind of blackmail?

547
00:34:01,321 --> 00:34:04,623
你真的以为我们理清了Caspere的案子吗?
You really think we cleared the Caspere case?

548
00:34:05,876 --> 00:34:07,375
那些墨西哥人?
Those Mexicans?

549
00:34:07,411 --> 00:34:10,045
他们手里有Caspere家里的东西
They had items from Caspere's house there.

550
00:34:10,080 --> 00:34:11,713
还有指纹 你在乎他们?
Fingerprints. What do you care?

551
00:34:11,749 --> 00:34:14,549
是这些人把你困在笼里的 Bezzerides
These people put you in a cage, Bezzerides.

552
00:34:14,585 --> 00:34:17,803
这个女孩失踪了
This girl's gone missing.

553
00:34:17,838 --> 00:34:20,172
没人在乎
Nobody cares.

554
00:34:20,174 --> 00:34:23,975
内陆被污染的地区突然寸土寸金
The interior's poisoned and suddenly worth billions,

555
00:34:24,011 --> 00:34:26,011
没人在乎
nobody cares.

556
00:34:26,013 --> 00:34:28,647
一群人被乱枪射死
Bunch of people got shot to shit,

557
00:34:28,682 --> 00:34:31,233
也没有人在乎
nobody fucking cares.

558
00:34:34,021 --> 00:34:37,773
好吧 我不再是警察了
Well, I'm not a cop anymore.

559
00:34:37,825 --> 00:34:40,192
听说 你也不再是侦探了
And you're not a detective last I heard.

560
00:34:42,029 --> 00:34:46,031
没错 你给某个重操旧业的暴徒当保镖
Nope, you do security for some comeback mobster

561
00:34:46,033 --> 00:34:47,365
我记录证物
and I log evidence.

562
00:34:47,417 --> 00:34:49,701
我做咨询的
I do consultation.

563
00:34:49,753 --> 00:34:53,505
你应该辞职的 太大材小用了
And you should get out. You're too good for 'em.

564
00:34:53,540 --> 00:34:55,707
有那个小子的消息吗?
You hear about the kid?

565
00:34:55,759 --> 00:34:58,710
我听说 欺诈调查?
I mean, fraud investigations?

566
00:34:58,712 --> 00:35:01,630
那天他是个十足的勇士
He was a fucking god warrior that day.

567
00:35:01,682 --> 00:35:04,466
是啊 我跟他聊过了
Yeah. I talked to him.

568
00:35:04,518 --> 00:35:07,052
他太惨了
He's miserable.

569
00:35:07,054 --> 00:35:08,220
是个执行任务的好手
Belongs in the field.

570
00:35:08,222 --> 00:35:10,272
那他也应该辞职
Then he should quit, too.

571
00:35:12,442 --> 00:35:15,443
为什么Dixon没看出来那是个毒品窝?
Why didn't Dixon make that place for a cookhouse, huh?

572
00:35:15,479 --> 00:35:17,479
我不知道
I don't know.

573
00:35:17,531 --> 00:35:19,114
因为他是个脑子进水的酒鬼
'Cause he's a wet brain alky.

574
00:35:19,149 --> 00:35:22,284
我有了个新的计划
I have this new program, see.

575
00:35:22,369 --> 00:35:24,452
因为在我们这种
Because my powers of influence

576
00:35:24,488 --> 00:35:27,823
不上台面的关系之间 我根本不能左右什么
are so meager in this sublunar world of ours,

577
00:35:27,875 --> 00:35:31,209
所以我试着尽量不去让别人失望
I try to limit the people I can disappoint.

578
00:35:31,245 --> 00:35:32,627
而且我分得清自己的职责
And I make sure to know the difference

579
00:35:32,663 --> 00:35:35,213
和别人的职责
between my obligations and somebody else's.

580
00:35:40,838 --> 00:35:45,590
# 分开时难 #
# breaking up is harder #

581
00:35:45,642 --> 00:35:48,977
# 别亦难... #
# than it seems... #

582
00:35:49,012 --> 00:35:51,730
不要那样 这个... 这...
Don't do that. It was... it was...

583
00:35:51,765 --> 00:35:54,399
见到你很高兴
it was good seeing you.

584
00:35:54,434 --> 00:35:56,601
我都快记不得还有你了
I didn't realize you had been on my mind.

585
00:35:58,272 --> 00:36:02,741
# 壁炉边上的画像 #
# pictures on the mantel #

586
00:36:02,776 --> 00:36:07,028
# 在呼唤你的名字 #
# speak your name #

587
00:36:07,080 --> 00:36:10,282
# 轻柔地唤起遗忘的旋律 #
# softly like forgotten tunes #

588
00:36:10,334 --> 00:36:15,287
# 让人忘记苦痛... #
# just outside the sound of pain... #

589
00:36:24,298 --> 00:36:27,265
TCM上面的Lee Marvin的电影
Some Lee Marvin movie on TCM.

590
00:36:31,305 --> 00:36:33,555
换个轻快的吧
Maybe something light.

591
00:36:33,607 --> 00:36:35,941
看什么都行
I don't care what we watch.

592
00:37:07,174 --> 00:37:08,924
什么情况?
What's it matter?

593
00:37:08,976 --> 00:37:10,976
是你老板甩手不干了的
Your boss moved off all this.

594
00:37:11,011 --> 00:37:13,395
- 一了百了  - 这就是我要说的
- Pretty cleanly, too.  - That's my point.

595
00:37:13,430 --> 00:37:15,597
我们结束了Vinci的调查 Geldof也宣布了
We closed the Vinci investigation and Geldof announces

596
00:37:15,649 --> 00:37:18,183
竞选州长并突然为此大肆筹款
a governor's run with a suddenly massive war chest.

597
00:37:18,185 --> 00:37:20,018
所以他是拿到了他的那份 这又是什么情况?
So he had his hand out. That what this is?

598
00:37:20,020 --> 00:37:22,520
你得到了你的那份? 我的呢?
You holding your hand out? Where's my cut?

599
00:37:22,572 --> 00:37:25,357
一个真正的司法部长可以做得更多
A real attorney general could do a lot of good in this state.

600
00:37:25,409 --> 00:37:26,691
她跟你说过那个失踪的女孩了吗?
Has she got to you with her missing girl?

601
00:37:26,743 --> 00:37:29,611
而你 怎么的 你要找麻烦吗?
And you, what, are you just looking for trouble?

602
00:37:31,949 --> 00:37:33,865
我要执行任务
I need to be in the field.

603
00:37:33,867 --> 00:37:35,867
不然的话我没办法开心起来
I'm not happy either how things played.

604
00:37:35,869 --> 00:37:39,120
Geldof的行为让Vinci的权力阶层与
Geldof's actions are the clearest indication of collusion

605
00:37:39,172 --> 00:37:42,257
上层州内机构的勾结昭然若揭
between the Vinci power structure and the larger state institutions.

606
00:37:42,292 --> 00:37:44,426
给未来的州长找麻烦
And it wouldn't hurt your job prospects

607
00:37:44,511 --> 00:37:46,544
不会影响你的前程吗
having dirt on the future governor.

608
00:37:46,546 --> 00:37:50,715
我在重组一个机密的特别调查小组
I'm putting together a confidential special investigation.

609
00:37:50,717 --> 00:37:53,385
既定目标是追踪Irina Rulfo
Stated goal is to track down Irina Rulfo,

610
00:37:53,387 --> 00:37:55,303
那个去典当行当东西 造成今天这一切的女孩
the girl who pawned that shit, brought you all to this place.

611
00:37:55,355 --> 00:37:57,389
你知道她从没被逮捕
You know she was never brought in.

612
00:37:57,391 --> 00:37:58,890
真正的目标是什么?
What's the real purpose?

613
00:37:58,892 --> 00:38:01,476
找出是谁杀了Caspere
Finding out who killed Caspere.

614
00:38:01,528 --> 00:38:03,228
揭露Vinci警局 市长办公室
Uncovering evidence of collusion

615
00:38:03,230 --> 00:38:05,030
司法部长以及任何其他的
between Vinci PD, mayor's office,

616
00:38:05,065 --> 00:38:06,815
州立机构之间的勾结
AG, and any other state bodies.

617
00:38:06,867 --> 00:38:08,533
你知道我不再是警察了
You know I'm not a cop anymore.

618
00:38:08,568 --> 00:38:10,402
你还有许可证 我查过了
You have your PI license. I checked.

619
00:38:10,454 --> 00:38:11,987
我可以把你选派为州检察官
I could detail you as a state attorney's

620
00:38:12,039 --> 00:38:13,905
调查失踪人口的特派员
investigator into a missing person.

621
00:38:13,957 --> 00:38:17,075
我需要那些不会引起注意的人
I need people who aren't gonna ping on our radar.

622
00:38:17,077 --> 00:38:18,243
如果走漏了消息
Word gets out what we're looking for,

623
00:38:18,295 --> 00:38:19,828
他们可以像上次一样将其扼杀
they could shut it down like last time.

624
00:38:19,880 --> 00:38:22,380
我有工作了
I got a job.

625
00:38:24,418 --> 00:38:26,418
多谢了 但我拒绝
Thanks, but no.

626
00:38:27,587 --> 00:38:29,421
你的工作能让孩子回到你身边吗?
That job gonna get you your kid back?

627
00:38:33,226 --> 00:38:34,759
你都知道些什么?
What do you know about him?

628
00:38:34,811 --> 00:38:37,062
我知道事情对你没那么有利
I know it's not looking good for you.

629
00:38:38,265 --> 00:38:39,931
州检察官办公室可以替你
State Attorney's office could intercede

630
00:38:39,933 --> 00:38:42,317
与家庭事务部进行斡旋
on your behalf with Family Services.

631
00:38:42,352 --> 00:38:44,436
提出建议 证词
Recommendations, testimony.

632
00:38:44,488 --> 00:38:47,939
我能保证孩子回到你的身边
I could make sure you keep your boy.

633
00:38:53,447 --> 00:38:56,114
好吧 他们从没找到录像还有硬盘
Well, they never found the camera and the hard drive.

634
00:38:58,869 --> 00:39:00,618
我也不认为向我开枪的人
I don't think the person who shotgunned me

635
00:39:00,620 --> 00:39:04,089
是那天在街上乱枪扫射的疯子之一
was one of those maniacs at the shoot-out either.

636
00:39:04,124 --> 00:39:06,124
顺便说一下...
While we're talking...

637
00:39:08,628 --> 00:39:11,963
我想去北边看看
I want to look at some of this land up north.

638
00:39:12,015 --> 00:39:14,265
也许在妓女的派对上会有些线索
Might have a line on those hooker parties, too.

639
00:39:14,301 --> 00:39:16,551
很多现金交易
A lot of money there.

640
00:39:16,603 --> 00:39:19,471
如果真的有个地方进行交易的话 那里不能错过
If it's a place, deals go down, we need to look at it.

641
00:39:19,473 --> 00:39:20,889
你的状况不可能去查的
You can't be cleared for this.

642
00:39:20,941 --> 00:39:22,390
她在休假
She's taking vacation time.

643
00:39:22,442 --> 00:39:25,026
我会派她作为机密调查员
I'm placing her as a confidential investigator.

644
00:39:25,062 --> 00:39:26,978
就是说我不需要给她注册
Means I don't have to register her.

645
00:39:26,980 --> 00:39:28,730
我可以追踪钻石那条线索
I can follow up on the diamonds.

646
00:39:28,782 --> 00:39:31,116
为什么出现在Caspere那里 为什么会丢失
Why Caspere had them. Why they're missing.

647
00:39:31,151 --> 00:39:32,951
为什么这个女孩拍照留了证据
Why the girl had photographs of them.

648
00:39:32,986 --> 00:39:35,703
我猜我的关键问题是 为什么是我?
I guess my million-dollar question is why me?

649
00:39:35,739 --> 00:39:37,789
你已经辞职了
You're out of the system.

650
00:39:37,824 --> 00:39:40,575
你了解Vinci警局
You know Vinci PD.

651
00:39:40,627 --> 00:39:43,328
有正确的动机 你能查出那些勾结和腐败
Properly motivated, you're a good bet to get the dirt.

652
00:39:44,831 --> 00:39:47,298
Velcoro 好好想想
Think it over, Velcoro.

653
00:39:48,718 --> 00:39:51,386
亡羊补牢永远不晚
Never too late to start all over again.

654
00:40:02,933 --> 00:40:05,767
你让我的孩子跟我
You let me keep my kid,

655
00:40:05,819 --> 00:40:07,569
我就干
I'm in.

656
00:40:08,655 --> 00:40:11,439
那就开始吧 得抓紧时间了
Get started. You're on the clock.

657
00:40:11,491 --> 00:40:13,024
每天都要向我汇报
I want daily reports.

658
00:40:14,528 --> 00:40:17,912
你不是认为我是这些人里最差的吗?
Wasn't it you who thought I was the worst of these people?

659
00:40:19,416 --> 00:40:22,917
我知道关于你杀人的传言 根本是狗屁
Saw that rumor about you killing a guy was bullshit.

660
00:40:22,953 --> 00:40:24,953
就觉得其他的传言或许也不可信
Figured maybe the rest of it was, too.

661
00:40:25,005 --> 00:40:27,205
你怎么决定那只是传言的?
How'd you decide it was just a rumor?

662
00:40:27,257 --> 00:40:29,374
我以为你知道
I thought you knew.

663
00:40:30,710 --> 00:40:32,043
他们抓到凶手了
They caught the guy.

664
00:40:32,095 --> 00:40:35,547
我以为你前妻告诉你了
I assumed maybe your ex told you.

665
00:40:37,968 --> 00:40:40,935
什么叫抓到凶手了?
What do you mean caught the guy?

666
00:40:40,971 --> 00:40:42,387
几周前
A few weeks back,

667
00:40:42,389 --> 00:40:45,440
在Venice有个家伙因为性骚扰被拘留了
guy got pulled in for sexual assault in Venice.

668
00:40:45,475 --> 00:40:47,559
DNA与六件未解决的强奸案相匹配
DNA matched six unsolved rapes,

669
00:40:47,561 --> 00:40:50,728
包括你前妻的那次
including your ex-wife's kit.

670
00:40:51,898 --> 00:40:54,232
好像会被判终身监禁
He'll get life, sounds like.

671
00:41:00,790 --> 00:41:02,907
给我结果
Get results.

672
00:41:02,959 --> 00:41:05,243
我会确保孩子回到你身边
I'll make sure you keep your kid.

673
00:41:33,018 --> 00:41:35,735
Frank 多谢你来
Frank, thanks for coming.

674
00:41:35,771 --> 00:41:38,605
我的态度是你的人欠我一些地皮
My position is you people owe me some land.

675
00:41:38,657 --> 00:41:41,074
用这个说服董事会还是很困难的
I'd have a hard time convincing my board of that.

676
00:41:43,361 --> 00:41:45,245
想像一下五年来 走廊的项目
Imagine word of how that corridor's

677
00:41:45,280 --> 00:41:48,114
是怎样被提上日程的
gotten bought up over the past five years.

678
00:41:48,166 --> 00:41:50,533
又是怎样变得一文不值的
How exactly it came to be so cheap.

679
00:41:57,008 --> 00:41:59,375
我不觉得这会对任何人有好处
I can't see that being of any interest.

680
00:41:59,427 --> 00:42:04,380
废弃处理设施污染了中央山谷附近的农田和公园
A waste removal service poisons park and farmland along the central valleys.

681
00:42:04,432 --> 00:42:06,766
一个转战房地产开发的
A major California landowner

682
00:42:06,802 --> 00:42:09,552
加州地产商已经进驻了
committed to real estate development steps in.

683
00:42:09,588 --> 00:42:11,721
你就快成功了
You're reaching.

684
00:42:11,756 --> 00:42:15,775
Archeron废物管理公司已经废除了
Archeron Waste Management is dissolved.

685
00:42:15,811 --> 00:42:19,445
我卖给的那个家伙自己玩砸了
The guy I sold it to ran himself off the road.

686
00:42:19,481 --> 00:42:21,781
这件事你听说了吗?
You know anything about that?

687
00:42:22,984 --> 00:42:25,034
也许还是有些东西适合你的
There might still be something for you.

688
00:42:25,070 --> 00:42:26,736
为什么这么说
Why I called.

689
00:42:26,738 --> 00:42:29,239
我来问你 你听过Caspere
Let me ask, have you ever heard of Caspere

690
00:42:29,241 --> 00:42:33,710
收藏了一些电影吗?
possessing a collection of films?

691
00:42:33,745 --> 00:42:35,962
自制的影片
Home movies.

692
00:42:35,997 --> 00:42:37,797
有个硬盘 里面全都是那些影片
A hard drive full of them.

693
00:42:39,301 --> 00:42:42,051
如果你有兴趣为我们做些什么...
If you're interested in doing something for us...

694
00:42:43,588 --> 00:42:45,805
也许可以让你重新回到走廊上来
it could put you back in the corridor.

695
00:42:49,394 --> 00:42:51,427
有人拿到了硬盘
Somebody's got that hard drive.

696
00:42:51,479 --> 00:42:55,064
我知道警方在他的两处房子里都没找到
I know the police never found it in either of his houses.

697
00:42:55,100 --> 00:42:56,766
那些墨西哥人呢?
What about the Mexicans?

698
00:42:56,768 --> 00:42:58,101
杀了Caspere?
Did Caspere?

699
00:42:58,103 --> 00:42:59,402
我不是侦探
I'm no detective,

700
00:42:59,437 --> 00:43:01,738
但也许是个正确的方向
but it might be a good place to start.

701
00:43:01,773 --> 00:43:04,107
如果你确定是他们杀了人
If you believe they're the ones that did it.

702
00:43:10,782 --> 00:43:13,283
五个区
Five parcels,

703
00:43:13,285 --> 00:43:15,118
商业用地
gifted,

704
00:43:15,170 --> 00:43:17,253
我来找那个硬盘
I find that hard drive.

705
00:43:46,318 --> 00:43:48,318
哦 是啊 我记得你
Oh, yes, I remember you.

706
00:43:48,370 --> 00:43:51,621
对吗? 我能为你做些什么?
Correct? How can I help you?

707
00:43:51,656 --> 00:43:54,457
我是来帮你的 医生
I'm here to help you, Doc.

708
00:43:54,492 --> 00:43:58,077
我来帮你保证你整的容不会毁掉
I'm here to help you keep all that cosmetic work intact.

709
00:43:59,664 --> 00:44:01,881
我想不起来我们有什么可以聊的 长官
I can't imagine we have anything to talk about, sir.

710
00:44:01,917 --> 00:44:04,334
上次谈话我配合得很好
I fully cooperated with you last we spoke.

711
00:44:04,336 --> 00:44:06,469
好吧 也许是我的问题
Well, maybe that's on me

712
00:44:06,504 --> 00:44:08,721
没有问到点子上
not asking the right questions.

713
00:44:12,677 --> 00:44:16,012
你 Chessani 妓女还有贩卖人口
You and Chessani, girls, human trafficking.

714
00:44:16,064 --> 00:44:17,931
你给她们隆胸 隆鼻
You do their implants, nose jobs.

715
00:44:17,983 --> 00:44:21,150
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.

716
00:44:21,186 --> 00:44:22,769
我是精神病医生
I'm a psychiatrist.

717
00:44:22,821 --> 00:44:25,939
以整容为第二职业的精神病医生
With a secondary concentration in reconstructive surgery.

718
00:44:25,991 --> 00:44:27,857
你 Chessani Caspere
You, Chessani, Caspere,

719
00:44:27,909 --> 00:44:30,326
你们的历史比你交代的久远多了
you went back farther than you made out.

720
00:44:31,613 --> 00:44:33,696
老实交代那些姑娘的事情
The girls, spill.

721
00:44:33,748 --> 00:44:36,950
你对暴力的补偿性措施
Your compensatory projection of menace

722
00:44:37,002 --> 00:44:38,868
恰恰表明你没那么暴力
is a guarantor of its lack.

723
00:44:38,870 --> 00:44:41,921
同时也彰显了
And it says something about the depths

724
00:44:41,957 --> 00:44:44,040
你的感知错误之深
of your misperceptions.

725
00:45:01,893 --> 00:45:03,276
我今天过得可不顺心
Kind of day I've had,

726
00:45:03,311 --> 00:45:06,396
打得你皮开肉绽 我或许还能开心点儿
seeing you pop a few stitches might start to make up for it.

727
00:45:06,398 --> 00:45:09,365
绿豆眼睛王八蛋
Pin-eyed motherfucker.

728
00:45:09,401 --> 00:45:11,617
那些皮条派对
Hooker parties.

729
00:45:11,653 --> 00:45:15,038
你口中的上流人物
What you'd call affluent men.

730
00:45:15,073 --> 00:45:16,739
Caspere参加过
Caspere attended.

731
00:45:18,243 --> 00:45:19,292
说吧
Go.

732
00:45:19,327 --> 00:45:22,495
我... 我只负责给姑娘做手术
I just... I just do work on girls.

733
00:45:22,547 --> 00:45:24,247
给她们隆胸
Make eights into 10s.

734
00:45:24,249 --> 00:45:26,666
确保她们在吃药 仅此而已
Make sure they have the proper prescriptions, that's it.

735
00:45:34,509 --> 00:45:36,142
那个派对类似安全屋
The parties are a safe place,

736
00:45:36,177 --> 00:45:37,760
有钱有势之人得以秘密集会
a conclave for men of influence.

737
00:45:37,762 --> 00:45:41,514
再跟我扯什么动机 我就挖烂你脸上拉过的皮
Talk motivations or I'll dig into that face-lift and yank.

738
00:45:45,520 --> 00:45:48,988
Caspere跟Tony Chessani商量出派对的想法
Caspere concocted the idea of the parties with Tony Chessani.

739
00:45:49,024 --> 00:45:51,941
Tony是个拉皮条的 却有政治抱负
Tony's a pimp with political ambition.

740
00:45:51,993 --> 00:45:55,194
他的父亲没有参与这些集会
His father doesn't participate in the gatherings.

741
00:45:55,246 --> 00:45:56,946
Tony这项业务使他和那些
Tony's service makes him friends

742
00:45:56,998 --> 00:45:59,165
你说过的上流人物成了朋友
with those men of affluence you mentioned.

743
00:45:59,200 --> 00:46:02,118
为Caspere经手的交易打下了人脉基础
Lays the groundwork for deals that Caspere facilitated.

744
00:46:02,170 --> 00:46:03,336
还有什么?
What else?

745
00:46:03,371 --> 00:46:05,955
我... 我觉得两个人都利用这个机会
I th... I think both men used the occasions

746
00:46:06,007 --> 00:46:09,292
搜刮潜在资料 以便敲诈他们的客人
to compile potential blackmail material on their guests.

747
00:46:09,294 --> 00:46:12,512
传闻Ben手头有很多
Rumored Ben had footage

748
00:46:12,547 --> 00:46:14,630
重要人物的录像
of various important people.

749
00:46:14,632 --> 00:46:15,965
比如McCandless
McCandless.

750
00:46:16,017 --> 00:46:17,633
谁?
Who?

751
00:46:17,685 --> 00:46:19,552
他是Santa Clara铁路公司的老板
He's the president of Santa Clara Railroad Company.

752
00:46:19,604 --> 00:46:22,021
现在这个公司缩水了 改叫Catalast
It's smaller now. Called Catalast.

753
00:46:28,813 --> 00:46:30,863
你和Chessani一家老朋友了
You go back with the Chessanis.

754
00:46:33,485 --> 00:46:36,035
把他的第一个妻子送进了精神病院
You put his first wife in a mental hospital.

755
00:46:36,071 --> 00:46:38,821
是的 我尽我所...
Yeah, I did every...

756
00:46:38,823 --> 00:46:41,157
尽我所能...
I did everything...

757
00:46:43,078 --> 00:46:45,628
我对Helene倾尽了全力
I did everything I could for Helene.

758
00:46:47,382 --> 00:46:49,298
她很难适应Chessani家的
Certain traditions of the Chessani patriarchs

759
00:46:49,334 --> 00:46:52,085
某些陈年家规
she had a difficult time with.

760
00:46:52,137 --> 00:46:54,170
他们...
They are...

761
00:46:54,222 --> 00:46:58,174
你可以说 他们是很有"创造力"的一家
you might say, a highly inventive family.

762
00:47:08,153 --> 00:47:11,571
回到现场 心里肯定不好受吧
Might be tough to get back into that scene.

763
00:47:11,606 --> 00:47:14,857
但也不是承受不住 对吧?
But not impossible, right?

764
00:47:14,859 --> 00:47:17,276
挑那些实心的
Look for the pieces that are solid,

765
00:47:17,328 --> 00:47:18,528
还没有中空
that haven't been hollowed out yet

766
00:47:18,580 --> 00:47:20,530
表面比较光滑
with, like, a smooth surface.

767
00:47:21,699 --> 00:47:24,250
就说你失业了 随便什么都行
Say you lost your job, whatever.

768
00:47:24,285 --> 00:47:27,036
随便编个故事 下一次派对你必须去
Just some story. You need to work the next party.

769
00:47:27,038 --> 00:47:30,923
我... 我都不知道还能不能联系上那些姑娘
I don't... I don't know if I can get in touch with those girls.

770
00:47:30,959 --> 00:47:33,960
她们的生活也谈不上稳定
They weren't exactly stable.

771
00:47:34,012 --> 00:47:36,262
我开始挺擅长这个了
I'm getting really good at this.

772
00:47:36,297 --> 00:47:37,847
当然还不如妈妈
Not like hers.

773
00:47:37,882 --> 00:47:41,050
如果你能搞到邀请
If you can get a line on an invite,

774
00:47:41,102 --> 00:47:43,469
必须得让我查查
I need to look into it.

775
00:47:43,521 --> 00:47:45,521
这个姑娘失踪了
This girl's missing.

776
00:47:45,557 --> 00:47:47,223
还有些别的事情
There's other stuff.

777
00:47:47,225 --> 00:47:49,308
还有别的?
Something else?

778
00:47:49,360 --> 00:47:50,943
那场枪击之后你还有案子?
After that shooting?

779
00:47:50,979 --> 00:47:52,979
你一直绝口不提
You haven't talked about it.

780
00:47:53,031 --> 00:47:56,232
爸爸也问过 说你不回他电话
Dad asks and says that you won't call him back.

781
00:47:56,234 --> 00:47:58,401
我很忙 工作上的事
I'm busy. Work.

782
00:47:59,904 --> 00:48:03,573
我就说你今天怎么这么急着来沙滩
I wondered why you were so hot to hit the beach today.

783
00:48:05,076 --> 00:48:08,544
亏我还仔细掂量过 该不该来听你唠叨
I tried weighing if it was worth the price of a lecture.

784
00:48:10,665 --> 00:48:12,882
我也没资格给你上课
I'm not in a spot to give those.

785
00:48:15,086 --> 00:48:16,669
我跟你说了我被加州艺术学院录取了吗?
Did I tell you I got into CalArts?

786
00:48:16,721 --> 00:48:20,423
你... 太棒了
You... that's great.

787
00:48:20,425 --> 00:48:21,924
真是太好了
Awesome.

788
00:48:21,976 --> 00:48:23,426
谢谢
Thank you.

789
00:48:23,478 --> 00:48:26,229
- 天啊 恭喜你  - 谢谢
- Congratulations. Jeez.  - Thanks.

790
00:48:27,732 --> 00:48:31,267
我应该... 我应该请你吃晚饭
I should, uh... I should buy you dinner.

791
00:48:33,438 --> 00:48:38,107
或许我能联系上几个之前认识的姑娘
Maybe I can reach out to a couple of the girls that I knew before.

792
00:48:40,111 --> 00:48:43,496
别忘了目的是为了让我混进派对 好吗?
For the straight up purpose of getting me into that party, okay?

793
00:48:43,531 --> 00:48:46,749
你不是该坐在办公桌工作吗?
Aren't you supposed to be behind a desk?

794
00:48:46,784 --> 00:48:49,335
我刚开始度假而已
I just started my vacation.

795
00:48:49,370 --> 00:48:52,171
准备去什么特别的地方吗?
Going anywhere special?

796
00:48:52,207 --> 00:48:54,290
嗯 Guerneville
Yep. Guerneville.

797
00:48:54,342 --> 00:48:55,925
你想家了?
You homesick?

798
00:48:55,960 --> 00:48:59,795
你倒是从没为了一个讨厌的地方跑那么远
For a place you hate, you never really got that far away.

799
00:49:19,651 --> 00:49:21,817
过量的硼会导致这种颜色
An excess of boron produces the color.

800
00:49:21,869 --> 00:49:24,320
是这样 大多有色钻石品质都不高
Now, most of your colored diamonds are of low quality,

801
00:49:24,372 --> 00:49:27,657
但像这些色调如此饱满
but something like these with such a rich hue,

802
00:49:27,659 --> 00:49:29,659
就非常稀有
it's just very rare.

803
00:49:29,661 --> 00:49:31,160
还有这样的八面体切割
And the cut, octahedron,

804
00:49:31,162 --> 00:49:33,546
这些一看就肯定是偷的
these must almost certainly be stolen.

805
00:49:33,581 --> 00:49:35,164
我跟另一个警察也是这么说的
I told the other policeman the same.

806
00:49:36,718 --> 00:49:38,551
另一个警察?
What other policeman?

807
00:49:38,586 --> 00:49:40,503
对 几个月前 有个警探进来
Oh, a few months back, a detective came by

808
00:49:40,555 --> 00:49:42,221
带着跟这一样的钻石图
with pictures of identical diamonds.

809
00:49:42,257 --> 00:49:46,175
询问我是否有人来兜售过这些钻石
Wanted to know if anybody had come around maybe trying to sell them.

810
00:49:46,177 --> 00:49:47,843
我告诉他我经常查看被偷物品清单
I told him I read the pawn sheets regular

811
00:49:47,845 --> 00:49:49,345
没见过列表里有
and I haven't seen them listed.

812
00:49:49,347 --> 00:49:52,265
他跟我说不希望这些钻石出现在清单上
He tells me they don't want the stolens on any sheets.

813
00:49:52,317 --> 00:49:55,101
于是他给了我他的名片
So he gives me his card,

814
00:49:55,153 --> 00:49:56,852
说是我这边有什么风声就让他知道
says to let him know if I hear anything.

815
00:49:56,904 --> 00:49:59,322
- 你还留着那张名片?  - 留着
- You still have that card?  - Yeah.

816
00:50:01,943 --> 00:50:04,944
他是个微胖的人 闻起来一身酒气
He was a portly man. Smelled like bourbon.

817
00:50:07,031 --> 00:50:09,498
而且趾高气扬的
Flatulent, too.

818
00:50:13,538 --> 00:50:17,740
问题是 Dixon来问钻石的时候
The thing is, when Dixon came around about the diamonds,

819
00:50:17,742 --> 00:50:20,994
是在我们找到安全柜之前
it would have been before we found the safety deposit box.

820
00:50:21,046 --> 00:50:23,546
所以他在我们找到之前就知道这些钻石
So he knew about the diamonds before we found them.

821
00:50:23,581 --> 00:50:26,215
而且还有一点 为什么不把钻石列入清单?
And in which case, why not put them on the hot sheets?

822
00:50:26,251 --> 00:50:29,052
我的前搭档查到这个地址
My ex-partner got this address

823
00:50:29,087 --> 00:50:31,421
是那个失踪女孩最后一次呼叫的地方
where the missing girl last called from.

824
00:50:32,507 --> 00:50:35,258
地点也在Caspere的GPS定位上
Spot was on Caspere's GPS, too.

825
00:50:37,846 --> 00:50:40,313
像是找对了地方
Seems like a happening place.

826
00:50:42,567 --> 00:50:45,151
在河谷那边
Used to be this commune here

827
00:50:45,186 --> 00:50:47,603
曾经有个公社
on the River Valley.

828
00:50:58,783 --> 00:51:00,750
你为什么说...
Why did you say...

829
00:51:02,253 --> 00:51:04,537
你追到的那个人 不是那个?
so that man that you tracked down, that was a lie?

830
00:51:04,589 --> 00:51:08,091
不 我... 不理解
No, I... I don't understand.

831
00:51:08,126 --> 00:51:10,460
他们几周前抓到他了
They caught him weeks ago.

832
00:51:10,462 --> 00:51:13,046
叫我去
Called me in.

833
00:51:13,098 --> 00:51:14,797
Richard也跟我去的
Richard came with me.

834
00:51:16,468 --> 00:51:18,017
他是个连环强奸犯
He's a serial rapist.

835
00:51:18,053 --> 00:51:21,104
DNA和我当时留存的记录相符
DNA matched the kit that they took on me back then.

836
00:51:22,307 --> 00:51:24,107
一切都是你编的?
Did you just make it up?

837
00:51:24,142 --> 00:51:26,642
你所说的一切?
What you said?

838
00:51:28,646 --> 00:51:31,314
我...
I...

839
00:51:31,316 --> 00:51:33,449
为什么?
Why?

840
00:51:33,485 --> 00:51:36,119
你为什么要这么做?
Why would you do that?

841
00:51:36,154 --> 00:51:37,987
就... 能怎样?
So... so, what?

842
00:51:38,039 --> 00:51:41,874
就能让我觉得你在保护我?
So you can make me think that you were protecting me or something?

843
00:51:41,910 --> 00:51:44,327
这...
It's...

844
00:51:44,379 --> 00:51:46,712
不是... 我不是...
it's not... it's not what I...

845
00:51:46,748 --> 00:51:49,665
Ray 这毁了一切
That ruined everything, Ray.

846
00:51:50,802 --> 00:51:53,386
也毁了你
That ruined you.

847
00:51:53,421 --> 00:51:58,057
这就是为什么我坚持做亲子鉴定
That's why I have to have the paternity test.

848
00:51:59,677 --> 00:52:02,011
我必须知道
I have to know.

849
00:52:02,981 --> 00:52:05,848
我必须知道 我才能...
I have to know so I can...

850
00:52:05,900 --> 00:52:07,733
把事情理清楚
put it all where it's supposed to be.

851
00:52:07,769 --> 00:52:10,853
我不想再假设
I don't want to live this fantasy

852
00:52:10,855 --> 00:52:13,072
你和Chad的关系了
about Chad with you anymore.

853
00:52:14,075 --> 00:52:15,858
等他准备好的时候
He should have the truth

854
00:52:15,910 --> 00:52:17,693
他有权知道真相
when he's ready.

855
00:52:17,745 --> 00:52:19,779
这...
This...

856
00:52:19,831 --> 00:52:21,614
我们的家庭建立在这个谎言之上
this fake story

857
00:52:21,666 --> 00:52:23,366
这个谎言必须终结
where we made a family has to end.

858
00:52:32,760 --> 00:52:36,212
是他算计了我
He set me up.

859
00:52:36,214 --> 00:52:37,880
是Frank
Frank.

860
00:52:37,882 --> 00:52:40,600
我听不懂 Ray
I don't know what that means, Ray.

861
00:52:54,983 --> 00:52:56,899
你是认真的?
You serious?

862
00:52:56,951 --> 00:52:58,901
领养孩子的事?
About the adoption?

863
00:53:00,071 --> 00:53:04,073
你跟我说的话 对我很有触动
It meant something to me, what you said.

864
00:53:07,795 --> 00:53:09,996
我想谢谢你告诉我这些话
I want to thank you for telling me that.

865
00:53:14,052 --> 00:53:16,969
我们的父母都不太尽如人意啊
We both could have used different parents.

866
00:53:31,436 --> 00:53:34,437
别担心孩子的事了
Don't worry about kids now.

867
00:53:34,439 --> 00:53:36,856
现在只有你我
This is between you and me.

868
00:53:55,927 --> 00:53:58,344
好像很久没人在家了
Seems like nobody's been home.

869
00:54:16,364 --> 00:54:17,730
要叫当地警方吗?
Want to call local?

870
00:54:17,815 --> 00:54:19,448
带我们进去?
Get us in here?

871
00:54:31,663 --> 00:54:33,496
现在线索又成了鸟儿了
Now we're following birds.

872
00:54:33,498 --> 00:54:35,998
是食腐鸟
Carrion birds.

873
00:54:50,064 --> 00:54:52,481
你闻到了吗?
You smell that?

874
00:54:52,517 --> 00:54:54,567
鸟屎吗?
What, bird shit?

875
00:55:30,605 --> 00:55:32,521
是动脉喷射出的
It's arterial spray.

876
00:55:35,393 --> 00:55:37,109
天啊
Jesus.

877
00:55:42,900 --> 00:55:45,568
天花板是干净的
The ceiling's clean.

878
00:55:47,238 --> 00:55:49,572
没有水渍
No water stains.

879
00:55:56,881 --> 00:55:59,131
我很喜欢这里
I like it here.

880
00:56:00,585 --> 00:56:03,169
真的
Really.

881
00:56:03,221 --> 00:56:05,971
那么大地方我们也用不到
We didn't need all that room.

882
00:56:06,007 --> 00:56:08,307
别这么说
Don't talk like that. Come on.

883
00:56:10,395 --> 00:56:14,063
有个叫McCandless的 Catalast公司...
There's a guy, McCandless, Catalast...

884
00:56:14,098 --> 00:56:16,232
别做生意了
Leave business.

885
00:56:20,271 --> 00:56:22,738
我们应该卖掉那些店
We should sell the clubs.

886
00:56:26,577 --> 00:56:28,911
买个农场
Buy a farm.

887
00:56:28,946 --> 00:56:32,948
种植有机作物
Grow organic produce.

888
00:56:32,950 --> 00:56:35,084
我都能想到我们当农民的样子
I could see us as farmers.

889
00:56:37,038 --> 00:56:38,871
等你头一次闻到大粪的时候
You would run for a plane

890
00:56:38,923 --> 00:56:40,790
会掉头就跑去找飞机
the first time you smelled shit.

891
00:56:40,842 --> 00:56:43,092
相信我
Trust me.

892
00:56:45,213 --> 00:56:47,129
我拾过大粪
I worked as a picker.

893
00:56:48,966 --> 00:56:52,101
当时我十四岁
I was 14.

894
00:56:52,136 --> 00:56:53,886
不对 十五
15.

895
00:56:56,023 --> 00:56:57,857
你不会想种东西的
You don't want to grow anything.

896
00:57:16,661 --> 00:57:20,880
这个人怎么样?
What about this guy?

897
00:57:22,216 --> 00:57:25,668
我能帮他做点事情
There's something I might be able to do for him.

898
00:57:25,670 --> 00:57:27,636
如果做到的话
If I can,

899
00:57:27,672 --> 00:57:30,256
我们就能全部赢回来
we can get it all back.

900
00:57:30,308 --> 00:57:32,341
你信任他吗?
Do you trust him?

901
00:57:32,393 --> 00:57:34,343
我信任自我利益
I trust self-interest.

902
00:57:40,852 --> 00:57:42,518
待在这
Stay here.

903
00:57:44,238 --> 00:57:47,356
我他妈的来了! 闭嘴!
I'm fucking coming! Shut the fuck up!

904
00:58:14,635 --> 00:58:15,801
你他妈有什么问题?
Got a fucking problem?

905
00:58:15,887 --> 00:58:17,553
你一个人?
You alone?

906
00:58:17,555 --> 00:58:20,055
是啊 怎么了?
Yeah. Why?

907
00:58:22,810 --> 00:58:24,727
咱俩得谈谈
You and me need to talk.

908
00:58:38,409 --> 00:58:43,779
# 一道颜色流过你的血 #
# there's a color running through your blood #

909
00:58:45,216 --> 00:58:49,752
# 匆匆一抹金色 #
# such a hasty shade of blond #

910
00:58:49,787 --> 00:58:55,124
# 你是如此危险 #
# you're that awful sort of dangerous #

911
00:58:56,460 --> 00:59:00,129
# 让我欲罢不能 #
# kind that keeps me hanging on #

912
00:59:01,265 --> 00:59:06,368
# 黑暗会降临 #
# darkness does appear when #

913
00:59:06,404 --> 00:59:10,840
# 当我拨开你身上的秘密 #
# I can see the secrets hanging 'round your neck #

914
00:59:10,875 --> 00:59:14,643
# 当我们一丝不挂 #
# when we're shirtless #

915
00:59:14,679 --> 00:59:17,613
# 割开手腕 #
# and slicing the wrist #

916
00:59:17,648 --> 00:59:22,151
# 用手指触摸一个吻 #
# prick your finger on a kiss #

917
00:59:23,354 --> 00:59:26,255
# 谁也不要告诉 #
# tell no one about it #

918
00:59:26,290 --> 00:59:28,991
# 他们不必知道 #
# they don't need to know #

919
00:59:29,026 --> 00:59:33,329
# 对谁也不提起你 #
# tell no one about you #

