1
00:00:01,160 --> 00:00:05,230
我们很高兴罗马的王子到访
We're only too happy to receive Rome's favored son.

2
00:00:05,230 --> 00:00:08,830
武器制造可以被视为一种挑衅的行为
The manufacture of armaments could be construed as a provocative moveve.

3
00:00:09,060 --> 00:00:11,400
我认为在我的宫廷里可能有奸细
I believe there may be a spy in my court.

4
00:00:11,660 --> 00:00:17,000
如果我们有事要告诉你 我们会刻字母Ω
If we have something to convey to you, we will inscribe the letter Omega.

5
00:00:17,300 --> 00:00:23,230
跟你的教皇说 不管是佛罗伦萨还是达芬奇 都永远不会屈从
Tell your Pope that neither Florence nor Da Vinci will be contained.

6
00:00:25,460 --> 00:00:27,260
不管钥匙的锁是什么样子
Whatever lock this corresponds with,

7
00:00:27,530 --> 00:00:30,900
我敢打赌 这把钥匙只是开锁机制的一半
I'd wager the key represents only half.

8
00:00:31,060 --> 00:00:32,800
没有另一半的钥匙没有任何意义
The key is useless without its counterpart.

9
00:00:33,030 --> 00:00:35,000
你听说过"叶之书"吗?
Have you heard of the Book of Leaves?

10
00:00:35,230 --> 00:00:37,560
那是个传说 就像独角兽一样
It's a myth. No more real than a unicorn.

11
00:00:37,760 --> 00:00:41,200
你和萨尔维亚蒂应该立即召集军队
You and Salviati should assemble the largest army you can find.

12
00:00:41,360 --> 00:00:44,860
好好干吧 大师... 佛罗伦萨就指望你了
Get to work, Maestro... Florence is counting on you.

13
00:01:10,000 --> 00:01:20,000
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==-- 
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途 

14
00:01:25,000 --> 00:01:40,000
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==-- 
协调: 潇妹纸
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：SceneryJuly 波特妹子 落寞卷菜 Tracy 潇妹纸 戴蜀
校对：岸

15
00:01:43,500 --> 00:01:48,000
达芬奇恶魔 第一季 第3集

16
00:02:04,830 --> 00:02:06,230
能谈谈吗?
Shall we?

17
00:02:28,860 --> 00:02:32,900
我发现这棋盘游戏很有意思
I find the game fascinating.

18
00:02:33,160 --> 00:02:36,060
看起来很简单 是吧?
Deceptively simple, isn't it?

19
00:02:37,160 --> 00:02:39,800
我备好餐了
I have a repast.

20
00:02:39,930 --> 00:02:41,860
是什么
Say it.

21
00:02:42,030 --> 00:02:45,160
糕点 奶酪和红酒
Panpepato, cheese, and wine.

22
00:02:45,330 --> 00:02:46,930
糕点是你做的吗?
You made the panpepato?

23
00:02:47,060 --> 00:02:49,500
是 因为您喜欢
Yes. Because you like it.

24
00:02:50,274 --> 00:02:52,359
有备

25
00:02:52,776 --> 00:02:54,778
无患

26
00:03:02,660 --> 00:03:05,100
- 阿姆哈拉语?  - 没错
- Was that Amharic?  - Yes.

27
00:03:05,260 --> 00:03:08,630
我在埃塞俄比亚待过
I spent time in Abyssinia.

28
00:03:08,800 --> 00:03:11,360
我刚才说你待她很好
I said that you hold her in high regard.

29
00:03:11,530 --> 00:03:17,330
她干活很努力 也信奉上帝 也会说我们的语言
She labors hard and has embraced both the Lord and our language.

30
00:03:17,600 --> 00:03:19,800
都是你教给她的 对吧?
You taught her, didn't you?

31
00:03:20,000 --> 00:03:26,360
没错 就像你有耐心教我这个游戏一样
I did. Just as you teach me this game with patient persistence.

32
00:03:26,530 --> 00:03:29,230
现在 我们能开始了吗?
Now, shall we get to play?

33
00:03:29,430 --> 00:03:30,500
你随意吧
That's the thing.

34
00:03:30,700 --> 00:03:32,230
虽然我尚未碰到棋盘
I've yet to touch the board

35
00:03:32,400 --> 00:03:35,100
可我已经开始了
but already I've begun.

36
00:03:37,930 --> 00:03:41,500
首要原则是要抢占角落
The first principle is to take the corners.

37
00:03:41,630 --> 00:03:43,160
这计策很好理解
The strategy is obvious.

38
00:03:43,400 --> 00:03:46,330
因为角落更容易防守
The corners are easier to defend.

39
00:03:50,460 --> 00:03:54,230
这个很精致 品味高雅 剪裁完美
It's brilliant. High grade, beautifully milled.

40
00:03:54,430 --> 00:03:56,460
可还是少了些什么
But it's missing something.

41
00:03:56,660 --> 00:04:00,460
我知道了! 还要再加上梭心蕾丝边
I know! A jaunty bobbin lace is what it needs.

42
00:04:00,730 --> 00:04:04,600
但即使是争夺局部的棋子时
But even as we engage in localized conflicts

43
00:04:04,900 --> 00:04:09,800
头脑中也必须要保持大局观
it is important to keep the broader landscape in mind.

44
00:04:21,200 --> 00:04:23,660
只有时刻欲擒故纵 声东击西
The game can only be won by pursuing

45
00:04:23,860 --> 00:04:28,900
才能在这个游戏中获胜
seemingly opposing objectives simultaneously.

46
00:04:37,960 --> 00:04:39,100
每一刻...
At any given moment...

47
00:04:39,330 --> 00:04:42,460
卢克蕾齐娅 亲爱的 看看怎么样
Lucrezia, my dear, come tell us what you think.

48
00:04:42,760 --> 00:04:46,330
棋子都有三种状态
A stone can be considered to inhabit one of three states,

49
00:04:46,630 --> 00:04:50,460
活子 死子 和未定的棋子
alive, dead, or unsettled.

50
00:04:50,660 --> 00:04:52,560
卢克蕾齐娅 能出来一下吗 亲爱的?
Lucrezia can you come out here, dear?

51
00:04:52,860 --> 00:04:55,500
未定的棋子往往能够...
An unsettled stone naturally presents the player...

52
00:04:55,700 --> 00:04:59,730
带给持棋者最大收益
with the largest potential outcomes.

53
00:05:01,730 --> 00:05:03,730
- 你要出门吗?  - 没错
- Are you heading out?  - Yes.

54
00:05:03,930 --> 00:05:05,760
- 宵禁之后出门?  - 不会有事的
- After curfew?  - I'll be fine.

55
00:05:06,000 --> 00:05:08,160
- 你确定?  - 我去找吉尼芙拉
- Is that wise?  - I'm calling on Ginevra.

56
00:05:08,460 --> 00:05:11,660
我从蒙特贝奇家买了些草药 可以治她的皮疹
I bought some herbs from the Montebianchi to treat her tetter.

57
00:05:11,830 --> 00:05:13,230
但我需要你帮忙
But I may need your help.

58
00:05:13,560 --> 00:05:17,060
我确信有恩佐帮你就足够了
I'm confident that Enzo is capable of handling all of your needs.

59
00:05:17,230 --> 00:05:18,500
晚安
Goodnight.

60
00:05:18,730 --> 00:05:21,730
能够控制住局势
An opponent who can control the flow of the game

61
00:05:21,930 --> 00:05:23,930
又能进行有效防御的对手
while appearing to play defensively

62
00:05:24,100 --> 00:05:28,200
通常是最可怕的
is often the most formidable.

63
00:05:32,330 --> 00:05:34,900
快走 快走
Go on. Move on.

64
00:05:40,300 --> 00:05:43,030
快点! 站起来
Come on! Stand up straight.

65
00:05:56,660 --> 00:05:58,400
快走 快走
Go on. Move on.

66
00:06:19,660 --> 00:06:21,060
去左面查一下
Look down here on the left.

67
00:06:31,400 --> 00:06:34,830
- 多纳蒂夫人  - 戈内蒂长官
- Signora Donati.  - Captain Dragonetti.

68
00:06:35,060 --> 00:06:38,200
您一位女士 这个时候出来散步 是不是有点晚了?
Isn't it late for a woman of your standing to be out for a stroll?

69
00:06:38,360 --> 00:06:41,100
按规矩 我可以因违反宵禁逮捕你
On principle, I could arrest you for violating curfew.

70
00:06:41,330 --> 00:06:45,000
没错 但你我都知道 受到惩罚的人
True. But we both know that it would be you, and not I,

71
00:06:45,160 --> 00:06:46,900
将会是你 而不是我
who would receive punishment.

72
00:06:49,060 --> 00:06:51,060
祝您晚上愉快 夫人
Enjoy the evening air, Signora.

73
00:07:05,500 --> 00:07:07,600
- 晚上好 盖尔伯托  - 夫人
- Good evening, Gualberto.  - Signora.

74
00:07:07,760 --> 00:07:09,230
您今晚看上去真迷人
You look lovely this evening.

75
00:07:09,460 --> 00:07:12,000
- 一如既往  - 谢谢
- As always.  - Thank you.

76
00:07:19,700 --> 00:07:23,200
- 你心跳得很快  - 我没想到你会在这儿
- Your heart is racing.  - I didn't expect you to be here.

77
00:07:25,960 --> 00:07:28,330
我在宫殿里等不及你了
I couldn't wait for you any longer at the palazzo.

78
00:07:32,460 --> 00:07:35,000
洛伦佐
Lorenzo.

79
00:07:35,160 --> 00:07:36,360
让我来
Let me.

80
00:08:29,230 --> 00:08:33,400
其中最难掌握的一种计策叫做...
One of the most difficult strategies to master is called...

81
00:08:33,530 --> 00:08:35,960
"瞒天过海"
"Cross The Sea Unseen".

82
00:08:36,200 --> 00:08:37,600
达芬奇!
Da Vinci!

83
00:08:37,900 --> 00:08:41,830
你必须要找出对手的弱点
It entails identifying the weakness in an opponent's position

84
00:08:42,060 --> 00:08:45,330
并加以利用 这一切都要小心 不让他们发现
and exploiting it beneath their notice.

85
00:08:48,560 --> 00:08:52,160
达芬奇! 洛伦佐以为你已经去锻造厂了!
Da Vinci! Lorenzo believes you are already at the forge!

86
00:08:55,130 --> 00:08:56,560
达芬奇!
Da Vinci!

87
00:09:02,300 --> 00:09:03,200
什么事?
What?

88
00:09:03,460 --> 00:09:05,100
你怎么早上没去?
Why weren't you there at first light?

89
00:09:05,260 --> 00:09:06,630
他们天亮时就要铸炮
They cast guns at sunrise.

90
00:09:06,830 --> 00:09:08,830
我不必亲自铸造 贝奇
I don't have to pour the metal myself, Becchi.

91
00:09:09,060 --> 00:09:10,830
这些武器对佛罗伦萨的安全至关重要
These weapons are vital to Florence's safety

92
00:09:11,100 --> 00:09:13,830
而你是雇来的武器工程师
and you've sold yourself as a war engineer.

93
00:09:14,100 --> 00:09:16,160
- 这是什么味道?  - 一个实验
- What is that noxious smell?  - It's an experiment.

94
00:09:16,430 --> 00:09:18,400
我正在评测自己的火枪
I'm assessing the implications of my guns.

95
00:09:20,630 --> 00:09:22,560
达芬奇!
Da Vinci!

96
00:09:43,100 --> 00:09:44,000
达芬奇!
Da Vinci!

97
00:09:44,160 --> 00:09:46,830
原来你在这啊 大师
Ah, there you are, Maestro.

98
00:09:47,000 --> 00:09:49,660
我相信 锻造进展很顺利吧?
Production progressing smoothly, I trust?

99
00:09:49,830 --> 00:09:53,400
有这种生产条件 再顺利不过了
As smoothly as can be expected, given these working conditions.

100
00:09:53,700 --> 00:09:57,730
好的 按照约定 将造出十门炮来 对吧?
Yes, but my guns. We will have ten, as promised, yes?

101
00:09:57,930 --> 00:10:00,900
我们拒绝接受罗马指派的比萨大主教
Our refusal to accept Rome's Archbishop of Pisa

102
00:10:01,060 --> 00:10:03,460
因此必须加强防御
only reinforces the need to bolster our defenses.

103
00:10:03,730 --> 00:10:07,560
我非常了解陛下现在的压力
I am acutely aware of the pressures converging on His Magnificence.

104
00:10:09,030 --> 00:10:11,330
那个瞎子在那干什么呢?
What the devil is that cloudy-eyed miscreant doing?

105
00:10:11,530 --> 00:10:15,060
- 声调不对  - 停!
- The tonality is off.  - Stop!

106
00:10:15,300 --> 00:10:19,760
失明者听力聪慧 我这位朋友听出了一件残次品
Our sightless friend's keen ears have detected an impurity.

107
00:10:20,700 --> 00:10:23,730
太荒唐了
This is absurd.

108
00:10:23,960 --> 00:10:25,460
你的做法 哪里变了?
Your methods, what's changed?

109
00:10:25,700 --> 00:10:28,600
没有啊 我按要求用了最好的煤炭
Nothing. I've used the finest ore, as dictated.

110
00:10:28,830 --> 00:10:31,160
- 好 那温度...  - 精准无误
- Well, then, the heat...  - Precisely as instructed.

111
00:10:31,330 --> 00:10:33,900
刚才我们没有硫磺了
Well, there was that one moment when we ran out of sulfur.

112
00:10:34,160 --> 00:10:36,800
- 为什么没人来问我?  - 这只是个意外
- Why wasn't I consulted?  - It was incidental.

113
00:10:36,930 --> 00:10:39,860
到底怎么回事?
What exactly is the issue here?

114
00:10:40,100 --> 00:10:41,760
要是他们用这种残次品
If they've used an inferior alloy,

115
00:10:42,000 --> 00:10:43,660
像这种不加硫的合金
in this case, too little sulfur,

116
00:10:43,960 --> 00:10:46,760
那么炮声就只能有原来的一半大
then the sound the guns make will be half as loud as they should be.

117
00:10:47,000 --> 00:10:49,230
谁他妈在乎声音大小?
Who cares about the fucking sound?

118
00:10:49,430 --> 00:10:51,500
我们不需要你装腔作势那套
We're not doing more of your goddamn theatre.

119
00:10:51,730 --> 00:10:53,560
枪炮是用来消灭敌人的
They need to obliterate the enemy.

120
00:10:53,730 --> 00:10:55,860
把他们打成碎片
Blow them to bits.

121
00:10:56,100 --> 00:10:58,300
- 请放手  - 否则呢?
- Please unhand me.  - Or what?

122
00:10:58,560 --> 00:11:00,130
你用勺子恐吓我?
You're threatening me with a spoon now?

123
00:11:00,300 --> 00:11:01,630
朱利亚诺!
Giuliano!

124
00:11:06,730 --> 00:11:08,460
要是我说
As I was saying,

125
00:11:08,630 --> 00:11:16,660
炮筒的音色也可以表明它的性能
the timbre of the barrel is also indicative of its general properties.

126
00:11:17,700 --> 00:11:18,860
回炉重造
Start again.

127
00:11:19,130 --> 00:11:21,400
这次别吝惜硫磺!
Don't scrimp on the sulfur this time!

128
00:11:21,630 --> 00:11:25,060
他不敢
He won't.

129
00:11:25,230 --> 00:11:26,560
你觉得我是个傻子
You treat me like a fool.

130
00:11:26,760 --> 00:11:29,830
可我有领导能力
But I'm capable of leading.

131
00:11:30,060 --> 00:11:32,030
- 民众爱戴我  - 他们是爱你的脸
- The people love me. - They love your face.

132
00:11:32,300 --> 00:11:37,730
但英俊的脸不能阻止罗马人进攻
But that smooth nose of yours won't keep Rome from striking.

133
00:11:37,930 --> 00:11:40,600
只有达芬奇的炮才能
Only Da Vinci's guns will.

134
00:11:45,460 --> 00:11:46,900
来吧 尼科
Come, Nico.

135
00:11:47,130 --> 00:11:50,530
美第奇货币正在拖我的后腿
These Medici currency vouchers are weighing me down.

136
00:11:50,760 --> 00:11:53,130
我需要飞翔 离开这个世界
I need to fly, be free of this world.

137
00:11:55,500 --> 00:11:57,700
你的全部存货卖多少钱?
How much for your entire inventory?

138
00:11:57,930 --> 00:11:59,930
比你上次给的贵
More than you gave me last time.

139
00:12:00,060 --> 00:12:02,000
两弗罗林?
Two florins?

140
00:12:02,160 --> 00:12:03,630
成交吧怎么样 疯子?
How about it, bird man?

141
00:12:05,160 --> 00:12:07,000
能帮个忙吗 尼科?
A little help, Nico?

142
00:12:07,160 --> 00:12:08,400
让一下
Excuse me.

143
00:12:13,560 --> 00:12:14,860
开!
Now!

144
00:12:34,930 --> 00:12:37,200
我对此真是百看不厌
I never tire of watching that.

145
00:12:43,400 --> 00:12:46,100
这只怎么不飞呢?
Why didn't this one fly away?

146
00:12:46,230 --> 00:12:48,160
达芬奇先生
Signor Da Vinci.

147
00:12:48,360 --> 00:12:50,200
我们见面次数这么少
When will you ever finish my portrait

148
00:12:50,400 --> 00:12:53,260
你什么时候才能完成我的肖像画呢?
if we sit together so infrequently?

149
00:12:53,530 --> 00:12:57,300
大师 我去买些鸡蛋给你做颜料
Maestro, I'll pick up some more eggs for your pigments.

150
00:12:57,530 --> 00:13:01,360
你刚从洛伦佐那儿回来 还是正要去?
On your way to or from Lorenzo, then?

151
00:13:01,700 --> 00:13:03,900
你明白我的处境 莱昂纳多
You know my situation, Leonardo.

152
00:13:07,730 --> 00:13:09,530
飞吧
Just go.

153
00:13:09,700 --> 00:13:11,600
这是你的机会
This is your chance,

154
00:13:11,760 --> 00:13:15,130
笼门已经打开
the cage is open.

155
00:13:15,330 --> 00:13:16,600
你以为对知识的探索
Do you think your pursuit of knowledge

156
00:13:16,800 --> 00:13:19,400
就能让自己逃避情感吗?
makes you immune to your emotions?

157
00:13:19,660 --> 00:13:21,900
你逃不掉的 懂吗
You can't outrun them, you know.

158
00:13:23,260 --> 00:13:24,800
你知道吗 我没有逃避
Do you know, I'm not running.

159
00:13:24,960 --> 00:13:27,900
只是无法兼得所有喜好
I just have competing interests.

160
00:13:31,230 --> 00:13:33,060
比如你
Like you.

161
00:13:35,900 --> 00:13:38,530
奇怪啊 这鸟
Curious, that bird.

162
00:13:38,700 --> 00:13:40,330
你买下来吧
And paid for.

163
00:13:40,460 --> 00:13:43,160
不买的话 我就吃了它
You take it or I eat it.

164
00:13:45,960 --> 00:13:48,060
局势错综复杂
So, the plot thickens.

165
00:13:48,400 --> 00:13:52,200
你放弃这片棋子 打开了新局面
You've broken off from a local exchange and opened up a new front.

166
00:13:52,500 --> 00:13:56,300
我想 该让这盘棋局势混乱些了
I thought it was time a little chaos was introduced into the play.

167
00:14:00,630 --> 00:14:03,260
发生什么事了?
What's going on?

168
00:14:03,430 --> 00:14:04,930
我身体里的...
Inside me...

169
00:14:05,100 --> 00:14:08,560
恶魔...
devil...

170
00:14:08,800 --> 00:14:12,400
在抓我的子宫 诅咒我!
clawing at my womb, damning me!

171
00:14:15,030 --> 00:14:16,230
噢 天啊
Oh, dear God.

172
00:14:19,300 --> 00:14:20,360
不可能
It can't be.

173
00:14:20,600 --> 00:14:22,630
别碰她 还不知道她怎么了
Don't touch her. We don't know what afflicts her.

174
00:14:22,900 --> 00:14:24,960
我必须帮她 她是修女德洛丽丝 我在修道院见过
I have to help her. It's Sister Dolores. I knew her at the Convent.

175
00:14:25,200 --> 00:14:28,960
最甜美 最纯净的灵魂
The sweetest, most innocent soul.

176
00:14:29,160 --> 00:14:32,300
你去找军官 带他们过来
You there. Find some officers, bring them here.

177
00:14:32,500 --> 00:14:34,760
是我... 瓦妮莎
It's me... Vanessa.

178
00:14:36,560 --> 00:14:40,500
你 你的哥哥洛伦佐 将这里变成罪恶之地
You, your brother, Lorenzo, making a new Sodom,

179
00:14:40,660 --> 00:14:41,960
他贪得无厌
gorging on filth,

180
00:14:42,160 --> 00:14:44,730
他让佛罗伦萨充满罪恶
spewing out sin onto Florence's streets.

181
00:14:44,900 --> 00:14:46,860
上帝恨你们!
The Lord hates you!

182
00:14:47,060 --> 00:14:49,630
- 这女人怎么了?  - 是恶魔干的 先生 
- What has befallen this woman?  - Demons,Signor.

183
00:14:49,900 --> 00:14:53,900
我们圣安东尼修道院已经有五个姐妹疯了
Five of our fellow sisters from the Convent of St Anthony have been possessed.

184
00:14:55,360 --> 00:14:58,630
美蒂奇家族... 亵渎神灵
The Medicis... copulators, blasphemers

185
00:14:58,800 --> 00:15:02,130
腐化我们的城市
corrupting our city.

186
00:15:02,260 --> 00:15:06,160
你们玷污了我的眼睛!
My eyes burn to look at you!

187
00:15:13,560 --> 00:15:16,630
一个疯女人都能拿走你的武器
You let a mad woman seize your blade.

188
00:15:16,800 --> 00:15:19,400
我真该用它杀了你!
I ought to kill you with it!

189
00:15:19,560 --> 00:15:21,060
把她带走
Take her away.

190
00:15:21,230 --> 00:15:23,600
小心点 尊重点
Carefully and with respect.

191
00:15:25,060 --> 00:15:28,200
其他人... 都回家
The rest of you... go home.

192
00:15:28,330 --> 00:15:29,730
为她的灵魂祈祷
Pray for her soul.

193
00:15:31,700 --> 00:15:34,200
走吧 走!
Go on, go!

194
00:15:49,630 --> 00:15:53,200
你到底在用这些尸体做什么? 都开始腐烂了
What in God's name are you doing with these bodies? They're beginning to putrefy.

195
00:15:55,700 --> 00:15:57,400
恶臭都飘到我的工作室了
And the stench has carried into my studio.

196
00:15:57,630 --> 00:16:01,530
安德里亚 拜托 你看不出我正在找东西吗?
Andrea, please, can you not see that I'm trying to pursue something here?

197
00:16:01,760 --> 00:16:03,860
来 瞧这里
Now look at this, look at this.

198
00:16:04,000 --> 00:16:07,760
非洲... 欧洲 对吧?
Africa... and Europe. Here?

199
00:16:07,960 --> 00:16:11,830
- 对  - 你看和这个轮廓多吻合
- Yes.  - See how they fit into this.

200
00:16:12,030 --> 00:16:14,460
欧洲和非洲 这里和这里...
Europe and Africa, here and here...

201
00:16:14,630 --> 00:16:16,230
还有犹太地图
and the Jew's map.

202
00:16:16,400 --> 00:16:18,860
这里肯定以前是一块大陆
It can only be where there are now two land masses,

203
00:16:19,000 --> 00:16:21,800
现在变成了两个大陆块
there once was just one.

204
00:16:25,300 --> 00:16:27,630
随时间逐渐漂移分开
Drifted apart over ages.

205
00:16:29,900 --> 00:16:33,800
而在它们之间的 是大西洋
And between them, the great Atlantic.

206
00:16:33,960 --> 00:16:37,700
安德里亚 叶之书肯定就在这儿...
The Book of Leaves has to be here, Andrea...

207
00:16:37,860 --> 00:16:39,400
在西边的大陆块上
on this land mass to the west.

208
00:16:39,630 --> 00:16:44,160
但你甚至不知道 这块大陆是否真的存在
But you don't even know that this land mass actually exists.

209
00:16:44,400 --> 00:16:47,830
鬼火 这就是密特拉神之子的杰作
Ignis fatuus. That's what this Sons of Mithras business is.

210
00:16:47,960 --> 00:16:49,430
"鬼火"(拉丁语中的说法)
"Foolish fire".

211
00:16:49,730 --> 00:16:52,900
孩子们追着发光的昆虫 以为它们是仙女的光
Children chasing after luminous insects, thinking them faerie lights

212
00:16:53,100 --> 00:16:55,730
最后陷在齐脖子深的沼泽
and finding themselves neck-deep in swamp-mire.

213
00:16:55,960 --> 00:16:58,400
- 我可不是孩子了 安德里亚  - 是吗? 那你还研究这些蠢事
- Well, I'm not a child, Andrea.  - Oh, really? Yet you pursue this folly

214
00:16:58,630 --> 00:17:01,700
而不管自己的正事
while your legitimate commissions languish.

215
00:17:03,900 --> 00:17:05,600
- 大师! 大师!  - 什么事 孩子?
- Maestro! Maestro!  - Yes, what is it, boy?

216
00:17:05,860 --> 00:17:09,430
多纳蒂夫人看到瓦妮莎去圣安东尼修道院了
Signora Donati saw Vanessa leaving for the Convent St Anthony.

217
00:17:09,560 --> 00:17:11,030
你想说什么?
And your point is?

218
00:17:11,260 --> 00:17:13,330
恶魔会控制那里的修女!
Demons possess the nuns there!

219
00:17:13,500 --> 00:17:15,860
我看到有位修女 她把自己的眼睛挖出来了!
I saw one of the sisters. She stabbed her own eyes out!

220
00:17:16,060 --> 00:17:18,100
瓦妮莎也可能遭恶魔毒手!
Vanessa can fall victim to the demons too!

221
00:17:18,260 --> 00:17:20,430
目前为止 除了一些相当无聊的布道
Demons have yet to be proven the cause of anything

222
00:17:20,600 --> 00:17:22,100
恶魔什么坏事都没做过
except some rather tedious sermons.

223
00:17:22,330 --> 00:17:24,630
- 我们必须帮助她!  - 够了 尼科!
- We need to help her!  - Fuck, Nico!

224
00:17:24,830 --> 00:17:28,660
如果我放下一切去研究什么毫无依据 愚蠢至极的幻想
If I dropped everything to pursue some ill-conceived and asinine flight of fancy,

225
00:17:28,830 --> 00:17:31,060
那只会一事无成!
I would never get anything done!

226
00:17:34,260 --> 00:17:36,330
好吧 下次你想
Well, I'll remember that

227
00:17:36,600 --> 00:17:40,860
把我或瓦妮莎绑上滑翔机时 我会记得这句话的
the next time you decide to strap me or Vanessa into your glider wings.

228
00:17:57,400 --> 00:18:00,130
她的自残行为 她的尖叫
The violence of her movements, her screeching,

229
00:18:00,300 --> 00:18:01,960
她似乎是被控制了 洛伦佐
she seemed possessed, Lorenzo.

230
00:18:02,100 --> 00:18:03,460
我弟弟看到一个疯修女
My brother saw one mad nun

231
00:18:03,630 --> 00:18:05,330
就以为恶魔在佛罗伦萨里肆意作恶了
and thinks the Devil is at large in Florence.

232
00:18:05,530 --> 00:18:07,000
不只是这一个人
It's not just the one.

233
00:18:07,230 --> 00:18:08,730
人们都说 恶魔的影响在蔓延
They say the Devil's influence is spreading,

234
00:18:08,960 --> 00:18:11,300
肯定是对这座城市的审判
and so must be a judgment on this city.

235
00:18:11,460 --> 00:18:13,060
对美第奇家族的审判
A judgment on the Medicis.

236
00:18:13,300 --> 00:18:15,030
我们的兴衰取决于民众的意愿
We rise and fall on the people's will.

237
00:18:15,260 --> 00:18:17,800
我们还未确定起因究竟是恶魔 或是另有他因时
Until we can assess the cause, demonic or otherwise,

238
00:18:18,000 --> 00:18:20,060
最好封闭女修道院
we'd best seal off the Convent.

239
00:18:20,200 --> 00:18:21,860
好 同意
Yes, agreed.

240
00:18:22,160 --> 00:18:26,000
我们与罗马间还有矛盾 这种时候 不要让自己的人民质疑我们的虔诚
Given our trouble with Rome, we don't want our own people questioning our piety.

241
00:18:26,160 --> 00:18:28,130
让我来处理吧
Let me handle it.

242
00:18:28,300 --> 00:18:31,430
民众亲眼目睹 这个女人一看到我就自杀了
The people beheld this woman kill herself at the sight of me.

243
00:18:31,660 --> 00:18:33,930
如果我能解决这件事 也能终止了谣言
If I resolve this, I end the gossips as well.

244
00:18:34,160 --> 00:18:36,630
我会带上戈内蒂和他手下的军官
I'll take Dragonetti and a couple of his officers.

245
00:18:36,900 --> 00:18:40,060
我会彻查此事的 我向你保证
I'll get to the bottom of this. I promise you.

246
00:18:44,200 --> 00:18:45,400
那就去吧
Oh, go on, then.

247
00:18:47,600 --> 00:18:48,800
去啊!
Go!

248
00:18:53,030 --> 00:18:56,660
有话就说 你的表情好像吃了什么脏东西似的
Out with it. You've the look of having eaten something distasteful.

249
00:19:02,560 --> 00:19:07,530
我们家族的礼堂 我确定这里能自由说话
If we can speak anywhere freely, it's here, in our family chapel.

250
00:19:07,830 --> 00:19:12,200
梵蒂冈似乎经常能了解到我们的策略 感觉就像是我们自己人一样
The Vatican often appears to know our strategies just as we employ them.

251
00:19:12,430 --> 00:19:14,960
他们谋害斯福尔扎 结束了我们和米兰的联盟
They murder Sforza to end our alliance with Milan.

252
00:19:15,160 --> 00:19:17,530
我们刚雇佣达芬奇 他们就要求见他
They ask to meet Da Vinci, just as we hire him.

253
00:19:17,760 --> 00:19:21,200
你也暗示过 我们内部显然有探子
Understandably, you've suggested we have a spy within our court.

254
00:19:21,400 --> 00:19:23,830
但在我们实施更多实质性举动
But before we take more aggressive steps

255
00:19:24,100 --> 00:19:25,900
铲除罗马探子之前
towards rooting out Rome's agent,

256
00:19:26,130 --> 00:19:28,900
我想肯定还有其他方面需要考虑
I believe there's something else we should consider.

257
00:19:31,200 --> 00:19:34,160
你娶克拉丽斯是为了和罗马联姻
You married Clarice to build ties with Rome.

258
00:19:34,400 --> 00:19:35,760
她在罗马仍有亲人
She still has family there.

259
00:19:35,960 --> 00:19:38,800
你是说 我妻子想要毁了我们吗?
Are you're suggesting that my wife is trying to destroy us?

260
00:19:38,960 --> 00:19:40,330
不是有意 不
Not trying, no.

261
00:19:40,630 --> 00:19:43,500
但她可能在信中不小心透露了什么
But she may be guilelessly expressing things in her letters.

262
00:19:43,730 --> 00:19:47,660
- 她或许不知情...  - 克拉丽斯很好 而且非常忠诚
- She may be unaware...  - Clarice is exceptional and she is loyal.

263
00:19:50,230 --> 00:19:53,500
"当人生之路陡峭时 要保持沉着"
"When life's path is steep, keep your mind even."

264
00:19:53,730 --> 00:19:57,860
小时候是你教给我的
You taught me that when I was a boy.

265
00:19:58,030 --> 00:20:00,100
要保持沉着
Keep your mind even.

266
00:20:04,930 --> 00:20:06,430
开始是修道院的危机
First this crisis at the Convent,

267
00:20:06,600 --> 00:20:08,400
现在我们当中又有叛徒
and now a traitor in our midst.

268
00:20:09,700 --> 00:20:12,860
不惜一切手段找到探子
Take whatever steps you must to find our spy.

269
00:20:13,000 --> 00:20:14,330
行动要快
Do it quickly.

270
00:20:26,600 --> 00:20:27,600
前面有人
There's someone ahead.

271
00:20:31,430 --> 00:20:33,300
- 我来处理  - 先生 应该我来
- I'll handle this.  - Signor, I must insist.

272
00:20:33,530 --> 00:20:35,300
只是个女孩 队长
It's just a girl, Captain.

273
00:20:43,860 --> 00:20:46,300
别动 伯蒂诺
Steel yourself, Bertino.

274
00:20:46,430 --> 00:20:49,660
修女 能听到我说话吗?
Sister, can you hear me?

275
00:20:49,830 --> 00:20:51,460
我们是来帮你的
We're here to help you.

276
00:20:51,630 --> 00:20:53,300
我是朱利亚诺·德·美第奇...
I am Giuliano de Medici...

277
00:21:03,230 --> 00:21:04,560
原地别动
Stay with the horses.

278
00:21:14,330 --> 00:21:17,000
把她放到我的马上 绑起来
Sling her onto my horse, tie her down.

279
00:21:17,200 --> 00:21:18,300
我们带她去女修道院
We'll take her to the Convent.

280
00:21:18,530 --> 00:21:22,600
小心!
Look out!

281
00:21:28,360 --> 00:21:29,700
还有多少忠诚的修女
How many deaths of the faithful

282
00:21:29,860 --> 00:21:31,630
要死在美第奇的脚下?
will be laid at the feet of the Medicis?

283
00:22:10,160 --> 00:22:11,600
伯蒂诺!
Bertino!

284
00:22:34,430 --> 00:22:35,960
戈内蒂
Dragonetti.

285
00:23:06,400 --> 00:23:10,200
一错再错 免于凶恶
Abyssus abyssum invocat. Sed libera nos a Malo.

286
00:23:10,330 --> 00:23:12,460
一错再错
Abyssus abyssum invocat.

287
00:23:12,630 --> 00:23:14,200
"地狱 召唤地狱"
"Hell calls hell".

288
00:23:14,360 --> 00:23:16,430
一步错步步错
One misstep leads to another.

289
00:23:16,730 --> 00:23:18,700
所以恶魔才会登门
That's what's brought the Devil to our doorstep.

290
00:23:19,900 --> 00:23:22,060
你和你哥哥违背了上帝的旨意
You and your brother have denied God's will.

291
00:23:22,230 --> 00:23:23,860
你们以为不用付出代价吗?
Did you think there wouldn't be a cost?

292
00:23:24,060 --> 00:23:27,900
诚然 这代价很大啊
Well, the cost is dear, to be sure.

293
00:23:29,760 --> 00:23:33,400
但我还是不信 这是上帝的惩罚
But I'm not yet convinced it was the Lord who levied it.

294
00:23:33,530 --> 00:23:34,530
你在这儿干吗?
What are you doing here?

295
00:23:34,800 --> 00:23:36,160
我来找一个朋友
I've come looking for a friend.

296
00:23:44,860 --> 00:23:46,330
瓦妮莎! 嘘!
Vanessa! Ssh!

297
00:23:46,560 --> 00:23:50,300
嘘! 嘘!
Ssh! Ssh!

298
00:23:55,060 --> 00:23:57,460
我认识这个女人
I know this woman.

299
00:23:57,660 --> 00:24:01,460
她曾是我们的一位姐妹
She was one of us, a fellow Sister,

300
00:24:01,800 --> 00:24:05,060
然后这个登徒浪子承诺给她更多彩的人生
then this lecher sold her promises of a more colorful life.

301
00:24:06,760 --> 00:24:11,530
燃烧 燃烧 我身体里有团火
Burning, burning, there's a fire inside me.

302
00:24:11,760 --> 00:24:12,830
这个可怜的女孩来帮助我们
The poor girl came to aid us

303
00:24:13,030 --> 00:24:14,630
却像其他人一样被击倒了
but was struck down like the others.

304
00:24:14,860 --> 00:24:18,000
她这样... 被控制有多久了?
Well, how long have these... possessions been going on?

305
00:24:18,230 --> 00:24:20,230
这跟你有什么关系?
What business is it of yours?

306
00:24:20,360 --> 00:24:22,500
你是为上帝服务的吗?
Are you for God?

307
00:24:22,730 --> 00:24:25,060
我知道你在作坊里的勾当
I know what goes on in your workshop.

308
00:24:25,300 --> 00:24:28,100
裸体模特 肉欲关系
The nude modeling, the carnal relations,

309
00:24:28,300 --> 00:24:31,500
以科学之名侮辱尸体
the cadavers you debase in the name of science.

310
00:24:31,730 --> 00:24:34,460
你的行为会玷污一切
Your endeavors condemn all they touch.

311
00:24:34,660 --> 00:24:37,030
我们不需要你的任何帮助
We want none of your assistance.

312
00:24:37,260 --> 00:24:39,500
还有你的 美第奇先生
Nor yours, Signor Medici.

313
00:24:39,660 --> 00:24:43,360
只有虔诚的祈祷和赎罪才能终止这浩劫
Only fervid prayer and penitence will stop this.

314
00:24:43,530 --> 00:24:46,130
艺术家 借一步说话
Artista. A word with you.

315
00:24:54,530 --> 00:24:58,460
你有花钱雇人算账的 不是吗?
Others are paid to do that, no?

316
00:25:00,560 --> 00:25:03,060
我父亲教我 不管身边发生什么事
My father taught me no matter the business surrounding you,

317
00:25:03,230 --> 00:25:04,660
别丢了账目
never lose the count.

318
00:25:05,900 --> 00:25:09,000
因为美第奇家族是银行家发家的
For the Medicis are bankers before all else.

319
00:25:09,230 --> 00:25:12,660
很睿智的人 可惜去世得早
A wise man. Taken before his time.

320
00:25:12,830 --> 00:25:14,200
"患痛风的皮埃罗"
"Piero the Gouty".

321
00:25:14,530 --> 00:25:17,400
他一生的业绩 就这病最被人记得
For everything he was, he's remembered most for his sickness.

322
00:25:17,560 --> 00:25:18,630
他是位让人尊敬的父亲
He is honored as a father.

323
00:25:18,930 --> 00:25:21,630
- 对"伟人洛伦佐"来说  - 目前而已
- To "Lorenzo the Magnificent".  - For now.

324
00:25:21,830 --> 00:25:24,500
不久他们会用别的名字称呼我
Soon they may call me by other names.

325
00:25:24,800 --> 00:25:28,160
也许将是将教皇账目都输给帕吉家族的银行家
Perhaps I'll be the banker who lost the Papal accounts to the Pazzis.

326
00:25:28,430 --> 00:25:32,430
又或者是把撒旦的怨气招致给佛罗伦萨无辜人民的异教徒
Or the heretic who incurred the wrath of Satan on Florence's innocents.

327
00:25:32,630 --> 00:25:34,830
我挚爱的丈夫 你得休息一下了
My beloved, you must get some rest.

328
00:25:38,160 --> 00:25:41,430
今天我曾想解雇贝奇
Today I thought of sending Becchi away.

329
00:25:41,660 --> 00:25:45,600
- 什么? 为什么?  - 我爱他
- What? Why?  - I love him.

330
00:25:45,860 --> 00:25:47,830
他就像我第二个父亲
He's been a second father to me.

331
00:25:48,000 --> 00:25:52,230
但是 他怀疑你
But, but he questioned you.

332
00:25:52,430 --> 00:25:54,360
他觉得你可能
He thought that you could be

333
00:25:54,660 --> 00:25:58,100
不小心给家人传递了一些消息
mistakenly sharing information with your family.

334
00:25:58,260 --> 00:25:59,260
罗马的家人
With Rome.

335
00:25:59,460 --> 00:26:01,130
你以为 这种问题会冒犯我吗?
Do you think asking would offend me?

336
00:26:01,400 --> 00:26:03,900
- 会冒犯我  - 不该的
- It offends me.  - It shouldn't.

337
00:26:04,030 --> 00:26:06,800
我们生活在懦夫的时代
We live in craven times.

338
00:26:07,060 --> 00:26:10,330
人们会为了让自己活得更好 而烧掉整座城
A man would have a city in flames to make his life more comfortable.

339
00:26:12,030 --> 00:26:16,160
洛伦佐 你不该与毒蛇正面对质
You don't come at a snake from the front, Lorenzo.

340
00:26:16,360 --> 00:26:20,530
如果我是探子 别人说什么对我都无所谓
If I were one, bringing this up would be pointless.

341
00:26:20,760 --> 00:26:23,500
而你这样的反应只会让人诟病
It would make you vulnerable.

342
00:26:23,760 --> 00:26:26,830
你就应该偷偷地读我的信
You simply should have had my letters read without my knowledge.

343
00:26:27,030 --> 00:26:30,860
我最近给家人的信里 有告诉他们:
In my last letter to my family, I told them this:

344
00:26:31,100 --> 00:26:37,230
"我对洛伦佐无比忠诚
"There are none more loyal to Lorenzo than I.

345
00:26:37,460 --> 00:26:44,860
如果洛伦佐失势 有人也许还会继续前行
There are others who, if Lorenzo fell, would move on.

346
00:26:45,000 --> 00:26:47,400
但我将永远无法'继续'"
I could never 'move on'."

347
00:26:47,630 --> 00:26:50,230
洛伦佐 我知道你想要逃离
I understand your need for escape, Lorenzo.

348
00:26:50,460 --> 00:26:53,300
卸下你的责任
To feel apart from your responsibility.

349
00:26:53,560 --> 00:26:57,130
你可以暂时逃避 但是你必须回来
You can have that escape. But you do have to come back.

350
00:27:07,860 --> 00:27:12,360
你永远都必须回来
You must always come back.

351
00:27:15,760 --> 00:27:17,530
达芬奇 专心造火炮去
Attend to your guns, Da Vinci.

352
00:27:17,760 --> 00:27:19,960
已经任命我来处理此事了
I've been tasked to handle this matter.

353
00:27:20,160 --> 00:27:21,660
而且你做得非常不错
And you're doing an admirable job.

354
00:27:21,930 --> 00:27:24,930
听说你来的路上 又屠杀了一个可怜的修女
I hear you slaughtered one of the poor Sisters on the way in.

355
00:27:25,130 --> 00:27:28,100
- 那是意外  - 通常是无能
- It was an accident.  - Incompetence often is.

356
00:27:28,260 --> 00:27:29,760
你怎么敢这么说!
How dare you!

357
00:27:36,130 --> 00:27:37,830
站着别动
Stay put.

358
00:27:42,700 --> 00:27:45,160
你就这样向洛伦佐证明自己的价值?
This is how you prove your worth to Lorenzo?

359
00:27:45,330 --> 00:27:47,500
杀了他的战争工程师?
By killing his war engineer?

360
00:27:52,300 --> 00:27:56,600
告诉我 朱利亚诺 你的计划是什么?
Tell me something, Giuliano. What is your plan?

361
00:27:56,800 --> 00:27:59,530
在恶魔撤退前 封了这个地方
To seal off this place until the evil spirits retreat.

362
00:27:59,730 --> 00:28:02,130
你不调查下 除了被魔鬼控制 是否是由于其他原因了?
You won't inquire into anything other than possession?

363
00:28:02,460 --> 00:28:06,800
- 我当然会的  - 那好 请赏脸说明你猜测的其他原因吧
- Of course I will.  - Well, grace us with your alternate theories then.

364
00:28:07,030 --> 00:28:09,830
- 请吧  - 或许是 疾病
- Please.  - Disease. Perhaps.

365
00:28:10,030 --> 00:28:12,130
- 没错  - 淋巴结核 瘟疫
- Right.  - Scrofula, plague.

366
00:28:12,400 --> 00:28:15,160
我还不知道有什么疾病 能这么快毁了病人
I know of no disease that can ravage its host this quickly.

367
00:28:15,330 --> 00:28:16,800
那能是什么?
Well, what, then?

368
00:28:17,030 --> 00:28:19,500
在我们接受恶魔理论前
Before we accept the Devil's work,

369
00:28:19,700 --> 00:28:22,630
难道不该首先排除些更渎神的原因吗?
shouldn't we first eliminate the more profane causes?

370
00:28:22,800 --> 00:28:24,660
比如豹斑毒伞
Consider panther cap mushrooms.

371
00:28:24,860 --> 00:28:27,300
它们以致幻出名 甚至可以致死
They're known to cause hallucinations, even death.

372
00:28:27,560 --> 00:28:29,600
好了 看看都找到了什么
Right, let's see what we've found.

373
00:28:34,230 --> 00:28:36,100
不是 不是
No, no, no,

374
00:28:37,330 --> 00:28:39,530
不 不 不是
no, no, no.

375
00:28:42,160 --> 00:28:43,430
这些都不是罪魁祸首
None of these are the culprit.

376
00:28:43,630 --> 00:28:46,760
好了 名单下一个 狼蛛
Right, next on our list, wolf spiders.

377
00:28:47,060 --> 00:28:48,560
狼蛛的咬伤有毒
The poisonous bite of the Lycosidae.

378
00:28:48,930 --> 00:28:51,900
能引发歇斯底里的活动状态 叫作毒蛛舞蹈症
That can cause a hysterical state of movement called Tarantism.

379
00:28:52,060 --> 00:28:53,460
慢着!
Wait!

380
00:28:53,760 --> 00:28:57,000
唉 不是我们要找的恶棍
Alas, that's not the villain we seek.

381
00:28:57,160 --> 00:28:59,830
现在怎么办 小文人?
Then what now, scribbler?

382
00:29:00,000 --> 00:29:02,060
我想 欣赏下艺术品 
Some art appreciation, I think.

383
00:29:05,130 --> 00:29:07,560
这里能找到什么污物?
What possible contaminant can be found in here?

384
00:29:07,760 --> 00:29:10,160
想想那些修女整日活在这些色彩艳丽的画中
Considering the florid images the Sisters live amidst,

385
00:29:10,400 --> 00:29:13,700
更别说这画一看就是外行的作品
not to mention the amateurish technique on display here,

386
00:29:13,830 --> 00:29:15,030
有没有可能是
is it any wonder

387
00:29:15,260 --> 00:29:18,700
由于这种折磨导致她们认为被控制了呢?
the afflicted believe themselves possessed?

388
00:29:18,860 --> 00:29:20,300
你也疯了吗?
Have you gone mad too?

389
00:29:20,530 --> 00:29:23,300
我本以为可能是颜料含有太多汞了
I thought the pigments might contain too much mercury.

390
00:29:23,530 --> 00:29:24,730
- 但没有  - 够了 达芬奇
- But no.  - Enough, Da Vinci.

391
00:29:24,960 --> 00:29:26,360
当你舔画的时候
When you start licking paintings

392
00:29:26,630 --> 00:29:28,760
我就该接受事实 恶魔确实降临这里了
I think it's time to accept that the Devil is here.

393
00:29:28,930 --> 00:29:30,600
罗马来的骑士!
Riders from Rome!

394
00:29:32,860 --> 00:29:36,930
朱利亚诺 就这次 你还真对了
For once, Giuliano, you may be correct.

395
00:29:41,400 --> 00:29:43,100
格伦沃尔德队长
Captain Grunwald.

396
00:29:43,260 --> 00:29:45,600
朱利亚诺·德·美第奇
Giuliano de Medici.

397
00:29:45,760 --> 00:29:47,600
一如既往啊
Pretty as always.

398
00:29:47,800 --> 00:29:49,460
我还以为 上次佛罗伦萨的任务后
I'd have thought you loath to return,

399
00:29:49,630 --> 00:29:52,260
你们会很不愿意回来
after your last mission to Florence.

400
00:29:54,800 --> 00:29:56,900
我们是代表墨丘利长官
We bring help to the dear Sisters,

401
00:29:57,130 --> 00:29:59,100
来给敬爱的修女们帮助的
in the person of Prefect Mercuri.

402
00:29:59,260 --> 00:30:00,860
卢珀·墨丘利?
Lupo Mercuri?

403
00:30:01,060 --> 00:30:02,960
梵蒂冈密令负责人?
Curator of the Vatican's Secret Archives?

404
00:30:03,200 --> 00:30:07,230
今天 我作为圣礼教会长官过来帮忙 
Today, I come as Prefect for the Sacred Congregation of Rites.

405
00:30:07,430 --> 00:30:09,760
长官 真是太感谢你的帮助了
Your offer of assistance is gracious, Prefect,

406
00:30:10,030 --> 00:30:14,360
但院长就足以照顾好这里的修女们了
but the Abbess is quite able to lead the prayers for her flock.

407
00:30:14,560 --> 00:30:19,330
我的职责就是举办神圣的宗教仪式来驱魔
My orders are to execute the holy rites for demonic exorcism.

408
00:30:19,530 --> 00:30:23,400
我不会因为善良的修女被骗子摆布 就抛弃她们
I have no plans to leave the good sisters at the mercy of the deceiver.

409
00:30:23,600 --> 00:30:25,200
你对魔鬼有那么了解吗
And are you so attuned to the infernal,

410
00:30:25,500 --> 00:30:27,900
刚从罗马过来 就能觉察出问题了?
you could sense their problems all the way from Rome?

411
00:30:28,060 --> 00:30:30,000
大画家 我们几天前就请求援助了
We sent for aid days ago, painter.

412
00:30:30,230 --> 00:30:33,600
在需要帮助的时候 我们可不敢拒绝主的军队
We dare not reject Christ's warriors in our hour of need.

413
00:30:42,930 --> 00:30:45,260
- 侄子  - 大人
- Nephew.  - Your Grace.

414
00:30:45,460 --> 00:30:47,230
修道院的情况怎么样?
How goes the business at the Convent?

415
00:30:47,400 --> 00:30:49,600
恐怕伤亡惨重
I fear the casualties mount.

416
00:30:49,760 --> 00:30:52,330
上帝总是要求我们做出牺牲
The Lord often requires sacrifice.

417
00:30:52,500 --> 00:30:54,600
美第奇家族拒绝任命比萨大主教
The Medicis crossed the Lord,

418
00:30:54,800 --> 00:30:57,300
私自雇佣战争工程师
refusing to appoint our Archbishop in Pisa,

419
00:30:57,460 --> 00:31:00,000
从而触怒了上帝
employing a war engineer.

420
00:31:00,200 --> 00:31:02,960
摧毁洛伦佐和所有支持他的人
It is God's will to break Lorenzo

421
00:31:03,100 --> 00:31:04,560
这是神的旨意
and all who support him.

422
00:31:04,800 --> 00:31:08,730
就达芬奇的部分 我可能有些异议
With the possible exception of Da Vinci, I agree with you.

423
00:31:08,900 --> 00:31:12,130
卢克蕾齐娅·多纳蒂已经将他玩弄于指掌
Lucrezia Donati has him tied up between her thighs,

424
00:31:12,360 --> 00:31:15,760
他和美第奇家族的联盟脆弱不堪
his alliance with the Medicis is a fragile one.

425
00:31:15,930 --> 00:31:20,500
他制造出的武器 反而可以为我们所用
Those weapons he makes, they could all be ours.

426
00:31:22,100 --> 00:31:24,500
达芬奇的其他盟友呢?
And what of Da Vinci's other alliances?

427
00:31:24,730 --> 00:31:26,660
他不是支持"密特拉之子"吗?
Has he not sided with the Sons of Mithras?

428
00:31:26,860 --> 00:31:29,100
达芬奇会带给我们叶之书
Da Vinci can deliver us The Book of Leaves.

429
00:31:29,330 --> 00:31:32,460
所有迹象都指明它就在佛罗伦萨
All signs point to it being in Florence,

430
00:31:32,660 --> 00:31:36,260
达芬奇可以帮我们发现其中绝无仅有的知识
and then he can aid in unlocking its unparalleled knowledge.

431
00:31:37,660 --> 00:31:42,500
无疑 神的旨意是让我们拉拢他
Surely, the Lord wills that we embrace him.

432
00:31:42,630 --> 00:31:45,100
轮到你来告诉我神的旨意了?
Do you tell me what the Lord wills?

433
00:31:46,630 --> 00:31:48,030
当然不是 教皇
Of course not, Father.

434
00:31:48,200 --> 00:31:49,700
教皇
Holy Father.

435
00:32:01,700 --> 00:32:03,730
那就找个办法
Find a way, then.

436
00:32:03,930 --> 00:32:07,600
如果你想拉拢达芬奇 那就去吧
Make this Da Vinci ours, if it amuses you.

437
00:32:09,900 --> 00:32:12,600
瑞阿里奥 你那个奴隶女工  
Oh, Riario, your slave girl.

438
00:32:12,730 --> 00:32:14,300
那个埃塞俄比亚人
The Abyssinian.

439
00:32:14,430 --> 00:32:16,000
我今晚要她
I want her for tonight.

440
00:32:19,100 --> 00:32:22,200
别舍不得啊 明天早上她就重回你怀抱了
Don't fret. You'll have her back in the morning.

441
00:32:32,260 --> 00:32:33,460
吁!
Whoa!

442
00:32:39,430 --> 00:32:40,860
谢谢 盖尔伯托
Thank you, Gualberto.

443
00:32:46,360 --> 00:32:48,200
洛伦佐?
Lorenzo?

444
00:32:48,400 --> 00:32:52,260
不是他 我知道他用什么方式召见你
No. I know how he summons you.

445
00:32:52,430 --> 00:32:57,130
盖尔伯托 四轮马车 芳香玫瑰
Gualberto, the carriage, the rose.

446
00:32:58,230 --> 00:33:00,130
他们都在这面墙上
They're all up there.

447
00:33:00,260 --> 00:33:01,800
洛伦佐 他父亲
Lorenzo, his father.

448
00:33:01,930 --> 00:33:03,460
他祖父 科西莫
His grandfather, Cosimo.

449
00:33:03,600 --> 00:33:05,300
朱利亚诺 他的宝贝猞猁
Giuliano, his lynx.

450
00:33:05,430 --> 00:33:11,100
他的姐妹 我 还有贝奇
His sisters, me, Becchi.

451
00:33:11,230 --> 00:33:14,760
甚至也有那个愚蠢的公爵 
Even that pig Dukepig Duke.

452
00:33:14,930 --> 00:33:17,730
因为他对于佛罗伦萨来说意义非凡
Because he was important to Florence.

453
00:33:20,530 --> 00:33:24,360
洛伦佐没有召见我
Lorenzo doesn't summon me.

454
00:33:24,500 --> 00:33:26,600
但是他有
Oh, but he does.

455
00:33:26,860 --> 00:33:29,930
总不能老是见你吧 洛伦佐有其他的事情需要做
It hasn't always been you. Lorenzo's had other diversions.

456
00:33:30,200 --> 00:33:33,630
那么 你想怎样? 让我离他远点?
Well, what do you want? For me to stay away from him?

457
00:33:33,800 --> 00:33:36,330
我爱他 我爱这座城市
I love him. And I love this city.

458
00:33:38,500 --> 00:33:41,100
或许是因为爱屋及乌吧
Perhaps because he is this city.

459
00:33:41,260 --> 00:33:42,830
你懂的 我们必须胜利
You see, we have to prevail.

460
00:33:43,060 --> 00:33:45,360
你认为 我会妨碍这场成功?
And do you think me an impediment to that end?

461
00:33:45,530 --> 00:33:47,860
你不能对自己造成的影响装作若无其事
You cannot be as brazen with your affections.

462
00:33:48,000 --> 00:33:50,160
不要公开露面了
Not in public.

463
00:33:51,430 --> 00:33:54,730
宫廷中有了叛徒
There is a conspirator in our court.

464
00:33:55,000 --> 00:33:58,030
不瞒你说 洛伦佐一直在逐个排除
As we speak, Lorenzo continues to eliminate suspects

465
00:33:58,200 --> 00:34:00,460
缩小嫌疑范围
and draws the noose tighter.

466
00:34:00,630 --> 00:34:02,700
他们会找到那个叛徒 处死他
They will find the traitor and execute him.

467
00:34:02,900 --> 00:34:06,560
但此前 洛伦佐的所有弱点都可能被人利用
But until then, any vulnerability against Lorenzo could be exploited.

468
00:34:06,730 --> 00:34:09,100
你也可能被人利用来对付他
You could be used as leverage against him.

469
00:34:11,330 --> 00:34:13,630
你只会让他分心 这就是你的功绩
You are a distraction. That's your function.

470
00:34:13,760 --> 00:34:15,200
我能容忍你们的胡闹
I will tolerate that.

471
00:34:15,360 --> 00:34:18,960
但是我不能容忍你成为他的弱点
But I will not tolerate you becoming a vulnerability.

472
00:34:21,760 --> 00:34:25,100
我走后五分钟 你再离开
Wait five minutes after I leave.

473
00:34:26,160 --> 00:34:32,300
克拉丽斯 我知道你爱他
Clarice, I know you love him.

474
00:34:32,500 --> 00:34:35,230
面对我这样的事情 你怎么承受得了?
How can you even stand to look at me?

475
00:34:35,460 --> 00:34:38,100
因为我知道 你永远也不可能出现在那面墙上
Because I know you will never be up on that wall.

476
00:34:43,230 --> 00:34:45,460
夫人
Ah, Signora.

477
00:34:45,630 --> 00:34:47,430
您离开前 能容我说两句吗?
Might I have a word before you depart?

478
00:34:47,600 --> 00:34:50,430
明天您和您丈夫会在家么?
Are you and your husband at home tomorrow?

479
00:34:50,630 --> 00:34:53,700
我是想问下你们最近的行程 此事非常重要
It's vital I question you about any recent travels.

480
00:34:53,900 --> 00:34:56,000
- 我们的行程?  - 恕我冒昧
- Our travels?  - Forgive my indelicacy,

481
00:34:56,300 --> 00:35:00,530
但是洛伦佐命令我跟踪
but Lorenzo requests I track the comings and goings of everyone

482
00:35:00,700 --> 00:35:02,530
所有能够进出宫殿的人
with access to the palace.

483
00:35:02,760 --> 00:35:05,430
时局紧张 没人能例外
Given these vexing times, we can't make exceptions.

484
00:35:05,730 --> 00:35:08,900
当然 我和尼科洛将会全力配合的
Absolutely. Niccolo and I will assist you in any way that we can.

485
00:35:09,130 --> 00:35:12,300
很好 那么明天中午怎么样?
Excellent. Tomorrow noon then?

486
00:35:12,500 --> 00:35:15,430
好的 再见 金泰尔
Yes. Good day, Gentile.

487
00:35:26,930 --> 00:35:31,260
盖尔伯托 你今晚还要去接我
Gualberto, you shall retrieve me again this evening.

488
00:35:31,430 --> 00:35:33,730
洛伦佐希望我过来
Lorenzo requires my presence.

489
00:35:44,760 --> 00:35:47,130
我命你离开 地狱魔鬼!
I cast you out, infernal adversary!

490
00:35:47,360 --> 00:35:49,100
离开奥丽埃纳修女
Begone from our Sister Oriana,

491
00:35:49,330 --> 00:35:51,200
离开所有主的创造物
from all made in the image of God

492
00:35:51,400 --> 00:35:53,800
让他们从邪恶统治中解放出来
and redeemed by the precious blood of the divine Lamb.

493
00:35:54,030 --> 00:35:56,100
最神圣的主命令你!
The most high God commands you!

494
00:35:56,400 --> 00:35:58,530
- 罗马人  - 最神圣的主命令你
- Man of Rome.  - The Most High God commands you.

495
00:35:58,830 --> 00:36:01,330
- 我知道你因何而来  - 永恒的神旨幻化为肉体
- I know why you came.  - Eternal Word of God made flesh.

496
00:36:01,600 --> 00:36:05,200
- 我知道你在渴求什么  - 神圣的十字架之谜命令你
- I know what you crave.  - The sacred mystery of the cross commands you.

497
00:36:05,460 --> 00:36:08,830
- 我知道你在渴求什么  - 尊贵的圣母玛利亚命令你
- I know what you crave.  - The exalted Virgin Mary commands you.

498
00:36:09,060 --> 00:36:11,360
你根本一无所知
All you think about is fucking.

499
00:36:11,530 --> 00:36:14,500
我以万能的主之名命令你
I adjure you by the living God, by the true God,

500
00:36:14,730 --> 00:36:18,360
停止欺骗这个女人!
cease your deception of this woman!

501
00:36:18,500 --> 00:36:20,500
离开!
Begone!

502
00:36:20,730 --> 00:36:22,400
- 离开!  - 墨丘利长官!
- Begone!  - Prefect Mercuri!

503
00:36:22,560 --> 00:36:23,960
安静!
Silence!

504
00:36:27,200 --> 00:36:33,500
我命令你 离开!
I command you, begone!

505
00:36:33,660 --> 00:36:35,860
在她死之前那一刻
The moments before she died,

506
00:36:36,100 --> 00:36:39,030
我在她眼中看到了神之光芒
I saw the light of God in her eyes.

507
00:36:39,200 --> 00:36:41,200
她被救赎了
She is saved.

508
00:36:42,860 --> 00:36:46,830
告诉我 长官 在你驱魔生涯中
Tell me something, Prefect. In all your time doing this,

509
00:36:47,030 --> 00:36:50,000
有没有遇到过不能驱逐的魔障呢?
have you ever met a demon that you couldn't expel?

510
00:36:50,160 --> 00:36:52,430
没有
No.

511
00:36:52,560 --> 00:36:54,260
"从黑暗转向光明"
"Ex umbra in solem".

512
00:36:54,430 --> 00:36:56,160
"从黑暗转向光明"
"From Shadow into the Light".

513
00:36:56,360 --> 00:37:00,300
密令中的警句
Epigram of the Secret Archives.

514
00:37:05,300 --> 00:37:08,530
我在哪儿? 我这是怎么了?
Where am I? What am I doing?

515
00:37:08,730 --> 00:37:10,400
你在女修道院
You're at the Convent.

516
00:37:10,660 --> 00:37:13,430
你在女修道院 嘘 嘘
You're at the Convent. Sshh. Sshh.

517
00:37:13,600 --> 00:37:16,360
- 但是我为你离开了  - 你又回来了
- But I left it for you.  - You returned.

518
00:37:16,560 --> 00:37:21,760
你回来帮助你的朋友们
You came back to aid your friends.

519
00:37:21,930 --> 00:37:25,060
你撒谎 莱昂纳多
You lied, Leonardo.

520
00:37:25,200 --> 00:37:29,300
你向我保证会有奇迹的
You promised me wonders.

521
00:37:29,700 --> 00:37:34,630
你说过我们能飞翔 我们会像太阳一样发光发热
You said we'd fly. You said we'd burn like the sun,

522
00:37:34,900 --> 00:37:38,700
但是你的世界没有太阳
but there's no sun in your world.

523
00:37:38,930 --> 00:37:43,500
只有黑暗和寒冷
There's only coldness and shadows.

524
00:37:43,630 --> 00:37:46,300
嘘 嘘 冷静点
Ssh. Ssh. Calm yourself.

525
00:37:46,500 --> 00:37:48,630
你病了
You've taken ill.

526
00:37:48,800 --> 00:37:51,830
你那么聪明
You're so smart,

527
00:37:52,030 --> 00:37:53,960
那么美
you're so beautiful,

528
00:37:54,260 --> 00:38:02,400
但我们只是你的玩物 是不是?
but we're just toys to you, aren't we?

529
00:38:04,200 --> 00:38:07,200
我想也该净化这个灵魂了
I think it is time to cleanse this dear soul as well.

530
00:38:07,460 --> 00:38:10,730
别碰她 你别...
Don't touch her. Don't you...

531
00:38:10,930 --> 00:38:14,860
她一定可以自己战胜恶魔 给她一次机会吧
Surely she deserves a chance to fight this herself.

532
00:38:15,030 --> 00:38:19,160
就再多给她一天时间
Just one more day.

533
00:38:19,360 --> 00:38:21,730
苍天为证
In God's name.

534
00:38:21,860 --> 00:38:24,230
那到明天黎明吧
Till dawn, then.

535
00:38:24,400 --> 00:38:26,260
如果早晨还解决不了
If you cannot solve this by morning,

536
00:38:26,430 --> 00:38:29,060
我们必须把魔鬼驱逐出她们的身体
we must burn this evil out of them.

537
00:38:43,260 --> 00:38:45,260
鬼火
Foolish fire.

538
00:38:52,730 --> 00:38:55,630
不要!
No!

539
00:39:01,200 --> 00:39:04,600
我要为你飞翔 莱昂 向太阳飞去
I'm going to fly for you, Leo, fly to the sun.

540
00:39:32,600 --> 00:39:37,930
你们这些伪善的小人 这是在佛罗伦萨 马上滚出去
You're on Florentine soil, you sheep-biting scut and I want you out. Now.

541
00:39:38,230 --> 00:39:40,700
黄发小孩发狠话了...
Tough talk from the golden boy...

542
00:39:40,930 --> 00:39:42,860
可他哥哥没陪着他
without your brother to back it up.

543
00:39:44,860 --> 00:39:48,000
无所谓 不用多久你们俩都会滚出城了
No matter. It won't be long till the both of you are run out of town.

544
00:39:48,230 --> 00:39:50,100
- 你怎么知道?  - 很简单
- How do you figure that?  - Simple.

545
00:39:50,330 --> 00:39:53,800
罗马人多势强 天时地利
Rome has more men. And the Lord on its side.

546
00:39:54,060 --> 00:39:56,260
我们有十架管风琴火炮
Well, we've got ten pipe organ muskets

547
00:39:56,500 --> 00:40:01,360
一分钟可以连续发射33次
capable of firing 33 rounds a minute on ours.

548
00:40:01,530 --> 00:40:03,900
十架火炮?
Ten guns?

549
00:40:04,130 --> 00:40:06,700
谢谢你告诉我
Good to know, thank you for that.

550
00:40:23,030 --> 00:40:24,860
我自己进去
I'll be fine on my own.

551
00:40:25,030 --> 00:40:27,400
如您所愿 夫人
As you wish, Signora.

552
00:40:27,600 --> 00:40:29,730
我们开始排除嫌犯
We're starting to eliminate suspects.

553
00:40:29,960 --> 00:40:32,430
一些记账员 厨师
Some of the counters, the cooks.

554
00:40:32,660 --> 00:40:34,530
嫌犯的范围越来越小
The circle of suspicion grows smaller.

555
00:40:34,730 --> 00:40:36,930
大部分都很忠诚
Most will prove loyal.

556
00:40:37,100 --> 00:40:38,600
那人总会露马脚
One will slip.

557
00:40:38,760 --> 00:40:40,800
那就找出他来了
And then we'll have him.

558
00:41:08,830 --> 00:41:10,200
我没让你来
I didn't send for you.

559
00:41:10,400 --> 00:41:14,160
我想你有 我感觉到了
I think you did. I felt it.

560
00:41:15,500 --> 00:41:18,500
我现在事务缠身
Matters of state obsess me.

561
00:41:18,660 --> 00:41:19,730
你还是走吧
Please go.

562
00:41:19,930 --> 00:41:22,400
有人看见我来了
There are those who saw me arrive,

563
00:41:22,630 --> 00:41:26,560
盖尔伯托... 值班的军官
Gualberto... Officers of the Night.

564
00:41:27,960 --> 00:41:30,860
他们知道 我是来找你的
And they know I only come here for you.

565
00:41:31,100 --> 00:41:34,460
如果我现在走 他们也许会以为你...
They may think that you finished with me...

566
00:41:34,600 --> 00:41:35,660
早泄了
prematurely.

567
00:41:35,900 --> 00:41:38,760
我想让他们怎么想 他们就得怎么想
They'll think what I'll have them think.

568
00:41:38,930 --> 00:41:40,260
我没让你过来
I don't want you here.

569
00:41:40,430 --> 00:41:42,760
当然
No.

570
00:41:42,930 --> 00:41:44,300
你当然不想
Of course you don't.

571
00:42:38,030 --> 00:42:39,560
你心烦
You're troubled.

572
00:42:39,730 --> 00:42:42,930
告诉我为什么
Tell me what it is.

573
00:42:43,100 --> 00:42:46,860
是因为有探子吗?
Is it the spy?

574
00:42:47,000 --> 00:42:49,360
是你妻子说的
Your wife.

575
00:42:49,600 --> 00:42:53,100
她今天早晨传召我来
She summoned me this morning.

576
00:42:53,400 --> 00:42:55,460
- 我会跟她谈的  - 别 拜托不要
- I'll have words with her.  - No, please don't.

577
00:42:55,700 --> 00:42:59,300
她这样做 是因为关心你的安全
Her actions were only out of concern for your safety.

578
00:43:01,460 --> 00:43:04,900
亲爱的 任何人都可能是叛徒
My love, this traitor could be anyone,

579
00:43:05,100 --> 00:43:07,000
不论是跟你多亲近的
no matter how close they are to you.

580
00:43:07,230 --> 00:43:08,930
克拉丽斯的怀疑很合乎情理
Clarice's suspicions are justified.

581
00:43:09,130 --> 00:43:11,800
你的调查不能放过任何人
You can't let your investigation overlook anyone.

582
00:43:12,030 --> 00:43:14,130
不论嫌疑多小 都要仔细搜查
Search even those you suspect the least,

583
00:43:14,360 --> 00:43:16,860
因为威胁无处不在
for the threat may reside anywhere 

584
00:43:17,030 --> 00:43:19,560
即便是自己家里
even in your own home.

585
00:43:37,460 --> 00:43:39,260
大师 都20个了 能不吃了吗?
Maestro, that's 20. Can I stop now?

586
00:43:39,500 --> 00:43:42,060
- 全喝了  - 为什么让我这样做?
- Wash it all down.  - Why are you making me do this?

587
00:43:42,300 --> 00:43:45,560
我们已经排除了偶然原因
We've eliminated accidental causes.

588
00:43:45,760 --> 00:43:49,730
只剩下蓄意下毒了
That leaves only intentional contamination.

589
00:43:50,030 --> 00:43:53,530
- 这酒和圆饼被下毒了吗?  - 显然没有啊
- The wine and wafers are poisoned?  - Apparently not.

590
00:43:53,700 --> 00:43:56,730
只是怀疑而已
It was a thought.

591
00:43:56,960 --> 00:43:58,960
不可能是恶魔引起的吗?
Is it not possible demons are the cause?

592
00:43:59,130 --> 00:44:00,560
那不符合逻辑
It goes against logic.

593
00:44:00,830 --> 00:44:05,330
上帝会惩罚他的追随者 却放过我们这些异教徒吗?
God punishes his admirers, and leaves heathens like us unscathed?

594
00:44:05,530 --> 00:44:07,060
这一定是个阴谋
This has the makings of a plot.

595
00:44:07,300 --> 00:44:09,330
利用恶魔 让人们害怕
Invoke the Devil, make people afraid,

596
00:44:09,600 --> 00:44:13,800
人们害怕的时候 就不会追根问源了
and when they're afraid, they stop asking questions.

597
00:44:14,000 --> 00:44:15,600
不 这不是骗子的骗术
No, this isn't the work of the Deceiver,

598
00:44:15,760 --> 00:44:18,500
这是在反击
this is a counter-attack.

599
00:44:18,660 --> 00:44:20,530
是罗马人干的
Rome is inducing this possession.

600
00:44:20,700 --> 00:44:22,560
我就知道
I know it.

601
00:44:22,760 --> 00:44:25,960
我只是... 不明白是怎么干的
I just... I don't know how.

602
00:44:32,400 --> 00:44:33,400
伯蒂诺!
Bertino!

603
00:44:33,560 --> 00:44:36,730
拿撒勒人耶稣人
I-N-R-I.

604
00:44:37,030 --> 00:44:40,200
我用救世主的十字架在他脖子上刻下字母
I carved the letters from our Savior's cross into his neck,

605
00:44:40,330 --> 00:44:42,960
这样就可以驱赶恶魔
driving out the demons.

606
00:44:43,200 --> 00:44:48,330
下一个我要来拯救谁呢?
Which of you will I save next?

607
00:44:48,530 --> 00:44:50,030
- 恶魔!  - 没有恶魔
- Devil!  - No devil.

608
00:44:50,230 --> 00:44:52,160
- 是美第奇  - 把他绑紧了!
- Just a Medici.  - Bind him securely!

609
00:44:57,030 --> 00:44:59,660
这个诅咒竟然从修女
For this curse to pass from the nuns

610
00:44:59,900 --> 00:45:02,500
传到了夜巡官
to one of the Officers of the Night,

611
00:45:02,660 --> 00:45:05,400
答案肯定就在我们面前
the answer has to be right before us.

612
00:45:05,700 --> 00:45:07,630
- 你的手下今天吃了什么东西?  - 什么都没吃
- What has your man eaten today?  - Nothing.

613
00:45:07,860 --> 00:45:11,330
他为了帮助困难的修女就斋戒了
He offered up a fast to Our Lord to help the afflicted nuns.

614
00:45:11,560 --> 00:45:13,800
- 他很虔诚  - 我们中最为虔诚的
- A pious man.  - The most pious of us all.

615
00:45:14,100 --> 00:45:19,260
他每一刻都会为圣安东尼祈祷 以求结束这些女人的痛苦
Every moment, he would pray to Saint Anthony to end the women's agony.

616
00:45:21,130 --> 00:45:23,600
- 他怎么祈祷?  - 亲吻雕像的脚部
- How did he pray?  - Kissing the feet of the statue.

617
00:45:23,860 --> 00:45:26,200
这是几个世纪以来的传统
It's been a custom for centuries.

618
00:45:26,500 --> 00:45:28,760
瓦妮莎 还有其他人... 她们都践行同样的传统吗?
Vanessa, the others... did they practice the same custom?

619
00:45:28,930 --> 00:45:31,900
这里的许多修女都会这么做
Many of the Sisters here do.

620
00:45:32,130 --> 00:45:36,500
你们的守护神要帮我们解决问题啦
It may be time for your patron to shed some light on our problem.

621
00:45:36,660 --> 00:45:38,200
给我找来萤火虫
I need fireflies.

622
00:45:56,030 --> 00:45:58,160
吃掉了
A capture.

623
00:45:58,360 --> 00:45:59,860
你教得很好
You've taught me well.

624
00:46:00,060 --> 00:46:03,930
我第一次胜利已指日可待
My first victory is close at hand.

625
00:46:04,200 --> 00:46:09,600
你要小心点 别对绝望的敌人赶尽杀绝
You should be careful not to press a desperate foe too hard.

626
00:46:09,830 --> 00:46:15,700
否则你会陷入神的掌控
Or you may find yourself at the mercy of a divine move.

627
00:46:15,960 --> 00:46:23,600
'妙棋一招 全盘皆活'
'The inspired play turns a losing game into victory.'

628
00:46:23,830 --> 00:46:27,000
叫你手下把灯灭掉
Have your men douse their lanterns.

629
00:46:27,160 --> 00:46:28,700
这些笨蛋在干什么?
What are the fools up to now?

630
00:46:28,860 --> 00:46:31,100
都无所谓了 马上都结束了
It matters not, this ends now.

631
00:46:31,300 --> 00:46:33,600
不同光的不同特质
The distinct properties of different lights

632
00:46:33,860 --> 00:46:37,400
可以让我们清楚地看到之前被隐匿的东西
enable us to see clearly what may previously have been hidden.

633
00:46:37,760 --> 00:46:41,160
'比如说 萤火虫的光 能强化红色的东西'
'The glow of the firefly, for instance, intensifies anything red.'

634
00:46:41,400 --> 00:46:43,460
我绘画时曾用它校准
I've used it in the past to calibrate crimson

635
00:46:43,660 --> 00:46:45,500
调出了最精准的深红色
in my paints to the most specific degree.

636
00:46:45,660 --> 00:46:47,630
但这跟恶魔有什么关系?
But what does this have to do with the demons?

637
00:46:49,860 --> 00:46:53,530
马上就能知道了
Everything, as it turns out.

638
00:46:53,700 --> 00:46:56,830
以某些真菌为例
Some fungi, for instance,

639
00:46:57,060 --> 00:47:00,300
在特定光下 会显出大红色
appear bright red in certain lights.

640
00:47:05,400 --> 00:47:07,530
火在烧啊! 快熄灭吧!
Burning! Make it stop!

641
00:47:07,700 --> 00:47:09,160
我会的 孩子
I will, my child.

642
00:47:09,400 --> 00:47:12,900
给她们上油 把恶魔烧出来!
Prepare them with oil. Time to burn the devil out!

643
00:47:24,300 --> 00:47:25,630
给她上烙印
Brand her.

644
00:47:25,800 --> 00:47:28,600
是红麦角菌!
Red ergot fungus!

645
00:47:28,760 --> 00:47:30,130
它通常生长在黑麦上
It normally grows on rye.

646
00:47:30,360 --> 00:47:34,030
症状很可怕 痉挛 呕吐 浮肿 腐烂
The effects are dire: spasms, vomiting, dropsy, gangrene,

647
00:47:34,200 --> 00:47:35,960
还有 据幸存者的说法
and, according to survivors,

648
00:47:36,200 --> 00:47:40,500
会有类似地狱之火的强烈灼烧感
a distinct sensation of being burned, as if by hellfire.

649
00:47:40,700 --> 00:47:42,060
这样会扰乱思维 你懂吧
It scrambles the mind, you see.

650
00:47:42,260 --> 00:47:44,160
令人产生幻觉和癫狂
It causes hallucinations and mania.

651
00:47:44,430 --> 00:47:47,700
达芬奇 你也和她们一样疯了吧 一边去 不然烧你
Your mind is as scrambled as theirs, Da Vinci. Now move aside or burn.

652
00:47:47,860 --> 00:47:51,200
我们必须清洗修道院 烧掉感染源
We must cleanse this convent, cauterize the infection.

653
00:47:51,360 --> 00:47:53,100
修女们已无药可救
The nuns are beyond help,

654
00:47:53,330 --> 00:47:55,260
她们是精神攻击的受害者
victims of a spiritual assault.

655
00:47:55,460 --> 00:47:57,300
这一点我同意你的说法
On that account, I agree with you.

656
00:47:57,560 --> 00:48:02,460
这是将圣灵化为武器的人做的恶行
An assault perpetrated by agents who would seek to weaponize the Holy Spirit.

657
00:48:05,300 --> 00:48:09,060
有人在外面那座雕像的脚上种满了菌类
The feet of the statue outside are dusted with ergot.

658
00:48:09,360 --> 00:48:13,260
这些受害者生病之前 都吻了圣安东尼的脚
All of the victims kissed the feet of Saint Anthony before falling sick.

659
00:48:13,530 --> 00:48:18,000
所有患病的修女 包括瓦妮莎... 甚至你虔诚的军官伯蒂诺
All of the stricken Sisters, Vanessa... even your pious Officer, Bertino.

660
00:48:18,160 --> 00:48:19,600
所有人都是
To a person.

661
00:48:19,860 --> 00:48:21,930
- 这些都是胡说!  - 是吗?
- What you're suggesting is absurd!  - Is it?

662
00:48:22,200 --> 00:48:24,930
那为什么你和格伦沃尔德长官的手下都没有生病?
Then why have neither you nor Captain Grunwald's men fallen sick?

663
00:48:25,100 --> 00:48:26,830
嗯?
Hmm?

664
00:48:27,100 --> 00:48:29,160
为什么像美第奇先生 小尼科 还有我
Why aren't heretics like Signor Medici,

665
00:48:29,400 --> 00:48:31,960
这样的异教徒都没有生病?
or young Nico, or myself fallen sick?

666
00:48:32,160 --> 00:48:34,730
是因为我们没有对雕像行亲吻礼
It's because we made no obeisance to the statue.

667
00:48:34,860 --> 00:48:36,130
你和你的手下也没有
Nor did you or your men.

668
00:48:36,430 --> 00:48:39,060
我再也受不了你这愚蠢的诽谤了
I won't stand for this fatuous slander another moment.

669
00:48:39,300 --> 00:48:42,860
那你吻下圣安东尼的脚 证明我错了啊
Well, all you need to do is kiss the feet of Saint Anthony to prove me wrong.

670
00:48:47,800 --> 00:48:50,630
"红麦角菌"?
"Red ergot"?

671
00:48:50,830 --> 00:48:52,900
谁听说过这玩意?
Who ever heard of such a thing?

672
00:48:53,060 --> 00:48:55,860
站住! 我告诉你
Stop! I will tell you.

673
00:48:56,060 --> 00:48:59,230
一名叫做杰弗洛伊·杜·布鲁利尔的历史学家
A historian by the name of Geoffroy du Breuil

674
00:48:59,460 --> 00:49:02,160
记载了12世纪一场类似的疫情爆发
recorded one such outbreak in the 12th century.

675
00:49:02,500 --> 00:49:07,600
也许你还有抄本 藏在密令里吧?
Perhaps you have a copy of it, hidden amongst your Secret Archives?

676
00:49:11,100 --> 00:49:13,230
存在治疗这种病痛的方法
A treatment for this affliction exists.

677
00:49:13,500 --> 00:49:16,660
由醋和草药混合而成的绿色药膏
It's a green ointment of these herbs and vinegar,

678
00:49:16,900 --> 00:49:19,200
加上元气旺盛的水蛭
and a vigorous regime of leeching.

679
00:49:22,330 --> 00:49:26,760
用这个方法 说不定剩下的病人们还有救
If we use this, we may still be able to save those who've fallen sick.

680
00:49:26,930 --> 00:49:29,000
干得不错 达芬奇
Well done, Da Vinci.

681
00:49:31,600 --> 00:49:32,900
谢谢大师
Thank you Maestro.

682
00:50:25,660 --> 00:50:27,130
你明白为何要带我们过来
You know why you brought us here.

683
00:50:28,500 --> 00:50:30,960
我们以死来证明你的天才
We died to prove your genius.

684
00:50:45,560 --> 00:50:48,200
瑞阿里奥!
Riario!

685
00:51:09,200 --> 00:51:11,960
告诉我说什么才能赢到另一个钥匙
Tell me what to say to win the other key.

686
00:51:12,200 --> 00:51:15,560
告诉我说什么才能赢到钥匙!
Tell me what to say to win the key!

687
00:51:15,700 --> 00:51:16,930
快告诉我!
Tell me!

688
00:51:20,130 --> 00:51:24,300
我是大地苍穹之子
I am a son of Earth and Starry Heaven.

689
00:51:25,660 --> 00:51:30,500
我是大地苍穹之...
I am a son of Earth and Starry...

690
00:51:36,700 --> 00:51:38,100
母亲?
Mother?

691
00:51:46,660 --> 00:51:47,930
母亲?
Mother?

692
00:51:48,130 --> 00:51:51,130
达芬奇... 能听到我说话吗?
Da Vinci... can you hear me?

693
00:51:51,400 --> 00:51:53,360
我觉得他开始有反应了
I think he's starting to respond.

694
00:52:01,500 --> 00:52:04,700
大师... 你还好吗?
Maestro... are you alright?

695
00:52:04,900 --> 00:52:08,130
你一直发癫 还狂喊
You kept stirring and crying out.

696
00:52:08,300 --> 00:52:10,860
瓦妮莎的嘴唇
Vanessa's lips.

697
00:52:11,130 --> 00:52:14,730
瓦妮莎的嘴唇... 也有毒
Vanessa's lips... they bore the poison.

698
00:52:18,160 --> 00:52:20,400
- 我看到了幻觉  - 是 我们明白
- I was in a deep vision.  - Yes, we know.

699
00:52:20,630 --> 00:52:23,900
修女一直在照顾你
The Sisters have been treating you all day long.

700
00:52:24,130 --> 00:52:27,360
- 瓦妮莎? 她...  - 毫发无损
- Vanessa? Is she...  - Perfectly fine.

701
00:52:32,000 --> 00:52:35,360
你的行为让罗马无法因修女的去世而怪罪我们
You've kept Rome from claiming a beautiful victim.

702
00:52:35,560 --> 00:52:37,530
一切都过去了
It's all over now.

703
00:52:37,730 --> 00:52:40,260
我看 这恐怕才刚开始
For me, I fear it's just begun.

704
00:52:44,660 --> 00:52:46,300
"撒旦 离开吧
"Begone, Satan,

705
00:52:46,460 --> 00:52:47,860
因为经上记载
for it is written,

706
00:52:48,100 --> 00:52:52,600
当拜主你的神 单要事奉他 "
you shall worship the Lord your God, and Him only shall you serve."

707
00:52:52,730 --> 00:52:54,360
你知道你的经文 各人拜主不同
You know your scripture.

708
00:52:54,560 --> 00:52:58,460
我现在知道很多事 红衣教主
I now know a great many things, Cardinal.

709
00:53:01,500 --> 00:53:04,800
有条消息一定要转达给瑞阿里奥
That's a message worth delivering to Riario.

710
00:53:05,000 --> 00:53:10,360
相信我 我和瑞阿里奥伯爵还有很多事情要讨论
Believe me, Count Riario and I have much to discuss.

711
00:53:16,960 --> 00:53:19,730
他们怎么做到的 大师?
How did they do it, Maestro?

712
00:53:19,930 --> 00:53:21,730
不会很难
It wouldn't have been hard.

713
00:53:22,030 --> 00:53:26,760
就像院长说的那样 女修道院对所有礼拜者开放
The Convent's open to all worshipers, as the Prioress said.

714
00:53:27,000 --> 00:53:30,130
随便一个自称有善心的人 就能混进来
Just one single, sympathetic agent could have strolled in,

715
00:53:30,360 --> 00:53:34,430
在圣安东尼的脚上下毒...
contaminated the toes of Saint Anthony...

716
00:53:34,600 --> 00:53:38,530
然后一直等
and waited.

717
00:53:38,760 --> 00:53:43,060
然后一错再错
And then "Abyssus abyssum invocat"

718
00:53:43,360 --> 00:53:45,500
一步错 步步错
One misstep leads to another.

719
00:54:08,730 --> 00:54:12,230
他们对神像下毒
They poisoned the pious.

720
00:54:12,430 --> 00:54:15,300
天啊 真同情那些信徒
Oh, God, have mercy on the believers.

721
00:54:15,600 --> 00:54:18,360
我们为佛罗伦萨又争取到了些时间
We just bought Florence more time.

722
00:54:24,500 --> 00:54:27,130
- 怎么了?  - 一名骑兵带来消息
- What is it?  - A rider brought word.

723
00:54:27,360 --> 00:54:30,560
你弟弟走漏了消息 说出了我们有多少火炮
Your brother let slip how many guns we have.

724
00:54:30,730 --> 00:54:32,660
虽然还在继续造 但...
Production continues, but...

725
00:54:32,930 --> 00:54:34,960
朱利亚诺本能把失误瞒住 但他承认了
Giuliano could've hidden his error but admitted it.

726
00:54:35,100 --> 00:54:37,160
还好如此
For all the good that does.

727
00:54:37,330 --> 00:54:41,360
罗马清楚了解敌情后 就会进攻了
Rome will strike when it knows exactly what it faces.

728
00:54:41,560 --> 00:54:43,800
我们得多生产点火炮了
We'll have to produce even more guns now.

729
00:54:46,130 --> 00:54:49,530
对了 我下令搜查全宫 一片瓦都没放过
Oh, yes, I ordered a full search of the palace, no stone unturned.

730
00:54:49,760 --> 00:54:50,900
查出什么了吗?
Have you discovered something?

731
00:54:51,100 --> 00:54:53,300
我们最好私下里说
Perhaps we should discuss this in private.

732
00:54:53,630 --> 00:55:01,760
现在说吧 康蒂 不然我会以为你在隐瞒什么
Show me now, Conti, or I'll think it's you with something to hide.

733
00:55:08,530 --> 00:55:09,930
你在哪儿找到的?
Where did you find this?

734
00:55:10,100 --> 00:55:12,060
在哪儿?
Where?

735
00:55:12,260 --> 00:55:13,860
在贝奇先生的住处
In Signor Becchi's quarters.

736
00:55:14,000 --> 00:55:15,800
你撒谎!
You lie!

737
00:55:15,960 --> 00:55:17,530
这不是我的!
These are not mine!

738
00:55:17,760 --> 00:55:20,130
在架子上面找到的 大人 我发誓
It was on a shelf, il Magnifico. I swear.

739
00:55:20,300 --> 00:55:21,900
混在其他书之间
Hidden amongst other books.

740
00:55:22,030 --> 00:55:26,230
原来是你
It was you.

741
00:55:26,430 --> 00:55:28,000
从头到尾原来叛徒是你
All along, the traitor was you.

742
00:55:28,160 --> 00:55:30,060
洛伦佐 这是场误会
Lorenzo, this is a mistake.

743
00:55:30,230 --> 00:55:32,460
罗马斯库多
Roman Scudos.

744
00:55:32,630 --> 00:55:33,860
盖有罗马密印的信
Papers with the Papal Seal.

745
00:55:34,060 --> 00:55:38,500
一张清单 记得都是放置给罗马寄信的地址
A list of locations to hide them for delivery to Rome.

746
00:55:38,660 --> 00:55:41,930
我自己家发现的!
Found in my home!

747
00:55:42,160 --> 00:55:43,600
- 请听我说 洛伦佐...  - 闭嘴!
- Please, Lorenzo...  - Silence!

748
00:55:43,830 --> 00:55:46,000
不然我亲手把你舌头割下来
Or I'll cut out your tongue myself.

749
00:55:50,230 --> 00:55:51,400
把他带走
Remove him.

750
00:55:56,330 --> 00:55:58,000
送到巴杰罗
To the Bargello.

751
00:56:01,260 --> 00:56:03,230
你似乎又赢了
It would appear you've won again.

752
00:56:05,160 --> 00:56:07,900
还有一场游戏
There will be other games.

753
00:56:08,100 --> 00:56:11,430
脚下的路很难选泽
It's difficult, choosing which path to follow,

754
00:56:11,760 --> 00:56:16,960
用我传授给你的所有策略 找到一条出路
trying to see a way through all the strategies you've initiated.

755
00:56:17,130 --> 00:56:18,630
不
No.

756
00:56:18,830 --> 00:56:22,060
不 那并不难
No, that's not difficult.

757
00:56:22,230 --> 00:56:25,260
你只要去坚持信仰
You simply have to believe.

758
00:56:25,500 --> 00:56:28,260
从我的经验来看 坚持信仰不会那么容易
In my experience, there's nothing simple about belief.

759
00:56:28,530 --> 00:56:31,260
这就是你我间的差异
That's the difference between you and me.

760
00:56:34,330 --> 00:56:35,530
不止这点
Not the only one.

761
00:56:49,830 --> 00:56:52,600
我听到你的话
I heard you.

762
00:56:52,760 --> 00:56:54,230
告诉琐罗把这些都解决掉
Tell Zo to dispose of these.

763
00:56:54,430 --> 00:56:56,100
他们已经尽其用了
They've served their purpose.

764
00:57:01,230 --> 00:57:05,230
我猜他很喜欢在里面呆着 是吧?
I gather he quite prefers it in there, no?

765
00:57:07,730 --> 00:57:10,260
他看起来似乎对自由不感兴趣
He doesn't seem to be interested in his freedom,

766
00:57:10,430 --> 00:57:13,060
也许他喜欢他的漂亮小笼
maybe he likes his pretty cage.

767
00:57:29,060 --> 00:57:32,330
鬼火
Ignis fatuus.

768
00:57:42,160 --> 00:57:45,960
随着一场游戏结束 另一场游戏开始
As one game ends, another begins.

769
00:58:00,000 --> 00:58:10,000
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==-- 
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途 

770
00:58:15,000 --> 00:58:30,000
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/ ==-- 
协调: 潇妹纸
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：SceneryJuly 波特妹子 落寞卷菜 Tracy 潇妹纸 戴蜀
校对：岸
