The noble House of Batiatus
stands humbled!
Humbled by the blessings
the gods have seen fit
to shower upon us.
And by the presence
of the most revered citizens
in all of Capua,
come to join in celebrating
the patronage
of Legatus Claudius Glaber!
The man himself regrets
the duties of the senate
prevent his attendance,
but he would see us
properly addressed,
his words delivered
by pleasing tongue
of trusted wife.
Good citizens
of Rome's favored sister.
It is with great
pleasure that
I, Legatus Claudius Glaber,
bestow upon
Quintus Lentulus Batiatus
my patronage,
and all encompassing benefits.
No man in all of Capua
is more deserving
of such esteemed privilege.
Good Batiatus
should be held as example
to a city mired in shadows
and treachery.
The guiding light
of his virtuous heart
providing illumination in
these dark and troubling times.
For this reason and too many
others to give voice...
Still yourself.
I lend my full
and unconditional support
to the honored position
of aedile.
Aemilia failed to mention
you had mind towards office.
Oh, I admit to none,
good Sextus.
Until the Legatus
broached the subject.
Aedile is but a breath
below magistrate.
Um.
We should dine, and discuss
the matter further.
My heart to Legatus Glaber
and his support.
In the hopes that you will
share it in the coming days,
I present a gift of blood!
Two legends of the arena,
to face each other
sine missione!
No quarter given!
No mercy shown!
Behold, Crixus!
The savage Gaul!
And who shall attempt
to tame him?
There can be but one man.
Spartacus!
Slayer of the shadow of death!
He is of a form, is he not?
He stands a god.
Crixus...
I have given my answer.
Let us finish this.
Begin!
You speak of dangerous things.
We live in dangerous times.
Many yet hold Crixus
our true champion.
Count me among them.
Doctore.
I would work the palus.
Permission for Spartacus.
Have you traded words
with Hamilcar?
He is with us.
But Castus and the other Gauls
refuse to grab cock without
Crixus holding their balls.
Where does Rhaskos stand?
The same.
Our numbers are yet shallow.
We must gain Crixus' support
and see them rise.
The fucking mad mans
still under lock and key.
How will you turn him to cause
if you cannot
break words with him?
Being champion
yet affords privilege.
A way shall present itself.
Answer!
It best "present" fucking soon.
Did I tell you to stand?
Glaber falls to patronage,
and the men
of influence greet me
as a fucking brother!
A day of shining glory.
Marred by darkening cloud.
I beg a word, Dominus.
In private.
Doctore,
well spill sour thoughts,
and hear them sweetened.
Glaber's mercenaries
punish absent cause.
The men suffer at their hand.
It is a burden
that must be endured
I have no time
for such petty concerns.
With respect,
every ludus requires
the attention of its lanista.
I seek a loftier title,
one far removed from the arena.
You would see your family's
heritage a thing of memory?
No.
Yet I tire of the dust
and drudgery,
and I would have my interests
in blood and sand
overseen by someone
with more attentive eyes.
Someone who has forever
proven loyal.
You would entrust
the ludus to a slave?
A slave, never.
I had thought to make
announcement at the celebration,
but you force my hand.
My advocate is drawing up
papers granting your freedom.
Freedom?
No longer shall you
be my Doctore.
You will assume
the mantle of lanista,
and be warmly greeted
by your name,
Oenomaus.
I had thought
the news to please.
Apologies,
I have heard rumor.
One that has vexed sleep.
Well give voice,
and dream again.
Barca was not granted freedom.
Instead he met his end,
at your hands.
The rumor is true.
Yet absent reasoning.
Barca was dispatched
to deliver
a simple message to Ovidius.
Instead he slaughtered the man
and his entire fucking family,
against command.
I had no choice
but to take his life,
before the magistrate
discovered the deed
and pulled us all to ruin.
And Ashur?
Did he aid in this "choice"?
When you are lanista,
you shall also be faced
with decisions
grave of consequence.
And know your measure
by how your blade falls.
Can you yet feel him move,
eager to make entrance
into the world?
How do you divine a boy?
Because the gods
fucking favor us.
Glaber's patronage,
access to the upper
strata of Capua,
the promise
of political office.
Everything we have bled for,
finally within our grasp.
We are truly blessed.
I deliver but
glorious news this day,
to be met with
tempered response!
Joy is restrained to lend
clear mind to celebration.
Glaber's patronage may
have paved road to the elite,
but they are
of ravenous appetite.
And what meal would you suggest
to see them sated?
One that only the house
of Batiatus can prepare.
Spartacus, Slayer of Theokoles,
in a contest to the death.
We have already
presented such diversion
at Numerius' toga virilis.
Varro was no match
for the Champion of Capua.
We must give them
what was denied that night.
What all of Capua
longs to see,
but only a privileged
few under our roof
may bear witness to.
The Champion of Capua,
Spartacus in a fight
for his life
against the only man
who has ever defeated him.
Is this your fucking hope?
That the fallen Gaul
is granted opportunity
to regain position?
Out.
You mistake intent.
I would see Crixus dead,
for offenses committed
against the House of Batiatus.
Then we stand as one
in such regard.
Oh your tongue
named cause of doubt.
Crixus is the only gladiator
to pose threat to Spartacus.
And there is yet
political advantage
to parading
the bringer of rain
as I campaign for office.
Then we must ensure
Spartacus victorious.
And Crixus fades from memory.
That will be all.
Patronage comes
with unfortunate attachment.
A fact I am well aware of.
I am reminded of the first time
you stood before me
in this office,
a savage in chains.
Now you stand as death,
made meat and bone.
It was your hand
that forged my purpose.
Yet it is upon your shoulders
the House of Batiatus
has been so elevated,
and continues to rise.
Two days hence we play host to
the most influential in Capua,
in celebration of patronage.
Although a closer look
at the Slayer of Theokoles
be the true draw.
A great honor.
Will the men be displayed
in the villa?
The Legatus would frown
upon such storied tradition.
You and the others will
be confined to the square.
And how will
our guests have view?
From purchase
of the balcony.
No eye will be denied
the Champion of Capua!
As he faces his arch enemy
in a match to the death!
I am to fight Crixus?
This concerns you?
It is long overdue.
Yet there is no honor
in taking the life
of a caged lion.
I would see him return
to training,
so he may better thrill
the crowd before his end.
You truly have
fucking mind for this.
Crixus shall be freed
from bond yet only for training.
I would not have
the animal run free,
lest he again bares teeth.
Remove yourself to slumber,
and dreams /c of extracting th.
Apologies, Dominus.
There is something
I crave more than sleep...
You ask the impossible.
The gates to the villa
must stand open
before I make a move
on Batiatus.
You would have me risk all.
And for what?
So that Spartacus
may have his revenge?
No.
So that his heart
might find a measure of peace.
Was she such a woman,
your wife.
She was the sun.
Never to rise again.
A heavy thing,
to be denied its warmth.
I will see the gate opened.
But I would have exchange...
This is my price.
To feel you inside me.
To know pale shadow of the love
that you felt for her...
I would not have
wagered the Gaul
such a challenge to Spartacus!
You underestimate
the man, Aemilia.
Crixus was once champion,
was he not?
The match is but newly born.
Much may yet happen
as it matures.
Apologies, Domina.
I must gather more
wine from the stores.
Send another.
I would keep you close,
to attend the guests.
You must listen to me...
Dominus has ordered my release?
It was Spartacus
that moved his hand.
Spartacus?
He desires you at your best...
When you stand before him
sine missione.
The gods finally
answer my prayers.
Had they but answered sooner.
You stand before him tomorrow,
as the sun fades.
If it were this very moment,
the outcome would not change.
I have made promise to Naevia.
I will not die until
I have gained my freedom,
and she is in my arms again.
Delay talk of freedom,
until there are ears
that would welcome the sound.
I fear Dominus shall
forever be deaf to it.
Place your faith
to closer quarters.
Dominus releases me
from the bonds of servitude,
to assume mantle as lanista.
It is a title well deserved.
Together we will restore
honor to this ludus...
And Naevia to your arms.
Spartacus but stands
in your way.
Then he shall fall.
A celebration?
Filled with the elite.
Their deaths will shatter
Capua to chaos.
It'll be days before
they regain senses
to pursue us.
Our plan takes form.
What of Crixus?
You still must find
way to broach subject
with the fucking Gaul.
It presents itself,
as promised.
Yeah!
Crixus.
Fuck my ass.
Now all that remains
is convincing
a man that hates you
to join your cause.
You have seen
task to completion?
My husband's patronage
has lifted
your celebration
beyond the heavens,
clouds bursting
with honored guests.
Altius and his cousin Gaius?
They are a necessity...
And are delivered,
as commanded.
Aemilia's husband, Sextus?
He's a former magistrate,
yet beloved by many.
His support would
all but secure office.
Pressing affairs
draw him to Rome.
That does not bring
comfort Ilithyia.
Then perhaps
his attendance shall.
He will delay travel,
with mind towards
your celebration.
How did you turn
his attentions?
He favors me.
Most husbands do.
Your services have been
deeply appreciated.
Yet more is needed.
In the absence of your
honored husband,
we would have you address
our most noble guests.
Just a few words
as if fallen from his mouth,
extolling the virtues
of the House of Batiatus.
I shall compose
something appropriate
for the occasion.
No need.
I've already seen to it.
My hands are no longer my own
and now you seize
my fucking tongue?
I would not have it flap about,
absent direction.
How much longer must
I suffer your indignities?
While breath gives life
to my command.
As you wish, then.
I know there have been
tensions between us.
Yet I see no cause
for our current arrangement
to fall into
unpleasantness.
We were such dear friends once.
Would you not see it so again?
Would that I had power
to reverse the sun,
and restore the world
to its proper place.
Rest.
Eat.
We resume after
midday sun has past.
You move well.
As if lash had never struck.
Pain is erased,
when inflicted upon others.
I would have you at your best
when we face each other.
Is that all you'd have from me?
Rhasko speaks of your desires.
What fever grips brain,
that Spartacus would
think me to band with him?
To risk the lives of my men?
My life?
Is there one?
Without the woman
you love within it?
I've never had stronger
reason to live.
I know your heart, Crixus.
I felt the beating of it
within my chest once.
Then you know
I'll fucking survive.
And see Naevia returned to me.
As my wife was returned?
Batiatus ordered her death.
How did you come upon this?
By tongue of his man Aulus,
before silencing it forever.
I will see
the House of Batiatus fall,
and with it the villain's
blood upon the earth.
As would I, in your position.
But I am far removed.
My escape would not aid Naevia.
How would I purchase
her freedom,
or even find her,
while being hunted
like a dog by the romans?
Join me,
and we will find her together.
You know that in another life,
you and I may
have been as brothers.
But not in this one.
I must win my freedom
in the arena.
Then we stand in the way
of each other's cause.
And both are just.
But if I fall,
I'd have you swear
to find Naevia
and see her freed.
And I would have word
that if you are victorious,
one day you will
have Batiatus' life.
Tomorrow, then.
One of us dies.
I fear it was always fated so.
Dominus.
Were you able to procure
what we need for tomorrow?
Good Marcellus
was ever helpful.
Leave us.
Varro possessed a fine eye.
Turn yours towards business.
What has coin extracted
from Marcellus?
A solution to most
vexing problem.
A few drops in his cup,
and fate is sealed.
It must not kill him.
Our guests need to believe
the match balanced,
lest goodwill
turn to accusation.
It will but weaken Crixus,
allowing Spartacus advantage.
It is a marvel.
That something so slight
could topple a legend.
All men fall.
It is but time
and method that differ.
See it done.
And in the act,
the end of that fucking Gaul.
Crixus moves
with deadly purpose.
He gives much better
showing against Spartacus
than the fool Varro.
Poor Varro.
He never stood
proper chance, did he?
Crixus, however,
threatens to strip the champion
of life and title.
Indeed.
The Gaul yet surprises.
To the very end.
Apologies.
The noble House of Batiatus
stands humbled...
Humbled by the fortunes
the gods have seen fit
to shower upon us...
I should use
"blessings" instead.
"Fortune" has but
connotation of coin.
Blessings, then.
Oh, Quintus, has this city
yet beheld such a man?
Your father would be so proud.
The old bastard would have
cracked with jealously,
to be so eclipsed
by unworthy son.
He loved you, Quintus.
Yet he never believed in me.
Would that he were alive
to see the House of Batiatus
soaring beneath
the flapping of my wings!
Our son shall inherit
a fucking empire!
An empire now, is it?
Eh, the foundations
already laid.
Today we build upon it!
Spartacus and Crixus!
Hated foes,
facing each other in death!
The whole of the Republic
shall whisper with envy
what so privileged
few bore witness.
It will be a thing
not soon forgotten.
I fear your resolve grows soft.
Stone.
I but wish an end
to the matter.
And to the man himself.
Ashur already attends to it.
Turn thoughts
from unfortunate past,
and fix on glorious future.
These celebrations
can cause hands to tremble.
Even most practiced ones.
Gratitude.
See nerves calmed.
You'll do well here.
I have a feeling of it.
You are allowed to eat
from your master's table?
I prepare this as a tribute
to the mighty Crixus,
before his match
against the champion.
May the gods bless it, then.
And give him strength
to kill Spartacus.
I would save prayer.
I do not believe
Spartacus will fall this day.
I have heard Crixus
bested him once in the arena,
at the Vulcanalia.
What leads you to certainty
against similar outcome?
I am certain of many things
within these walls.
Your beauty among them.
Aurelia.
You are needed in the square.
Stay to my side
do not stray from it,
and I will see you
beyond these walls.
I do not need you to hold hand.
I only wish your life
protected, you fucking cock!
Speak louder,
and see us all undone.
Ha, I would have
his fucking whip removed,
along with the arm
that wields it.
Doctore is an honorable man.
I would not have him dead.
Nor any slave.
You fret of shit and piss.
Rhaskos and the others
still will not fall
to purpose without Crixus.
They will seize the moment.
Crixus is dead,
and there stands
but one champion.
Doctore.
Water?
These celebrations have habit
of turning from control.
Should they again,
remove to a safe place.
None exist.
Not since Varro was taken
from me by your hand.
And I shall forever
despise it for the deed.
In company with the voice
that commanded it.
You blame Batiatus.
For many things.
But not this.
It was the boy
Numerius who demanded
simple sport end in death.
And I should believe a man
that would do anything to win?
Do not take me a fool.
Ashur prepares meal for Crixus,
and speaks of the certainty
of your fucking victory.
They corrupt his food?
Was it the same for Varro?
Is that how you bested him?
I have no hand in this.
Were that true,
I would still pray Crixus
takes your life
before he falls.
You betrayed me.
Yet I've come to see
that the fault
is not your own.
You cannot be blamed
for being weak.
All men are, when faced
with wet opportunity.
I would put it behind us.
All I ask in return
is the truth.
Tell me Naevia
held no meaning for you.
You ask me to speak
with false tongue.
What would it conjure
for our child?
Child?
Seed has at last taken hold.
The gods bless us.
You would divine me as father?
Not Dominus?
I feel the blood of a champion,
swelling inside me.
I feel you, Crixus.
I have often dreamt,
in quiet moments
of having a child.
With Naevia.
There is nothing
left between us.
Crixus...
I didn't intend
for it to end this way.
Crixus begins to fade.
As all memories do.
You're weakened because
they have poisoned you!
Finish him!
They wish you dead.
I would not have this.
Join me, brother.
And we shall see
the House of Batiatus fall.
Kill the dog!
Spartacus.
Argh!
Kill them!
Kill them all!
Do not be alarmed people.
Everything is under control.
Please.
He tried to kill you.
That fucking animal.
We must calm this!
Where are the fucking guards?!
Why do you stand there?
Gather your men!
I shall see you
properly attended.
Argh!
Hamilcar!
Crixus!
What is this madness?!
Spartacus shows us the way.
He is a dog without honor!
This house is without honor!
Batiatus ordered his wife dead!
And Domina...
She has tainted me,
because I spur
her fucking heart.
I have given my life
to this ludus!
No, they stole it from you.
From all of us.
You asked me
to put faith in you.
I ask the same.
Honor us all,
and see an end
of this fucking house.
Go.
No!
I save you this time,
brother...
Ahhh!
Friends.
We are perfectly safe
inside the villa.
The situation
is being attended!
Still your hearts.
This very moment my guards
are no doubt
dealing with these...
They've lost mind!
Where the fuck is Ilithyia?
Come! Let us away!
Seal the doors.
Let no one beyond them.
What of the guests?
I am the wife of the Legatus.
Seal the fucking doors!
Ilithyia!
Open the doors!
Do you recall what I said?
In this very room?
That if there was
more to Barca's departure,
you and I would share words.
Doctore...
Do not fucking speak.
I have seen you ply
tongue upon ear,
whispering poison.
Infecting the honor
of this house.
You would kill
a defenseless man?
Where is the fucking
honor in that?
Let's see if you recall
what I taught you.
When you were yet a man.
The doors...
Glaber's men...
Sealed the doors...
Ilithyia.
Why would she do such a thing?
Mother!
Quintus...
Go!
Come.
Come here you roman pussies.
We are all of us dead.
No. We will
regain this house.
Take Numerius,
conceal yourselves.
Come.
I know a place.
Where do you go?
To my husband.
And the death of Spartacus.
Pathetic.
You think this
will cause difference?
Even if life fades,
my hand shall yet be felt.
It plotted the death of Barca.
Saw the magistrate's end.
It even helped force
Glaber to patronage.
Every beam, every stone
in this fucking house
bears the mark of Ashur!
It bears only your treachery.
My fucking treachery?
When did you
stand forth for Ashur?
When did any of you greet me
short of mockery and scorn,
fucking cunts!
You received what you deserved!
For Barca and all the others
that you have betrayed,
your time is done.
Would that this were the arena.
Your blood would
dishonor the sand.
Send me on my way, then.
As you would a gladiator.
Please, Doctore.
A parting kindness...
Ashur!
Quintus...
Quintus?
You were right.
There is still something
between you and I.
Where is Naevia?
Where?!
See me and the Dominus
out of the villa
and I will tell you.
I do not believe you.
Please...
Crixus...
Our child...
I would rather see it dead,
than suckle your breast.
We must conceal ourselves...
Was it yours?
That small, little voice.
Did it form the words
that robbed Varro
of his life?
Varro?!
He deserved to die!
He was nothing!
What did you know of the man?
That he would
sing to his child,
sleeping in his arms?
Or kiss the tears
from my cheek,
when I was of a mood?
Did you know the father?
The husband?
He was not a perfect man.
But he was mine.
He was mine!
Yaaa!
Mine!
Ahhh!
He was mine.
Yaaa!
Mine...
Aurelia...
Be still.
It's done.
Look to the girl.
Is this not enough?
How many more must die?
I would see but one.
I am your Dominus!
I will have your
fucking hearts!
Quintus...
Lucretia!
What would you do?
To hold your wife again?
To feel the warmth
of her skin?
The taste of her lips?
How many men
would you kill?
A hundred?
A thousand?
Here stands but one,
between you and her.
Go to her.
Tell her the gods themselves
would not keep you apart.
Lie!
As you lied to me of my wife.
Oenemaus...
You were nothing before me!
I gave you everything!
I gave you the means
to accept your fate!
And now you
are destroyed by it.
I have done this thing
because it is just.
Blood demands blood.
We have lived and lost,
at the whims of our masters
for too long.
I would not have it so.
I would not see
the passing of a brother
for the purpose of sport.
I would not see another
heart ripped from chest,
or breath forfeit for no cause.
I know not all of you
wished this.
Yet it is done.
It is done.
Your lives are your own.
Forge your own path...
Or join with us,
and together we shall
see Rome tremble.
\N\N,\Nwww.kuntesi.com