1
00:00:05,000 --> 00:00:10,000
{\an4}{\pos(70,211.2)}打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息

2
00:00:05,000 --> 00:00:15,000
{\an7}{\pos(22.2,180.8)} m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340

3
00:03:11,600 --> 00:03:14,530
饥饿

4
00:03:11,810 --> 00:03:14,530
的青春

5
00:03:12,560 --> 00:03:14,530
第二季  第一集

6
00:02:26,100 --> 00:02:29,100
{\an4} 翻译  冰蓝   roaddog   aaaBao

7
00:02:29,100 --> 00:02:32,100
{\an4} 校对  roaddog

8
00:02:35,100 --> 00:02:38,100
{\an4} 后期  斯人   总监  roaddog

9
00:02:32,100 --> 00:02:35,100
{\an4} 时间轴  aaaBao

10
00:00:06,190 --> 00:00:08,780
以下30秒是对《饥饿的青春》的全部介绍
Everything you need to know about Young & Hungry in 30 seconds.

11
00:00:06,270 --> 00:00:08,870
{\an8}饥饿的青春

12
00:00:08,780 --> 00:00:10,300
加比是一位厨师  被乔什雇佣了
Gabi's a chef who was hired by Josh

13
00:00:10,300 --> 00:00:12,380
一个有钱的科技巨头  想娶卡洛琳
who's a rich tech mogul who wanted to marry Caroline.

14
00:00:12,380 --> 00:00:13,280
但乔什被甩时
But when Josh got dumped,

15
00:00:13,280 --> 00:00:14,830
他和加比酒后乱性
he and Gabi got drunk and slept together.

16
00:00:14,830 --> 00:00:15,480
好尴尬
Awkward.

17
00:00:15,480 --> 00:00:17,150
第二天  乔什跟卡洛琳订婚了
The next day, Josh got engaged to Caroline

18
00:00:17,150 --> 00:00:18,890
而加比余情未了
leaving Gabi with unresolved feelings.

19
00:00:18,890 --> 00:00:19,750
更尴尬的是
More awkward:

20
00:00:19,760 --> 00:00:21,890
加比重织了乔什最爱的童年毯子
when Gabi recreated Josh's favorite childhood blanket

21
00:00:21,890 --> 00:00:24,430
作为他30岁生日礼物  乔什疯狂地爱上了她
for his 30th birthday, josh caught mad feelings for her,

22
00:00:24,430 --> 00:00:25,220
取消了婚礼
called off his wedding,

23
00:00:25,220 --> 00:00:27,780
跑去她家  爬上逃生梯来表达爱意
ran over to her place to profess his love on her fire escape,

24
00:00:27,780 --> 00:00:29,170
结果发现她在亲吻库珀
only to find her kissing Cooper.

25
00:00:29,170 --> 00:00:30,570
一开始在跟加比约会  然后分手
Who she dated, but then wasn't dating,

26
00:00:30,570 --> 00:00:32,160
现在显然又在约会的人
but now is apparently dating again.

27
00:00:33,210 --> 00:00:35,590
你即将收看第二季
You are now ready to board Season Two.

28
00:00:40,020 --> 00:00:41,160
天啊
Oh my god!

29
00:00:41,260 --> 00:00:43,040
你按时来上班了
You're on time for work!

30
00:00:43,040 --> 00:00:44,130
出了什么事
What's wrong?

31
00:00:45,460 --> 00:00:48,200
你说什么呢  我一直按时上班
What are you talking about? I'm always on time for work.

32
00:00:49,120 --> 00:00:50,950
这话我自己都想笑
I couldn't say that with a straight face.

33
00:00:51,230 --> 00:00:52,270
坐下
Sit.

34
00:00:54,750 --> 00:00:57,890
昨天深夜  我去看乔什
So, late last night I came to check on Josh.

35
00:00:57,890 --> 00:01:01,110
我坐在那里  听着他倾诉衷肠
I sat there as that boy poured his heart out.

36
00:01:01,110 --> 00:01:03,620
最后我终于说服他去加比家
Until I finally convinced him to go over to Gabi's

37
00:01:03,620 --> 00:01:05,430
告诉她自己的感受
and to tell her how he felt.

38
00:01:05,440 --> 00:01:07,200
不成功便成仁
Go big or go home!

39
00:01:08,130 --> 00:01:09,610
我就是这样说的
That's what I said.

40
00:01:10,930 --> 00:01:12,520
所以出了什么事
So what happened?

41
00:01:12,650 --> 00:01:13,950
我马上就要知道了
That's what I'm going to find out.

42
00:01:13,950 --> 00:01:16,270
她现在可能跟他一起在楼上呢
She could be up there with him right now.

43
00:01:36,030 --> 00:01:38,200
-天啊  -天啊
- Oh my god. - Oh my god!

44
00:01:39,370 --> 00:01:40,490
我就知道
Oh, I knew it!

45
00:01:40,490 --> 00:01:41,710
我说了要努力争取
I said go for it.

46
00:01:41,710 --> 00:01:43,260
现在一切顺利...
Now all is well with--

47
00:01:43,260 --> 00:01:44,720
早安  各位
Hey, good morning, everybody.

48
00:01:44,940 --> 00:01:45,990
搞什么...
What the--

49
00:01:47,630 --> 00:01:48,770
你怎么做到的
How'd you do that?

50
00:01:49,080 --> 00:01:49,710
我的头发吗
My hair?

51
00:01:49,710 --> 00:01:51,980
怎么样  这是"我愿意"的盘发造型
What do you think? It's an updo for the "I do."

52
00:01:52,980 --> 00:01:55,130
现在是"我不愿意"了  婚礼取消
Well, now it's an "I don't." The wedding's off.

53
00:01:55,130 --> 00:01:57,110
什么  你这话是什么意思
What? What do you mean "The wedding's off"?

54
00:01:57,190 --> 00:01:58,190
你不知道吗
You didn't know?

55
00:01:58,580 --> 00:02:00,620
乔什昨晚没和你"谈谈"吗
Josh didn't "talk" to you last night?

56
00:02:00,620 --> 00:02:02,730
不  我完全不知道  怎么了
No, no! I had no idea! What happened?

57
00:02:02,730 --> 00:02:05,340
他发现毯子是你送的  不是卡洛琳
He found out that blanket was from you, not Caroline.

58
00:02:05,340 --> 00:02:06,460
不关我事
I don't know how.

59
00:02:09,140 --> 00:02:10,220
什么
What?

60
00:02:10,220 --> 00:02:13,060
不不不  不不不
No! No, no, no! No, no, no, no, no!

61
00:02:13,060 --> 00:02:14,640
他不该发现那事的
He was not supposed to find that out.

62
00:02:14,640 --> 00:02:17,440
有阵子我希望他发现
I mean, for a minute I wanted him to find out,

63
00:02:17,440 --> 00:02:18,820
之后意识到我不该告诉他
but then I realized I shouldn't tell him

64
00:02:18,820 --> 00:02:20,850
也没法告诉他  我最终说服了自己
and I couldn't tell him and I was finally okay with that.

65
00:02:20,850 --> 00:02:22,030
一切都很好
You know, everything was good.

66
00:02:22,030 --> 00:02:23,020
大家都很开心
And everybody was happy.

67
00:02:23,020 --> 00:02:26,110
天啊  乔什一定很生气[在...边上]
Oh, god! Josh, he must be beside himself.

68
00:02:26,660 --> 00:02:28,320
他旁边的确有人
He's beside something, all right.

69
00:02:30,950 --> 00:02:31,930
他一定很恨我
He must hate me.

70
00:02:31,930 --> 00:02:34,230
天啊  我得告诉他我为什么要那样做
God, I have to tell him why I did what I did.

71
00:02:34,230 --> 00:02:35,390
加比  等等
Gabi, wait!

72
00:02:38,980 --> 00:02:39,930
乔什
Josh.

73
00:02:48,340 --> 00:02:49,340
那人什么毛病啊
What is it with that guy?

74
00:02:49,340 --> 00:02:50,640
每次他跟卡洛琳分手
Everytime he breaks up with Caroline,

75
00:02:50,650 --> 00:02:52,390
都要和金发女上床
he ends up in bed with a blonde.

76
00:03:15,120 --> 00:03:18,460
对于一个叫停婚礼  转头就跟另一个女人
What do you make for the guy that calls off his wedding

77
00:03:18,460 --> 00:03:21,390
上床的男人  你该给他做什么吃啊
and then has sex with another girl 30 seconds later.

78
00:03:21,390 --> 00:03:22,200
虽然我不在乎
I mean, not that I care.

79
00:03:22,200 --> 00:03:23,070
我为什么要在乎啊
You know, why would I care?

80
00:03:23,070 --> 00:03:25,550
我是说  我在干什么呢  什么情况啊
What I'm saying is what am I doing here? What is happening?

81
00:03:25,550 --> 00:03:26,360
知道吗
You know?

82
00:03:26,360 --> 00:03:29,140
什么情况啊
What is happening?

83
00:03:32,440 --> 00:03:34,190
我跟你说说是什么情况
I'll tell you what's happening.

84
00:03:34,700 --> 00:03:37,240
我取消了在安德烈那里订的花
I was cancelling the flowers from Andre,

85
00:03:37,240 --> 00:03:40,350
他是个超性感的花商  下颌轮廓和希腊雕像一样
the super hot florist with the jawline of a greek statue.

86
00:03:41,460 --> 00:03:43,540
他邀请我一起去喝酒
And he asked me out for drinks.

87
00:03:45,040 --> 00:03:48,110
瞧瞧我  从婚礼灾难的废墟中爬起来
Look at me rising from the ashes of this wedding disaster,

88
00:03:48,110 --> 00:03:49,990
像是浴火的凤凰
like a flaming phoenix.

89
00:03:51,730 --> 00:03:53,470
这碰巧就是我们今晚要去
Which is coincidentally the name of the bar

90
00:03:53,470 --> 00:03:55,230
喝酒的酒吧名字
we're having drinks at tonight.

91
00:03:59,110 --> 00:04:00,720
-早上好  -天啊  乔什  
- Morning. - Oh my god. Josh,

92
00:04:00,720 --> 00:04:02,110
对这一切我感到很抱歉
I'm so sorry About all this.

93
00:04:02,110 --> 00:04:02,740
我只想告诉你
 I just need you to know

94
00:04:02,740 --> 00:04:04,200
我没跟你说毯子的事的唯一原因...
the only reason I didn't tell you about the blanket--

95
00:04:04,200 --> 00:04:06,290
加比  拜托别说了
No, Gabi, please. Stop.

96
00:04:06,290 --> 00:04:07,230
你帮了我一个忙
You did me a favor.

97
00:04:07,230 --> 00:04:08,690
没有你  我不会意识到
Without you, I never would have realized that

98
00:04:08,690 --> 00:04:09,840
卡洛琳不是适合我的女孩
Caroline wasn't the right girl for me.

99
00:04:09,840 --> 00:04:10,760
但是说够我的事了
But enough about me.

100
00:04:10,760 --> 00:04:11,900
你们姑娘们昨晚都做什么啦
What did you gals get into last night?

101
00:04:11,900 --> 00:04:13,650
尤兰达  什么事都没做  加比呢
Yolanda? Nothing. Gabi?

102
00:04:16,240 --> 00:04:17,750
你昨晚有没有做
Did you do anything...

103
00:04:18,480 --> 00:04:19,870
什么疯狂的事
crazy last night?

104
00:04:20,400 --> 00:04:22,010
没有
Uh... nope.

105
00:04:22,020 --> 00:04:23,420
太平无事
Totally uneventful.

106
00:04:23,430 --> 00:04:24,390
真的吗
Really?

107
00:04:24,390 --> 00:04:25,550
因为...
'Cause, I mean...

108
00:04:25,550 --> 00:04:28,350
太平无事的意思是没有事情发生
Totally uneventful would mean that nothing happened.

109
00:04:28,350 --> 00:04:31,270
肯定发生了什么事  你是激情的年轻人
Something must have happened. You're an exciting young person.

110
00:04:32,250 --> 00:04:33,690
好吧
Fine. Um...

111
00:04:34,870 --> 00:04:36,090
库珀从中国飞来了
Cooper flew in from China

112
00:04:36,090 --> 00:04:37,580
半夜给了我一个惊喜
and surprised me in the middle of the night.

113
00:04:37,590 --> 00:04:39,240
-库珀  -不
- Cooper? - No.

114
00:04:41,280 --> 00:04:42,420
什么
What?

115
00:04:43,060 --> 00:04:44,140
库珀从中国来了
Cooper from China?

116
00:04:44,140 --> 00:04:46,280
戴眼镜的那位吗  昨晚吗
With the glasses? Last night?

117
00:04:46,280 --> 00:04:47,250
你信吗  尤兰达
Do you believe this, Yolanda?

118
00:04:47,250 --> 00:04:48,310
我也不信
Neither do I.

119
00:04:48,860 --> 00:04:49,950
那么
So...

120
00:04:50,150 --> 00:04:52,000
你俩恋爱了吗
Are you guys in love?

121
00:04:52,000 --> 00:04:53,740
你爱他吗  爱  不爱
Do you love him? Yes? No?

122
00:04:53,740 --> 00:04:54,790
我是说  我该为你感到高兴吗
 I mean, should I be happy for you?

123
00:04:54,790 --> 00:04:55,690
该高兴的话告诉我
I need to know if I should be happy for you.

124
00:04:55,690 --> 00:04:59,080
我觉得我们得搞清该替谁高兴
You know what? I think it's important to know who to be happy for

125
00:04:59,080 --> 00:05:00,530
谁又会成单身狗
and who's just gonna be alone.

126
00:05:02,050 --> 00:05:04,250
库珀昨晚为什么要飞来啊
Why did Cooper fly in last night?

127
00:05:04,250 --> 00:05:05,880
为什么
Why? Why?

128
00:05:07,230 --> 00:05:09,270
他给我买了份礼物
Well he bought me a present and

129
00:05:09,270 --> 00:05:11,120
等不及要看我拆礼物的表情
he couldn't wait to see my face when I opened it.

130
00:05:11,130 --> 00:05:13,340
天啊
Oh ma god!

131
00:05:14,920 --> 00:05:16,570
你听到了吗  尤兰达
Are you hearing this, Yolanda?

132
00:05:16,570 --> 00:05:18,870
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
Chills. I have chills.

133
00:05:18,880 --> 00:05:21,870
这是我听过的最浪漫的事
This is just the most romantic thing I've ever heard.

134
00:05:22,750 --> 00:05:23,640
是啊
Yeah.

135
00:05:23,640 --> 00:05:24,960
唯一更浪漫的事
The only thing that would have been more romantic

136
00:05:24,960 --> 00:05:26,110
就是他在倾盆大雨里
is if he climbed up my fire escape

137
00:05:26,110 --> 00:05:27,820
带着玫瑰爬上逃生梯
with roses in the pouring rain.

138
00:05:29,850 --> 00:05:30,880
是啊
Yeah.

139
00:05:31,470 --> 00:05:32,590
谁会那样啊
Who does that?

140
00:05:33,790 --> 00:05:34,790
好吧
Well,

141
00:05:35,280 --> 00:05:38,820
看样子昨晚我们俩都过得非常浪漫
sounds like we both had wildly romantic nights last night.

142
00:05:38,820 --> 00:05:40,220
我知道这话听上去有些疯狂
Now I know this is gonna sound crazy,

143
00:05:40,340 --> 00:05:41,970
但你明白那种遇到一个
but you know that feeling you get when you meet someone

144
00:05:41,980 --> 00:05:44,020
似曾相识的人的感觉吗
and you have that instant connection?

145
00:05:44,020 --> 00:05:44,850
我和劳拉之间就是
I had that with Laura.

146
00:05:44,860 --> 00:05:45,890
我叫劳伦
It's Lauren.

147
00:05:46,400 --> 00:05:47,510
我知道
I know that.

148
00:05:48,040 --> 00:05:50,330
我简称其为劳拉
I call her Laura for short.

149
00:05:51,530 --> 00:05:52,240
对了
Yeah.

150
00:05:52,240 --> 00:05:54,580
我想这位小姐肯定有事要忙
I believe this one's definitely gonna go somewhere.

151
00:05:54,580 --> 00:05:56,200
-她留下来吃早餐吗  -不吃
- Is she staying for breakfast? - Nope.

152
00:06:03,710 --> 00:06:05,520
天了噜  天了噜
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.

153
00:06:07,030 --> 00:06:08,100
库珀在吗
Is Cooper here?

154
00:06:08,230 --> 00:06:09,210
不在
Nope.

155
00:06:10,010 --> 00:06:11,450
乔什取消了婚礼
Josh called off his wedding.

156
00:06:11,770 --> 00:06:12,810
什么
What?

157
00:06:13,310 --> 00:06:15,470
真的  他知道那条毯子是我织的了
Yeah. He found out the blanket was from me.

158
00:06:15,500 --> 00:06:16,560
他怎么知道的
Uh, how?

159
00:06:16,560 --> 00:06:17,420
这不是重点
Who cares?

160
00:06:17,420 --> 00:06:18,890
你知道这意味着什么吗
Do you know what this means?

161
00:06:18,900 --> 00:06:20,400
当乔什发现我才是那个
When Josh found out that I was the one

162
00:06:20,400 --> 00:06:21,450
花了好几周时间
that spent all those weeks

163
00:06:21,450 --> 00:06:23,580
重织他童年毯子的人的时候
recreating his special childhood blanket,

164
00:06:23,580 --> 00:06:25,620
他意识到我才是那个懂他心思的人
he realized I was the one that knows his heart,

165
00:06:25,620 --> 00:06:27,480
这说明他是因为我才取消婚礼的
which means I'm the reason he called off the wedding!

166
00:06:27,480 --> 00:06:29,080
我现在该怎么办
Now what am I gonna do?

167
00:06:29,420 --> 00:06:31,110
你说这话是什么意思
What do you mean what are you gonna do?

168
00:06:31,310 --> 00:06:33,120
索菲亚  昨晚想到乔什要结婚
Sofia, last night I was freaking out

169
00:06:33,120 --> 00:06:35,830
我就很沮丧  因为我对他有好感
that Josh was getting married because I had feelings for him.

170
00:06:35,830 --> 00:06:38,380
是啊  然后库珀来了  迷得你神魂颠倒
Yeah, and then Cooper came in and swept you off your feet,

171
00:06:38,380 --> 00:06:40,630
现在你们又重修旧好了
and now you're back together with Cooper.

172
00:06:40,940 --> 00:06:41,720
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.

173
00:06:41,720 --> 00:06:44,110
但乔什因为我取消了婚礼
But then Josh, he called off his wedding because of me!

174
00:06:44,120 --> 00:06:45,910
这说明他对我有好感
Which means he has feelings for me!

175
00:06:45,910 --> 00:06:47,050
对我啊
For me!

176
00:06:48,390 --> 00:06:51,010
不不  不是这样的
Oh, no, no, no. No, no, no, no. No, it doesn't.

177
00:06:51,010 --> 00:06:53,960
是吗  那你说说他昨晚
Oh, really? Then explain to me why last night

178
00:06:53,960 --> 00:06:55,280
为什么睡了一个
he had sex with a girl

179
00:06:55,280 --> 00:06:58,130
长得跟我一模一样的妹子
who looks exactly like me.

180
00:06:59,200 --> 00:07:00,670
你听见你说的话了吗
Do you hear yourself?

181
00:07:01,380 --> 00:07:02,510
听见了
I do.

182
00:07:05,050 --> 00:07:06,520
什么情况啊
What is happening? You know?

183
00:07:06,690 --> 00:07:09,220
-什么情况啊  -好吧
- What is happening? - Okay.

184
00:07:10,280 --> 00:07:10,910
行了
Okay.

185
00:07:10,920 --> 00:07:12,420
我知道你很困惑
Look, I know you're confused.

186
00:07:12,420 --> 00:07:13,690
你对乔什有好感
You had feelings for Josh.

187
00:07:13,690 --> 00:07:15,970
要是昨晚乔什过来对你表白
And if Josh had come here last night declaring his love for you,

188
00:07:15,970 --> 00:07:17,440
那事情就大不一样了
it would be a different story.

189
00:07:17,440 --> 00:07:18,400
但他没来
But he didn't.

190
00:07:18,400 --> 00:07:19,530
-是的  -谁来了呢
- Yeah. - Who did?

191
00:07:19,530 --> 00:07:21,140
库珀  我明白了
Cooper. Yeah, I know.

192
00:07:21,140 --> 00:07:22,650
我明白了  你是对的  索菲亚
I know, you're so right, Sofia.

193
00:07:22,650 --> 00:07:23,610
你真聪明
You're so smart.

194
00:07:23,610 --> 00:07:25,250
天生机智难自弃
Well, we are who we are.

195
00:07:27,210 --> 00:07:29,000
我只希望神能给我指条明路
I just wish I had a sign.

196
00:07:35,010 --> 00:07:36,620
我说完了  西服很赞
I'm done. Nice tux.

197
00:07:36,620 --> 00:07:37,700
谢谢
Thank you.

198
00:07:37,870 --> 00:07:40,030
从没参加过要穿正装的婚礼
Never been to a black tie wedding before.

199
00:07:40,550 --> 00:07:41,670
芬利
Finley.

200
00:07:40,550 --> 00:07:43,240
{\an8}詹姆斯·邦德常说这句话

201
00:07:41,990 --> 00:07:43,240
库珀·芬利
Cooper Finley.

202
00:07:44,420 --> 00:07:46,790
-我有个大惊喜给你  - 快坐下
- I have a huge surprise for you. - Sit down.

203
00:07:46,790 --> 00:07:49,010
你知道我打算今晚怎么回中国吗
So you know how I'm supposed to go back to China tonight?

204
00:07:49,050 --> 00:07:50,880
我把我的头等舱机票
Well, I traded in my first class ticket

205
00:07:50,880 --> 00:07:53,050
换成了两张经济舱的票
for two coach tickets.

206
00:07:53,630 --> 00:07:54,910
两张什么
Two what-what?

207
00:07:55,510 --> 00:07:57,150
我知道  让程序员坐头等舱
I know, first class for a programmer.

208
00:07:57,150 --> 00:07:58,560
公司特别贴心  对吧
Pretty sweet, right?

209
00:07:59,160 --> 00:08:01,650
总之  等乔什去度蜜月的时候
Anyway, I figured while Josh was away on his honeymoon,

210
00:08:01,660 --> 00:08:04,190
你能和我在中国待三周
you could spend three weeks with me in China!

211
00:08:04,350 --> 00:08:05,860
那是个超棒的地方
It's such an amazing place.

212
00:08:05,860 --> 00:08:08,190
这屋里所有的东西都是那制造的
Everything in this apartment is from there.

213
00:08:16,640 --> 00:08:17,420
怎么说呢
I don't know.

214
00:08:17,430 --> 00:08:18,870
要是她迷路了
I mean, what if she gets lost,

215
00:08:18,870 --> 00:08:20,710
那里有人指路吗
do they have any signs there?

216
00:08:21,930 --> 00:08:22,820
库珀...
Cooper...

217
00:08:22,820 --> 00:08:23,820
我想说
Wow! I mean,

218
00:08:23,820 --> 00:08:25,480
这是我听过的最甜蜜的事情了
that's the sweetest thing I've ever heard,

219
00:08:25,480 --> 00:08:28,830
但我不能去  乔什取消了婚礼
but I can't go. Josh called off his wedding.

220
00:08:29,200 --> 00:08:30,510
什么  为什么
What? Why?

221
00:08:30,510 --> 00:08:32,180
-别问  -原因很复杂
- Oh, don't ask. - It's complicated.

222
00:08:32,770 --> 00:08:35,500
所以我没法请三周假
So, you know, I can't really ask for three weeks off.

223
00:08:35,500 --> 00:08:37,750
既然乔什本来就该让你休假
But since Josh was gonna give you the time off anyway,

224
00:08:37,750 --> 00:08:39,130
说不定他会同意你去
maybe he'll let you go.

225
00:08:39,740 --> 00:08:42,560
再加上他又不是因为你才取消婚礼的
Plus it's not like you're the reason he called off the wedding.

226
00:08:44,280 --> 00:08:46,000
是啊  有道理
Yeah, that's a really good point.

227
00:08:46,920 --> 00:08:47,800
太好了
Great.

228
00:08:47,800 --> 00:08:48,970
在我坐出褶之前就去退了这套西服的话
Now, if I leave before I wrinkle

229
00:08:48,970 --> 00:08:51,750
-说不定能退全款  -好吧
- maybe I can get a refund on this tux. - Okay.

230
00:08:52,000 --> 00:08:53,270
加比  问下乔什
Gabi, please ask Josh.

231
00:08:53,270 --> 00:08:55,310
这会是你一生中最美好的时光
It will be the best time you've ever had.

232
00:08:55,830 --> 00:08:57,170
我俩的美好时光
That we've ever had.

233
00:09:01,590 --> 00:09:02,560
再见
Bye.

234
00:09:05,540 --> 00:09:06,650
好吧
Well...

235
00:09:06,790 --> 00:09:08,270
库珀给我指了条明路
Cooper gave me my sign.

236
00:09:08,270 --> 00:09:09,410
谢天谢地
Well, thank God.

237
00:09:09,410 --> 00:09:11,800
现在只要看看乔什的反映了
Yeah, now all I need is a sign from Josh.

238
00:09:13,670 --> 00:09:14,630
什么
What?

239
00:09:14,630 --> 00:09:16,790
我要去问问乔什同不同意让我跟库珀去中国
I'm gonna ask Josh if I can go to China with Cooper,

240
00:09:16,790 --> 00:09:19,030
要是他同意了  说明他不喜欢我
and if he lets me, it means he doesn't have feelings for me.

241
00:09:19,030 --> 00:09:21,750
但他要是不让我去  说明他的确对我有好感
But if he says no, it means he does have feelings for me.

242
00:09:21,760 --> 00:09:23,000
好吧  然后呢
Okay, and then what?

243
00:09:23,000 --> 00:09:24,310
要是乔什喜欢你呢
What if Josh has feelings for you?

244
00:09:24,310 --> 00:09:27,890
然后我...也不知道
And then I... I don't know.

245
00:09:34,650 --> 00:09:36,630
亲爱的  你怎么样了
Oh, hey, baby. How are you feeling?

246
00:09:36,630 --> 00:09:37,670
我怎么样了
How am I feeling?

247
00:09:37,670 --> 00:09:40,130
我想去骑车  但找不到另一只手套
I want to go on a bike ride and I can't find my other glove.

248
00:09:40,130 --> 00:09:41,680
我来帮你找
Okay, well let me help you.

249
00:09:41,680 --> 00:09:43,160
你上一次看到它是什么时候
When's the last time you saw it?

250
00:09:43,160 --> 00:09:44,390
都怪你
This is all your fault.

251
00:09:44,390 --> 00:09:46,000
我又没弄丢你手套
I didn't lose your damn glove.

252
00:09:48,490 --> 00:09:50,750
都怪你  让我像个傻子一样跑去加比家
Your fault that I went over to Gabi's like a fool.

253
00:09:50,760 --> 00:09:51,890
{\an8}要么做大  要么回家

254
00:09:50,760 --> 00:09:51,890
是你说的"不成功便成仁"
"Go big or go home," you said.

255
00:09:51,890 --> 00:09:53,530
这话一点道理都没  我本来就在家
That doesn't make sense! I was home!

256
00:09:54,880 --> 00:09:58,190
容我提醒你一句  我让你去告诉加比
May I remind you that I told you to go tell Gabi

257
00:09:58,190 --> 00:09:59,390
你对她的感情
how you feel.

258
00:09:59,390 --> 00:10:02,430
不是让你悄悄去她公寓外又逃跑
Not to creep outside around her apartment and then run away.

259
00:10:03,350 --> 00:10:04,720
我没逃跑
I did not run away.

260
00:10:05,600 --> 00:10:06,700
我是悄悄溜走的
I snuck away.

261
00:10:07,950 --> 00:10:10,160
我该怎么办  她在和库珀接吻
What was I supposed to do? She was making out with Cooper.

262
00:10:10,440 --> 00:10:12,250
相信我  那说明不了什么
Trust me, that didn't mean anything.

263
00:10:12,370 --> 00:10:15,050
这姑娘喜欢你
That girl has feelings for you.

264
00:10:17,020 --> 00:10:18,420
你们好
Hey, guys. Um...

265
00:10:19,100 --> 00:10:20,890
乔什  我能和你谈谈吗
Josh, can I talk to you for a minute?

266
00:10:21,180 --> 00:10:22,270
单独谈谈
Alone.

267
00:10:26,830 --> 00:10:27,900
怎么了
So, what's up?

268
00:10:29,040 --> 00:10:30,810
我想问你点事
I wanted to ask you something.

269
00:10:30,810 --> 00:10:33,940
-但首先  你还好吗  -很好
- But first, how are you doing? - Good!

270
00:10:35,060 --> 00:10:36,050
很好
Good.

271
00:10:37,210 --> 00:10:38,220
你呢
How are you?

272
00:10:39,310 --> 00:10:40,340
很好
Good!

273
00:10:40,710 --> 00:10:41,760
很好
Good.

274
00:10:43,580 --> 00:10:44,400
我还是走吧
I'm gonna go.

275
00:10:44,410 --> 00:10:45,410
等等  加比
Wait, Gabi.

276
00:10:48,570 --> 00:10:50,350
我也有事要跟你说
I needed to talk to you about something, too.

277
00:10:51,320 --> 00:10:52,460
是吗
You did?

278
00:10:52,710 --> 00:10:53,850
是的
Yeah.

279
00:10:55,160 --> 00:10:57,650
我想让你知道昨晚那姑娘只是...
I want you to know that girl from last night was just a--

280
00:10:57,650 --> 00:10:59,840
疗伤的嘛  我懂
Oh, rebound. Yeah, I know.

281
00:11:00,850 --> 00:11:02,510
我是说  你今天本来该结婚的
I mean, today was supposed to be your wedding day.

282
00:11:02,510 --> 00:11:03,610
但不是了
But it's not.

283
00:11:04,090 --> 00:11:05,400
因为我取消了
Because I called it off.

284
00:11:05,720 --> 00:11:06,870
对
Right.

285
00:11:06,990 --> 00:11:08,410
这个...
Which is, um...

286
00:11:09,470 --> 00:11:11,380
也是我想跟你聊的
it's kind of what I wanted to talk to you about.

287
00:11:13,300 --> 00:11:14,340
-我们能坐下吗  -可以
- Should we sit? - I can sit.

288
00:11:14,340 --> 00:11:15,620
-坐着说吧  -坐
- Let's sit. - I need to sit.

289
00:11:24,480 --> 00:11:25,720
乔什
Josh, um...

290
00:11:26,700 --> 00:11:28,310
我有些事想问你  但是...
I wanted to ask you something, but...

291
00:11:28,630 --> 00:11:30,150
首先你要知道  不管你说什么
first I want you to know no matter what you say,

292
00:11:30,150 --> 00:11:31,210
我都可以接受
I'm totally gonna be fine.

293
00:11:31,210 --> 00:11:32,020
所以别有压力
So no pressure.

294
00:11:32,020 --> 00:11:34,020
-好吗  就...  -我很好  继续说别停
- You know? Just say-- - I'm good. Don't stop, you're doing great.

295
00:11:34,020 --> 00:11:34,710
好
Okay.

296
00:11:37,580 --> 00:11:38,720
我在想...
I was wondering...

297
00:11:41,270 --> 00:11:42,500
既然你现在取消了婚礼
now that you called off the wedding...

298
00:11:42,500 --> 00:11:43,610
对
Yeah?

299
00:11:43,920 --> 00:11:45,870
那你对我...
How you feel about me...

300
00:11:45,870 --> 00:11:47,360
我对你什么感觉
How I feel about you?

301
00:11:47,360 --> 00:11:49,540
休假三周和库珀去中国有什么感觉
Taking three weeks off and going to China with Cooper?

302
00:11:49,540 --> 00:11:51,240
加比  我也是一样的感觉
Gabi, I feel the same way.

303
00:11:51,240 --> 00:11:52,150
什么
What?

304
00:11:55,710 --> 00:11:57,530
对...中国
About... China

305
00:11:57,920 --> 00:11:59,170
和库珀一样
As Cooper does.

306
00:11:59,850 --> 00:12:01,020
我爱中国
I love China.

307
00:12:01,620 --> 00:12:04,010
一定要看看那什么城
I mean, yeah, you-- don't miss that wall.

308
00:12:04,010 --> 00:12:06,420
很...很长的
It's, uh... it's great.

309
00:12:08,870 --> 00:12:11,290
好吧  我是想
Oh, okay. Well I just thought

310
00:12:11,290 --> 00:12:13,550
因为你不去度蜜月了
maybe since you're not going on your honeymoon,

311
00:12:13,660 --> 00:12:16,990
或许想让我留下来做饭
that maybe you wanted me to stay here with you

312
00:12:16,990 --> 00:12:19,870
不跟库珀走
and not go away with Cooper.

313
00:12:19,870 --> 00:12:21,880
不不不
No! No, no, no.

314
00:12:22,100 --> 00:12:23,700
去中国吧  你应该去
Go to China. You should go.

315
00:12:24,090 --> 00:12:25,270
跟库珀去吧
Go with Cooper.

316
00:12:25,340 --> 00:12:26,980
去吧  你知道吗
Go! And you know what?

317
00:12:27,550 --> 00:12:29,680
中国挺冷的  不如带上这个吧
China gets cold, so why don't you take that with you.

318
00:12:35,470 --> 00:12:36,490
谢谢
Thanks.

319
00:12:44,460 --> 00:12:46,020
我收到反映了
Well, I got my sign.

320
00:12:50,290 --> 00:12:53,760
最终反映  还是要继续试探三次的反映
Uh, final sign? Or you-still- need-three-more-signs sign.

321
00:12:55,010 --> 00:12:57,360
我问乔什  能不能跟库珀去中国
I asked Josh if I could go to China with Cooper,

322
00:12:57,360 --> 00:12:58,880
他说没关系
and he said it was fine,

323
00:12:58,880 --> 00:13:01,260
也就是说他对我没感觉
which means that he doesn't have feelings for me.

324
00:13:01,260 --> 00:13:02,790
其实也松了口气啦
Which is actually kind of a relief.

325
00:13:02,790 --> 00:13:04,550
这说明我注定和库珀在一起
You know, it means I'm meant to be with Cooper.

326
00:13:05,570 --> 00:13:07,680
你能接受吗
Well, are you okay with that?

327
00:13:08,270 --> 00:13:09,330
那...
So...

328
00:13:09,610 --> 00:13:10,820
你是去中国咯
are you going to China?

329
00:13:14,090 --> 00:13:15,570
这能回答你的问题吗
Does that answer your question?

330
00:13:16,860 --> 00:13:18,930
-不知道  再回答一次嘛  -好吧
- Not sure. Tell me one more time. - Okay.

331
00:13:24,620 --> 00:13:26,580
-亲爱的  -现在不行  尤兰达
- Hey, baby-- - Not now, Yolanda.

332
00:13:27,390 --> 00:13:28,390
我在写代码
I'm writing code.

333
00:13:28,390 --> 00:13:30,190
要不停赚钱  才能付钱
You know, keeping the money flowing so I can continue

334
00:13:30,190 --> 00:13:32,000
请你给我建议
to pay you to give me advice.

335
00:13:32,410 --> 00:13:33,780
乔什  我知道...
Look, Josh, I know that--

336
00:13:33,780 --> 00:13:36,260
记得你跟我说过"不成功便成仁"吗
Remember when you told me "Go big or go home"?

337
00:13:37,060 --> 00:13:38,680
现在我告诉你
Well, now I'm telling you,

338
00:13:39,200 --> 00:13:40,280
"成仁了"[回家吧]
"Go home."

339
00:13:42,530 --> 00:13:43,700
行
Okay.

340
00:13:52,530 --> 00:13:53,660
所以...
So...

341
00:13:54,170 --> 00:13:56,030
我这样能让安德烈高兴吗
will I make Andre happy?

342
00:13:58,650 --> 00:13:59,760
很高兴
Very!

343
00:13:59,780 --> 00:14:01,120
因为你不许去
'Cause you're not going.

344
00:14:01,640 --> 00:14:03,400
你今晚留下来陪乔什
You're staying with Josh tonight.

345
00:14:03,410 --> 00:14:04,520
我不要
No, I'm not.

346
00:14:04,520 --> 00:14:06,060
我要去见安德烈
I'm meeting Andre.

347
00:14:06,160 --> 00:14:07,400
今晚不行
Not tonight.

348
00:14:07,400 --> 00:14:08,930
就今晚
Yes, tonight.

349
00:14:08,970 --> 00:14:11,190
安德烈已经坐上"艾号街车"了
Andre is riding the "E" train.

350
00:14:11,190 --> 00:14:12,330
就是我
That's me.

351
00:14:14,200 --> 00:14:15,620
你留下陪乔什
You stay with Josh.

352
00:14:15,940 --> 00:14:18,070
我是想  但他不给
I would, but he doesn't want me to.

353
00:14:18,610 --> 00:14:20,160
乔什需要你
Josh needs you.

354
00:14:22,070 --> 00:14:23,770
怎么人人都想要我
Everybody wants a piece of me.

355
00:14:32,000 --> 00:14:33,990
老兄
Hey, buddy.

356
00:14:35,400 --> 00:14:36,620
你还好吗
How's it going?

357
00:14:37,980 --> 00:14:39,940
你今晚不用我留下来  对不对
You don't need me here tonight, right?

358
00:14:39,940 --> 00:14:41,350
我的人生糟透了
My life sucks.

359
00:14:44,390 --> 00:14:45,710
我知道了
Oh, I know!

360
00:14:45,740 --> 00:14:47,370
或许你该出去
Maybe you need to get out.

361
00:14:47,370 --> 00:14:48,510
去个酒吧什么的
You know, go to a bar.

362
00:14:48,510 --> 00:14:49,760
喝两杯
Get your drink on.

363
00:14:49,760 --> 00:14:51,210
别想这些东西了
Take your mind off things.

364
00:14:51,390 --> 00:14:52,530
不行
No way.

365
00:14:52,560 --> 00:14:55,510
我现在最不想去的就是有女人的地方
The last thing I want to do is be anywhere where there's women.

366
00:14:59,160 --> 00:15:00,940
你乖乖坐这
You stay right here.

367
00:15:01,050 --> 00:15:04,040
让帅哥们给你买酒喝吧
And let all the nice boys buy you drinks.

368
00:15:05,140 --> 00:15:06,720
我的约会对象在那
Oh, there's my date.

369
00:15:07,410 --> 00:15:08,500
安德烈
Andre!

370
00:15:08,580 --> 00:15:11,010
你好啊  帅哥
Hey, handsome!

371
00:15:13,510 --> 00:15:14,960
艾略特都告诉我了
Elliot told me everything.

372
00:15:14,960 --> 00:15:17,710
我是个花商  和执业的心理医生没两样
I'm a florist, that practically makes me a licensed psychologist.

373
00:15:17,820 --> 00:15:18,960
倾诉吧
Spill.

374
00:15:19,080 --> 00:15:19,800
我很好
I'm good.

375
00:15:19,800 --> 00:15:21,240
对  他很好
Yeah, he's good.

376
00:15:21,490 --> 00:15:22,480
你确定吗
You sure?

377
00:15:22,480 --> 00:15:23,490
他确定
He's sure.

378
00:15:25,230 --> 00:15:27,620
这要从加比替我工作说起了
It all started when Gabi began working for me.

379
00:15:31,850 --> 00:15:32,780
所以...
So...

380
00:15:32,780 --> 00:15:34,090
你感觉如何
how are you feeling?

381
00:15:34,250 --> 00:15:35,290
超级棒
Amazing.

382
00:15:35,290 --> 00:15:36,940
好像一切都是应有的样子
Like everything's the way it's supposed to be.

383
00:15:37,070 --> 00:15:38,520
叫的车来了
Uber is here.

384
00:15:38,770 --> 00:15:39,620
东西拿齐了吗
You got everything?

385
00:15:39,620 --> 00:15:41,300
有你就齐了
I got everything I need right here.

386
00:15:42,170 --> 00:15:43,360
你们能出去腻歪吗
Can you have it out there?

387
00:15:45,670 --> 00:15:46,910
好了  拜拜
Okay, bye.

388
00:15:46,910 --> 00:15:48,730
-再见  -拜拜  玩高兴点
- See you later! - Bye, have so much fun!

389
00:15:48,730 --> 00:15:50,000
-拜拜  -拜拜
- Bye! - Bye!

390
00:15:54,320 --> 00:15:57,000
*我就喜欢一个人住*
*I love to live alone*

391
00:15:58,090 --> 00:16:00,780
*我就喜欢一个人住*
*I love to live alone*

392
00:16:01,820 --> 00:16:03,140
*我就喜欢...*
*I love to live...*

393
00:16:03,140 --> 00:16:04,900
在你脱下胸罩开始高歌之前...
Before you take off your bra and start singing...

394
00:16:08,220 --> 00:16:09,280
晚了哈
Too late.

395
00:16:09,890 --> 00:16:11,550
我想谢谢你
I just wanted to thank you.

396
00:16:11,770 --> 00:16:13,230
真的很感谢你陪我一起挺过去
I really appreciate you getting me through this.

397
00:16:13,230 --> 00:16:14,710
闺蜜不就是这样嘛
What are best friends for?

398
00:16:14,890 --> 00:16:16,410
-好啦  再见  -再见
- Okay. All right, bye. - Bye!

399
00:16:16,510 --> 00:16:17,530
爱你哦  再见
Love you, see you later.

400
00:16:17,540 --> 00:16:20,250
-拜拜  -中国我来啦
- See ya, bye! - Ah, China!

401
00:16:21,160 --> 00:16:24,270
*我就喜欢一个人住*
*And I love to live alone*

402
00:16:25,730 --> 00:16:26,760
护照没带
Passport.

403
00:16:27,550 --> 00:16:28,640
加比
Gabi.

404
00:16:29,190 --> 00:16:30,900
加比  加比
Gabi! Gabi!

405
00:16:30,900 --> 00:16:31,850
你的护照
Your passport.

406
00:16:31,860 --> 00:16:33,180
带了  就在我手上
Yeah, it's right here in my hand.

407
00:16:33,180 --> 00:16:34,830
在我手上吧  接着
You mean my hand? Catch!

408
00:16:35,050 --> 00:16:36,300
谢谢
Thank you!

409
00:16:36,300 --> 00:16:37,450
拜拜
Bye!

410
00:16:37,610 --> 00:16:39,070
库珀
Oh, Cooper!

411
00:16:39,690 --> 00:16:41,060
你手套忘了
You forgot your glove.

412
00:16:41,950 --> 00:16:43,440
我的是连指手套
I wear mittens!

413
00:16:46,030 --> 00:16:46,900
好吧
Okay.

414
00:16:46,910 --> 00:16:48,130
拜拜
Bye!

415
00:16:50,430 --> 00:16:52,070
"JXK"
"JXK"?

416
00:16:54,210 --> 00:16:56,750
乔什·奇葩的中间名·卡明斯基
Josh, something weird, Kaminski.

417
00:16:57,300 --> 00:16:58,400
天啊
Oh my god!

418
00:17:04,260 --> 00:17:05,740
所以我狂跑起来
So I'm running, right?

419
00:17:06,290 --> 00:17:07,940
在倾盆大雨里
I get all the way up the fire escape

420
00:17:07,940 --> 00:17:10,200
拿着玫瑰花爬上了逃生梯
in the pouring rain with roses.

421
00:17:10,200 --> 00:17:12,540
天啊  就像《风月俏佳人》里演的
Oh my god, just like Pretty Woman.

422
00:17:13,650 --> 00:17:15,030
更像废话烦死人吧
More like pretty boring.

423
00:17:16,360 --> 00:17:17,870
然后我看向窗内
And then I look inside,

424
00:17:18,770 --> 00:17:20,300
-看到了...  -乔什
- and I see-- - Josh.

425
00:17:21,090 --> 00:17:22,240
她是加比吗
Is that Gabi?

426
00:17:22,480 --> 00:17:24,270
不  是她室友  索菲亚
No, it's her roommate, Sofia.

427
00:17:26,630 --> 00:17:27,630
你来干什么
What are you doing here?

428
00:17:27,630 --> 00:17:29,490
你不接电话  所以我打给艾略特了
Well, you didn't answer your phone so I called Elliot,

429
00:17:29,490 --> 00:17:30,830
他说你在这里
he said that you were here,

430
00:17:30,830 --> 00:17:32,330
还有你中间名是山德
and that your middle name is Xander,

431
00:17:32,330 --> 00:17:35,650
X开头的  也就是JXK
with an "X," aka JXK.

432
00:17:35,660 --> 00:17:36,730
我的手套
My glove!

433
00:17:36,730 --> 00:17:37,620
你在哪找到的
Where'd you find this?

434
00:17:37,620 --> 00:17:39,070
我们家的逃生梯上
On our fire escape.

435
00:17:39,910 --> 00:17:42,360
不  那不是我的手套  绝对不是
Nope, that's not my glove. Definitely not my glove.

436
00:17:42,890 --> 00:17:44,650
他骗人的  是他的...
He's lying, it is his...

437
00:17:44,820 --> 00:17:45,990
好大的手套
big glove.

438
00:17:46,500 --> 00:17:47,720
好大的手
Big hands.

439
00:17:48,500 --> 00:17:50,440
反正他昨晚就是在雨里拿着玫瑰花
Anyway, he was there last night on the fire escape

440
00:17:50,440 --> 00:17:52,380
站在你家逃生梯上的
in the rain with roses.

441
00:17:52,380 --> 00:17:53,280
你是把我卖了吗
Did you just out me?

442
00:17:53,290 --> 00:17:55,160
抱歉  但人家喜欢大团圆结局[竖起的XX]啦
I'm sorry, but I'd like a happy ending.

443
00:17:55,180 --> 00:17:56,380
发现了
Duly noted.

444
00:17:58,090 --> 00:18:00,160
好吧  所以你昨晚真来了
Okay, so you did come over last night?

445
00:18:01,950 --> 00:18:04,480
严格说来  我不想叫站在屋外的大雨里
Technically, I wouldn't call standing outside in the rain

446
00:18:04,550 --> 00:18:05,630
"来了"
"coming over."

447
00:18:08,210 --> 00:18:09,820
我就是想跟加比聊聊
I just needed to talk to Gabi.

448
00:18:10,540 --> 00:18:11,620
为什么
Why?

449
00:18:11,640 --> 00:18:12,970
你没看过《风月俏佳人》吗
Have you not seen Pretty Woman?

450
00:18:12,970 --> 00:18:14,070
他爱她
He loves her.

451
00:18:14,090 --> 00:18:15,290
我不知道算不算爱
I don't know if it's love.

452
00:18:16,930 --> 00:18:18,200
那还能是什么
Well then what the hell is it?

453
00:18:18,200 --> 00:18:19,740
她现在正要跟库珀坐飞机走
She's getting on a plane with Cooper right now

454
00:18:19,740 --> 00:18:21,910
因为我告诉她  如果你对她有感觉
because I told her that if you had feelings for her,

455
00:18:21,910 --> 00:18:23,550
昨晚会过来的
you would have come over last night.

456
00:18:24,020 --> 00:18:25,130
你真的来了
And you did.

457
00:18:26,810 --> 00:18:27,800
等等
Wait.

458
00:18:27,800 --> 00:18:29,880
你是说加比也喜欢我吗
Are you saying that Gabi has feelings for me?

459
00:18:30,170 --> 00:18:31,350
别闹了  乔什
Come on, Josh.

460
00:18:31,350 --> 00:18:32,530
你看不出来吗
You had no idea?

461
00:18:32,530 --> 00:18:34,300
好看的从来都笨哈
The pretty ones are never smart.

462
00:18:36,920 --> 00:18:38,510
不敢相信  我要打电话给她
I don't believe-- I've got to call her.

463
00:18:38,860 --> 00:18:39,950
不
No!

464
00:18:39,950 --> 00:18:41,410
去找她吧
Go to her!

465
00:18:42,230 --> 00:18:44,350
别急着结账  去找她
Leave your tab open and go to her.

466
00:18:45,270 --> 00:18:46,860
是  乔什  他说得对
No, yeah, Josh. He's right.

467
00:18:46,860 --> 00:18:47,800
她要知道真相
She has to know everything.

468
00:18:47,800 --> 00:18:50,160
如果她还是想跟库珀走  没关系  但...
And if she still wants to go with Cooper-- fine, but...

469
00:18:50,370 --> 00:18:51,530
她需要知道
she needs to know.

470
00:18:51,620 --> 00:18:54,670
跑吧  像风一样跑去机场
Run! Run like the wind to that airport.

471
00:18:54,910 --> 00:18:56,560
赶快走
Get out of here now.

472
00:18:58,240 --> 00:18:59,300
好运
Good luck.

473
00:19:02,530 --> 00:19:03,550
你也是
You too.

474
00:19:08,720 --> 00:19:09,830
抱歉
Excuse me.

475
00:19:09,890 --> 00:19:10,560
借过
Pardon me.

476
00:19:10,560 --> 00:19:12,550
不好意思  这事关生死
I'm sorry, this is a matter of life and death.

477
00:19:12,550 --> 00:19:14,790
是啊  他要告诉个姑娘自己可能喜欢她
Yeah, he has to tell a girl he might like her.

478
00:19:15,920 --> 00:19:17,050
你好
Hi.

479
00:19:18,300 --> 00:19:20,150
你能告诉我加比·戴蒙德
Can you tell me if Gabi Diamond

480
00:19:20,150 --> 00:19:22,640
是否检票上飞北京的YL125航班了吗
has checked in to flight YL125 to Beijing?

481
00:19:22,640 --> 00:19:25,160
抱歉  先生  这信息我无法提供
I'm sorry sir, but I can't give out that information.

482
00:19:25,170 --> 00:19:26,670
好吧  我理解
All right, fine. I get that.

483
00:19:27,780 --> 00:19:29,440
但你看过《风月俏佳人》吗
But have you seen Pretty Woman?

484
00:19:30,610 --> 00:19:33,020
加比  中国  票  买机票啊
Gabi. China. Ticket. Buy a ticket!

485
00:19:34,600 --> 00:19:36,020
抱歉  您来晚了
I'm sorry, you're too late.

486
00:19:36,020 --> 00:19:37,510
该航班已经开始登机
That flight's already boarding.

487
00:19:37,530 --> 00:19:39,380
好吧  现在你得打给[喊]她
Okay. Well, now you have to call her.

488
00:19:40,790 --> 00:19:42,830
加比
Gabi!

489
00:19:43,580 --> 00:19:44,550
-乔什  -干什么
- Josh? - Yeah?

490
00:19:44,550 --> 00:19:45,860
-用电话打  -对哦
- On the phone. - Yes.

491
00:19:47,430 --> 00:19:48,980
好看的从来都笨哈
Pretty ones are never smart.

492
00:19:50,270 --> 00:19:51,720
这是金茂大厦
This is Jin Mao Tower.

493
00:19:52,150 --> 00:19:54,270
还记得网上那个打喷嚏的大熊猫吗
Oh, and remember the sneezing panda from the internet?

494
00:19:54,270 --> 00:19:56,010
-记得  -这是他长大以后
- Yeah. - Here he is all grown up.

495
00:19:56,010 --> 00:19:57,670
好可爱
Oh, cute.

496
00:19:57,740 --> 00:20:01,860
飞往北京的YL125次航班最后一次登机广播
Final boarding call for Flight YL125 to Beijing.

497
00:20:02,620 --> 00:20:04,740
我们要把手机调成飞行模式
Oh, hey, we should put our phones on airplane mode.

498
00:20:04,740 --> 00:20:07,110
对哦  是的
Oh, right. Yeah, we should do that.

499
00:20:08,270 --> 00:20:09,600
怎么调来着
How would one do that?

500
00:20:13,640 --> 00:20:14,670
通了
It's ringing.

501
00:20:17,810 --> 00:20:19,230
转到语音信箱了  我要说什么
I got her voicemail. What do I say?

502
00:20:19,990 --> 00:20:21,170
说你想说的
Say everything.

503
00:20:25,100 --> 00:20:26,830
喂  加比
Hey, Gabi.

504
00:20:28,920 --> 00:20:30,280
我是从...
I'm calling you from...

505
00:20:31,250 --> 00:20:32,340
机场打给你的
the airport,

506
00:20:32,600 --> 00:20:33,740
实际上
actually.

507
00:20:33,890 --> 00:20:36,010
相信你好奇我为什么会在机场
I'm sure you're wondering why I'm at the airport.

508
00:20:37,110 --> 00:20:37,890
问得好
Good question.

509
00:20:37,890 --> 00:20:41,040
你总是问这种好问题
You always ask good questions.

510
00:20:43,390 --> 00:20:44,480
是因为...
It's because...

511
00:20:45,340 --> 00:20:47,430
昨晚  我取消婚礼之后
last night, after I called off my wedding,

512
00:20:49,270 --> 00:20:50,910
想见的人是你
you're the person that I wanted to see.

513
00:20:52,450 --> 00:20:54,870
我甚至拿着玫瑰花跑上你家逃生梯
I even ran up your fire escape with roses.

514
00:20:57,840 --> 00:21:00,040
我不知道自己要说什么  但我知道
I didn't know what I was going to say, but I knew that

515
00:21:00,250 --> 00:21:02,990
我必须要见你  然后我看见了你和库珀
I needed to see you, and then I saw Cooper and you.

516
00:21:03,940 --> 00:21:05,900
如果你和库珀在一起很幸福
And look, if you're happy with Cooper,

517
00:21:05,900 --> 00:21:08,420
就当我没打这通电话
just disregard this whole message.

518
00:21:09,570 --> 00:21:10,660
但是...
But...

519
00:21:11,370 --> 00:21:13,080
如果你觉得或许...
if you think you might,

520
00:21:13,390 --> 00:21:15,070
和我一起更幸福
like, be happier with me...

521
00:21:17,350 --> 00:21:18,420
回我电话吧
call me back.

522
00:21:20,080 --> 00:21:21,350
我是乔什
This is Josh, by the way.

523
00:21:27,180 --> 00:21:28,980
不敢相信我到中国了
I can't believe I'm in China,

524
00:21:29,200 --> 00:21:32,090
如果六岁的加比挖个洞  就能看到我
if six-year-old Gabi digging a hole could see me now.

525
00:21:33,430 --> 00:21:35,310
别开手机
Oh, don't turn you phone on.

526
00:21:35,680 --> 00:21:37,270
为什么  那我怎么查短信
Why? How I'm I suppose to check messages?

527
00:21:37,270 --> 00:21:38,970
如果你没办国际流量套餐
Well, if you don't have an international dataplan,

528
00:21:38,970 --> 00:21:40,860
话费会很贵很贵的
it'll cost you thousands of dollars.

529
00:21:40,910 --> 00:21:42,300
我的确没办
Oh, I don't have those.

530
00:21:43,630 --> 00:21:45,100
反正也没人会找我
Who's gonna call me, anyway.

531
00:21:48,840 --> 00:21:51,430
-知道吗  在中国大家一般亲两次  -好吧
- You know, in China they always kiss twice. - Okay.

