Oenomaus:
Freedom?
Batiatus: No longer shall
you be my Doctore.
You will assume the mantle
of Lanista
and be warmly greeted
by your name-- Oenomaus.
- What is this madness?!
- Spartacus shows us the way.
He sends word to me
that one of the fallen
bore your name
carved into his chest.
The consuls will present a motion
dispatching you to Capua.
There are villas and farms
far from the city.
Naevia was handed
from dominus to dominus.
- ( gags )
- Spartacus: We move south
to find Naevia.
( screams )
This is Batiatus' wife?
- A shadow of the same.
- And yet she lives.
lt would give the city hope
to see a woman
survive Spartacus and his men.
- ( screams )
- Where do you go?
There is but one place
for an animal without honor.
( panting )
( muted crowd booing )
( crowd jeering )
- Come on!
- Raah!
( yelling )
Go on!
Yeah!
Kill!
- Yeah!
- Get up!
Man:
Take his fucking face off! Yeah!
- ( laughing )
- Yeah!
( yells )
( screaming )
Yeah!
( yelling )
( cheering )
Yeah!
That is no boy,
but fucking demon
belched from the cunt
of the underworld.
Your presence in the Pits
comes as welcome surprise.
When word that Titus Batiatus
graced us with his presence--
Where did you find him?
He's from a pack of Numidians
purchased from Maalok.
The others fell
within the week.
This one proves too dim
to sniff out their trail.
- Has he any training?
- Training?
A rabid dog would be
more agreeable pupil.
Barely answers
to the name given him.
All men can be tamed,
no matter how wild.
One must only find
an ember of purpose
and give it breath.
l give no shit to embers.
Coin warms my breast.
And the price
to see you so inflamed?
10 denarii,
and the boy is yours
to train, to fuck,
whatever you would
have of him.
Eight.
Eight? You appear
as honorable man,
yet attempt
to slip cock in ass.
lf l held such desire...
you would be split in two.
l give you this bargain
only to entice further purchases.
Rise.
Greet your new master, Oenomaus.
( crowd cheering nearby )
lt is time.
Filthy animals.
Living in offal and shit
beneath the city.
lf we'd known
they were there,
we would be riding
towards Rome
with news
of Spartacus's death.
Now they could be
anywhere.
He would have left the city
to rougher terrain.
lt will be no simple task
to sweep such an area.
More men would spur
to purpose.
Attempts to raise soldiers
have borne shriveled fruit.
lt is the fault of Seppius.
He's secured every man
familiar with sword as his own.
Perhaps it's time
we called on his support.
He is Varinius' man,
not worthy of such invitation.
And yet his men
prove a necessity.
lf we had them
in the marketplace,
Spartacus would never have
found himself so close to you.
The gods conspire
against you.
Return to your quarters.
They demand proper offering,
one of blood and sacrifice.
You speak of ritual?
To restore this house
and to force our enemies
to their knees.
See yourself to market
to gather what you require
when sun greets day.
And we shall confer
with Seppius.
l'll make arrangement.
You believe the gods
will heed your prayers?
lf my cause is just.
Then entreat them
to divine
where Spartacus
has gone to ground
before the villain
robs another Roman of his life.
( gasping )
( gags )
( yells )
Tiberius, l would finish.
Place cock in ass.
- ( men yell )
- Come on.
- ( yelling outside )
- ( metal clanging )
My robes! Quickly!
( women yelling )
( overlapping chatter )
Strike fear, and quiet concern.
Our quarrel is not with you.
lt's with those that would
place themselves your master...
a title that bears
no meaning to us,
nor to you now,
should you wish it so.
You are presented choice
as we once were:
to submit forever
to Roman cruelty
or take up arms
and to join us in freedom.
( whispers )
And who are you
to present such fucking offer?
l am Spartacus.
( gasping, murmuring )
Still your fucking tongues!
Are you the dominus
of this house?
l am.
( blade scrapes )
Then we should have words.
( yells )
What is it you seek?!
Give desire voice,
and see it satisfied.
You are a man
of fucking influence.
Yes. Yes.
l have the ear
of the magistrate.
l can deliver message.
lt is message sent to you
which l have interest in.
You were friends of Batiatus,
were you not?
( whimpering )
Were you not?!
l knew him only in passing.
He was filled with mad dreams
of rising
in prominence of office.
Yet he needed support.
To gain it, he sent a gift
from villa to villa
in this region,
a woman.
- A woman.
- You know of her?
lf l do...
my life yet spared?
Speak while you still
have fucking tongue!
She was-- she was here.
She was here.
You would break false word
to Jupiter himself
just to see another dawn.
No, no. No.
Dark of skin.
Hair roughly shorn.
The mark of her domina
upon the back of her shoulder.
Where is she?
l do not know.
She was put to cart after.
After?
How-- how--
how could l know
that she held meaning?
Did she not breathe?
Did her heart not beat
like any other woman's?
Yet you did not see
a woman, did you?
You just saw something
to be used and discarded.
- Please.
- You just saw a fucking slave!
- ( laughter )
- ( crashing )
Everything is in the back.
Yeah!
Take everything.
Your beauty stirs my cock.
A rise too slight
for eyes to notice.
- ( laughter )
- Hey!
That's how it's done.
( cheering )
That one smells of shit.
From where does he hail?
Gallia.
Gauls, they fuck absent regard
of pleasing a woman.
A skill lacking in most men.
And what of Spartacus?
How does he stand?
Above the rest...
in all regard.
Apologies.
l did not know he was yours.
l do not claim him
in such terms,
nor would he be
so enslaved.
He offers you protection
in return for affections.
We have no such
arrangement.
ls it love then?
Of course.
The hope of love to come.
A danger in its own right.
l need an accounting
of all food and supplies.
Find Vitus and see it done.
We suffered no casualties,
though Liscus and Acer
took minor wounds.
The Gauls grow careless.
How many weapons were secured?
Enough to see
a dozen more men well armed.
And we will put them to use
in the next villa that we take.
The dominus?
He recalled a slave
marked the same as Naevia.
Where was she taken?
She was put to cart
to be passed
to the next fucking dominus.
Crixus.
We will find her, brother,
and see everyone
that has kept her from your arms
to the afterlife.
♪ ...rains down
from an angry sky ♪
♪ My cock rages on ♪
♪ My cock rages on. ♪
l will see to my men
and Rhaskos's cock to cover.
( laughter )
Ah, Crixus.
Get down.
He is given crumbs,
yet you present
his fucking meal.
His heart aches
for nourishment.
l would have it well fed.
Even if Naevia lives,
she will not be the woman
he holds to memory.
lf we are to stand against Glaber
and the Romans,
we must liberate fighting men,
not waste effort
on dwindling hope
- and worthless house slaves.
- Every man has his worth,
a lesson
the Romans will soon learn.
The bonds of slavery
have been struck.
Never again
will you feel them tighten
around your neck
robbing you
of breath and life.
See your own join
your brothers
and take up just cause.
We will see the Romans bleed
for taking us as dogs,
to be yanked by the leash
at their command.
Tychos, Sophus,
weapons.
Now...
who would have blood?
This place...
the very air clings
to the flesh, tainting it.
Close eyes, Domina,
and replace thought.
( gasping )
llithyia.
( gasps )
Oh, Gaius.
You give heart
cause to flutter.
The water ripples
in evidence.
The result of your child
and firm kick
upon swollen belly.
Such aggression
prophesies a boy.
Would l give you any less?
You have given me much of late.
Your sacrifice
has not gone unnoticed.
Yet there is more
that l would ask.
You need but command it.
Escort Lucretia
to market at dawn.
She intends ceremony
to cleanse this house
and deliver my enemies.
The gods
would rather piss on Rome
than whisper in her ear.
People of this city
believe her prophet.
She is not to be trusted.
lt was not long ago
you named her friend.
A mistake dearly paid for.
A sum costing us both.
You truly believe her blessed?
Spartacus must fall
if we are to be
returned to Rome,
and l am willing to believe
whatever revelations
tumble from her lips
if they shall hasten
such a day.
Now...
see yourself dried
by loving hands
and to our bed.
( bleats )
Spartacus: Oh, to have
a proper bed once more.
lt's been a lifetime.
l have never
known such a thing.
Then it is much deserved.
Spartacus...
what we share...
what meaning
does it hold for you?
What answer would you have?
One spoken from the heart.
l have feasted so long
on pain and sorrow,
it is difficult
to recall sweeter taste
except when you
are in my arms.
Then let me
never be from them.
Spartacus!
You've already killed me once.
Do not hesitate
to revisit the deed.
He did nothing
but offer freedom,
and this is how you repay?
lt was not his to grant!
l was body slave
to the dominus.
l had position and respect.
You were a slave,
everything you possessed
a mere fleeting illusion.
You but take my master's place.
And what would your master
do now,
if he stood so assaulted?
He would see me dead.
Yes, he would.
You yet wish
to train this fuck?
The boy deserves opportunity.
He was given such a thing
and made attempt
on your life in response.
Gods save me.
l find myself in agreement
with a Gaul.
He has known nothing
but slavery,
the strength of such a tether
not easily severed.
- Perhaps never to be so.
- And if we take his life?
What message
will that send to those
who wish to join our cause?
That they
had best be agreeable.
We're Romans then?
Commanding through fear
and threat of death?
lf he makes attempt again,
l will make sure he joins
his fucking dominus.
And how do you propose
we train this wild little dog?
As Batiatus
had Doctore train me.
And that turned out so well.
( crowd cheering )
Liberius draws plumbatae!
- ( cheering )
- ( snarls )
Addonexus selects vinculum!
( cheering )
( yells )
Take his fucking head off!
Go on! Come on!
- ( yells )
- Yeah!
Release him.
- ( groans )
- Broken.
A minor injury,
meant only to instruct.
( groans )
l stand in victory in my match,
yet Doctore provides
only lash and rod as reward.
You believe
you deserve otherwise?
This is a house of champions,
Oenomaus.
lt does not submit to you.
You submit to it.
Yes, Dominus.
One must learn to kneel
if he is ever to rise.
A necessary lesson
if you are to one day
join the champions
of the House of Batiatus.
How is such a thing possible?
The answer lies
within your breast.
You fight with a strength of men
beyond your meager years,
yet lack the discipline
to see it properly harnessed.
Quintus, two cups of mulsum.
Tell me what l must do.
The most difficult of tasks.
You must discover your purpose.
- My purpose?
- That which you fight for.
l fight to stay alive.
( laughs )
As do we all.
But to grasp the heavens,
you must fight
for something greater,
something beyond
mere survival.
You are my dominus.
l fight for whatever you decide.
No, no.
This is a decision each man,
whether slave or freeborn,
must forge himself.
lt is yours alone.
To your purpose
and the destiny
it shall lead you to.
( yells )
Yeah!
Come on! Bring it!
( grunting )
( cheering )
Addonexus, victor!
Yeah!
Just fucking barely.
Send another to face me.
And what of his opponent?
Send him as well.
You wish to leave this world,
l shall ferry you.
Addonexus thirsts
for yet more blood.
- ( cheering )
- And he shall have it!
Last position!
- Attack!
- ( metal clanging )
( grunting )
Keep your left arm up!
- ( blade slaps )
- ( growls )
You carry a shield
as well as sword.
Not the man, the shoulder.
- Again.
- ( men grunt )
Attack!
Good.
( groans )
You expose flank,
the ruin of many a great man.
l'm no fucking soldier.
( laughs )
Not yet.
First and second position.
- Attack!
- ( men grunting )
lt's heavier than l imagined.
lt will lighten in time.
And when it becomes
as a feather,
what purpose
do you think it shall fly to?
One of your own choosing.
Now set foot to path...
- And second positions!
- ...and come at me again.
- Attack!
- ( men grunt )
Should have put the boy down.
A dog bites once,
he will bare
fucking teeth again.
Pity.
( goat bleats )
Why do they stare?
How could they not
when one blessed by the gods
moves among them?
The gods?
Oh, yes.
You rarely spoke of them
in times past.
Now the divine is held
as confidant and council.
Much has changed.
( bleating )
Curious words
from one who claims
no memory of the past.
Shadows of it begin to form
in the light of a new day.
( goat bleating )
What shape do they take?
One of secrets
passed between us.
You confessed
that you do not always heed
the commands of your father
or your husband.
( laughs )
You speak of my first visit
to your villa...
when we had yet to come
to truly know one another.
l so wished to please you.
You're the wife of the legatus.
Such a gift.
You do not know what it means
to find you within the walls
of my house once again,
filling it with life
and promise.
To survive such barbarity,
you are truly touched
by the gods.
Gratitude.
May the gods bless you.
( crowd murmuring )
- Lucretia.
llithyia.
Bless me.
They seem
rather taken with her.
Seppia. A welcome sight.
Unless you intend tribute to
the oracle of Batiatus as well.
l do not push about in throngs.
l find the odor of desperation
lingers upon garment.
We are of similar mind.
More so tethered
by blood and marriage.
My brother only just departed
to sit with your husband.
- Men and their politics.
- Let us leave them to it
and turn thought
toward more pressing subject.
What news
of latest scandal from Rome?
Husband and coming child
have drawn attention
from such events.
l cannot believe you
so removed.
You are acquainted
with positively everybody.
And yet desired
by more than a few.
( giggles )
How l envy such attentions.
And how l miss them.
Must all joy be so abandoned
when weighted with husband?
lt must
if a woman is
of proper breeding.
Oh.
How miserable.
Perhaps l should
entreat the gods
to shield me from such dour fate.
( laughs )
Lucretia:
May the gods bless you.
- May the gods bless you.
- Lucretia.
- lt's a sign.
May the gods bless you
- Lucretia.
May the gods bless you.
Lucretia.
Bless me. Bless me.
May the gods bless you.
- Lucretia.
Spartacus was one of yours,
was he not?
During your overly brief
campaign in Thrace.
Conscripted to the auxiliary.
An animal prone
to disobedience even then.
A beast you brought
to our shores.
To die in the arena.
Yet he lives,
a pleasure denied
my noble cousin Sextus.
Many have suffered injury.
To be healed by news
of Spartacus' fall.
A venture l eagerly
set hands to months past.
Yes, word touched me
in the Senate of your efforts.
How many of your men
has he sent to the afterlife?
( sighs )
The man proves resourceful,
as he did when he set upon you
in the market square.
lt is a pity my men were not
present to end the matter.
Spartacus stands
a common foe, as l said.
Yes, my tribune cleaves
to the heart of it.
Spartacus is enemy
to us both,
shared in offense
and blood,
so let us
sweep aside differences
and in union
see him forced to knee.
l would need to consult Varinius
towards such agreement.
Are they your men or his?
And who would lead
combined effort?
You shall hold
station of note,
second only
to my command,
and promise
that you shall be present
when Spartacus
is put to grass.
The man takes habit of slipping
through your fingers.
What moves you
to certainty of victory?
Because the gods
themselves will it.
They speak with you now,
do they?
Through voice of former domina
of this very house.
- ( laughs ) Lucretia?
- They have blessed her,
as they blessed her
the night they guided her
from death
in the massacre.
Yet she is not alone
in such fortune.
Did the gods not...
guide your wife
to safety as well?
llithyia took leave
before unfortunate turn.
And with her,
a clutch of your men
soldiers that might have
tipped the balance
towards halting Spartacus
short of fucking slaughter.
You will tend your words with
more care in my presence, boy.
- Come, let us take seat--
- My words are carefully chosen
for a man holding title
as favor to his wife's father.
You speak to me
in such manner again,
and l will have your tongue.
Yet not my men.
♪ ...cock rages on,
my cock rages on ♪
♪ l put you down,
l give you shit ♪
♪ l piss on your grave
for the sport of it ♪
♪ And when l die,
expect no less ♪
♪ My mind is gone,
my cock rages on. ♪
( cheering )
You.
Slave, see my jug filled.
Rhaskos.
Fetch drink yourself.
Do not fucking drain jug
before return, slave.
- ( laughter )
- ♪ Fight to fuck ♪
♪ Fuck to fight,
l fight to fuck again... ♪
You offer privilege
before it is properly earned.
And you would have them bow
and scrape in service
as they did
before their dominus?
No.
Yet neither would l have them
seen as equal.
They were not forged
of the brotherhood, as we were.
They join our cause
of their own free will.
Such fire may yet
prove more fierce.
Or be extinguished
by threatening storm.
l would move at first light.
There are yet more villas.
( men yelling )
You press fortune
glaring so
at the Slayer of Theokoles.
His victory
but proving even giants fall.
( laughs )
What name do you go by,
little man?
So l may properly
mourn your passing.
l'm called Tiberius.
Tiberius?
You are far too dark
to have such a fair Roman name.
l'm more Roman than Syrian.
There was a Syrian at our ludus.
A treacherous fuck,
if ever there breathed.
You had family there?
l only recall a brother.
l too had a brother.
No longer?
He was struck down
by the Romans.
When you turned swords
against them?
As you shall one day
if you hold any fucking sense.
Look at me.
l would see that pretty face
as l finish.
You fucking animal!
- Mira!
- Go!
Or part with your cock.
lf you were
not Spartacus' bitch,
l would show you
how to use that and my cock.
Apologies.
l will see that Rhaskos--
l chose to lay
with the fucking Gaul.
Why?
Not all of us have Spartacus
warm our beds
and see us to position.
You gain freedom
only to be enslaved
by that shit?
Freedom is not without cost.
l pay with the only coin l have.
As do you.
( men cheering )
Perhaps we should
stand further away
for fear of errant bolt
from the heavens.
Such ritual may bring profit,
absent cost.
The goat came
at no small expense.
The gods whisper
of deceit and treachery
and give assurance
that those who would harbor
secrets against you
shall be brought to light.
Accept our offering
and bless us with your favor
against our enemies.
ls it wise
to allow such unsteady hands
to play with knives?
Hold tongue.
( bleats )
Your will, my hands.
Hmm.
Perhaps another goat?
When ritual is ended,
see blood cleansed
and Lucretia attended.
( crowd cheering )
( footsteps )
You are to fight Caratacus next,
a beast that has claimed
many lives.
You believe he shall end mine?
ln your condition?
( laughs )
lf he does not,
send one that will.
Spectator:
Get up! Get up!
You have taken
important step
towards rising above
base animal.
lt shames me
l fought in that place,
absent thoughts of honor.
The Pits are for men whose lives
promise nothing greater
than an ugly end.
You are destined
for far grander fate.
The arena.
Place where legends are forged.
l fear for those that dare
take the sands against you.
l shall make
their deaths memorable.
The gods will be pleased.
l do not fight for the gods.
l fight for you.
That is my purpose, my life,
to honor the House of Batiatus.
The honor is mine.
( thunder rumbles )
( crowd yelling )
Yeah!
( cheering )
- Come on! Finish it!
- Yeah.
Take his head off!
Here. His blade!
( blade strikes )
( crowd groaning )
You.
Domina!
Men approach.
Torches arriving from the north.
How many?
Six, maybe more.
Gather the men.
Spartacus: Wait.
These may be scouts
from a larger force.
lf a single rider
was to escape our grasp,
it could bring
a far greater concern.
Then we shall grip tightly.
There is a better way,
one that will keep our movements
yet hidden from the Romans.
( bangs on door )
l would have words
with your dominus,
on orders of Seppius.
Apologies. Business has
called him to Picentia.
Picentia?
l have never known him
to favor the city.
He does not.
He favors its whores.
( laughs )
You are his body slave,
are you not?
Tiberius.
Tell me...
why are you
not at your dominus' side?
Because there's
no one he trusts more
to see his villa attended
while his cock is satisfied.
You serve your master well.
Return to your charge.
Wait.
You have come
a fair distance from Capua.
Come, and l will
give you something
to make effort worthwhile.
He betrays us.
( yells )
Spartacus!
( man yells )
Why did you stop them
from leaving?
He killed a man.
When he saw
they would not win.
His eyes fell to my neck.
He saw the absence
of my collar.
lf l had not allowed him in,
he would have returned
with more men.
You did well, Tiberius.
Nasir.
My brother called me Nasir.
Who disturbs peace
at such an hour?
l come bearing a gift
which shall set you upon path
to the fall of Spartacus.
The gods truly heed my prayers.
字幕来源于互联网\N美剧控☆昆特斯\N欧美史诗大片推荐,请上\Nwww.kuntesi.com