( laughter )
Glaber: l did not care
for Varinius' hand upon you.
Nor l.
The girl, Naevia.
- What did he say?
- Dead.
The slaver told
not of her death,
but of her suffering
in the mines!
l stand with Crixus and will
see Naevia from bondage.
l move for Vesuvius.
Those that would live,
join me.
Noble Varinius!
l offer apologies.
My soldiers have been set
to higher purpose!
- lnto the mines.
- Quickly!
At this very moment,
they close on Spartacus!
( cheering )
You're safe.
You're safe now.
Crixus?
- ( chuckles )
- See Naevia to safety.
- ( blade rings )
- No!
( theme music playing )
( birds chirping )
( croaks )
- ( whimpers )
- Shh.
Shh.
( screams )
- Mira: Naevia!
- Halt!
- Swing around to the left!
- ( yelling )
Soldier: l've got her!
( yells )
( yelling )
( panting )
- You made me run.
- ( sobbing )
l fucking hate running.
( Mira screaming )
- ( men grunting )
- ( metal clanging )
- ( flesh squelches )
- ( bone cracks )
l would see Tychos to ground,
far from Roman hands.
More come.
- Soldier: For Rome!
- ( horn sounds )
( soldier yelling orders )
Right.
- There is no time for it.
- lt does not fucking matter.
We shall all join him soon.
Spartacus shall fall.
ls that not the reason
for my presence in Capua?
To shit with reason.
The absence of your troops
from the games
was an insult to good Varinius.
The Republic would bear
far greater slight
were l to turn from purpose.
Seppius has been searching
for the Thracian for months.
How came you to divine
he would make attempt
on the mines at Lucania?
Because the gods
themselves presented it
through voice
of humble servant.
- Lucretia?
- Her counsel moved my hand.
Perhaps your course
was justified then.
l pray it true.
Otherwise offense has been made
upon the ramblings
of a madwoman.
We have moved
past this, llithyia.
ln spirit, at least.
Let us make it a thing
of the flesh with celebration
here within these walls
to pay tribute owed.
An excellent notion.
Well received, yes?
lt would stand the more
grievous insult to refuse.
( chuckles )
You honor me.
The honor is mine.
l only thought to help.
By plying that preening shit
with celebration
in our own house?
Our house is in Rome, Gaius,
and l would speed return.
With Varinius' support,
you will have Seppius' men.
Now worth their weight in piss.
When Marcus returns with
Spartacus as Lucretia fore--
You place
too high a value on her.
She will drag us to ruin
when it plummets.
Lucretia continues
to prove herself
worthy of such estimation.
Would that my own wife
held the same.
- ( gasps )
- Spartacus!
- She needs a moment.
- She needs to fucking move.
How quickly
would your feet carry
after months
condemned to that place?
She is not alone
in needing rest.
The lack of it
sets nerve to edge.
We will find higher ground,
better defended if set upon.
Can you walk but a little more?
She will make it.
Come on.
The weight of her increases
with each step.
Perhaps it is time
to lighten burden.
l swore a promise to Crixus.
She is the man's heart.
Would you again
tear it from his chest?
Crixus is dead,
and l would be freed
of his woman
before we fucking share
the same fate.
We move for Vesuvius
to rejoin Agron,
all of us.
Speak of this again,
and the Romans
will be the least
of your concerns.
Ashur: Tychos,
one of the lesser men.
Let him serve as a warning
that Rome is not
so easily defied.
Their numbers dwindle.
Yet ours follow
at more rapid pace.
- Up!
- We still hold the greater sum.
Spartacus and his men
are gladiators.
A handful of your men
would stand a pale shadow
against one--
Roman soldiers
know something of death
and the dealing of it.
Do not measure their worth
against common slaves.
Slaves, true,
but far from common.
Move absent proper force,
and see the rank
of the dead swell.
Your men...
are spread too thin
throughout the forest.
A single man
carried by a swift purpose
could return
with reinforcements--
Carry word to the other squads.
- We do not rest.
- Tribune--
See this to its end
in the name
of Gaius Claudius Glaber.
Turn from your charge,
and l'll put a sword
in your fucking back.
Varinius is a man
of the highest regard.
See his cup always full
and all desires met.
Am l understood?
- Domina.
- Yes, domina.
- ( laughs )
- lt's true.
Promise.
Bathe and prepare yourselves.
- ( laughs )
- Seppia.
Apologies. l was not
told of your arrival.
None required.
l came seeking Lucretia's counsel.
A thing desired by many,
it would seem.
Your words set her to path.
Mine?
You are forever extolling
the virtues of marriage.
Wisdom of years
has finally proven
master over fatuous youth.
You've found a husband
so quickly?
lf the gods bless such a union.
l shall entreat them
on your behalf.
With their favor,
Varinius shall be yours.
Varinius?
ls he not handsome
and tall and strong
and of means?
The form of a man every woman
longs to call her own.
He would make a husband
to rival all others.
( Seppia giggles )
l must prepare myself
for his celebration.
l would catch his eye
and, with it, see the rest
of him swiftly follow.
You have made
impression upon her.
As have you.
No longer is pilgrimage
needed to Delphi.
Those seeking
the consideration of the gods
need only bow
to the oracle of Capua.
l am but humble vessel
offering a mere taste
of their will.
Then Seppia shall find tonight
a bitter draft.
Varinius is a praetor.
As is your husband.
Yet Varinius
rises more quickly
and one day shall
hold title of consul.
The wife of such a man must
possess refinement and poise,
traits yet lacking
in a spoiled little girl.
Perhaps you would have me
petition the gods
for a different union...
one closer to heart.
The morning cock
has better chance
of crowing
to such heights.
Your husband believes otherwise,
as does your father.
When Marcus returns
absent Spartacus,
you shall be revealed
as what you are,
an empty vessel,
barren of life and prophecy.
See yourself
dressed for tonight.
l have no doubt my husband
will wish to parade you about
as favored pet.
Your husband's trust
is valued gift.
Yet yours would prove
the greater treasure.
Soldier:
Open the gates!
Packers, tend to your horses!
( overlapping chatter )
( chuckles )
Soldier: Line them up!
The faith placed in me
is not mislaid.
Spartacus proves
where l predicted.
Praetor.
This is all that stand captured?
Many more lay dead
in the mines.
Your Gaul returns
to you at least.
Where is Spartacus?
He fled into the woods
with a clutch of slaves.
Marcus gives chase.
Alert me the moment
he is sighted upon road.
- To the cells.
- Move!
Even aided
by your divine guidance,
he stands with empty hands.
He will yet find
Spartacus between them.
The gods--
Your tongue writhes
absent their purpose.
Was Naevia not found
in the mines as l foretold?
And who so condemned her
to such a place?
Juno...
or a lanista's wife,
more earthly bound?
Your prophecies bear
the stench of opportunity.
Oenomaus--
Was delivered
by your dead husband's man,
a toad who has seen
his share of wounds.
l wonder if he
could mend them as well.
Do not think me the fool
as my husband and father.
You and l have
unfinished affairs...
and l would see them
draw to a close.
Get in!
( laughs )
Again to this house
of piss and shit.
A fate l alone should bear.
The risk was known to us all.
Fuck risk,
and fuck the fucking Romans.
l stand with you
in this life and the next.
As do l.
The bonds of brotherhood.
They have always run deep
within these walls.
Oenomaus.
What has happened?
How did you come here?
l was a fool...
that now stands
in fellow company.
Their fault lies
only in following me
on impossible journey.
Naevia lives.
We liberated her from the mines.
Love.
You fall to ruin for love.
She is my heart.
She is a woman...
a delicate creature
at the best of times.
They are moved by desires
unknown by the men
that place trust in them.
She lives.
That is all that matters.
( gasping )
Mira: Shh.
You're safe now.
You are safe.
You do not rest?
l would not see
another of us fall.
Not even the gods could have
done more to prevent it.
A thought holding
no comfort to the dead.
( Naevia screams )
- Naevia.
- ( men shout )
- ( Naevia screams )
- Liscus!
- ( wails )
- Nasir.
He risked life to save my own.
And l am forever in his debt.
( yells )
You were right.
My sword becomes lighter
with each Roman l have taken.
( gasping )
- ( music playing )
- ♪ Aphrodita ♪
♪ Aphrodita ♪
( singing in Latin )
Most impressive showing.
Staggers to think
this house so recently a tomb.
♪ Aphrodita... ♪
These walls truly present
no evidence
of witnessed horrors.
♪ Aphrodita, Aphrodita. ♪
- ( yells )
- ( screams )
Such memories shall soon
be cleansed from thought,
never again to darken mind.
l long for such a day.
Let us hasten it
with ample libation.
l fear Mercato
may lose himself
in the bottom of a cup
and forget that
we are of position.
l would never
make spectacle of myself.
( giggles )
Gallienus:
Come then.
l would test the strength
of your resolve
and my own as well!
l have never
beheld sour Gallienus
in such high spirits.
This celebration already
proves clever suggestion.
To be made brilliant
if Spartacus's capture
were to be announced.
The gods may yet bless us this night
with unexpected gifts.
Let us entreat them
with wine and song,
our voices to carry
to Olympus itself.
This house once sat
perched within its reach.
l have worshiped here
myself upon occasion.
( Varinius laughs )
Good Cossutius.
l had not heard
you were in Capua.
He comes for my games.
And to remove himself
from the prudish eyes of Rome.
Ah! Both just cause.
llithyia: Come.
Let us enjoy spectacle.
Truly a feast for the senses.
Even l stand speechless.
Then l shall seize
upon rare moment...
to honor noble guest.
Good citizens of Capua,
your presence
here in this house
once stood cursed
is testament
to your courage and faith,
faith not only in me,
but in the body
of the Senate as well,
represented
by beloved Albinius...
- Good Albinius!
- ...and noble Varinius.
( applause )
A man worthy of celebration
for his generosity in providing
distraction with games
to ease troubled thoughts.
( applause )
Man:
Praise Praetor Varinius.
- ( overlapping chatter )
- To the Republic!
See how they admire you.
Man:
Good Varinius.
( applause continues )
The girl takes
your counsel to heart.
And l repay
your kind attendance
with welcome news
of retribution.
( crowd murmurs )
My soldiers return
with news of Spartacus'
imminent capture...
- ( crowd gasping )
- Yes!
( cheering )
And offer in advance
the lives of the few
surviving remnants
of his most trusted men.
These gladiators...
these slaves,
were responsible
for the deaths
of many of your noble kin...
and they will pay...
with blood.
( crowd yelling )
Praetor Varinius.
Pressing concerns
forced hand
in preventing my men
from presenting at your games.
l offer you the lives
of these enemies of Rome
to balm unintentional wounds.
Man: Cut the pig!
( crowd cheering )
Man:
Come on, we want blood!
Gratitude for this honor
and for your tireless pursuit
of the villain Spartacus.
- Yet l cannot accept.
- ( crowd gasping )
l cannot accept,
because to do so
would rob the people of this
city of deserved pleasures.
Let these men
not fall here tonight
in the honor of a single man,
but in the arena
before all of Capua!
( cheering )
Man:
Justice be had!
- Great Varinius!
- ( applause )
( water splashing )
Water!
( gasping )
Drink.
The boy fought well.
Would this were wine to send him
properly on his way.
You speak of him
as if already gone.
Then he speaks the truth.
Naevia is burden enough.
We have settled this.
Come to reason.
There is more blood upon
the ground than within him.
Even if we carry him,
he will not survive.
But he will leave a trail,
one that the Romans
shall follow.
We cannot just leave him.
No, we cannot.
You would take his life?
l would but sever
dangling thread.
lt would be a kindness.
You will not touch him.
Then do it yourself.
Put him from misery,
as you did Varro.
Crixus.
He survived worse
against Theokoles.
The boy too will live
if his wound
is sealed with fire.
Fire would call
the Romans down upon us.
Then we must be quick
and be gone before they arrive.
And if we are not?
We do not have enough men.
No, we do not.
Find Agron
and bring all to purpose.
We will follow as swiftly
as we are able.
l fear it will not
be swift enough.
( music playing )
( laughter )
( no audible dialogue )
Trussed as game
awaiting slaughter,
yet the man
still eyes us as prey.
The fire will soon be put
from rebellious eyes.
A fitting end
to your games, Varinius.
lt shall be a day
etched in memory.
l cannot wait to see their blood
spill upon the sands.
- ( giggles )
- Nor l.
Yet should they not fall here,
in the very place
they robbed our beloved
cousin Sextus of his life?
A man dearly missed.
lt is a pity he shall
not be honored this night.
Would the greater honor
not be before all of Capua?
( Varinius chuckles )
We are politicians, are we not?
Let us come to middle ground
and see everyone satisfied.
Choose a single man,
and let us make sport of him
in memory of your cousin.
A most judicious compromise.
Seppius is not the only one
who stands injured.
The gods themselves took note
of the horrors
inflicted upon Lucretia
and pluck her from
the shores of the afterlife
to voice their desires.
Should she not choose
what blood is shed
beneath roof
she once claimed her own?
She has been
most sorely grieved.
lf there are no objections...
What mortal
dares defy the gods?
Only one who would draw
their wrath.
Varinius has seen fit
to allow us a taste
of the blood to come,
a single man to be sacrificed
to this house
where so many lives
were stolen
by Spartacus
and his jackals,
to be chosen
by its former domina,
the gods themselves
guiding her hand.
( applause )
The gods have chosen.
This one.
( cheering )
We shall draw lots
and cut but shallow
to prolong the game.
Seppius to stand first,
in honor of fallen cousin.
Fuck the lot of you Roman cunts!
( laughs )
( overlapping chatter )
Do not think that the gods
have shown you mercy.
l but delay your passing
so that l may savor it.
My life is gladly given
for Naevia's.
She lives?
( chuckles )
Far from your fucking grasp.
News greeted with joy.
l would have her hear
of your final moments
in the arena
you held so dear
and the crowd
which once cheered your name
spitting upon you.
And when you fall,
it will not be as champion,
but as a common slave,
absent honor
and absent glory
and your name
forever lost to history.
( muffled grunting )
- ( yelling )
- ( laughter )
Let this shit speak now
of Romans!
( cheering )
( groaning continues )
First blood has been drawn!
Who stands next?
Remember, do not cut too deep.
l would not deprive
everyone fair turn.
( laughter )
Varinius in town
but a handful of days,
and already
outshines your husband.
The man does exude...
presence.
- The breast!
- ( yelling )
- ( laughs )
- ( applause )
But your heart was
always set upon Gaius.
lt is a deceitful thing
that has led many astray.
Well, the fault
stands equally shared,
for succumbing
to your teary-eyed pleas
in defense
of misplaced affections.
( grunting continues )
Years have proven them so.
Yet mistakes of youth
need not forever
haunt maturity.
( laughter )
You would see
marriage dissolved?
l do not hold such power.
That decision lies
in trusted father.
Well, Gaius is not without
considerable fault.
Yet it would not lend
favorably upon your name.
You carry his child,
and he yet holds position
of praetor.
He is not the only one
with such title.
( screams )
Let him bleed.
lt would seem the gods favor
less mature schemes.
Strike it
from your thoughts,
as l have from mine.
Don't be greedy, Gallienus.
- Leave us some.
- l'm trying.
( screaming )
( laughing )
Mira: He is fading.
Fetch something for him
to clutch between teeth.
When it is done,
we must smother fire
and move quickly.
l've seen that look
and the blame
it inflicts inward.
None other deserve it.
We chose to do this,
even fucking Liscus.
Glaber does not send
his men against Liscus.
He sends them against me,
and all suffer because of it.
Yes.
lt is because of you
that we are free.
( grunts )
What are you doing?
We must close your wound.
l am to be branded with fire,
as a true gladiator would.
You have earned your place
amongst the brotherhood.
Hold him down.
Do not cry out.
( muffled gasping )
The fire, quickly.
Soldier:
Smoke sighted!
Take my sword. Go.
( laughter )
The man fades.
As do l...
from prying eyes.
( laughs )
l do not care for the way
he looks at me.
Few women do.
Come, it is your turn.
( chuckles )
l have never held one before.
My brother would not allow it.
( chuckles )
Well, then it falls
to more experienced hands
to guide you. Come.
( Seppia giggling )
You do not care
for your master's affections?
l am slave to no man.
Yet you bow and scrape
toward Varinius' purpose.
lf it aids me in pursuit
of Spartacus.
l would have done so as well,
absent attempt
to fuck your sister.
Magistrate, a word.
( giggling )
Varinius: Now place
the tip against flesh...
...and feel it part
at your desire.
( giggling )
Uh...
l cannot.
Apologies.
Our honored guest
asks too much
of inexperienced hands.
( crowd gasping )
Your wife does not shy
from taking life.
l only regret
she moves prematurely,
robbing deed
from more deserving hands.
That is how you sate desire,
for love or vengeance,
without hesitation.
( chuckles )
- ( applause )
- Yeah!
( revelry echoing )
lt is a sight, is it not,
all of Capua laid at your feet?
lt is not the view,
but quiet respite
from celebration that draws me.
l have shattered it
with prattling tongue.
Apologies.
Linger.
l would not sweep you
from perch once your own.
lt seems a lifetime ago
l called it so.
Time flees from us all,
leaving regret for what might
have been churning in our wake.
l fear we share much
in such regard.
A husband lost.
A wife...
Dearly missed.
Let us turn to common joy
of friend and daughter.
llithyia. Hmm.
The name fails to lighten
troubled thoughts.
Give them voice,
and see them fly to the heavens.
l've not the lungs
to shout so loud.
Then whisper desire to me,
and l shall entreat the gods
to see them satisfied.
Your counsel
would be much appreciated.
( twig crunches )
Where's Fortis?
We avoided one squad of Romans.
A second, we could not.
l lost Fortis
in the woods as we fled.
- Which direction?
- The one which you travel in.
We shall break west
and hope to miss them
before righting course.
And if we do not?
Then they shall learn
that a wounded animal
may yet bare teeth.
But of course we can.
( women giggle )
You overreach,
and hot tears burn in result.
Turn from him...
and dry your eyes.
Let us leave this fucking house
and see memory of this night
fade in warm embrace.
Yes, brother.
( Varinius laughs )
Crassus, yes.
Yes, l have dined and bathed
with him on many occasion.
A man large of coin,
small of cock.
( laughter )
His wife has often
spoken of it...
in far grander terms.
Seek more wine.
l shall join you presently.
Your eye flits from young
to younger still.
lf celebration stretches,
l fear to discover you
with a newborn clutched in hand.
llithyia, l would not see
my jest towards Crassus
reach his ear.
And what do you offer
to purchase my silence?
What is it you seek?
Favor for your husband?
l have secured many
for him over the years.
Perhaps it is time to place
myself higher in concern.
lt would be well deserved.
Why do you chase
after simple little girls,
barely formed of breast?
They are unencumbered
of marriage...
and obligation.
And if a woman your equal
stood removed from such?
We speak
in ever-tightening circles.
l would see them
come to a point.
My father never favored Gaius.
lf a more suitable husband
with equal title
and greater promise
were to make
his intentions known...
You play a dangerous game.
With stakes worth the risk.
Your name...
wed to my father's--
power and wealth
to rival Crassus himself.
Gain your father's approval
to dissolve your marriage...
and find me as wet
with desire as you now stand.
( music playing )
( panting )
Fuck the gods.
Fortis.
Back the way we came.
Soldier: ...to the northwest,
General.
( soldiers yelling )
Soldier: One, two, three, four.
Go!
( all yelling )
( blade rings )
- Liscus!
- ( Roman yells )
( metal clanging )
( groans )
Did l not fucking warn you?
A serious wound,
- but you should live--
- Call the remaining squad.
lt will not make a difference.
Spartacus is possessed
by the gods themselves--
Spartacus is here!
Bear arms!
You will draw them to us.
And we will fight until
the last drop of Roman blood--
l am not a Roman.
And l will not
fucking die this night.
( blade squelches )
( gasps )
( Spartacus yells )
( coughing )
We must move before more come.
l am done running.
Do not fucking
let this be for nothing.
Live...
and see many Romans fall.
You really believe
this will save you?
Maneuvering my father's cock
inside you?
You mistake intent--
Do not attempt to twist
fucking word to advantage.
l will not be placed
beneath your heel again,
you withered cunt.
You think so low of me?
Based upon lasting memory
of blood and betrayal.
l've done many things
to hurt you,
because l was jealous
of your position,
your beauty,
your youth,
moved by base passions
which served only
to wound my own heart.
l would do anything, llithyia,
to erase injury
my actions have caused.
You remember
what happened between us?
l remember everything.
Do not think l will be
so easily threatened.
Again, you mistake intent--
Mistake is yours.
l will dash your head
against the stones
- as l did Licinia...
- Wait.
...with tales of how
you lost wits and came to me.
- Your father--
- Will not mourn
the passing of a faded whore.
He will dissolve your marriage!
That is the reason
l took him to my thighs...
to sway him to your cause
of wedding Varinius.
That is what you desire,
is it not?
Even if it were,
why would my father be moved
by serpent's tongue?
The gods speak through me.
He sees wisdom
in their counsel.
l did it for you, llithyia...
to secure future
for you and your child.
l would mend rift between us...
one torn by my own
foolish hands.
Perhaps it is l
that have been foolish...
to ever doubt such dear friend
was blessed by the gods.
Laughter and drink
have done much
to dispel darkening gloom.
Good.
But yet l fear shall
see split head come morning.
( laughter )
You stand satisfied then?
ln all things.
Let us set past aside and look
towards deserving future.
Words of significant worth.
Come, l would
break more with you
before sleep claims us.
Apologies for earlier doubt.
This evening has proven
most advantageous.
Yes.
l long to see
what dawn shall bring.
( birds chirping )
Vesuvius.
How far?
Half a day's journey.
( men yelling )
( equipment jangling )
Take Nasir.
l will hold them back
for as long as l am able.
No.
l stay by your side.
Naevia.
( theme music playing )
字幕来源于互联网\N美剧控☆昆特斯\N欧美史诗大片推荐,请上\Nwww.kuntesi.com