- ( roars )
- Gannicus has proven himself.
Let him be rewarded
with freedom.
You have earned the rudis--
proof you no longer stand
a slave.
Your wife betrayed you--
one last fuck.
And we will fight until
the last drop of Roman blood--
l am not a Roman.
( man grunts )
- Naevia is dead.
- ( screaming )
- Fucking shit!
- l'll fucking kill you.
- Have you lost mind?
- Naevia lives.
l will not fucking die
for this.
( men shouting in distance )
- ( grunting )
- Crixus!
Varinius: Let these men
not fall here tonight,
but in the arena,
before all of Capua!
Gain your father's approval
to dissolve your marriage,
and find me as wet with desire
as you now stand.
( theme music playing )
Crowd:
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
( distant crowd roaring )
( crowd stomping )
( crowd chanting )
Boo!
( hit thuds )
( shouting )
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
A fine showing.
To be forever remembered
by adoring crowd,
as will the name Varinius,
who bestows such
generous gifts.
lndeed, he shall never be
forgotten.
Same cannot be said
of all men.
Would that more
stood your equal.
A pity there is but one of him,
so soon recalled to Rome.
Magistrate:
A brief yet profitable stay.
Your games have given
the city much needed
distraction in these
dark times.
( fanfare )
The executions begin.
A glorious finale
to our stay at Capua.
lf only Spartacus
were among the condemned.
The man shall be put to grass
soon enough, Mercato.
My men move towards
this very purpose.
Until such a time,
let us send message
punctuated in blood.
( crowd cheering )
( cheering subsides )
"Hannibal stands at our gates"--
a phrase used to invoke fear
among the children of Rome,
a specter
of the Carthaginian animal
who besieged this city
with terror and death
many years past.
Yet, as is the fate
of all enemies of the Republic,
Hannibal passed from this life
at the end of a Roman sword!
( cheering )
A fate that will
one day be shared
by the rebel Spartacus!
Was it not your
distant relative,
Appius Claudius Pulcher,
who failed to defeat Hannibal
in the first battle of Capua?
lt was.
( chuckles )
The gods have yet to bless us
with such glorious sight.
Yet they grace us
with portent upon horizon--
three of Spartacus's
most trusted men,
their deaths to serve
as warning
to all who would
challenge Rome!
( crowd jeering )
Boo!
Man: Kill those bastards!
Woman: Get ready to die,
you fuckers!
Varinius: They've got to be shed
ad gladium
by the warriors
whose victories this day
have earned them
position in the Primus.
Yet who shall lead
the forces of Rome?
Who deserves
such storied mantle?
There stands but one--
the only gladiator
from this fair city
to ever earn his freedom
upon the sands,
a true god of the arena.
l give you Gannicus!
( crowd cheering )
Gannicus! Gannicus! Gannicus!
Gannicus! Gannicus!
Woman:
Fuck me, Gannicus!
Man: Come on, Gannicus,
kill them all!
Why would he do this?
Because he's a man
without honor.
We at last face each other
upon the sands...
as Melitta always feared.
ls it true?
Did you lay with her
the night she left this world?
Oenomaus--
Begin.
We should not have torn
our forces.
lf we had been
with you at the mines--
Even more would lay dead
within its tunnels.
Mistakes were made
on both sides.
Let us place them behind us,
or risk finding them repeated.
( wings fluttering )
We have found something.
Finally the gods show
a fucking favor.
Let us see to what extent.
Bring the others.
Search for weapons.
Something may have been left behind.
A roof over our heads.
Mostly.
We shall take rest,
consider future.
There holds none for you
in my fucking temple.
Apologies.
lt appeared abandoned.
l stand proof it is not.
Return to where you came.
So the gods finally
fuck me to the afterlife.
Care to join me?
We seek only shelter...
nothing more.
Spartacus.
You are Spartacus?
l am.
Then l mistake
fucking for blessing.
( laughing )
This temple has remained
absent worship for many years.
lt does not offer much
in the way of comforts,
but l would share what l have.
Gratitude.
You would trust wine and words
from a Roman shit?
And what are you?
A Gaul, by your
lack of manners?
l am no fucking Gaul.
l am Agron, from the lands
east of the Rhine.
And l am Lucius,
a Roman of the Caelian clan.
A pleasure to make
fucking acquaintance.
Why are you here, Lucius?
l did have more
esteemed lodgings once--
a villa,
land, horses,
a family,
struck from this world
by Sulla's black heart.
Sulla?
He too was a Roman,
yet marched upon
his own people,
punishing any
who dared to defy him.
A slave is so treated.
l have owned them.
lf that be offense enough,
have my life.
Wine's gone anyway.
Your eyes seemed to brighten
when you heard my name--
unexpected from a Roman.
The ones l held to heart
were slaughtered by the same.
They stand no kin to me now.
And yet
the man who
would make them suffer,
l would gladly call brother.
You could not have made speech
before swilling the last of the wine?
( Lucius laughs ) lf l had l known
you were for this temple,
l'd have stocked it
to the fucking rafters.
l thought the lot of you fallen
in the mines of Lucania.
Where have you heard such tales?
ln the streets of Neapolis,
frequented for trading.
The city is afire
with news of your defeat,
the only survivors to be executed
at Varinius's fucking games.
- Survivors?
- Give names.
l know only that three
stand for the sands
and one by word marked
as the Undefeated Gaul.
Crixus?
He yet lives?
Only to see sun
break dawn once more.
The games come to an end
when it sets,
as do the lives of your men.
( footsteps )
Spartacus yet evades death.
While we fucking embrace it.
As l will embrace Naevia
when she is returned to my arms
in the afterlife...
where Melitta awaits you.
l long for reunion
and the answers it will bring.
How you will stir the crowd!
Tales of the prowess
of Gannicus yet fill the air,
rivaling those
of Hercules himself.
His labors were rewarded
with immortality.
Fortunate for you,
l seek more earthly payment.
To be provided upon
completion of your services.
l find myself light of coin.
A few dropped in hand
would anchor purpose.
Of course.
l would not wish to see wind
carry you aloft
short of the appointed hour.
l shall see it done.
lt will be glorious spectacle.
Come. l would present you
to the Magistrate
and Praetor Varinius
himself.
Let them gaze upon
the legend in the arena,
with the rest
of the howling mob.
l am for wine
and the embrace
of questionable women.
How did he fall?
We came upon Spartacus
and his men while giving chase.
The villain himself
delivered grievous injury.
And yet you stand before me,
drawing breath.
l came to your tribune's aid,
pulling him away
to staunch life
flowing from wound.
Noble effort, bearing no fruit.
- Praetor--
- Send word to Senator Albinius.
Spartacus will not be among the slaves
executed at tomorrow's games.
- And the Syrian?
- Oh, he will yet have chance
to afford himself in battle,
in the arena,
to be executed with
the other worthless slaves.
No. Praetor, l beg of you.
Praetor!
Yet another disappointment.
Spartacus evades
poor Gaius once again.
l fear your games will suffer
from the Thracian's absence.
Good Mercato
assures me grand spectacle
to be spoken of for years
throughout the Republic.
l would not have your husband's
failure dampen spirits.
As l would not have him
remain so titled.
The very purpose
of our gathering.
News of your desires
towards loving daughter
lifts heart.
l have invoked the god Hymenaeus
to sanction the union.
His blessing is affirmed.
The gods bestow gift
beyond measure.
Albinius: Yet we must proceed
with caution.
l would not have Gaius
aware of our plans
until presented with dissolution,
lets he make public scene.
Let us take leave
and further discuss how to proceed.
l long for constraints
to be shed
and our fortunes
returned to Rome.
As l long for you by my side,
holding position of wife.
He appears well pleased.
Remove encumbrance
as discussed,
and we will see this
to proper end.
Encumbrance?
l am to untether myself
from unfortunate lineage.
You would see your child
never born?
A necessary thing
to ensure a more worthy heir.
l am in your debt.
Spartacus told me
what you have done for Nasir.
lf it were not for you--
lt's because of me
that he lays near death.
They never should have
come to the mines.
l did what l could to stop them.
Would that you had done more.
Naevia.
The hope of seeing Crixus again
was all that kept me alive.
Each day l begged the gods
to see him to my arms.
And this is how
they fucking answer?
By allowing his touch,
only to be ripped
from it forever?
He would not be swayed
from attempt.
None of them would.
l wish Lucretia
had taken my life.
Then Crixus would not have
to sacrificed his
for something soiled
and ruined.
Spartacus calls for you.
Nasir?
He yet fights.
As do we all.
The Romans would have it
believed otherwise.
Lucius tells of spreading word
that we are all but defeated.
Let them come
and find assumption false.
l would not wait for such a day,
nor see our brothers
fall in the arena.
You would lay attack
on the arena?
Our numbers are low,
more so of men able with sword.
A thing known by Glaber
and his soldiers.
They would never think us
to make attempt.
- For good fucking reason.
- Who is more familiar with the arena
than men who have fought
upon its sands?
What are your thoughts?
These executions
serve as message
that Rome
will smother any flame
that burns against its rule.
l would send message
of our own,
one that will ignite the hearts
of all yet enslaved.
( footsteps )
'Tis a heavy burden--
stilling life that grows inside you.
l had thought deed
of lighter concern.
l do not know why l pause.
A woman will always be moved
to protect her child.
Yet it must be done.
Perhaps it wise
to delay the act.
Your absence at the games
will draw notice.
My absence?
l have forced silphium
on many slaves
to rid the House of Batiatus
of unwanted burden.
You will sicken and bleed
for many days.
l will attest such to your father.
lf he so presses for reason
of staying hand.
You prove wise counsel.
A service l would continue
to provide.
Do you wish to
accompany me to Rome?
l wish only to be at your side
until life leaves from body.
There is yet much
of the past between us.
Let us see
if there is a future.
( door opens )
Guard: Be quick.
( chuckles )
At last she comes.
Other matters have drawn
my attention.
l would see it towards
current fucking plight.
Do you think that l would allow you
to perish upon the sands
after all you have done
for me?
l will break words
with Glaber.
( grunts )
He places blame
for Spartacus
evading capture.
He will not listen to you.
Yet he will heed
the will of the gods,
as he has so graciously
in the past.
l shall whisper of them,
of how you were returned to us
from dark woods for a purpose,
of how the gods
yet have use for you,
as do l.
What would you have
of me now?
A simple task.
There is a red vial
secreted among llithyia's jewelry.
l would see its contents replaced
with water and bitter herb.
l've seen such red vials
within this house before...
- and witnessed their effect.
- And when none are presented,
it will be taken as a sign
that her child must be born.
A task easier seen
by your own hand.
You are close to her
and move freely through the villa.
The risk of discovery
is too great.
llithyia must be given
no reason to doubt me,
or all will fall to ruin.
And how am l
to do such a thing?
Even free of bondage, l am no spirit
able to pass through fucking gate.
Was l not the domina
of this house?
Gates part in remembrance.
You have a way of making a man
invisible as well.
Great spectacle is being made
of the games tomorrow.
llithyia's slaves attend her.
Most of Glaber's men
provide welcome security
to calm nervous city.
lt should not be hard
for a man of your talents
to avoid the remainder.
And if l am discovered?
Do not be.
l will see myself
free of bondage
at any cost.
ls such a thing possible?
l would see it so,
or fall with Crixus in the arena.
lf the gods yet care,
may they speed your return.
Where do we go?
Nasir.
Give me a sword.
l will join you.
l would have you rest
yet a while longer.
This time you stay and l go.
We must move.
The boy cheats death.
Perhaps it is a sign.
We can not rely on omen.
We must take strength
in just cause
and bring it to bear.
You have all heard whispers
of what we attempt.
l would overtake soft voice
with bold words.
We are for the arena in Capua.
Woman: What?
Man: And if you do not return?
Lucius Caelius
knows these lands.
lf we are too long from you,
l would ask that
he show you safe path,
far from the reach of Glaber
and his soldiers.
We have suffered wound and loss.
We have been divided.
Yet we are free--
a thing beyond price...
a thing l would see
condemned brothers
embrace once again
and in the doing of it
spread word to every slave
yet beneath heel
that even the mighty Republic
bleeds when struck!
( crowd cheering )
( cheering )
You fuck like a god.
l would share a cup
to regain sense.
l have not seen you here
before, have l?
l've been many years
from Capua.
What brings return?
l come for the games.
l wish l could see them.
l would trade place.
You stand upon the sands
and l will drink and fuck
until the gods take me.
The sands?
You're Gannicus--
the gladiator
who gained his freedom.
Shadow of the same.
l've never heard of another
who's won the rudis.
May l touch it?
These markings--
they tell of your victories?
They tell of glories
long forgotten.
Why do you carry it,
if it troubles mind?
lt must always remain
at my side,
even in the arena--
proof that l am
no longer a slave...
reminder of choices
made while l was yet one.
Please, Melitta, breathe!
Let us put talk behind us.
l would fall to bed,
wine and the memory
of your thighs
to brace against coming day.
lt is a blessing
to be forever removed
from this fucking house.
May it crumble in our wake.
See them delivered to the arena,
prepared for execution.
Praetor.
Praetor, apologies.
l would have word.
You draw breath
only because Lucretia cautions
the gods yet foretell
of your worth.
Press me,
and see prophecy ignored.
l but wish to fulfill it
this very day.
- ( horse neighs )
- Guard: Ready?
March.
Speak then,
and let us gauge divinity.
My eyes fell upon
most curious sight,
witnessed from my cell--
your wife's slave
stealing through the night,
in her hand
a thing familiar to me,
one l fear
you may have
no knowledge of.
See the litter well stocked
with water and wine.
l would not stand
before Varinius
parched from this fucking heat.
Yes, Domina.
Gaius.
l thought you for the arena
with your men.
Have the gods ever beheld
such beauty?
You flatter.
Leave us.
We will be past
the appointed hour.
They will wait,
as l have waited
for blessings longed for.
'Twill be a glorious day.
One you would see
- Gaius--
- Do not fucking attempt lie!
l know what l hold
and the intent it carries!
Why?
Because you are not
worthy of an heir.
You are not worthy of me.
Have we drifted so far
from the love we once held?
lt is a speck
upon distant shore,
too small to draw notice.
l will hold my child in my arms
and you will play part
of dutiful mother and wife.
l will not.
You will do as your husband
commands!
Then l pray Varinius
gives them with softer voice.
Varinius?
My father dissolves
our marriage
in favor of more
promising opportunity.
l return with him to Rome
at the close of the games.
You conspire against me.
We do what we must
in face of growing
disappointment.
l will have words
with your father.
To what end?
He allowed you my hand
only because l begged
with teary eye,
wet with thoughts of love.
They now stand dry,
a desert deprived of rain.
ls there nothing left
between us?
Memories only.
Yet they too shall fade.
Come,
let us present ourselves
as husband and wife
for the last time.
( crowd cheering )
( shouting )
The crowd has turned
to sour mood.
We can place no blame,
except perhaps upon cause of delay.
Apologies. My husband
found himself
distracted by
unexpected concerns.
Matters of great import then,
to keep honored guest
and all of Capua waiting.
lt was of a pressing nature.
l would condemn such
transgressions to distant past
and turn eye toward
more deserving future.
Such thoughts
kept sleep at bay.
l pray the conclusion of this day
brings you comfort,
as you have brought to all
touched by your divine presence.
Let us begin,
and see it come to pass.
- Woman: What are we waiting for?
- Man: Get on with it!
Citizens of Capua!
We gather this day
to witness an end
to the storied games
of your humble editor
Publius Varinius.
And in their closing,
know that l have not foregone
the mores
of noonday execution
but rather find tradition
exalted to position of the Primus.
And each contest
that leads us to it
shall determine which men
stand worthy
to deliver
the justice of Rome.
( cheering )
Let spectacles of blood
no longer hold pause.
Enter Mycter-- Samnite!
Enter Abiron-- Murmillo!
( screams )
May the gods bless us with a day
forever etched upon memory.
Begin!
Crowd:
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
( screams )
A display
to shake the heavens.
You possess a gift for
the pairing of gladiators, Mercato.
Have you ever considered
plying such trade in Rome?
You honor me, Praetor.
Yet my fortunes
are tied to Capua.
ls it your intent to spirit away
everyone of note?
l have thoughts toward
but a few.
Your husband's eyes
betray darkening storm.
He has made
unfortunate discovery
within my bedchambers.
Unfortunate indeed.
Varinius: We reach final contest
before the Primus.
Who shall prove himself a god,
worthy to take vengeance
against the enemies of Rome?
Enter Masonius, Hoplomachus!
( crowd cheering )
Enter Strabo, Murmillo!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
( crowd continues chanting )
( crowd cheering )
( roars )
A fine showing.
Magistrate: To be forever remembered
by adoring crowd,
as will the name Varinius,
who bestows such
generous gifts.
lndeed, he shall never be
forgotten.
Same cannot be said
of all men.
( fanfare )
Lucretia:
The executions begin.
( crowd cheering )
Crowd:
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill! Kill!
Two against an army?
l do not care for your odds.
You will see them
towards our favor.
You are clear
to your purpose?
We will see it done.
lt gives strength
knowing you stand with me.
We must work quickly.
lf any of you hold faith
in any gods,
now would be time
to fucking entreat them.
Quick. Quick.
"Hannibal stands at our gates"--
a phrase used to invoke fear
among the children of Rome,
a specter
of the Carthaginian animal...
For many years
l have dreamed
of my return to the arena.
lt is an honor to stand beside you
upon the sands.
Varinius: Hannibal passed from this life
at the end of a Roman sword!
Guard: Your time has come.
Varinius: A fate that will one day be
shared by the rebel Spartacus!
( crowd cheering )
They give us swords
absent fucking edge.
Absent hope of victory as well.
Then let us prove them fools
for giving us swords at all.
( crowd jeering )
Boo!
Man:
Kill those bastards!
( distant crowd shouting )
Man: You'll die, fuckers!
( laughs )
Woman: l want to see
your insides, prisoners!
( guard shouts )
Gladiator: This day grants us
undeserved honor.
l have longed to share the sands
with Gannicus--
the greatest champion
ever to enter the arena.
There stand no champions here,
only men and their fates.
Varinius: Yet who shall lead
the forces of Rome?
Who deserves such storied mantle?
- You're from the House of Batiatus.
- Varinius: There stands but one.
A lifetime ago.
And now you take
to the sands
to claim the lives
of your brothers?
Gannicus: lf they must fall,
l would see them to honorable death...
Varinius: A true god
of the arena.
...given by one who
yet holds them to heart.
Varinius:
l give you Gannicus!
( crowd cheering )
Gannicus!
Woman:
Fuck me, Gannicus!
Man: Kill them, Gannicus!
Kill them all!
Crowd: Gannicus!
Gannicus! Gannicus!
Gannicus! Gannicus! Gannicus!
l begin to question
fucking plan.
We are committed.
Steel nerve and be ready for--
( shouts )
She was my wife...
and you my brother.
He is mine.
This is the place.
You there!
Veronius, send for more men!
Halt!
( screaming )
The Gaul finally nears his end.
A fate long overdue.
They take too long.
We must wait
or see effort fail.
l never wanted to feel
what l felt for her.
l never wanted any of this.
Rhaskos!
- Fuck.
- Wait.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
lt's not working fast enough.
The chains--
wrap them around the supports.
Boo!
Yeah!
Pull!
l will send you
to her arms, brother.
Pull!
( screaming )
Now!
What's happening?
Let's get out of here!
Clear way!
Clear fucking way!
Mercato!
l would see us gone
from here, brother.
Kill them!
Give hand!
Spartacus.
( screaming )
Cossutius!
The path is clear!
Spartacus once again
makes fool of you.
Your days in the Senate
have found their end.
Spartacus, we must move!
No. We must find Oenomaus.
This way.
( wheezing, coughing )
Gaius.
Help me, please.
l'm not the fool
you and your daughter think me.
Help me with him.
( loud crashing )
Go. l will follow.
Spartacus.
l have had my fill of games.
Let us leave this arena forever.
Citizens!
Citizens, calm yourselves!
Gather your fucking men.
Come. l would see you safe
to the villa.
Gaius, where is my father?
He has fallen
at the hands of Spartacus.
Shh.
We will survive this
together...
as husband and wife.
( theme music playing )
字幕来源于互联网\N美剧控☆昆特斯\N欧美史诗大片推荐,请上\Nwww.kuntesi.com