Gannicus:
See end to vengeance.
Take the life of Glaber's woman
as he took the life of yours.
The child is yours!
Lucretia: You sought Praetor
Varinius' affections once.
Send message,
and you could yet gain them.
Do you not see it?
The gods have lead me
upon path to Gaius,
as their will
has removed llithyia from it.
Have you lost mind?
Lucretia:
lt's your brother's, is it not?
- How did you come by this?
- Hidden amongst Ashur's treasures.
Yet the villain
moves only upon command
of Gaius Claudius Glaber.
Crixus:
Glaber agrees to terms.
Spartacus:
l am for Atella. To see it done.
He chose vengeance against me
over your life.
You let me live?
Do not think it a kindness.
( theme music playing )
( liquid splashing )
( sighs )
( blow strikes )
Lugo...
open fucking eyes.
To see what?
Wake when trees attack,
little man.
- ( grunts )
- Romans!
- Fucking Romans! Move!
- ( overlapping clamor )
- We're under attack!
My sword!
Enough!
( all gasping )
( woman speaks )
Stand down!
( man speaking )
Agron:
This was but fucking test?
lf it had not been,
you would all
be for the afterlife.
We will not be taken
unaware next time.
l would see words
forged into action.
Rise, and take morning meal.
The day ahead of us
will be long.
lt causes worry
to stir and find you
gone from our bed.
l could not remain there.
The mind churns with thoughts
of those taken too soon from us
and the monsters who tore them
from loving embrace.
We have both suffered
immeasurable loss.
We must take comforts
from what we have found...
...in each other.
l have moved foolishly
and with regret
that l have denied
you opportunity
to properly
mourn your wife.
She is but fleeting memory...
one that shall fade...
as the night mist caressed
by morning sun.
( gasps )
llithyia.
( rushing water echoes )
( soft distorted speaking )
She lives.
She will survive it.
What of the child?
lt yet moves within her.
- ( normal sound resumes)
- She wakes.
Out.
Are you of this world?
Take hand...
and know that l am flesh.
Leave us.
l thought you
gone from this world.
As did l.
Yet the gods have seen me
returned to your arms.
lt is a blessing.
One shared by our child.
The warmth
of the life inside me,
it gave strength and comfort
when all seemed lost.
How did you escape?
l could not.
He let me go.
Spartacus released you?
He said that taking my life
would have no meaning.
And where were you held?
l do not know.
l was bound
and stripped of sight.
How did Gannicus
carry you to him?
By horse for part of a day.
By foot through woods
for hours more.
And you saw nothing
of their camp?
Only the dank hole
they kept me.
Dug into the earth
Or made of stone and wood?
What does it fucking matter?
lt was made of stone,
with beams of wood,
scribblings carved
into the rock.
- What did they say?
- l do not know.
They were faded
and broken.
ln what tongue
were they etched?
They appeared Greek.
Why am l not
in our bedchambers?
- llithyia--
- l thought it a dream.
Seppia in your arms?
Your hands upon her?
Spartacus was right.
My death would not
have held meaning.
You do not love me.
And you greet this
as revelation?
Time and again,
you tore my heart from my chest.
ls it a wonder it now
stands empty in your regard?
ls there nothing left
between us?
l once asked the same of you.
Do you recall your reply?
Have l not suffered
enough for it?
l would have life as it was,
with my husband beside me.
The man you speak of
no longer exists.
Then what stands before me
assuming his manner and form?
A monster...
rough-hewn
by unfortunate events...
and given breath
by necessity.
( overlapping clamoring )
We cannot defend the temple
if we are at odds
with one another.
Give Lugo a warrior
to share watch,
not little man
with little balls.
My balls did not allow breach.
Your eyes were closed
in pursuit of dreams.
You fell to slumber?
And you blame Nasir,
you lazy shit?
Turn effort
from defending your boy,
and look upon
your own failings.
Then let us relive the moment
and see different
fucking result.
The Romans will come.
( growls )
And if they find us divided,
we will fall before them.
- Words of meaning.
- She speaks the truth.
What would you have us do?
Try not to get
your head fucking bashed.
Bold words from one
who tumbled so quickly.
l was absent fucking sword!
Why does little man
have sword, and not Lugo?
We cannot face the Romans
with fucking sticks.
Then l will teach you the bow.
- ( laughter )
- We are from east of the Rhine.
- We fight with fucking steel.
- We must use what we have.
She asks why
you let llithyia go
when Glaber did not
trade weapons as promised.
A thing l have also wondered.
Taking her life would not
have gained us what we need.
lt would only have served
misplaced vengeance.
We are better than this.
We are better than the Romans.
Oenomaus,
Gannicus, see everyone
to guarded position.
We will train against assault
by light of day
and attempt to elevate
night's low defeat.
Let us see it done.
l have no need of aid.
Lugo, Nasir,
take position upon wall.
Donar, Nemetes,
Lydon, Saxa, fall to my side!
l fear result will be the same
in light of day.
We are not a fist,
but fingers twitching
absent single purpose.
Oenomaus:
Lugo, form one.
- My words crash upon ear...
- Begin.
...but fail to pierce heart.
Then we must stab deeper.
Perhaps punishment
for those who fail
in the day's training?
You cannot forge
trust and loyalty
at the ends of a whip,
as the Romans believe.
Then what would you use?
Soft kisses
and whispers of love?
Gather Fulco and Harudes.
There is a thing
l would have you do.
What are your thoughts?
To see fingers
joined in single purpose.
( laughs )
lt is a thing of much regret.
Lucius is no longer among us.
A loss keenly felt.
Yet we must move
from wounded heart,
turn towards
what must be done.
l would have
you train more archers,
as you suggested.
ls that all
you would have from me?
Gather your bow.
You have not slept by my side.
You do not speak,
unless to give order.
How long do you seek
to punish me?
lt is not my intent.
Yet result stands the same.
- You turn from me.
- You turned from yourself
when you made attempt
upon llithyia,
an act that would have
stained you forever.
l thought only to save you
from the same.
You thought to save
what we had.
Had?
Can you no longer
find comfort in my arms?
Can you find such in mine?
Yes...
if you would but give me
more of your heart.
l have given all that remains.
lt is not enough.
No.
lt is not.
l felt it
since the very start,
an absence in your touch,
no matter how warm,
an emptiness.
l turned from it,
certain one day
l would be able to fill it.
The gods themselves
would fail such effort.
Will it move you...
one day when you see me
in the arms of another?
l will know the sting of it...
yet l pray
you find in them...
what you could not
find in mine.
Let us see to training
and what must be done.
Spartacus' voice:
He does not love you.
- llithyia's voice: You let me live?
- Do not think it a kindness.
llithyia?
( sobs )
The gods have heard my prayers
to return you to my arms.
You alone offer such embrace.
l have not taken food nor rest
since you were torn from them.
Nor would l have,
until l had followed you
to suspected fate.
Would that all
held me as close to heart.
Well, you're the reason
that mine still beats,
you and the blessing you carry.
l have never
considered it as such.
Yet in that final moment,
when l thought life
was forfeit,
l felt a great sadness,
not for myself,
but for innocent child,
doomed to suffer
for the mistakes of the mother.
We have both made many.
The child is Spartacus'.
He gave seed
the night you maneuvered me
into laying with him.
llithyia--
l no longer
lay blame at your feet.
lt was my hands that forced you
to seek vengeance,
my choices
that have cast me adrift...
clinging to a woman
l once hated
and a child l unreasonably
grow to love.
To feel such hope and such joy
blossoming within you,
that's the rarest
of all flowers,
regardless of why it blooms.
( footsteps )
Apologies, l--
l did not know you were--
Apologies.
She moves to assume
my place at Gaius' side.
One day, she will see him
for what he truly is.
Oh, her eyes
have already been opened.
Seppius was not murdered
by his slaves,
but by your husband.
Gaius?
A thing which l discovered
through most unfortunate manner
and shared only with Seppia.
Yet she stays
within this house...
body offered to the man
that so wounded her?
To leave now would only serve
to arouse suspicion.
Yet she burns with thoughts
of avenging her brother.
l would see such embers
given breath...
and in resulting flames...
my child and l
to rise from the ashes
of ill-fated past.
They traveled by horse,
then on foot through forest
for several hours,
yet she does not know
what direction she traveled in.
Man:
Open the gates!
Spartacus has attacked
the mine of Lucania here,
the arena in Capua,
port of Neapolis,
and attempted to make trade
in Atella.
The curve
would suggest they move
outward from a central position,
this region.
Yet a vast area.
Did she mention anything more
that may be of use?
Only that she was kept
beneath ground
in a chamber
with faded lettering,
perhaps Greek in origin.
Hmm.
Apologies.
He's a Roman--
Lucius Caelius...
from Vesuvius.
( exhales, chuckles )
See yourself to wine and food.
His efforts bear fruit?
Plucked from Spartacus'
own garden.
His overly ripe friend
goes by name of Lucius Caelius,
known by those questioned
to frequent market
in Neapolis and Atella
and to dwell
in the shadows of Vesuvius.
Still too vast an area.
Made smaller by your wife's
discerning eyes.
There is a temple
near mountain's foot,
long abandoned,
erected many years past
by Greek hands.
Then we march at nightfall
and by dawn's light
see an end to Spartacus.
l would urge
no small amount of caution.
lf memory serve,
there's a wall
protecting this temple.
Spartacus and his men will
surely have fortified position.
Then we shall bring to bear
the fiery might of Rome
and see defenses fall
in advance of the man himself.
Prepare your men.
And l would have you
at my side
to share in glorious moment.
A great honor.
lt shames me
to seek reward beyond it,
yet hard desires
turn reason a fool.
You are many things, Syrian,
but do not expect me
to believe you a fool.
Give voice to your desire.
See it considered.
( yelling )
Nemetes,
you attack
before command is given.
We must remain hidden
until the Romans are drawn in.
You would see them
breach the wall?
We would see them trapped,
you simple fuck.
Like fish in a net.
Wagon approaches.
Nasir: Agron leads it.
He has attacked another one,
without command.
No. He acts upon my orders.
Towards what purpose?
To secure
what we desperately need.
( laughter )
l barely know the man
absent furrowed brow.
He is not a man
of drunken pursuits.
His brow may not reveal it,
but there is
yet intent upon mind.
lt lifts heart
to hear voices
raised in spirit...
to see us bonded...
( cheering )
...not by brand,
not by homeland,
but by an ideal
that every man...
every woman
should be born, should live,
and should die
with the taste of freedom
forever upon their lips.
- ( cheering )
- Yeah!
Yet if we are
to defeat the Romans,
we must put aside
our differences
and come together as one.
Let us have sport,
pairing those
of you with ill feelings
against your equals,
and let us see
if thirst for victory
triumphs petty quarrel.
lntent is revealed.
- Donar!
- ( cheering )
Nemetes!
- Spartacus: Take position.
- Lugo!
- Yeah!
Nasir! You will face them.
We win if you keep
out of way, little man.
- ( laughs )
- Don't fucking call me that.
( yells )
( laughs )
Begin!
lt is a thing of beauty,
is it not...
what a man
may accomplish
if mind is set
to purpose?
Yet there's something missing.
Freedom.
To see treasures put to use
absent constraint,
to live, knowing
each choice made...
( scoffs )
( laughs )
Spartacus and l stand together
in such desires.
Then you find yourself
in low company.
Soon to be elevated.
Ashur has done the impossible
and discovered
where the dreaded villain
secrets himself,
and in reward...
Glaber bestows
deepest wish...
upon me.
He sets you free?
After we take Spartacus
at Vesuvius.
Yet releasing me from bond
is but a taste of more...
sumptuous meal.
One which you
shall feast upon alone.
After Spartacus is defeated,
llithyia will return to Rome
with her husband,
and trusted friend
will be at her side.
l fear llithyia
must find a new one.
You will remain here
to assume mantle
of loving wife.
Glaber will not allow this.
He more than allows it.
He gives union blessing
and presents gift
of this ludus
in recognition
of honored service.
He gives you
my husband's legacy?
We shall forge a new one,
my love,
as husband and wife,
and together...
...we shall see the noble rise
of the House of Ashur.
( whimpers )
Have the men equipped,
ready to travel by sunrise.
See that it happens.
You were able to acquire
what is needed?
Move! Hup!
They are upon road
from Neapolis.
Meet them, and hasten arrival.
l will hold no delay
in marching south.
Varinius: l would advise
a different course.
l have been dispatched
with message from the Senate.
You are to cease
pursuit of Spartacus
and return to Rome immediately.
l am a praetor of the Republic.
The Senate holds no power
to make such demands of me.
True, they do not.
They have only the power
to recommend a path of action,
one only a man
with no intent to rise
above current position
would ignore.
And they send words
through the man
who conspires
to claim my wife?
l am hardly alone
in such ambitions, am l?
Troubling news
has lit upon ear
that Spartacus has seized
what l could not.
You do not know
of what you speak.
And you are
an incompetent fool
to allow your wife
to be taken by a slave.
llithyia: Taken?
llithyia?
lt appears
you have been misinformed.
l have been taken only to bed,
my child causing
unexpected discomfort
in waning months
of pregnancy.
Did it also cause
the bruise upon your cheek?
No, it did not.
( laughs )
The fault was mine.
A misplaced step
as l was coming from the bath.
You should choose footing
more carefully.
As you should choose
your words.
Return home, Gaius,
and tend to your wife
before yet another man
makes attempt upon her.
l shall take my leave
when Spartacus falls.
A task long overdue
in its completion.
Yet now within grasp.
l march to Vesuvius
and an end to the man.
Vesuvius?
ls that where he hides?
lt is of no concern to you.
The Senate believes otherwise.
l've been appointed
to assume your place
with an army of worth
and bring Spartacus to justice.
And if l refuse to step aside?
lt is a choice
you are free to make,
but one that would end
all hope of rising
from the shit
you have mired yourself in.
Save what little worth
your name yet holds,
and set path towards Rome.
Varinius!
Thank the gods
you received my message!
And l respond to it,
only to find llithyia
safely within these walls.
- Spartacus freed her.
- Why would he show mercy
to the wife of the man
that hunts him?
l make no attempt to understand
the mind of a slave.
Your time instead spent
inventing tales of abduction.
Does what you write of
your brother hold similar merit?
Everything l have
told you is true.
Gaius took the life
of my brother.
And what evidence do you claim
to dare place charge
against a praetor of Rome?
Seppius' bracelet,
a mirror of my own,
found hidden
among the belongings
of a man loyal to--
A fucking bracelet
is all you hold?
You stupid little girl.
Please do not turn from this.
Gaius must pay
for what he's done.
l hold no love for the man,
yet to make accusation based
upon the air and teary eye
would serve no purpose.
Nor will further words.
( cheering )
Yeah!
You lower guard
just before launching attack.
Advice gained too late.
- We lose.
- Yeah!
But little man
fight like giant!
( laughs )
( cheering continues )
Drink and contest--
a clever strategy
to forge necessary bonds.
And l would see more follow.
Battle well fought.
( cheering )
Let us have new contest!
Agron!
( cheering )
Crixus!
Get him, Agron!
He's too fast for you, Agron!
Take position.
- ( murmuring )
- ( laughter )
Gannicus!
- Huh?
- ( cheering )
Oenomaus!
Stand against them.
- ( cheering )
- Yeah!
Yeah!
We can easily best them
if we fight as one.
Hold this, you fuck.
Do not drink it.
- Come...
- Come on, Oenomaus!
...and do what is necessary.
- ( laughs )
- Yes!
( cheering )
Ready?
Begin!
Naevia: Come on, Crixus!
Teach him who
the true champion is, Crixus!
lt astounds to witness
the change in you.
The world itself
can reverse course
when moved by loving hands.
A blessing...
to hold each other
in such regard.
As Spartacus holds you.
No longer.
( yells )
( laughs )
( cheering )
That was well put.
You almost had them.
Almost.
Agron.
You fought well
for a simple fuck
from the east of the Rhine.
As did you
for a shit-eating Gaul.
( both laugh )
Let us share drink
and balm wounded pride.
( laughter echoes )
Lucretia:
To suffer the sting of loss
absent course
to right what has been done.
l sent for Varinius,
as you prompted...
only to have him
shun word
and touch.
You are no longer a girl,
unblemished by the world.
You're a woman now.
And our hands
shape the fates
when those
of men tremble.
lt is l who tremble.
The thought of Gaius' hands
upon me.
( crying )
There, there.
Shh.
lt is such desire...
that presents opportunity.
You suggest the impossible.
l suggest only
that you consider the years
unfolding before you,
every moment swollen
with the knowledge
that Gaius Claudius Glaber
lives out his life
in the privileged lap of Rome...
while your brother
is forever denied breath.
lt should not be so.
lt should not.
Everything l held dear
was taken from me as well,
this house,
my husband,
promise of a child.
The things
that have been done to us
cannot stand unanswered.
To allow it...
would be to turn from those
we claim to have loved.
ls there no other course?
lf you wish to see
your brother's murder avenged...
blood must be spilled.
She is moved towards deed?
l believe it so.
Are you certain
this is what you desire?
lf Gaius is not moved
by pleading word,
then l will have
blood and death
and, in the bringing of it,
my life returned to me.
Seppia: ls it true?
That you depart for Rome?
l'm left with little choice.
lt is a terrible thing
to be stripped of such.
Made more grievous
by hand that removes it.
You speak of Varinius?
He once more makes attempt
to claim
what is rightfully mine.
As Spartacus claimed
my brother's life?
An unfortunate tragedy.
One that yet demands justice.
The Senate appoints
Varinius the task.
( metal jingles )
l do not have faith in him
to take the life of the man
responsible
for grievous injury.
Nor l.
Yet we must turn
from such thought
and seek comfort in the hands
of warm embrace.
Your fucking hands ripped
my brother from this world,
and mine shall see you from it.
Gaius.
l cast you aside.
Yet you save my life?
You are my husband.
We cannot be what we were.
Then let us be what we are.
We have done terrible things
to each other.
l would see such venom
turned outward
to those truly deserving of it,
Seppia,
the Senate,
and the man they dispatch
to steal your glory.
You would move
against Varinius?
We are both monsters, Gaius.
Let us be so together
and seize the fucking heavens.
l shall march to Vesuvius,
see it done.
Pause but a moment.
l have been too long absent
you inside me.
Forgive me.
l lose myself in the moment.
No.
lt is l who have been lost...
and your touch
that guides me home.
( all singing )
♪ And lift your sword ♪
♪ Drain your wine ♪
♪ Drain your cock ♪
♪ Dawn comes too soon ♪
♪ Night flees too soon ♪
♪ So lift fucking cup ♪
♪ Lift fucking cup... ♪
l still believe you will see us all
to untimely end.
Man:
♪ Drain my cock ♪
♪ Drain my cock. ♪
Yet it will be
a glorious fucking death.
( laughs )
The signal.
Glaber.
( overlapping chatter )
Glaber commands from the rear,
a coward's position.
He will advance his troops
in tight formation,
intending to overpower.
lt is the Roman way.
We will teach them ours.
( cheering )
( yelling )
- Soldier: Advance!
- ( yelling )
- Fall back to the temple!
- Advance!
- Fulco!
- Hold the line!
- There are too many!
- Move!
Praetor!
The rebels are in retreat.
( yelling )
( neighs )
Stage one.
Two.
Three. Advance!
( yelling )
Crixus: Now!
( neighs )
You are not the man l seek.
Lay down your arms!
Do it!
Now we have steel.
All: Yeah!
Gather their weapons.
- Yeah!
- Varinius.
l owe you a debt of blood,
for Acer and Rhaskos.
And we shall see it paid
after answer is given.
Where is Glaber?
- ( catapult releases )
- Spartacus.
Fuck!
( yelling )
( yelling orders )
Pull!
lgnite!
Push!
On the ready!
Ready!
On my signal!
Load!
- lgnite!
- Release!
Again!
- ( yelling )
- We have to move!
( groans )
Fall back! lnto the tunnel!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Crixus!
Go! We'll follow!
Oenomaus!
( screaming )
Move! Move!
Agron!
Move! Go!
- Move!
- Go!
Move!
Go! Come on!
Quickly!
- Move!
- Keep moving!
( woman screams )
( rebels screaming )
No. There are too many of them.
The mountain pass! Hurry!
But there is no other path down.
We'll be trapped.
There's no choice!
We must move! Go!
( marching )
Crixus: Spartacus.
Go! Move!
This way! This way!
( wind blowing )
ls there no other way
to gain the mountain?
None, save for the narrow path
they escaped upon.
Scores of men were lost
in attempted pursuit.
Foolish endeavor.
They now hold the high ground.
We've lost advantage.
You would let them go free?
No.
l would let them feast...
on mud and rock.
And when hunger and madness
drive them from their perch...
we shall kill them all.
( theme music playing )
字幕来源于互联网\N美剧控☆昆特斯\N欧美史诗大片推荐,请上\Nwww.kuntesi.com