( panting )
( neighs )
( men yelling )
( horse snorts )
( neighs )
Come back!
- ( neighs )
- Behind you!
( neighs )
l believe the man's dead.
( laughs )
Agron!
Supplies. Be quick.
Take anything of value.
( wind blowing )
Spartacus, you leave
his cock to the sun?
No.
l send a message...
to an old friend.
Glaber:
Pompey was a fool
to engage Sertorius
absent support.
When has Pompey
ever delayed action
in favor of reason?
Advancing in years,
yet ever the adolescent butcher.
Where youth plummets,
maturity may soar.
Rome will lose all of Hispania
if Pompey's numbers
are not shored against the renegade.
And who would lead such a force
to glorious accolade?
Freshly minted praetor, perhaps?
l serve the Republic, Marcus.
We will take arms
against her enemies
if so commanded.
The embellished robes
of a praetor not yet to wrinkle,
and yet he speaks of war
and laurels.
l speak only
of pressing matters.
We need not tread foreign soil
to find them, do we, Varinius?
Not when Spartacus
and his mongrels
continue to evade capture.
The man is no longer
bound to my concerns.
More of young Seppius's men
were slaughtered
on the road outside Capua.
He sends word to me that one
of the fallen bore your name
carved into his chest.
An unfortunate tether.
Albinius:
Quickly to be severed.
Cossutius awaits my attentions.
Apologies to your daughter,
that l could not linger
to gaze upon her.
Disappointment
to be tempered
with promise
of future visit, hmm?
Come. Let us break meal.
The consuls
will present a motion
dispatching you
to Capua at once.
This is a simple tumultus,
Albinius,
undeserving the attentions
of a praetor.
You brought the Thracian
to Roman soil, Gaius.
You granted patronage
to that grinning shit Batiatus
a breath before his house
fell to massacre,
a massacre my daughter
barely fucking escaped!
Varinius lends his support
to Seppius.
lf he's the one to bring
Spartacus to justice,
then that victory will be used
to embarrass you.
Attend to this,
or see yourself rise
no further within the Senate.
( rats squeaking )
( men grunting )
Man:
Don't lower your sword.
( grunting continues )
Eight more Romans
sent to the afterlife!
( cheering )
Peirastes!
Replace wood with steel
for those who are ready.
Vitus, Pyrrhus, Lysandros,
divide these among you
according to skill,
and ready the rest
for demonstration.
l will kill many Romans.
Of that, l have no doubt.
Return to training.
Spartacus, we need food,
not more weapons.
Steel and coin
are all they carried.
( laughter )
- Whoo!
- ( overlapping chatter )
Oh, good.
My fish supper.
Crixus's men fare better.
Rhaskos.
Where is Crixus?
He seeks Marcellus,
the cunt peddler.
( laughter )
Your men have done well
for themselves.
See everyone to equal portion.
Fuck!
Let the rabbits
fend for themselves.
You have more than enough.
Gained by blood and risk.
What do they do but lay about?
Divide what you have.
l will not ask again.
Fucking Gauls.
Rhaskos is a selfish fool,
unable to see
beyond his own desires.
Spartacus:
No one will go hungry tonight.
That is all that matters.
And tomorrow?
Will bring death
to yet more Romans.
l would see all of them
struck down...
yet not at the cost
of your life.
l have proven
troublesome to kill.
( laughs )
There is no one
that stands your equal.
Hmm.
Yet for those less skilled,
moving towards
the mountains in the east
would be sorely welcome.
Game is plentiful there
and Roman numbers sparse.
lt would be wise.
Then why do we stay?
What holds us here,
so near Capua and the threat--
Spartacus.
l hear you wish
to command my men.
No.
Simply to remind them
of what is just.
You would have done the same,
had you been present.
l shall have words with them.
They would be better received
from your lips.
You were in town again.
You risk discovery.
l was not seen,
except by Marcellus,
and he will never speak of it.
Did his blood bear fruit?
A name.
Trebius.
The slaver?
Spartacus:
He will point us towards her?
Marcellus revealed that he
brokered deal of Naevia.
Where do we find him?
He frequents Capua upon
each moon to trade his wares
and to wet his cock
at Arminius's brothel.
News to lift the heart.
lt remains firmly bound
until Naevia is back in my arms.
l will have those words now.
Crixus.
Have you had sight of Doctore?
The ludus was his life's blood.
To lay eyes upon those
who have spilled it,
it would salt mortal wound.
- ( cheering )
- ( yells )
( screams )
You fight like a woman!
Fucking kill him!
( booing )
( groaning )
A poor showing,
even for the lesser games
of the Vulcanalia.
Apologies, Magistrate.
These were the best
that could be procured.
The crowd demands spectacle,
Mercato.
Hmm?
They must be distracted,
lest the city fall
to ill temper and panic.
Gladiators and games
while Spartacus and
his murdering horde roam free.
Your brother has the matter
well in hand, Seppia.
Words of comfort
to the eight of his men
slaughtered this morning.
Eight?
( crowd cheering )
Yeah!
Apologies.
Pressing business
conspired to delay me.
ls it true, Seppius?
Eight more of your men,
fallen to Spartacus?
- ( giggles )
- A thing of little note.
Spartacus will soon
be brought to terms.
And our beloved
cousin Sextus avenged.
Or you to join him,
leaving me woefully unattended.
What form of brother would l be
to abandon such cherished blood?
( giggles )
Would that Batiatus yet lived
to feel the sting of blame
properly braced.
Spartacus and his shits will be
put to grass soon enough.
l have already
sent dispatch to Rome
for aid in the matter.
Perhaps you can secure
better entertainment as well.
The current offerings bore
beyond the telling.
( cheering )
( gasping )
( groans )
( jeering, booing )
Crowd: No! No! No!
No! No! No! No!
A poor showing.
( cheering )
l have nothing of worth.
We seek only words.
l am absent them as well.
You were Batiatus's man,
were you not?
You are mistaken.
No, l saw him
when he yet commanded
the sands of the arena.
l was there in Pompeii
the day he faced Theokoles
and barely lived to speak of it.
Oenomaus, he was called.
lt is fortunate you are not him.
The man stands accused
of turning upon his dominus,
the reward for his capture
a substantial sum,
toward Spartacus yet higher.
lf he were to be revealed,
a man such as you could...
continue not being himself.
As l said,
l have nothing of worth.
A lesser sum, then.
( screams )
Apologies.
You are not Batiatus' man.
( gurgles )
( dog barks )
Spartacus:
You should not be outside.
l wanted to see the moon.
Janus loves to gaze upon it.
Varro would hoist him
upon his shoulders,
and he would stretch
his hands out,
attempting to wrest it
from the heavens.
Perhaps one day he shall.
But not upon
his father's shoulders.
Janus is yet too young
for memory to take proper hold.
l doubt he would recall
the sight of me now.
You are his mother.
Years would not lessen
such a bond.
He will burst
as sun through clouds
at the sight of you.
l have dreamt of nothing else
since our parting.
A lopsided grin,
eyes promising mischief.
l've seen it many times...
on his father.
lt was what drew me to him.
l fell to love the crooked bend
of Varro's lips
long before the man himself.
As did l.
Mira speaks of the mountains
to the east.
l have thoughts
towards dispatching men
to hunt for game.
Your brother tends to Janus
not far from there, does he not?
The moon within closer reach.
l would shorten the distance.
You think l have not longed
to have it so?
To be far from all of this?
l am branded fugitivus
with the rest of you.
What life could l offer my son
beneath such shadow?
None...
within the Republic.
All the coin l have relieved
of the Romans since our escape--
enough to buy you
and your son passage
far from these shores.
Spartacus--
Varro's last words
were of you and Janus,
that l see you cared for.
lt need not have been spoken.
Send word to Crescentia
that l must move our midday meal
to later in the week.
And respond to Varis' request
for our presence
at his celebration.
We will not be attending.
( giggles )
l know you
do not care for the man,
yet he is well connected.
We must make appearance.
Your father
would have it otherwise.
He dispatches me to Capua
to deal with Spartacus.
- l will have word with him.
- He is set upon it.
You are a praetor, Gaius.
Hunting errant slaves
is beneath you.
Yet it must be done.
But l promise
we will return to Rome
well before our child
enters this world.
We?
You will accompany me,
of course.
l will not.
Out.
l am bound to the house
of Batiatus by patronage,
granted only
to bury knowledge
of the blood
staining your hands.
What happened to Licinia
was an accident.
She was the cousin
of Marcus Crassus!
She was a fucking bitch!
All who knew of the deed
speak no more.
Let us put it behind us.
l intend to.
Now make preparations.
We leave for Capua
to put an end
to the curse of Spartacus.
You believe
the words of Marcellus,
bleated from tongue
with sword to neck?
Crixus moves on Arminius
and his place of whores,
and l will be at his side.
So we follow
the fucking Gaul now?
l swore aid in the matter.
You did not.
l would not think less
if you stayed from it.
l am with you.
You had me at whores.
Avoid unnecessary risk
and provoking words
towards the Gauls.
( man laughs )
( man coughs )
Was he swayed?
Have you met the man?
Taking such a large force
to the city is foolish.
As are all things
in the pursuit of a woman.
Peirastes leads
the hunt for game.
He will see you safely
to your son's arms,
from where you have been
too long absent.
See your boy to a man,
that l may one day greet him
as a brother.
l will tell Janus of you,
of the man who loved his father
above all others.
She takes to foot?
Long overdue.
As are many things this night.
This is not your fight,
Spartacus.
l gave my word.
Blood and honor,
it yet speaks to the man.
Then let us split darkness
with the cries of Romans.
( music playing )
( women laughing,
squealing )
( man shrieks )
( woman laughs )
( man yelling )
( laughter )
( screams )
( all screaming )
Go!
Trebius!
( screams )
( gasping )
Where is Trebius?
Where?
( women sobbing )
- Get off the fucking floor!
- No!
Get off the fucking floor,
bitch!
( screams )
( spits )
- ( chuckles )
- ( screaming )
Trebius.
l would have words.
l would not.
Raah!
( metal ringing )
Hah!
No!
- Your man?
- More guards!
We need--
Trebius. You fucking cunt!
Agron!
This is the Roman shit
that sold me and Duro to Batiatus.
My brother would be alive
if it were not for him.
He knows the whereabouts
of Naevia.
We will take him and go.
He will not last.
( groans )
l need but a moment.
You shall have it.
The man meets his end.
That is all that matters.
( men grunting )
- ( metal ringing )
- Man: Go!
( sobbing )
You brokered the sale of a woman
from the house of Batiatus,
dark of skin,
the mark of the domina
upon the back of her shoulder.
Where is she?
Fuck yourself.
l'm already dead.
( groans )
There is life in you yet.
Speak, and see it
ended quickly.
( gasping )
Spartacus: South?
There are villas and farms
far from the city.
And Naevia was sold
to one of them?
No. She was handed
from dominus to dominus,
a gift from Batiatus
to secure favor
on his campaign
for fucking aedile.
These places you speak of,
how heavily are they guarded?
lt would not matter
if the gods stood watch.
How many villas are there
in the south?
Over what spread of distance?
How will you know if Naevia's
even located in one of them?
Only a few are owned
by men of note,
cocks Batiatus would have sucked
to further his cause.
We'd be exposed,
in the open.
We must proceed
with caution.
( sighs )
You advising caution?
The tempest shouts
for the breeze to calm itself!
What good will
your death be to Naevia
if we do not pause to think?
She has been
from my arms too long.
l do not have time
to sit and ponder.
None of us do now.
What is your meaning?
With his last breath,
Trebius frothed of Rome
and the death that has been
dispatched from her bosom
to wash us away
in rivers of blood.
Soldiers.
Arriving with the sun.
Who leads them?
( neighs )
The city is in a panic.
Scores were slaughtered
in the raid against Arminius.
Halt!
See the men fed and rested.
Squads to sweep the countryside
by nightfall.
Your will, Praetor.
Fall out! Break supplies!
( shouting orders )
Do you have enough men for this?
lt does not appear
you have enough men.
They face only slaves,
not Hannibal at the gates.
They are gladiators,
led by Spartacus,
- the Slayer of the Shadow of--
- Where is the magistrate?
l would discuss this
with someone of note.
He was otherwise detained,
in view of last night's--
He sends apologies.
Seppius, however,
is eager for audience.
The man has
Praetor Varinius's ear.
l have no desire for his tongue
to fill mine as well.
l would address the people,
put their minds to ease,
tomorrow as the sun rises
in the marketplace.
( laughs )
What will you say?
Attend to the arrangements.
Yes, Praetor.
Why have l been brought here?
Gaius, why have l
been brought here?
To this house?
The hilltop offers
excellent vantage
of the surrounding country.
The ludus below will easily
garrison my men.
Then use it as such.
l will remove myself
to my father's villa.
You will stay at my side.
Now, set the house to order.
This is our home now, llithyia.
Until Spartacus falls.
l want everything
in this fucking house
seen over the cliff.
We will purchase
new appointments of much coin.
lf my husband
would have me here,
he can certainly pay
for the comfort.
And see all traces
of blood cleansed.
lt reeks of Batiatus
and his faded bitch.
- Go! Go!
- Yes, Domina.
( laughter )
( moaning )
( screams )
What has happened?
ln matters concerning my wife,
the gods themselves
fear to speculate.
( shuddering )
Have you lost wit?
Speak.
You should have sent word
you were coming.
We would have prepared a feast.
Lucretia.
You see it, then?
- You see it?
- ( claps hands ) Naevia,
bring wine
for our honored guests.
Kill it. Kill it! Kill it!
Praetor!
This is Batiatus's wife?
A shadow of the same.
And yet she lives.
To be spared from such carnage,
a blessing from the gods,
one that would calm a city,
if it were known to be such.
Naevia!
Apologies.
l do not know
where she's gone.
Lucretia: What...
Why do you pause?
She could prove
a powerful symbol.
lt would give the city hope
to see a woman
survive Spartacus and his men
and courage to confront them,
speeding your return to Rome.
Gaius...
you cannot let her live.
See her bathed and tended
and what fragments
her shattered mind yet holds.
( Lucretia muttering )
- The Roman army?!
- We are all of us dead!
- Grab your fucking cock.
- We never wanted this!
You gladiators,
you will see us all to our end.
- You little fuck.
- Agron!
We knew this day would come.
Some have feared its approach.
Others have longed for it.
Yet few have grasped
deeper meaning...
that this moment...
was always fated to be so.
l made promise to all of you
when the house of Batiatus fell...
that we would
see Rome tremble.
Doctore: You are the ones
that shall quake.
( murmuring )
l have witnessed Glaber
and his men entering the city,
enough in number
to end your lives.
Then stand with us,
and balance the odds.
Mercato has announced
Glaber will make address
in the market as day breaks.
lt would be wise to use
the distraction
and leave
such thoughts behind.
Doctore!
That is no longer my title.
Where do you go?
There is but one place
for an animal without honor.
( murmuring )
He is lost to us.
How many more
would you have follow?
- ( sobbing )
- Come on.
Join with us, brother.
We can head south
while Glaber cups his balls
and makes speeches.
He's the reason l am here
and my wife forever absent.
You often preach to me
about caution.
Turn advice now towards self.
- We are ready.
- ( gasping )
House slaves
playing at being men.
They are not gladiators.
They are not an army,
as much you wish it to be so.
Sleep upon it, Spartacus,
but when the sun rises,
l would see reason dawn.
Lucretia: Water.
How did we come by it,
with the drought?
llithyia: Drought is long past.
Do you not recall its ending?
lt is of no concern. Come.
l would have you dry
and seen to proper dress.
Your wound.
Wound?
How did you come by it?
Leave us.
lt must have been terrible...
trapped within these walls,
your beasts running wild.
Everyone believed you dead,
smashed upon the cliffs,
bits of bone and flesh...
your only testament.
How did you survive all alone?
Lucretia.
We are friends, are we not?
The very best.
And you have so many--
Aemilia, Caecilia...
...Licinia.
Cousin to Marcus Crassus.
lt would be a very great honor
to be seen at her side.
Would you make introduction?
Let us see you dressed.
llithyia.
Why didn't you tell me?
You're with child.
Quintus and l have been trying
for such a long time.
This is a sign,
a sign from the gods.
Life blossoms
in the house of Batiatus.
This is why
we are yet in Capua...
why you saw Aurelia away.
You hoped
they would send Glaber.
No.
l prayed for it.
And what do you pray for now
to the gods
you do not believe in?
Would your wife
have wanted this?
To see her husband
consumed?
There are many things
she would not have wanted,
and yet they are so.
Follow Crixus to the south.
Do not let your vengeance
claim so many
you have saved from bondage.
l would not see another life
forfeit to my desires.
We will find Naevia
and move far beyond
the grasp of Rome...
far from the name Spartacus
they have branded you with.
Let us turn thought
from uncertain future
and embrace
fleeting moment.
Get up!
Move to fucking purpose.
Be ready when word is given.
You bark as a dominus.
Sheep stand idle
if not prodded by snapping jaw.
- Lazy fuck.
- Get up!
Does the maw from a pup
spur the same?
( laughter )
Let us compare teeth
and have answer.
Cease your quarrels.
l am for Spartacus
and the lay of his thoughts.
Last night, they were
towards heeding caution
and joining you in the south.
And in the light of morning?
He was gone from our bed
when l awoke.
( crowd murmuring )
Magistrate: There is no cause
for rising concerns!
The situation
is well in control!
What of Arminius?!
ls that fucking control?!
Seppius: No!
lt was an act of savagery,
committed by animals
who know nothing more.
These same beasts laid waste
to the house of Batiatus.
Many were lost that night,
women of proper standing,
men of honor and position,
my own cousin Sextus,
your beloved magistrate
of years past,
among the dead.
- ( murmuring )
- He speaks the truth!
At the hands of butchers,
who crave only blood and death.
And they shall see it
returned in kind.
But Spartacus leads them!
Even Theokoles fell before him!
He's the Bringer of Rain!
Spartacus is but a man,
and not all fall to his touch.
The wife
of Quintus Lentulus Batiatus
stood against
the merciless assault
of Spartacus and his dogs,
and by favor of the gods...
she yet lives.
Woman: lt's a miracle!
- Gods be praised!
- ( gasping )
- lt is a blessing!
- ( murmuring )
You stand eclipsed.
You ought to shed
a fucking tear.
She is their herald...
plucked from the shores
of the afterlife
to deliver a message
that Spartacus
shall never triumph
over the people of Capua!
( cheering )
He comes.
- He comes.
- Still yourself.
And yet the gods
grace us with further signs
that Spartacus's end is near.
Woman: Burn! Burn!
Just fucking burn her!
( crowd jeering )
Man: Open her guts
onto the ground!
Hack that bitch! Fuck her!
- Get rid of her!
- Gut the cunt!
My men came upon
a clutch of Batiatus' slaves
attempting harm
in the mountains to the east.
( gasps )
This one is all that remains
amongst the living.
Before she succumbs
to her wounds,
l will force
her tongue to purpose,
and with her dying breath,
she will tell me
where Spartacus and his men
hide themselves.
And they shall be struck
from this mortal world
by the hand
of Gaius Claudius Glaber!
( cheering )
Glaber! Glaber! Glaber!
Preening little shit.
l rather favor him.
As l favor the shade
of our villa.
( giggles )
Thank you.
- Yaah!
- ( screams )
( yelling )
Surround him!
Seize him!
Spartacus!
Take Aurelia and go!
- Where is Naevia?
- ( screams )
Take him!
You cannot win this!
Stay, and see vengeance
forever denied.
You are no better than Rhaskos
and the fucking Gauls.
All driven
only by your own desires.
Do any of us hold
fucking worth to you?
The reason l went alone.
A hard comfort, if you had
fallen to Glaber's men.
Agron would have led you south.
We need a leader,
not some angry boy
who can barely piss
without splashing
everyone about him.
What would you have me do?
Turn from the man that condemned
my wife to slavery?
Let him live,
that took everything from me?
Your heart still beats.
Place ear to chest,
and you will find it
absent sound.
And yet you are not dead.
Because of you.
Know that you have my gratitude.
l didn't come to lend you aid,
you mad fuck.
- ( coughs )
- l came to stop you.
You would place yourself between
Glaber and what he deserves?
As you would place yourself
between Naevia and me.
What do you think
would be the result
of killing a fucking praetor?
The Senate would burn upon itself,
belching forth fire and vengeance.
They would not send a few men,
as they do with Glaber.
They would send thousands,
a true army...
which we will never be.
( footsteps )
Aurelia calls for you.
( gasping )
Spartacus.
l am here.
Promise me...
Anything.
Promise...
you will stay far from my son.
l would not have him die
in your wake...
as his father
and mother.
Glaber and his men
will pay in blood.
Gather swords.
No.
We move south...
to find Naevia.
Let Crixus and the other Gauls
chase lost hope.
- Spartacus--
- The decision's been made.
We must stand as one...
or fall divided.
A lesson hard learned.
Shackle will be struck
from every slave
upon our path.
We will see
our numbers grow,
and when they
have become legion,
we will face Glaber
and the hordes of Rome again,
and the gods shall weep
for their suffering.
\N\N,\Nwww.kuntesi.com.