Gain your father's approval
to dissolve your marriage
and find me as wet with desire
as you now stand.
Albinius: News of your desires
towards loving daughter lifts heart.
Remove encumbrance
as discussed.
Lucretia: You would see your child
never born?
llithyia: A necessary thing.
Lucretia: There's a red vial.
l would see its contents
replaced with water and bitter herb.
Your wife's slave
stealing through the night,
in her hand
a thing familiar to me.
l know what l hold
and the intent it carries!
Let these men not fall here tonight
but in the arena.
We are for the arena
in Capua.
Varinius:
l give you Gannicus!
Gannicus: We at last face each other
upon the sands
as Melitta always feared.
- Did you lay with her?
- Oenomaus.
Spartacus: We will cover
this land in ash and blood
until Rome falls as a cinder
to scorched ground.
Spartacus.
Gaius, where is my father?
Help me, please.
Glaber: He has fallen at the hands
of Spartacus.
( theme music playing )
They live!
( crowd chattering )
- Woman: Get the medicus.
- Man: Quickly.
Get water and cloth
to tend wounds.
- What news?
- The arena is burned to fucking ground,
with many Romans
among the ashes!
What of Rhaskos?
He fell as all men should.
With sword in hand
and blood upon his thoughts.
( crowd cheers )
Nasir:
You suffer no wound.
The gods favor me,
little man.
Call me that again
and they shall turn from you.
Can he be healed?
Nasir had but a single wound.
This man-- beyond what should
warrant life.
His name is Oenomaus
and he is more than common man.
Let's pray the gods
hold him in equal esteem.
Do l yet dream?
lf so,
l would never
have you wake.
Then it began to collapse.
They screamed
and flailed like children
as the arena burned
around them,
the scent of smoke and death
carried by the winds
to the very heart of Rome!
Spartacus:
Lift troubled heart.
Oenomaus stands a titan,
one that shall live
to raise sword again.
To fight by your side?
lf he chooses to take up cause
against the Romans.
Cause?
You have cock to rival
Jupiter himself.
A few errant slaves
amounts to
flies circling a bull's ass.
Did he miss the part where we pulled
the arena down on his head?
Rome is propped up by more
than a few wooden beams.
lf your cause is
to see your lives cut short,
you march towards
certain victory.
Why did you choose to aid us,
if you believe such?
You mistake choice
for repayment of a debt,
one owed to Oenomaus.
Absent it,
we would not be
breaking words.
He is right.
We were mistaken--
to have placed faith
in his intentions.
Nasir once made attempt
on my life,
and yet now he stands
trusted among us.
Perhaps Gannicus
can be swayed as well.
Or perhaps you should have
killed him in the arena.
Man: The witnesses in Rome
also attest
the will grants
the family domicile in Rome
and the villa here in Capua.
ln addition, there is
the vineyard in Atella,
40 goats in the hills
of Pompeii,
20 head of cattle--
What is the worth
of the livestock?
9,000 denarii,
depending upon deal struck.
See them to market.
And post decree
announcing reward of the coin
for knowledge leading
to the capture of Spartacus.
Forgive me, Praetor,
but the law grants you
no such authority
to part with these assets.
You are only to oversee
Senator Albinius's holdings
until his heir comes of age.
Glaber: Laws must bend
toward greater purpose.
Spartacus is to pay
for what he has done.
- Praetor--
- Prattling on serves only
to inflict further wound
on grieving heart.
Man: Apologies.
The memory of your father
shall not soon fade.
All the Republic mourns his loss.
Leave us.
What moves your tears
the most--
a father forever removed
from loving embrace
or his tongue forever stilled
before commanding
to dissolve this marriage
in favor of Varinius?
l have made a grave mistake.
And the gods have punished me
by striking down my father.
lt is not enough.
- Gaius.
- The only reason
you have not joined
your father
is the child that grows
within you--
my child, my heir.
Protect him with your life...
or see it forfeit.
Man:
Workers, to the stockade!
Man #2:
Open the gate!
We must keep appearance
of mourning
for the prescribed days.
l would not have the stench of grief
slick upon you.
See yourself to a bath.
Give report.
100 more bodies
pulled from the arena.
This was found at wreckage.
Why do our numbers
stand so few?
Guard: More have been recalled
from Neapolis, to return by nightfall.
Yet many have taken to the wind.
They turn from their oath
to Rome?
Fear and panic grip the region,
and our men.
Many believe that Spartacus
unleashes the wrath of the gods.
Ashur:
A meaningless thing.
Legions could return
to swell rank
yet still fall to Spartacus
and his men.
Apologies, but as l warned
young Marcus
before life fled,
gladiators are far from
common slaves.
You'll not recall Spartacus facing
a clutch of your men
for exhibition in this very villa
and the result of such contest?
Not all fight as Spartacus.
Yet many are
of the Brotherhood.
Three of your men would not equal
one so trained...
( clears throat )
...despite their
eagerness to die.
No.
Did you not once stand
amongst the brotherhood...
( snaps fingers )
upon the sands?
A lifetime ago.
Glaber: Then give lesson,
prove boast.
Praetor, l--
Be quick.
l would not linger in this heat.
Man: The Syrian wants to taste
his own blood.
( men laughing )
Man:
The Syrian shit.
Get in there, come on.
( men jeering )
- Man: What's the matter?
- Come on!
Begin!
Come on.
Get him!
And l was considered lowest
among the brotherhood.
Would that l had an army
formed in your base image.
There are others
that share my reflection--
men in name only,
a word masking truer nature
of rabid animal.
Such a force
under my guidance
could prove useful
in these difficult times.
The Senate would frown upon
lowering standard
into muck and shit...
as they frown upon
many things
that ambitious men
must embrace.
Lucretia:
You leave these walls?
( sighs )
At request of the praetor.
He blesses Ashur
with well-deserved favor.
Would that he turn
such grace
toward grieving wife.
lt is a hard thing to have father
torn from breast.
l never knew mine.
Though l often wondered--
How did Glaber come to know
of the silphium in llithyia's chambers?
Perhaps the gods spoke to him.
You forget your place.
No, l secure it.
You secure nothing
without me,
you fucking Syrian.
Move against
my commands again--
You command shit and piss.
l am Glaber's man now.
A word from me how you knew
of his wife's intent
to rob him
of his unborn child
or how the gods
had nothing to do
with delivering Oenomaus--
You yet draw breath
because l have not whispered
your secrets into the praetor's ear.
No, Ashur. Ashur.
Shh. Consider it a kindness,
one that l shall see repaid.
( Lucretia sobbing )
No.
Does it hurt?
A few cuts and scrapes,
soon faded from memory.
Would that all scars
were so easily erased.
l see no scars.
You risked all
for pale shadow of the woman
you once loved.
Then let us ignite the sun
and strike darkness
with its warmth.
Stop.
Naevia.
They have taken everything
from me...
even your touch.
l have heard tales
of your victories in the arena.
Days long past.
Mira tells you were
just upon its sands,
standing as executioner
for the Romans.
l stood for a brother,
to see him
to an honorable death.
And Rhaskos?
Did he find the same?
The man held
some meaning to you?
He elevated position.
l gave comfort.
lt appears that bargain
has come to an end.
l would see another struck
with a man of greater worth.
l hold no position
among these men,
nor do l seek it.
Yet you stand among them.
l seek only words
with an old friend,
nothing more.
We are here,
in the shadow of Vesuvius.
A single man
placed upon its crest
would have clear view
for many miles in all direction.
A Roman advance
easily spotted.
ls there a way
to its peak?
A single path,
narrow, but easily tread.
The rest is sheer rock,
impassable, absent wings.
We will choose three men
of years beyond
the taking up of sword,
each to command
a separate watch.
Mira: There's but one entrance
to the temple.
The Romans could
easily trap us inside.
Spartacus: Tunnels extend
below our feet.
Perhaps one can be dug
beyond these walls.
A few men with bows
would give the Romans pause
long enough to make use of it,
if walkway were built.
How many among you
shoot with purpose?
There is not much call
for arrows in the arena.
You no longer fight
upon the sands,
nor can you forge a sword
from a fucking tree.
Then we will fashion weapons
from what nature provides,
with practiced hand
instructing in their use.
We can train
until the gods take us.
House slaves
will never be gladiators--
something we are
in short supply of now.
We need fighting men.
Perhaps it is time to revisit plans
towards Neapolis
and its slaver ships
from foreign wars.
You would attack the port
with a few men?
We brought the arena down
with less.
Take two men
and what coin we have.
Weight palm in Neapolis
to loosen tongue
of ships soon to dock.
Do it quietly.
l would not have
intention known.
Apologies. l did not intend
to halt conversation.
Unless l can drink that,
it holds no worth to me.
l seek only wine.
We have none.
Then l truly am
among the damned.
For both of you?
( laughs ) l'm a whore,
not a fool.
- ( man shouts )
- ( woman screams )
l would have words.
Fuck your words.
( chuckles )
lt is not with you
that l seek them.
l have an offer to discuss,
one suited
to your particular talents.
( insects chirping )
Apologies.
l did not think
you would need the bath,
with days of mourning
yet left.
My husband commands it,
despite tradition.
Stay.
l would have your company.
Your eyes betray recent tears.
Events weigh heavy
on the heart.
To the point of crushing it.
Why did the gods not warn
of Spartacus's attack
or of my father's--?
Do they punish me--
a life, for the one
l had planned to take?
We both carry
the burden of our acts.
lf the gods
have cast us adrift,
we must together
discover the course
for return to the blessings
of their shores.
Varinius has turned from me.
Gaius-- l fear
not even the gods
could sway
his hatred of me now.
Resume appearance
of loving wife.
Submit to his will.
The day will come
when he will lose sight
of hateful intention--
a slip, however fleeting,
that we shall
take advantage of.
There was a time...
when all l dreamt of was
your throat beneath my hands.
Now your breath
is all that gives me life.
l shall not be moved
from your side
until my own husband
calls me to the afterlife.
( men chattering )
l have seen that look.
lt often fell upon me,
when we were yet
beneath Batiatus's roof.
Spartacus:
You knew Gannicus then,
years before my arrival.
What is your opinion
of the man?
He is a champion,
as we once stood,
a boon to your cause.
He has expressed doubts
toward it.
As have we all.
Yet you always find way
to convince otherwise.
We have done
the impossible.
We have brought down
the arena in Capua--
a monument of Rome
built upon
the backs of slaves.
We have struck a deep blow
to the very heart of our enemy.
Yet...
their numbers are vast,
as vast as their desire
to see freedom
crushed beneath heel.
One day,
perhaps soon,
they will strike back.
How do we avoid them?
l do not intend to.
ls that true?
Spartacus: lf we are to face
the might of Rome,
l would do it here,
in the shadow of Vesuvius,
upon terms that we set.
No hand will stand idle.
We must prepare ourselves
for what is to come.
- Well, what is to come?
- What is to happen to us?
Proper weapons
are in short supply.
Fashion what you can
from wood and stone
till more can be secured.
l would also see
the tunnels beneath our feet
further dug towards escape,
which we will need...
To set eyes again
upon your heart--
l understand now why a man
would risk all for such a thing.
lf it were not for you
and the others,
l would have fallen
in the arena,
never to gaze upon her face again
in this life.
lt is a thing l will not forget.
- Spartacus: Continue to hone skill.
- Nor the lie you told
that saw her stay in that place
another fucking day.
She is safe now.
All other things
fall to unimportance.
Do you think a few words
can change all that has happened?
You stand a larger fool
than l thought.
...than a thousand men.
Apologies.
The mistake was mine,
to offer comfort
to a fucking Gaul.
You offer shit.
- Regain yourself.
- Crixus.
l thought we had moved
past this.
Wounds still linger.
l move for Neapolis
and thoughts of swelling rank
with better men.
( Gannicus laughing )
You need not fear
the Romans.
Your own men make attempt
to kill each other.
You know what must be done.
See to it.
Gannicus,
l would have words.
You would have me fight?
l would have you hunt.
Everyone has been set
to purpose.
Ours is to provide meat.
You spoke of a debt
to Oenomaus.
Was saving his life
not repayment enough?
That is for him to decide.
You are a free man.
Your decision's your own,
as they were
when you stood in the arena
to strike down your brothers.
What moved your hand?
Honor, as you would have it,
or the promise of coin?
Never to be collected,
because l chose
not to kill you in the arena.
And now my rudis--
my freedom--
is forever buried
beneath its rubble.
Freedom is not
a stick of wood
to be presented as bone
to obedient dog.
lt is a thing all men deserve.
We are gladiators,
deserving only death
equal to the lives that we have taken.
lt was not always so for me.
l lived free once
in the lands of Thrace
with a wife,
promise of children.
What became of her?
Batiatus claimed her life.
l took his in return.
Then you have balanced scale.
lt was Glaber
who condemned us to slavery.
And l will not rest
while he yet draws breath.
This is the reason
you provoke the Romans--
for the memory
of your woman?
For love--
the greatest cause of all.
A thing that has dragged
many a man to ruin.
You have scared away
the game.
l would fare better alone.
Man:
Keep fucking sword up.
Let it drop,
and fall forever beside it.
Again.
Attack.
l would not have you expire
from the heat.
Donar: Attack.
Gratitude.
l would also not have you
at Agron's throat.
Donar: Again.
lf he had had his way,
he would have
left you in the mines.
Perhaps he was right.
Do not say such a thing.
Have you not thought the same
after last night?
lf such a thought
threatened,
l would rip it from fucking brain
with bare hands.
All that matters
is the woman l love
stands before me once again.
Does she?
Or is it but faint spirit
haunting the memory
of her body?
You have lost mind.
Hundreds dead, an arena destroyed,
and this is what you offer?
Lucretia to prostrate herself
in the market,
begging the gods to piss out
the flames that yet smolder?
Apologies.
Young Seppius is but moved
by passionate heart.
Glaber:
l'm sure the gods take notice
of his lack of faith.
Lucretia: We must humble ourselves
before the gods
in attempt to regain
their favor.
Glaber: Ritual will do much
to ease the people's fears.
Seppius: Better assuaged
by the capture of Spartacus.
My men sweep the countryside,
taking action in favor of prayer.
As they have for months,
to no result.
Yours have fared no better.
True.
The only one who benefits
from our divide
is the man
who causes us injury.
And most keenly felt.
Your father's guidance
and even hand
is deeply missed.
His absence
from this world
has set it upon end.
Seppia fell to similar heart
when our cousin Sextus
was snatched from life by Spartacus.
And she relives the moment
in Mercato's passing--
a family friend
since she was yet a child.
Glaber:
Too many have been lost.
l would see no more of note
to follow.
Let us set difference aside,
one which will overwhelm Spartacus
and his murdering horde.
Yes, for the good of the people.
The city will praise you both,
l would need to consult
with Varinius.
The very same man
who galloped back to Rome
while the stones of the arena
were yet falling?
Varinius moves
to distance himself
from all that has happened here,
including you.
Take my hand
and with it
see more lasting bond forged.
l will consider your proposal,
to give answer tomorrow.
Gallienus:
A night's rest--
Loving sister may sway a brother
where others fail.
Gallienus: --mind to be certainly
cleared by morning.
Seppius,
l would extend invitation
to your sister
in hopes that we may find
greater strength
in the beating
of two wounded hearts.
Gallienus:
A thoughtful offer.
There is no deeper solace
for a woman
than in the bosom
of her gender.
lt would come
as great comfort.
Gratitude.
l will arrange visit.
Your wife speaks
with swift thought.
Seppia will take words
to heart on the matter,
with Seppius to find them
better received from her lips.
Yes.
Your invitation may yet prove
to be welcome aid.
Come.
l would discuss
other matters with you.
Did l not tell you?
Together...
we will see ourselves freed
from this abyss.
( crows cawing )
l do not see the man.
You are certain he lives?
There were four others
held with him at the bottom.
He did not care
for the company.
Their memory is carved
into his flesh,
joining the marks of the other souls
that he has taken.
( laughs )
What is it you seek
of such a beast?
What l seek of the Egyptian
is none of your concern.
l come under the authority
of Praetor Gaius Claudius Glaber.
A noble title.
Yet absent the man himself,
l cannot break my charge.
Of course.
lf you do not mind
waiting here with my men,
until l return with him...
Well, the day has been
long and hot.
l would have shade
and wine
to cool overheating concerns.
Let us see you to the light,
my friend...
and set hands to purpose.
( Mira chuckles )
You must keep
your left arm steady,
pull through to the cheek,
take breath and release.
Make attempt.
Pull through to cheek,
deep breath
and release.
Do not jerk from the string
but let it gently slip
from your fingers.
With practice, you will be
as the goddess Diana,
striking enemies from afar.
Donar.
l would accompany you.
l hold no interest in the bow.
We lay together once
and you expect us to never be parted?
You mistake me
for a fucking Gaul.
You seek
Donar's affection now?
l seek only my place
in this world.
Then seize it
with your own hands,
not by the spreading
of your legs.
ln two weeks time
a ship will dock here,
its hold laden with fighting men
captured by the Romans.
lf a few of us
dressed as merchants
could gain entry
before they're unloaded--
Such a thing is possible.
Your labors have born fruit.
Not all is sweet.
News carries
through the streets--
Glaber has raised the bounty
on your head to 9,000 denarii.
lt seems you have caught
nothing but Rome's attention.
You will find that a sour meal.
( laughs )
Were the Gauls
not fucking bad enough?
l have heard many tales
of the Undefeated Gaul.
A fine title.
Yet l recall you
absent victory
when we faced Solonius's men
in the opening of the arena.
True.
l was not awarded victory.
Yet l did not suffer defeat
in proper challenge.
( chuckles )
Perhaps we will yet have one.
Perhaps.
lt warms heart
to know that you were champion,
how much you desired it.
Yet it comes as a surprise
to see you here,
following a Thracian's lead.
Spartacus has opened my eyes.
We stand together.
Then why do you now sit
while he and the lumbering oaf
make plans that affect all?
l am taken
by other concerns.
Naevia is your woman now?
l remember her when she was yet
a flower untouched.
What led her
to be so rudely handled?
My affections
and discovery of them
by Lucretia.
The heaviest price is always paid
by those we love.
You should carry her
far from Spartacus
and his foolish cause
before he drags you all
to your end.
Oenomaus awakes.
l am here only for words.
Which do you think
could ever
hold meaning now?
That Melitta chose you.
That your heart was cherished
above all others.
Then why was she with you
the night she died?
To share a final drink
before l was to be sold to Tullius.
The only reason?
Whatever happened
between us,
l am to blame,
not her,
never her.
l loved you as a brother.
And l you.
No.
You are a man
that stands only for himself
and would betray the gods
to gain what he desires.
Perhaps l was a fool
to have ever believed
otherwise.
( Seppia crying )
l see it every time
l close my eyes--
Spartacus hurling his spear,
Cossutius's final
gasping breath.
And Mercato--
poor Mercato.
He will be sorely missed.
Apologies.
l babble on as if l am the only one
that has suffered loss,
and you grieve
a father's passing.
The heart is overwhelmed
by his absence.
You shall embrace him again,
as l shall Mercato
and beloved cousin Sextus.
Upon the shores of the afterlife,
where my husband Quintus
patiently awaits.
And with him
countless other Romans of note,
all snatched from this life
too soon
by common foe.
The years between you
far outweigh mine,
yet do not think me naive.
You extend invitation
not to counsel grief,
but to maneuver me
to sway my brother's position.
- Seppia.
- He's been clear in his desire
that he, and he alone,
will bring our common foe
to justice.
And his passions, when set,
are not easily moved.
You have uncovered
the veiled schemes of two old women.
But know attempt springs
from wounded heart,
one shared between us all,
regardless of age or experience.
l looked into his eyes
when Spartacus
stood down upon the sands.
They burned with a fire
that would consume the world.
Glaber: And it shall,
if good men fail
to set quarrel aside
and face Spartacus
as one.
As l have said to your wife,
my brother can be most difficult.
The fault is not his alone.
l regret not having taken
different path
towards more
agreeable solution.
But know that l place foot
firmly upon it now.
l will have words
and attempt to set him upon it
beside you.
Most welcome news,
is it not, Gaius?
Yes.
Most welcome.
You are a ray of light
in a house mired in shadow.
( footsteps )
Ah, forgive me.
Pressing matters
call my attention.
You are blessed
to hold such a man.
The gods grant
only what is deserved.
The men required
have been assembled.
Come then.
l would see if they are
all that you've promised.
( footsteps )
Gannicus's bounty
is being prepared.
Come, let us take food.
You have honed it
to fine edge.
Life would easily run
from veins,
if brought to bear
upon flesh.
Naevia.
That is a name
that holds no meaning.
She was a different girl,
young and foolish,
ripped from this world
by rough hands
and hot breath upon neck.
The things she was forced
to do to survive--
We will go from this place,
find a new life
on distant shores,
beyond the shadow of Rome.
There is no place
that memory would not follow.
l cannot run from this.
What would you have me do--
stand idle
and watch as you fade?
No, l would not
have you watch.
l would have you teach
how to breathe again,
how to live,
how to fight,
so that no man will ever
lay hands on me
against my will
and the girl
whose name was robbed
may reclaim it.
We will have vengeance
for what the Romans
have done.
Together we shall
see them drown
in rivers of blood.
- ( men shouting )
- ( loud crash )
Man:
Where has it gone?
- Nothing.
- Nor here.
Spartacus:
Calm yourselves.
What moves to such fits?
Our remaining coin is missing.
Fuck the coin.
The map is gone--
our position,
plans towards Neapolis.
Someone seeks to betray us
for promise of Glaber's reward.
Spartacus.
Gannicus.
You leave without words?
( thunder rumbling )
l have had them
with Oenomaus.
What do you carry
with you?
Water.
Meat caught by my own
fucking hands.
Open it.
l am not one of your fools,
falling to command.
Our map takes flight
in your wake.
A thing l have seen
your gaze upon.
l am guilty of many things.
Betraying ill-fated cause
does not stand among them.
Remove yourself
from fucking path.
( thunder crashing )
( laughs )
l knew you would lead these men
to their deaths eventually.
ls this the day
you would do it?
They are but loyal--
a quality you seem
unfamiliar with.
No! Do not come
between us.
l would show him
what a man with cause is capable of.
Your sword.
You fight in the style
of Dimachaerus.
Trained by Oenomaus himself.
Let me pass,
or put skill to final test.
We must stop this.
Spartacus has made
his desire known.
We shall honor it.
Spartacus!
( people exclaiming )
Chadara!
Mira: She was trying to slip away
when all others stood fixed.
A fine shot.
l meant only to wound.
She took the map.
Why would she do
such a thing?
Mira: She felt she had
no place among us.
She sought to secure one
elsewhere.
Apologies.
Your words prove true.
lt has not always been so.
l would take to path now,
unless you would seek
further quarrel.
Go. Enough blood
has been spilled.
Do you stay?
We do.
Then l shall mourn
your passing.
ls it wise to let him go?
Every man has a right
to his own choice.
Gannicus has made his.
And may yet prove a threat.
We have faced far worse.
( screams )
The Egyptian and your men
prove themselves.
As promised.
See the bodies of the slaves
properly attended.
Draw no attention.
Apologies.
l could not wait
till morning.
( moans )
You wish to give voice
to my offer?
l fear it comes too late.
S-S-Seppia.
l've seen how close
you hold her to heart.
Leave this life
knowing she's safe
beneath my roof,
my hands to comfort her
in days to come.
Words no longer hold meaning.
And l've had too many of them
by fools
presuming themselves
to be my better.
Such days are at an end.
Your men are now mine
and, with their addition
to my own,
clear path to the end
of Spartacus.
( theme music playing )
字幕来源于互联网\N美剧控☆昆特斯\N欧美史诗大片推荐,请上\Nwww.kuntesi.com