We march at nightfall
and, by dawn's light,
see an end to Spartacus.
- Gannicus: The signal.
- Glaber.
Again!
( all yelling )
Spartacus: Fall back!
lnto the tunnel!
Move! Move!
The mountain pass! Hurry!
We'll be trapped.
There's no choice.
We must move!
Ashur:
You will let them go free?
No.
We shall kill them all.
( theme music playing )
( thunder rumbling )
- ( shivers )
- ( coughs )
The wood for fire
is almost gone.
Our food quickly follows.
We have stripped the mountain
of what little it had
ever since Glaber
forced us upon it.
A thing that should
not have happened.
You will find a way
to see us from this.
You always do.
As you always find words
to pull me
from darkest thoughts.
A talent l pray
your next woman holds.
Spartacus!
Nemetes and a clutch of fools
have taken afoot.
Towards what purpose?
They attempt
to breach the Romans
at the foot of the path.
( water splashes )
Give word next time.
Be mistaken as enemy.
Glaber summons you.
We only just finished dining
on the most succulent lamb.
There may yet
be few scraps left.
You overstep, slave.
l but place foot
where our praetor commands.
lf you do not care
where it falls,
you are free to take issue.
( men yelling )
l do not know your tongue
nor have cause to learn it.
( yells )
Spartacus: Pull back!
Go! Move!
( soldiers shouting cadence )
Gannicus: Spartacus!
Mira!
( men yelling )
( gasps )
( soldiers shouting cadence )
Advance! Hup!
We must go!
( thunder crashing )
Woman: Who is it?
( overlapping chatter )
- Mira.
- Mira!
We must seal her wound. Nasir!
Heat your sword in the fire!
Quickly!
( wind blowing )
Spartacus.
Was it worth it?
Was it worth her life
to make attempt
to save your own?!
( crowd murmuring )
( yells )
Stay your fucking ground.
She is gone from this world
'cause of you!
You were the mad fuck
that led us to our deaths!
At least she claimed hers
as a warrior,
not starving
and robbed of strength,
as the rest of us
are doomed.
You are right.
We will all perish...
( crowd gasping )
...if we do not stand together.
lt will make
no fucking difference.
Seize tongue,
and open fucking ears.
The cliffs of Vesuvius
are impassable.
The southern path holds the only
promise of making purchase.
We hold the higher ground
and, with it, advantage
over superior numbers.
Only if Glaber
is foolish enough to attack
before we are too weak
from hunger to fight.
A man is never too weak
or too wounded to fight...
if the cause is greater
than his own life.
Glaber and his army will come.
And when they do...
Vesuvius will be
forever stained
with the blood of vengeance.
( coughing )
He is all that was captured?
Several more lay dead.
A fortunate thing
you are not among them.
Had the Egyptian and l
not been present,
l fear position
would have been overrun.
The gods favor us then...
and turn from those
who would do us harm.
Tell me of Spartacus
and his thoughts
toward coming storm.
( coughs )
Can he form proper words?
He has yet to break them.
A most unpleasant tongue.
Conditions must be dire
to abandon the higher ground
and attempt at such foolish act.
One that did not appear
commanded by Spartacus.
You laid eyes upon the man?
Briefly, as he and his shits
gave opportunities
for others to retreat.
How did he appear?
Deadly.
Yet there was a look about eye,
one found reflected
in wild beast
when pressed to corner.
Such an animal
never greets the afterlife
absent desperate blood.
Vesuvius is not Ceres' horn,
offering endless bounty.
There cannot be much
in way of nourishment
left upon barren peak.
We shall stay our hand
yet a while longer.
And when hunger and despair
are the only taste
upon his lips,
Spartacus shall kneel
before Rome
for the final time.
( horse neighs )
We should not be upon road.
Let us turn back.
No.
l will not sit idle in Capua as
weeks threaten unwelcome months.
All will soon come to an end.
l would see the day hastened
and my child born in a city
befitting the heir of a praetor.
The glorious occasion
is almost upon us.
To risk the journey to Rome--
There is yet time
if my husband is moved
to bring siege against Spartacus
to early conclusion.
The reason we are for Vesuvius.
A fraction of it.
The whole of the truth
encompassing greater need.
Has heart returned
so fiercely in such regard?
Gaius and l share but one now,
his absence leaving chest
but half filled.
To find yourself in the arms
of a husband thought lost...
that's a blessing
beyond measure.
A happiness l would share
with treasured friend.
You will come with me
to Rome.
l will entreat Gaius
towards dowry
in honor of your service...
and you shall again find
comfort in title of wife.
Your husband would not
have me follow with you.
You have been invaluable
to his cause.
He believes another more so.
l have been promised
to Ashur.
Ashur?
My hand and house
in payment
for blood spilled
in your husband's name.
Why have you not told me this?
l would not have such thoughts
weigh mind and body
with your day so close at hand.
l will seize opportunity
at Vesuvius
and attempt
to rid myself of burden.
Reveal intentions...
and see them embraced.
( metal tapping )
We sit here waiting to die,
and he tends to fucking weeds.
He tends to his heart,
as any man should.
There is not enough wood
to build a pyre.
The ground is too hard
to lay her beneath it.
He can only grieve
and bind her in his cloak.
Blessing then...
that we shall all be dead
before she turns overly ripe.
( man coughs )
( overlapping conversations )
Nemetes and his kind
grow ever more restless.
l fear they're not alone.
l cannot lay blame.
Yet our only chance of survival
is to hold fast to sound tactic.
Like attacking the arena
with a handful of men?
l once thought you
reckless fool.
Now l see bold strategy
is the only reason
you are not already dead.
l have been but fortunate
to have seized opportunity
the Romans would consider mad.
There stand none left to us now,
absent wings to fly from cliff.
The day comes when we must
face Glaber and his army
in open battle.
lf l am to die,
at least l shall die
among brothers.
( laughs )
We share a bond
forged not upon the sands,
but upon grander stage
of battle,
and when it ends,
as all conflict must,
l will gain
Batiatus' ludus and villa
as reward for loyal service.
lt will become
the noble House of Ashur,
where l shall train
the mightiest gladiators
in all the Republic.
l would count you
among my first recruits.
You will become
gods of the arena,
showered in wine and women.
l ask but for your oath,
- pledging--
- Open the gate!
Wait here...
and see
weighted heart lifted.
There's been
no further movement?
We have taught Spartacus
the futility
of attempting breach.
You cannot school rabid dog
not to bare teeth.
llithyia.
( laughs )
You should not have come.
Yes, l know the rules.
Women are forbidden
in the encampment.
Oh.
My concern is only for you
and the life you carry.
l would not have you travel
in such condition.
l have never felt stronger
and would travel
a greater distance still.
You wish to return to Rome.
With my husband beside me.
The rebels become desperate.
ln a few more weeks,
when starvation--
A few more weeks,
and your heir will be born
in a house tainted
with blood and shit.
End Spartacus' life,
and let us return home to ours.
He holds the higher ground.
lt cannot be taken yet
without severe loss of men.
Yet...
it can be taken?
Await me in Capua...
and prepare to celebrate
the birth of our child
in the arms of mother Rome.
You truly stand a titan,
threatening the very heavens.
Go,
and know that you
are in my thoughts.
l would linger
but a moment longer.
What is this?
A warning from the gods.
How did this come to you?
l uncovered it while
cleansing trace of Seppia,
secreted among her things.
My slave Amana recalls seeing it
pressed into Seppia's hands
by the Syrian toad.
That is how she knew
her brother's true fate
and why she moved against you.
But it holds no sense.
Ashur's fortunes
are tethered to my own.
He is a serpent,
forever seeking the heat
of power and position.
When yours
was threatened by Varinius,
is it a wonder
he sought to slither
towards warmer clime?
A venomous creature to the last.
One no longer holding worth.
He is not alone in such regard.
Serpent and oracle
have both served purpose.
You speak of Lucretia?
l speak of a woman
who knows secrets
l would not have revealed.
You would ask me
to do such a thing?
l would put unfortunate
past behind us...
and seize glorious future.
You are my husband...
and l, dutiful wife.
l have missed
your delicate scent...
among other offerings
of more personal nature.
lt lifts spirits
to find you close again.
l stay but a moment.
A thing of low importance
when set against the promise
of a lifetime
held in loving embrace.
Do not shed tear when we part.
Know that campaign soon
draws to inevitable close...
and Ashur
to deserving reward.
l long to greet the day.
( gate clanks )
( Ashur chuckles )
Syrian.
Do you think me the fool?
Praetor?
l do not understand.
Do you deny taking it?
l take many things
from the fallen.
l thought l had
your blessing to do so.
And did you also
seek Seppia's blessing...
before she made attempt
on my life?
Seppia?
l've never broken words
with the girl.
l have had my fill
of serpent's tongue.
Wait! Wait.
l do not know what you
have been told,
but l fear you have made
a grave error.
No, l fear
you have made the error
in attempting to maneuver
beyond your station.
Unfortunate end
to profitable association.
Perhaps it best my men and l
quietly take leave,
absent further disagreement.
Oh, l would make better offer.
Land and a thousand denarii
to each of you,
in return for faithful service.
You fucking cunts.
Hold.
You once swore to me,
"Your will, my hands."
An oath that has not wavered.
l swear it to you, Praetor.
l would test such vaunted words
and the depths of your loyalty.
Spartacus!
There's movement upon the path.
Take position.
( overlapping chatter )
Ashur.
l come bearing a message
from Glaber.
Speak it.
He has grown weary
of this conflict
and would return home
to see his child born in Rome.
A thing of no interest.
( laughter )
Perhaps the lives
of your people hold more.
He offers terms of surrender.
Lay down your arms,
you'll be allowed to live.
( crowd murmur )
Spartacus: As slaves?
Beneath the heel
of the Republic?
Yes, as slaves.
Yet you will have your lives!
Refuse,
and Glaber has sworn
torturous death upon the cross
for all that survive
the taking of the mountain.
And what of Spartacus' life?
The cost of the bargain.
( crowd murmurs )
l for one do not wish
to die this day...
( crowd murmuring )
...yet if it is
to be fucking so,
l shall do it as a free man!
( cheering )
Woman:
Fuck the Romans!
Man:
No surrender!
Syrian cunt!
( laughter )
You have your answer.
Very well.
l shall deliver it
to waiting ears.
l would not have us
part so quickly.
Glaber awaits.
l must return with a reply.
Your head
would serve equal purpose.
Spartacus?
l find no fault
with his reasoning.
( laughter )
The mighty Crixus,
forever intoning
of the honor of a gladiator.
Where stands such now
in the cutting down
of a defenseless man?
Give him a sword.
Crixus: You once dreamt
of honor upon the sand.
Make this your final arena.
You stand a champion...
and l gravely wounded.
There is yet no honor
in such contest.
To shit with honor.
No!
l will not have you soil name
to gain vengeance in mine.
Naevia.
l shall take it myself.
No one has been
more wronged by Ashur...
and no one has greater claim
on his fucking life.
l will see him fall...
and with him,
memories that haunt
darkest nights.
See it done.
Are you certain of this?
l am far removed.
Very well.
lf Ashur must die today,
at least he will
see Crixus' bitch
to the afterlife before him.
( overlapping chatter )
Take it off!
Rip his head off!
Delicate flower
has grown thorns.
Get that cunt!
Sharpened by
the Undefeated Gaul.
l fear it will not help.
( laughter )
Yeah!
She fades,
as all beautiful things do.
Naevia!
Naevia: No!
He is mine.
Stay back!
l will have his life
for what he did to me.
Or die in attempt!
Yeah! Come on!
Do you recall this,
my body pressed against yours?
You trembling helpless,
as you tremble now?
( yells )
l am far from helpless.
You think
this makes difference?
( coughs )
My death...
will not heal
the scars you bear.
Nor erase memory
of my cock inside of her...
or all those that followed.
( laughs )
( gasps )
No...
it will not.
But it is a fucking start.
( yelling )
You were right.
lt is no easy task...
to cleave a man's head
from his shoulders
in a single blow.
Then l will teach you.
Donar! Lydon!
See Ashur's head upon the path
as reply to Glaber.
You send a clear one.
lt will be nail and cross
for those who live.
Glaber would have seen
us all to such fate,
regardless of answer carried.
Nemetes: So we are
dead either way.
Pity there are not enough vines
for all our corpses.
Close fucking mouth.
No.
Nemetes is right.
There are not
enough vines for us all.
But perhaps
there's enough for a few.
Your words carry no meaning.
They carry
the weight of the world,
braced by your own advice.
Glaber expects us to defend
the higher ground,
as any reasonable leader would.
Yet perhaps
there is another course,
a bold one,
that the Romans
will never see coming.
And what madness
does the Bringer of Rain
contemplate this time?
That we shall sprout wings
and do the impossible.
Man: Head off.
( thunder crashing )
Praetor.
They have given reply.
Spartacus makes expected choice.
Tell the men to eat well
and gather sleep.
Dawn's first light,
we take Vesuvius
and the lives of all those
who stand in defiance of Rome.
Soon we shall leave this place,
never to return.
What your friendship
brings me...
there are no words
to express gratitude.
You have returned the favor
many times over.
The debt l owe far exceeds
modest repayment.
You drew me
from the depths of madness.
You gave me strength
and purpose
to live beyond the tragedy
which betided this house.
Such things are of the past.
Let them give you
no further pain.
l have tried to put it from me.
The memory
of all l have lost,
it fills the very air,
choking each breath
with the sting of loss...
and binding my heart
in chains.
You stand upon precipice
of release.
Because of you.
You're my savior, llithyia.
And you mine.
You have given me hope
of a life l thought denied me
when my husband fell.
Know that such a gift
shall be eternally treasured.
( gasps )
The child.
lt comes too soon.
This is a sign from the gods.
( gasping )
lt must be born
within these walls.
( groaning )
Come.
Let us see their will be done.
We have used every vine
we could gather,
enough for four men.
( thunder crashing )
Agron, Crixus, Gannicus,
l would have you by my side.
Naevia: Crixus.
We will be reunited soon
in this life or the next.
l know fear wells
within your breast,
and it does so
with great cause.
The Romans hold numbers
far outweighing our own,
yet they have revealed
time and again fatal flaw,
that they believe the Roman way
is the only one...
just as they believe
that there is only one way
to leave this mountain.
We shall teach them
that we forge our own paths
and nothing in this world
is impossible
when heart and mind
are put towards it.
( cheering )
Brace rope.
Let us begin a lesson
forever remembered.
( thunder continues )
Agron: The sound
will mask descent.
The gods bless us
with good fortune.
Free men create their own.
We are all gods this night,
and the Romans
shall feel our wrath.
( cheering )
( thunder continues )
- ( rock clatters )
- Agron: Fuck.
( grunting )
lf we but fought as an army,
like the Romans.
They hold only
advantage of number.
One we shall see evened.
Prepare yourselves.
When signal comes,
death shall quickly follow.
( grunts )
( gurgles )
Spartacus:
We must move quickly,
before deed is discovered.
The hour is late.
Sleep will not come.
All l see when eyes close,
it is the end of Spartacus...
and with him,
reason for being
so long absent from Rome
and more important matters.
You will be victorious
where Varinius failed...
a great advantage
within the Senate.
To be used towards elevation.
One day l shall rise
above all others...
the light of accomplishment
giving warmth
to loving wife
and cherished heir.
Raise alarm.
- Praetor!
- Gather the men to formation!
Awake the men!
Fire!
The signal!
( all yelling )
( Romans yelling )
( neighs )
( screams )
( wails )
Where the fuck is the medicus?!
He had gone to town,
the child
not expected for weeks.
l have sent
the guards to fetch him.
( gasping )
Something is wrong.
lt claws at me,
not wanting to leave womb to be
born in this place. ( wails )
l will find something
to ease the pain.
Do not leave me.
Know that l will return,
and together we will see
this blessing into the world.
Again!
( yelling )
l need help over here!
Relocate ammunition.
Advance on rear position!
Kill anyone
who stands in your path!
Halt!
A glorious death.
( laughs )
Kill them!
( all yelling )
( laughs )
( rebels yelling )
( groaning )
( woman screams )
( objects clatter )
l thought l heard a cry.
( thunder crashing )
What have you done?
What was always intended,
to see curse
upon this house lifted.
( screaming )
Shh.
( gasping )
There.
No one left to come between us.
Fall back.
- Fall back!
Press advantage,
and see victory ours!
Stop.
Please.
We are friends, are we not?
The very best.
Then why would you do this?
Why would you take my life
and that of my child?
Your child?
You are but a vessel
carrying a gift
from the gods
to the House of Batiatus.
Now then...
let us see it unwrapped.
( screams )
( yelling )
l owe you pain.
Oenomaus!
Oenomaus.
l go to my wife's arms.
We shall greet you
in the afterlife, my brother.
( gate clanks )
Secure the perimeter!
Signal all men
to defend this position
Mark your stations!
Romans, ready!
( yelling )
( baby crying )
Lucretia!
Hush now, little one.
You are safe now.
You are loved
and shall be forever.
Please.
Quintus always wanted a son.
Because of you...
we shall have one.
No.
( child laughing )
l will not die
at the hands
of a fucking slave.
l am a free man.
The Roman finally
learns his place before us...
on his knees.
You've won nothing.
Rome will send legions
in my wake,
and one day soon you shall fall
to deserved end.
( gasping )
Perhaps.
Yet it is not this day.
( screams )
Let Rome send their legions.
We will face them
and see all
follow Glaber in death.
- Yeah!
- ( cheering )
Now we will become an army.
- Yeah!
( cheering )
Spartacus! Spartacus! Spartacus!
Spartacus!
Spartacus! Spartacus!
字幕来源于互联网\N美剧控☆昆特斯\N欧美史诗大片推荐,请上\Nwww.kuntesi.com