The U.S.A.
Richest nation on earth.
Hard work and ingenuity
earned us that title.
But we also got lucky.
This country has natural resources to spare.
How they came to be here is an ancient story,
and an unbelievably violent one.
I'm in California
where we get an occasional jolt to remind us
that this country is not built on solid ground.
Down there under my feet,
there's a fiery world of chaos,explosions,
collisions, contortions, upheaval
all on a scale we can hardly imagine.
How did the extreme subterranean forces
and cataclysmic climatic events above ground
shake the Continent?
How did grinding sheets of ice miles thick
flatten the middle of the country?
What great pressures belched metals
to the surface from below?
How are entire mountain ranges
thrust up by colliding tectonic plates?
And how did all that violence give us the raw materials
to ultimately build this land of power and bounty?
Because it did just that.
It built our cities,our rich farmland,
our waterways, our factories
and lots of the things they make.
We're going to take you across America
from the newest land here in the Pacific
to some of the oldest land near the Great Lakes
and along the Atlantic seaboard.
We're going to find out
just how this country's savage geological past
made it great.
First stop, Hawaii,
where the same geological forces that created America
are still bubbling and exploding today.
They're building the most dangerous volcano in America.
This 14,000 foot mountain
is constantly growing.
Molded by forces that shaped and reshaped the earth
over the last four and a half billion years.
As heat rises up from deep inside the earth,
it melts rock and blasts it through the crust.
When it cools,it hardens into a black basalt crust
that builds up over time,layer upon layer.
It has created almost a thousand acres of new land
in less than a half century.
Two and a half thousand miles to the east
on the mainland is much older land,
long,dormant volcanoes have left golden riches
buried in the California rocks.
California is the richest state in the U.S.,
and its good fortune began with its gold.
Todd Bracken has been seeking and finding that gold for 20 years.
This is the most exciting part of my gold mining yet,
this is a 43 gram natural California gold nugget.
A nugget worth a cool  2,500.
California's gold is as old as her hills.
It's been here over 100 million years.
It was forced up to the surface
when the entire continent was on the move.
California rests on top one of
seven massive tectonic plates that make up the earth's crust.
Blazing heat from the earth's core,up to 10,000 degrees
keeps those plates in constant motion.
150 Million years ago,
the North American and Pacific Plates Collided.
The force of that impact pushed up a chain of volcanoes
along what is now the west coast of the United States.
And the Sierra Nevada Mountain Range was born.
This process had another effect.
It seeded rocks throughout California with treasure.
When tectonic plates smash into each other,
things get hot,
and turn solid rock into magma.
Water,super heated by the magma
rip upward through the cracks in the California crust,
carrying gold from deep within the planet.
When the liquid cooled,
the gold solidified into flakes and nuggets
inside the quartz rich veins of the Sierra Nevada.
Good news for California and for this modern day prospector
who is also a jeweler.
Many people like the idea of buying my jewelry
because they know that
it is mined right out of the ground here in California,
and handmade right here in California.
Todd prospects for gold in the shadow of the original 49ers.
The California Gold Rush lasted only 15 busy years.
300,000 Prospectors from all over the world
scooped up more than 70 million ounces.
At today's prices,
their total haul would be worth  130 billion.
California gold helped the union win the war.
It also founded the Hearst and Stanford Dynasties.
So how exactly do you find the gold?
The power of water erodes the rock,
freeing the imbedded gold
and sweeping it downstream.
A boulder like this slows the river water down,
creating a low pressure system behind it.
And when gravel fills in around it,
it sucks and holds the gold in behind boulders like that.
So this is the ideal situation to find gold.
Two years ago
we found 16 ounces
in the course of about six weeks.
Six weeks of work.
A  27,000 pay day.
Todd's prospecting methods haven't changed from
those used by the 49ers.
This is gold panning.
First,you pour the material into the pan
and you give it quite a few shakes,
and what this does is
settle the heavier gold down to the bottom of the pan.
If you pan it too fast,
you run the risk of losing the gold.
Gold.
One, two, three.
That's a nice piece.
The geological forces that
shot gold into the Sierra Nevada's
gave America more than mineral riches,
they built our magnificent landscapes,too.
800 Miles east
and 80 million years later,
they created the greatest mountain range in the U.S.
For tens of millions of years,
the North American Plate
continued to grind up and over the Pacific Plate.
That relentless force contorted and buckled the land,
thrusting up the Rocky Mountains,5 miles into the sky.
The American Rockies run for 1,500 miles,
from Canada to New Mexico.
To the east,they towered above
what would become the Powder River Basin in Wyoming.
Now a dry prairie,
this was once a feted swamp.
The surprising source of another one of America's natural treasures.
Coal.
This ever restless planet possesses awesome power.
It can move mountains,
divert the course of mighty rivers,
and transform millions of square miles of dry land
into a vast,simmering swamp.
How did millions of years of rotting vegetation in just such a swamp
turn into America's most abundant source of fuel?
Coal fuels half of the power stations in America.
Almost half of all that coal
comes from a single valley in Wyoming.
The powder river basin.
It covers over 20,000 square
miles of flat,dry prairie.
Coal from the powder river basin
yields enough electricity for
one in five American homes.
It is nice to be able to help
millions of people out in their daily life.
So they can see at night
alarm clocks can go off in the morning.
They can fix their breakfast.
Dennis Rogg operates a shovel
that loads the mine's gargantuan trucks.
Each one holds 250 tons.
There's about 35 ton of coal in that bucket.
About seven bucket fulls in a truck.
And it goes up in silos,through
crushers into the silos,then
they load it out on the trains from there.
Lynn Huskinson drives one of
our largest loaders in America.
It is as high as a two-story house.
Actually the shovels are more efficient than the loader,
but the loader can get into a tighter place
because it has articulation.
Next step,you need a mile-long train
to put the coal in.
Lots of coal.
Like sometimes five,six,seven trains,
110 coal cars.
That's a good day I think.
I love my job.
I guess I have kind of taken it for granted,
because this is something I've always done.
I started when I was 19 years old.
I'm a native of Wyoming.
It's a beautiful state.
Coal was created here.
55 million years ago.
Back then,this place looked very different.
It was a giant bowl,surrounded
on all sides by mountains.
The climate was radically different then,too.
Subtropical, like Florida.
Warm and wet.
Rivers draining the newly formed.
Rockies drowned the land.
The basin filled up and
it turned into a swamp,teaming with life.
You won't find them in Wyoming today,
but back then,there were
alligators, flamingos, and the
ancestors of today's redwood trees.
When trees and plants die and
fall into a swamp,they can't
decompose,and instead turn into peat.
Over millions of years,
the peat compacts to form coal.
This piece of coal that I picked up here
actually is has a piece of ambrite in it,
which is fossilized tree resin.
About one foot of coal takes about 7 to 10
feet of peat to do that.
We have approximately 100 feet of coal here
that derive from that peat
that accumulated in the swamp over those years.
And this whole deposit the Powder River Basin
there's billions of tons of coal.
Blasting is an easy way to
get at these unusually shallow coal bins.
They cover an area twice the
size of New Jersey.
A legacy from the earth that
keeps America's lights on and
appliances and computers humming.
Enough here for at least another 100 years.
And that's not the only fuel we've got under our American feet.
We've also got
oil.
From Alaska to Texas,
California to Pennsylvania.
But this time the raw ingredients for the fuel
were not dead plants,but dead animals.
360 Million years ago,
three-quarters of the American.
Continent was under a shallow sea.
The ancient sea swarmed with life.
As trillions of these sea creatures died,
their remains build up as thick organic sludge
on the seabed.
When the sludge was buried by
layers of sediment and pressure-cooked
for millions of years inside the earth,
it was transformed into oil.
Heading further east,
we reach the fastest growing oil region in the U.S.
North Dakota.
Here at the Bakken Oil Field,
there are 5400 wells,
each with around 100 workers.
I think it is great,
putting American citizens to work.
It is millions of people that
are having jobs from this,and
doing our economy great.
Derek has worked on oil rigs for the last 20 years.
Once you get mud in your blood,
it just doesn't come out.
Hopefully I get to teach my
children this trade and they
enjoy it as much as I do.
The oil here is trapped
inside porous rock that's more than two miles deep.
When the drill penetrates the oil-rich layers
the rock is shattered by small explosions
and oil is forced up to the surface.
With such heavy and dangerous equipment,
teamwork helps keep the men safe.
Best part of the job is
the people you work with.
Everybody on a rig is important
because no matter what,if that
one person makes a mistake,
it could jeopardize somebody's life
somewhere else on the rig.
Anything there gets loose,if
it hits you,it's gonna hurt.
Depending on the size,
may permanently injure you,may kill You.
The oil reserves beneath North Dakota
will keep these guys in work for at least 50 years.
It really makes you feel good
going home at the end of the day,
and knowing that you've done something good for your country,
and trying to supply for them and
a good day's work.
Oil is turned into a vast range of products,
none more essential than gas for our cars.
American cars and trucks swallow.
378 million gallons of gas a day.
That's more than a gallon for each American citizen.
Every man,woman,and child.
Gold, oil, and coal.
All valuable natural resources
that lie beneath America.
As our eastward trip continues,
we'll find another lucky break.
The super fertile soil of the mid-west.
Midwest,where this nation of
farmers found the perfect land.
Stretching from Kansas to
the Dakotas,Iowa to Ohio is
what's called the fruited plain
in America the beautiful.
The nation's bread basket.
Kevin Ames farms his Ilinois
land like his father and grandfather before him.
Well,it's interesting living
out here and farming for a living.
My family has been doing it over a hundred years.
There is great abundance here.
The fine-grain prairie soil
is perfect for wheat,corn,and soy beans.
Well,this soil is very highly productive.
It's a silty clay-loam soil.
It's probably five or six
percent organic matter.
Has great water-holding ability.
This soil is very dark
and just grows great crops
to help feed illinois and the world.
There's a two-million-year-old
secret behind the richness of this soil.
Right around then,the Great Ice Age arrived.
85% Of the area we now call the
midwest was cloaked in ice.
Glaciers up to a mile high moved
relentlessly across the land.
They ripped up rock and
pulverized anything that stood in their way.
This bulldozing effect ground
the rock into dust.
Almost two million years later
when the ice sheets finally retreated,
they exposed what they crushed.
Rock dust,rich in minerals,
was blown across the land.
And that's why the midwestern
soil is so very fertile.
We had several glaciers come through this area
that helped level the soil,
and grind the stones into soil.
The giant glaciers had a further beneficial effect.
The heavy ice flattened and leveled the landscape.
To work these flat expanses,
American ingenuity created mega machines.
This increased productivity by leaps and bounds
to feed our ever growing population.
I think as a farmer,
a lot of times we take the land for granted,
but we're very fortunate
to live in this rich,
fertile part of the country.
It's something that is a blessing.
The legacy of the Great Ice Age
didn't end with these flat,fertile fields.
When the glaciers melted,
they unleashed billions of gallons of Water.
It surged across the land.
The torrents rerouted ancient Rivers,
eventually creating one mighty river.
The Mississippi.
Today,it's a critical commercial thoroughfare.
The Mississippi connects the agricultural,
industrial,and resource rich northern
and central states to the gulf of mexico.
Water from 31 states flows into this river.
Its million-square-mile watershed
drains 40% of the U.S.
30,000 Barges work the river.
Each year,they transport more
than  20 billion of American goods and commodities.
Steel,cement,coal,and wheat.
Products going all over the World.
It's good for America,you know.
If it comes out of america
and it goes somewhere else,
then it's good for America,
and I'm all for that.
Longer than the ill fated.
Titanic and more than a little tricky to navigate,
Each barge stretches 1,000 feet
or more from bow to stern.
For twenty eight days straight
the barges are home sweet home
to the men that work them.
Our boat is like -- it's a pride thing,you know.
We take care of each other.
Actually,as we love each other.
Yeah, a family thing.
We eat at the dinner table together,
spend Christmas together,Thanksgivings together.
It is a lifestyle.
I love it right now.
You see pleasure boats,
people waving,we wave back.
August this year will be.
13 Years that I been on the river.
Right now,the crew of the virginia Ingram
is navigating the upper reaches of the.
Mississippi,north of st.Louis,Missouri.
A fully laden barge like this
needs an 18-man crew.
We're the eyes and ears of the pilot,you know.
He can't see where he's at,
especially these covered tops,
they can't see the corners.
The lock is 110 wide,
and tow is 105 wide.
So what I see are relate to him on the radio.
He has to trust me.
If he don't trust me,you have catastrophe.
We're a little cog in a big wheel,but,you know,
We try to do our best,work safely,
and keep things going like they should.
Navigating the river on a
mega barge takes enormous skill.
In 1996,
a barge this size lost its steering
and demolished a riverside shopping mall.
Pushed a lot of tonnage.
We've got about 28,000 tons that
we're shoving up through the river system.
And right now,
probably about 1,000 feet to stop.
I like my job.
I like being around the water for some reason.
I don't know,
I always liked it since I was a kid,
being around Water.
It is a cheap means of transportation.
It is what helped build this country.
When these cargos reach their destination,
they're offloaded,bound for other parts of the U.S.
And the rest of the world.
All made possible by melting glaciers.
Off the river and heading east again,
the next stop is michigan.
It's a state endowed with what
is arguably America's greatest natural resource.
Iron.
Michigan's iron drove America's industrial revolution
and literally built modern America.
America has a backbone of solid steel.
It's built our bridges,
railroads, ships, tanks,
factories, cars, and aircraft.
For centuries,
we have dug,carved,blasted
great bands of iron ore out of the ground.
But what made American iron so accessible and
how did it get there in the first place?
The story of america's iron
begins 11 billion years ago.
Earth did not exist.
But iron rich dust left behind
from an ancient exploding star
began to circle and collide in space.
Five and a half billion years later,
our planet was formed.
Heavy elements,which included most of the iron,
sank to form the Earth's molten core.
But some iron remained topside,
trapped in rock in the crust of the ancient planet.
A rich concentration of these rocks is here
in Michigan's upper peninsula.
Michigan mines produce a quarter of America's iron ore.
Driving down the road in an active mine,
so a lot of the rocks in this area
have already been extracted out.
Like our underground stores of oil,
the iron deposits here date back to
when much of our continent was covered in water.
You would have to go 1.85 billion years.
At that time,there would have been a shallow sea in this area.
So we would be under water right now.
The ancient sea ebbed and flowed for a billion years.
Over that time,iron from deeper in the Earth's crust
came up through cracks in the sea bed,carried by super-heated steam.
The iron particles sank and settled on the ocean floor,
mixed between layers of sand.
These are the red banded iron deposits
found in this Michigan mine today.
We know from exploration drilling
that we have at least 3,000 feet
of continuous iron formation.
And in most of the areas here,
we actually have not drilled down
to the bottom of that iron formation yet.
What we got right here is the banded iron formation.
It is a lot harder.
It wears our bits out,
takes longer to drill.
The numbers tells us how deep we are in the hole,
so we don't lose track of what depth we're at.
This is Dearborn, Michigan.
The site of Henry Ford's original steel plant.
Here iron mined from the banded iron ore
is transformed into steel.
24 Automobiles can be made from one single slab of this steel.
Turning iron into steel is not for the faint-hearted.
Carbon and other elements need to be added at extreme temperatures--
up to 3,500 degrees--
seven times hotter than a home oven.
That's why we wear aluminized jackets,
shrouds, spats.
Lt can be pretty frightening at times,
because we have sparks shooting at you,
sometimes you may get a drop of iron coming your way.
You have to really pay attention to what you're doing.
Nothing to play with.
Iron is one of Earth's heaviest metals.
It's so heavy,
it sinks to the bottom of the furnace,
leaving the impurities which are lighter behind.
We have a lot of pressure on the furnace,
and the iron is heavy.
And so when you open the hole,
iron is the first thing that comes out.
More than 11 billion years after its creation,
the iron is returned to its liquid state.
Then the workers add metal alloys to produce steel,
which is much stronger and more malleable than pure iron.
I feel very fortunate that America has given us
all the great resources of iron to make steel,
so we can give them to the rest of the world.
Henry Ford started this a hundred years ago.
We still have some of the original building.
I have great pride to be able to work in this place
that Henry Ford started.
From the iron ore beneath our feet,
American steel has found its way
into millions of automobiles.
Iron has been used to make everything
from skyscraper girders to fire hydrants.
Actually,it's kind of funny.
We'll drive down the road,
and I know that we made a part for that vehicle
or we made steel for that appliance,
and I can say that I was part of that.
As we continue heading east,
we come to a mountain range that,
like the Rockies,
stretches down the entire length of the continent.
Only these mountains are much older
and were much taller.
They were a critical factor
in the success of the earliest European settlers.
The Appalachians.
America,the most powerful land on Earth.
Solid as a rock,right?
Wrong.
Go back a few hundred million years,
and this continent was being battered,bent
and shunted around by forces almost impossible to imagine.
What knocked our continent into
the shape we know today
and created the oldest mountains we have?
It all happened 300 million years ago
when the ancient continents of Europe and North Africa
smashed into the forerunner of North America...
And formed a new super continent -- Pangaea.
The impact was even greater than the geological collision
that formed the Rockies.
It forced up one of the tallest mountain ranges
that has ever been,
although you wouldn't know it today.
The ground here is still moving,
shifting along fault lines left over
from that primeval collision...
and occasionally creating earthquakes,
like the one in Virginia,
felt over much of the eastern U.S.In August,2011.
When they were first formed,
the Appalachians were jagged and higher
than the Himalayas.
Like all old mountains,
they have eroded down to gentler slopes,
little more than hills
running 2,000 miles
from Alabama to Canada.
They may be old,
but they still yield natural riches.
The northern end of the range
dominates the interior of Maine.
Here, the worn-down mountains
are shrouded in 17 million acres of forest.
Trees cover 80% of the state.
Dick Slike manages the forest.
If you look at the state of Maine
and think of its geologic history,
of course,the mountains were built ages ago.
They're ancient,ancient mountains,
and the bedrock is granite.
Over time, that rock
that rock has eroded
and donated its valuable minerals to the forest soil.
And,of course,then you have the trees dropping the leaves,
which becomes humus.
And so the soil becomes a thin layer of inorganic soil
topped by a thick layer of leaves and needles
and things that become an organic component.
Maine's logging industry is worth  4 billion a year,
and it has been important economically for hundreds of years.
My father was a logger.
His father before him was a logger.
They basically started logging
when they came over here from Scotland and England,
so it goes back a long ways.
The forests that grow on the Appalachian slopes
up and down the eastern U.S.Were a vital resource
for both Native Americans and early settlers from Europe.
I think when people came across on the wooden ships,
instantly people that had worked wood in Scandinavia or Europe
saw the potential.
They built their homes out of the wood.
It was a basic building block that got people started.
The first Europeans arrived in Maine in 1609.
The Appalachian forest gave them
not only the means to survive,
but to expand.
[Sandian]Started to build,
they took the trees down all over the state of Maine,
pushed them down the rivers to Bangor and those places,
sawed them into boards,
and basically built America with those boards.
Boards from Appalachian timber are still used
to build American homes,churches,and railroad ties.
And Maine's logging industry supports more than 50,000 jobs.
I honestly believe that you couldn't live without logging
because you basically build your houses out of it,
a lot of people keep warm by it,and it's real important.
I think the forests of Maine will definitely help give America
its future and its shape.
There's always going to be vast forest production here.
Appalachian rock underpins more than just economic success.
It's the solid platform that allowed New York City
to reach for the sky.
Along the Atlantic coast,
mountains are so eroded
that you would hardly know they're there.
But the bedrock remains
and plays a surprisingly important role.
It gives a solid base for the skyscrapers of Manhattan.
The higher these buildings rise into the sky,
the more they have to be rooted into the earth beneath.
This is ground zero,
site of the new World Trade Center -
the biggest civil engineering project in America.
Here,the hard,eroded bedrock of the Appalachians
will soon support seven soaring towers.
The first - 52 stories high - has already been built.
Engineers have dug over 100 feet down
into the ancient bedrock.
Right now,we are about 74 feet below sea level.
So we're standing on a rock excavation,
and the natural bedrock was probably 10 or 15 feet higher
than where I'm standing right now.
It's actually a very hard rock.
It was originally soft,sedimentary rock
and was transformed into hard,crystalline rock
when the continents collided.
The heat and the pressure changed the rock
from the original components
into this crystalline rock that we have now
that allows us to put these building loads on top of it.
There's no question there would have been a settlement here,
and probably a city,
but not this city -
not without its natural platform for building up.
I grew up here,I live here,it's great.
But,you know,just think of the history of Manhattan,
you know,it's where it all started.
America began,yeah,the pilgrims came to other parts,
but they all came to New York
because it was a great place to build a city.
The hard bedrock meant that
some of the first-ever skyscrapers were built here.
And today,
the city has the most famous skyscrapers in the world.
You've got the Chrysler Building,
and then,of course,we've got the Empire State Building.
That's,you know,everyone thinks of New York,
they think of the Chrysler Building
and the Empire State Building.
They're all sitting on bedrock.
But Manhattan's bedrock isn't totally flat.
In some places it curves downward,
and the depressions have been filled in
with softer, younger rock.
Under Greenwich Village,
a dip in the bedrock below is mirrored above ground
by a dip in the skyline.
In Midtown,where the bedrock is nearer the surface,
the skyscrapers reappear.
A 21st-century American city
built upon foundations created 300 million years ago.
When the Appalachians were thrown up,
they were the greatest mountains on Earth.
100 Million years later,
the supercontinent,Pangaea,split apart.
North America,
in more or less the same shape we know it today,
was born.
In our journey across America,
we've found tremendous riches
that have come from beneath our feet -
volcanic outpourings of lava in our most western state...
gold that helped create California's wealth...
coal and oil from living plants and animals
that once thrived in ancient seas and swamps...
iron from which we have built our cars,bridges,and railroads...
timber to build our houses...
and the rock foundations of our mighty skyscrapers.
Over billions of years,the land that was to become the U.S.A.
Was endowed with greater geological riches
than any other nation on Earth.
It's taken centuries of invention,industry and skill
for us to dig,blast,and tease those resources -
what lies beneath America - out of the ground.
Nature's raw power and the courage of the American people
have been the unstoppable forces
that made us the rich and powerful nation we are today.
M 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
YYeTs.com
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0