1
00:00:50,610 --> 00:01:20,610
{\an7}{\pos(39.5,211)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14 

2
00:00:50,610 --> 00:01:20,610
{\pos(51.4,231.16)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 

3
00:00:50,610 --> 00:01:20,610
{\pos(27.7,188.26)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 

5
00:00:50,610 --> 00:00:55,610
{\an4}本字幕由YYeTs字幕組原創翻譯
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流

6
00:00:55,610 --> 00:01:00,610
{\an4}{\pos(57.12,210.56)}翻譯   aaaBao  冰藍

7
00:01:00,610 --> 00:01:05,610
{\an4}{\pos(57.12,210.56)}翻譯  roaddog

8
00:01:05,610 --> 00:01:10,610
{\an4}{\pos(57.12,210.56)}校對  roaddog

9
00:01:10,610 --> 00:01:15,610
{\an4}時間軸 aaaBao

10
00:01:15,610 --> 00:01:20,610
{\an4}{\pos(57.12,210.56)}后期 斯人  總監 roaddog

11
00:01:20,610 --> 00:01:25,610
{\an4}{\pos(70,211.2)}打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息

12
00:01:20,610 --> 00:01:30,610
{\an7}{\pos(22.2,180.8)} m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340

13
00:00:07,310 --> 00:00:08,910
你知道什么讓我很生氣嗎
You know what makes me really mad?

14
00:00:09,370 --> 00:00:11,690
種族歧視  階級歧視
Racism? Classism?

15
00:00:12,270 --> 00:00:13,770
我不知道別的"歧視"了
I don't know any more isms.

16
00:00:14,510 --> 00:00:15,930
我沒有升職
I didn't get the promotion.

17
00:00:16,430 --> 00:00:17,920
當然啦  他們給一個男人升職了
They gave it to a guy, of course,

18
00:00:17,920 --> 00:00:19,910
我在公司待的時間是他的兩倍
who's been there half the time I have.

19
00:00:20,230 --> 00:00:22,460
他肯定也只有你一半的能力吧
I bet he's only half as qualified too.

20
00:00:22,530 --> 00:00:23,870
那是性別歧視
That's sexism.

21
00:00:24,560 --> 00:00:25,820
又一個歧視
Another ism.

22
00:00:26,360 --> 00:00:27,860
加比  我真的很生氣
Gabi, I'm really upset.

23
00:00:28,280 --> 00:00:30,570
索菲亞  如果你覺得生氣  那你就該辭職
Sofia, if you feel that way then you should just quit.

24
00:00:31,300 --> 00:00:33,490
-我辭了  -什么
- I did. - What?

25
00:00:35,270 --> 00:00:36,680
我們要怎么付賬單啊
How are we gonna pay our bills?

26
00:00:36,680 --> 00:00:38,050
我們要怎么付房租啊
How are we gonna pay our rent?

27
00:00:38,060 --> 00:00:39,800
你在瑞士的時候我還幫你
Hey, how about a little support for the girl

28
00:00:39,800 --> 00:00:41,970
付房租好嗎  支持我一下會死嗎
who floated your rent when you were in Switzerland?

29
00:00:41,970 --> 00:00:44,510
我還放棄了有線電視  好讓你買廚師刀
Or who gave up cable so that you could have chef's knives?

30
00:00:44,510 --> 00:00:47,930
我真的需要一個擁抱和一盤曲奇
And who really needs a hug and a roll of cookie dough.

31
00:00:48,080 --> 00:00:50,740
好吧  知道嗎  你說得對
Oh, okay. No, you know what? You're right.

32
00:00:50,740 --> 00:00:52,020
會沒事的
It's gonna be fine.

33
00:00:52,770 --> 00:00:55,220
好棒哦  你辭職了
Yeah, you quit your job.

34
00:01:13,500 --> 00:01:16,220
{\an8}饑餓的青春
第二季  第十三集

35
00:01:34,490 --> 00:01:36,460
加比  給他們準備點咖啡
Gabi, how bout some coffee for these guys?

36
00:01:36,460 --> 00:01:37,590
我不確定那是不是個好主意
I don't know if that's a good idea,

37
00:01:37,590 --> 00:01:39,460
我來之后他們都沒眨過眼
they haven't blinked since I got here.

38
00:01:40,420 --> 00:01:42,010
他們可能沉浸在面試的氛圍中
They're probably just in the zone for their interview.

39
00:01:42,010 --> 00:01:44,410
我要雇一個帶薪實習生  幫忙推出新應用
I'm hiring a paid intern to help me roll out my new app.

40
00:01:44,610 --> 00:01:46,520
我知道一個需要薪水的人
I know somebody who needs to get paid.

41
00:01:46,650 --> 00:01:47,730
索菲亞
Sofia.

42
00:01:48,960 --> 00:01:51,010
加比  這些人都是工商管理碩士
Gabi, these guys all have MBA's.

43
00:01:51,320 --> 00:01:53,670
喬什  我不在乎籃球啦
Josh, I don't care about basketball.

44
00:01:55,570 --> 00:01:57,670
我在乎的是索菲亞找到工作  好嗎
I care about Sofia getting a job, okay?

45
00:01:57,670 --> 00:01:59,030
你能面試一下她嗎
Will you please just interview her?

46
00:01:59,030 --> 00:02:00,760
你這樣讓我很尷尬啊
You're putting me in a really awkward position.

47
00:02:01,120 --> 00:02:02,590
我現在應該習慣了
Which I should be used to by now.

48
00:02:03,100 --> 00:02:04,970
面試一下她嘛  你可能會大吃一驚的
Just give her an interview. You might be surprised.

49
00:02:04,970 --> 00:02:06,930
雖然我們是好閨蜜  但一點也不像
I mean we are best friends but we are nothing alike.

50
00:02:06,930 --> 00:02:08,110
成交
Sold.

51
00:02:08,600 --> 00:02:09,810
讓她一小時內過來
Have her here in an hour.

52
00:02:10,080 --> 00:02:11,140
謝謝
Thank you.

53
00:02:11,140 --> 00:02:13,170
如果她不是最合適的候選人
And if she's not the best interview you've ever had

54
00:02:13,180 --> 00:02:14,520
我就免費工作
I will work for free.

55
00:02:14,520 --> 00:02:16,140
不  玩脫了
No, went too far. 

56
00:02:16,570 --> 00:02:18,380
我的意思是  她會很棒的
The point is, she will be great 

57
00:02:18,380 --> 00:02:20,890
你還是得付我工資  日安  先生
and you will still have to pay me. Good day, sir.

58
00:02:25,980 --> 00:02:29,070
你真是個可愛的小紅帽
Well, you're an adorable little red riding hood.

59
00:02:29,950 --> 00:02:32,230
你的聲音真低沉  外婆
What a deep voice you have, grandmother.

60
00:02:33,590 --> 00:02:35,700
我不想這樣  這很古怪
You know what, I'm not feeling this, it's weird.

61
00:02:37,610 --> 00:02:39,690
我媽媽給你送了烤布丁
My mother dropped off a kugel for you,

62
00:02:39,690 --> 00:02:41,850
因為她喜歡你
'cause she adores you.

63
00:02:42,530 --> 00:02:44,650
我真高興你和我媽處得好
I love that you and my mom get along.

64
00:02:44,680 --> 00:02:47,090
我什么時候跟你媽媽見面啊
So when the hell am I gonna meet your mother?

65
00:02:47,660 --> 00:02:51,270
我們得做這件事嗎
Oh, is that a thing? That we have to do?

66
00:02:52,220 --> 00:02:53,220
怎么回事
What's going on?

67
00:02:53,220 --> 00:02:55,550
你覺得我丟人嗎  我不夠好嗎
Are you embarrassed of me? Am I not good enough?

68
00:02:55,550 --> 00:02:57,400
你跟她說我是韓國人嗎
Did you tell her I was Korean?

69
00:02:59,320 --> 00:03:01,550
問題不在你身上  而是她
It's not you, it's her.

70
00:03:01,550 --> 00:03:04,280
我媽媽超刻薄
My mom is crazy mean.

71
00:03:04,310 --> 00:03:07,640
像是矮小的亞洲版西蒙·考威爾[美偶評委]
Like a short, Asian, Simon Cowell.

72
00:03:08,900 --> 00:03:11,300
那我可以做她的瑞安·西克雷斯特[美偶主持人]
And I can be her Ryan Seacrest.

73
00:03:13,810 --> 00:03:16,340
別擔心  媽媽們都很喜歡我
Don't worry, moms love me.

74
00:03:16,340 --> 00:03:17,960
我們會成為一家人的
And we're gonna be family.

75
00:03:21,400 --> 00:03:23,330
你跟她說我們訂婚了吧
You have told her we're engaged?

76
00:03:23,960 --> 00:03:26,210
加比在我父母面前幫我出柜
Gabi's the one that outed me to my parents.

77
00:03:26,320 --> 00:03:29,190
她告訴他們訂婚也就是時間問題
Only a matter of time before she tells them this.

78
00:03:29,550 --> 00:03:31,080
艾略特  如果你不打電話給你媽
Elliot, if you don't call your mom 

79
00:03:31,090 --> 00:03:32,380
邀請她這周末過來
and invite her over this weekend,

80
00:03:32,380 --> 00:03:33,890
我的烤布丁就不給你吃
you're not getting my kugel.

81
00:03:35,400 --> 00:03:37,220
你應該明白那句話是什么意思
And I think you know what that means.

82
00:03:43,000 --> 00:03:45,590
親愛的  你知道案板是空的吧
Oh, honey, you know you're not chopping anything, right?

83
00:03:45,590 --> 00:03:46,210
我在假裝工作
I'm pretending to work

84
00:03:46,210 --> 00:03:48,460
喬什正在面試索菲亞
while Sofia finishes her interview with Josh.

85
00:03:49,070 --> 00:03:51,450
懂了  就像我假裝戒酒
I get it. I'm pretending to be sober.

86
00:03:54,030 --> 00:03:55,150
怎么樣
Hey, how'd it go?

87
00:03:55,160 --> 00:03:57,610
超棒  我都能教一堂如何做到超棒的課了
Crushed it! I could teach a class on crushing it.

88
00:03:57,620 --> 00:03:59,300
但是我會忙著做我的新工作
But I'm gonna be too busy in my fancy new job

89
00:03:59,300 --> 00:04:00,780
而我做得超棒
where I will be crushing it.

90
00:04:00,780 --> 00:04:01,770
真好
Yeah!

91
00:04:01,770 --> 00:04:03,510
真是太好了  我們要做同事了
This is so great, we're gonna be working together.

92
00:04:03,510 --> 00:04:05,820
就像我們做夏令營顧問那時候一樣
It's gonna be just like when we were camp counselors,

93
00:04:05,820 --> 00:04:08,960
不過我們現在可沒法再失貞了
except with no pesky virginity to lose.

94
00:04:09,660 --> 00:04:10,530
沒錯
Yeah!

95
00:04:10,540 --> 00:04:13,350
我要跟魯本共進午餐  因為
Well, I am going to lunch with Reuben because, well,

96
00:04:13,360 --> 00:04:16,630
我覺得他要對我說L打頭的字[愛]了
I don't know. I think he's about to drop the l-word.

97
00:04:17,130 --> 00:04:18,820
我愛這個字
I l-word the l-word.

98
00:04:19,140 --> 00:04:22,360
我也是  這是最棒的一天了  謝謝
Me too! This is the best day ever, thank you!

99
00:04:22,370 --> 00:04:24,490
-不客氣  拜拜  -拜拜
- Welcome. Bye. - Bye.

100
00:04:27,130 --> 00:04:29,200
索菲亞很棒吧
Isn't Sofia amazing?

101
00:04:29,200 --> 00:04:31,350
她很聰明  很有商業頭腦
She's smart, she has a good head for business,

102
00:04:31,350 --> 00:04:32,600
很干凈
she's clean.

103
00:04:34,040 --> 00:04:36,630
沒錯  她的確有那些優點
You're right, she is all of those things.

104
00:04:38,060 --> 00:04:39,320
但我要聘德克斯特
But I'm gonna go with Dexter.

105
00:04:39,320 --> 00:04:41,420
他有斯坦福大學的商學院學位  業余時間里
He's got a business degree from Stanford and in his spare time

106
00:04:41,420 --> 00:04:43,210
還研究人工智能
he researches artificial intelligence.

107
00:04:44,990 --> 00:04:47,120
但是索菲亞有真人智能
But Sofia's intelligence is real.

108
00:04:48,690 --> 00:04:51,570
加比  對不起  我下定決心了
Gabi, look, I'm sorry. I made up my mind.

109
00:04:52,210 --> 00:04:53,570
你想讓我跟她說這個消息嗎
Do you want me to break the news to her?

110
00:04:53,870 --> 00:04:55,620
不  我回去再跟她說
No, I'll do it when I get home.

111
00:04:55,620 --> 00:04:57,460
最好是朋友來說
It's better coming from a friend.

112
00:04:57,880 --> 00:04:59,150
等等  最后一個問題
Wait, last question.

113
00:05:00,540 --> 00:05:02,790
我可以雇傭一個實習...
Is it possible that I could hire an intern?

114
00:05:06,980 --> 00:05:08,870
索菲亞  我有事要告...
Hey, Sofia, I got something to tell you.

115
00:05:11,300 --> 00:05:13,350
不不  他說讓我告訴你的
No, no, no, he said I could tell you.

116
00:05:13,350 --> 00:05:16,190
等等  魯本為什么要讓你跟我說分手啊
Wait, why would Ruben tell you to break up with me?

117
00:05:17,040 --> 00:05:19,930
因為他是個懦夫窩囊廢
'Cause he's a candy ass, little baby man.

118
00:05:21,190 --> 00:05:23,670
真遺憾
Oh, I'm so sorry.

119
00:05:24,680 --> 00:05:26,640
他的確說了L打頭的字
He dropped the l-word all right.

120
00:05:26,880 --> 00:05:29,280
"放開我胳膊  索菲亞  我們結束了"
"Let go of my arm, Sofia. It's over."

121
00:05:30,780 --> 00:05:34,440
天啊  我真是糟透了  沒男友  沒工作
God, I suck. I've got no man, no job.

122
00:05:34,920 --> 00:05:36,510
得到在喬什那的工作機會
The only shred of hope I have left

123
00:05:36,520 --> 00:05:38,730
是我僅存的希望了
is if I get that job at Josh's.

124
00:05:40,670 --> 00:05:42,350
關于這希望...
Yeah, about that shred.

125
00:05:42,740 --> 00:05:44,660
沒成  對嗎
I didn't get it, did I?

126
00:05:53,180 --> 00:05:55,660
你讓喬什...
The only thing you blew...

127
00:05:56,270 --> 00:05:58,660
大吃一驚
was Josh's mind.

128
00:05:59,390 --> 00:06:00,390
什么意思
What do you mean?

129
00:06:00,400 --> 00:06:02,030
我是說你...
I mean you, uh...

130
00:06:02,740 --> 00:06:04,330
-你...  -我得到那工作了嗎
- you, uh... - I got the job?

131
00:06:04,330 --> 00:06:05,650
我得到工作啦
I got the job!

132
00:06:06,620 --> 00:06:07,770
貌似是這樣的
It appears that way.

133
00:06:07,770 --> 00:06:10,460
天吶  你為什么不早點發短信告訴我
Oh, my God! Why didn't you text me earlier?

134
00:06:10,470 --> 00:06:13,060
因為我想要看你聽到...
'Cause I, wanted to see your face when you...

135
00:06:13,060 --> 00:06:14,100
這條消息時的表情
you heard the news.

136
00:06:14,110 --> 00:06:15,510
謝天謝地  我太開心了
Thank God, I'm so happy!

137
00:06:15,520 --> 00:06:17,600
謝謝  這真是太不可思議了
Thank you, this is unbelievable!

138
00:06:17,600 --> 00:06:19,020
的確如此
It sure is.

139
00:06:25,190 --> 00:06:26,330
你在干嗎
What are you doing?

140
00:06:26,330 --> 00:06:28,890
現在九點  我要讓鐘變成九點半
Oh, it's nine o'clock and I need it to be nine-thirty.

141
00:06:30,300 --> 00:06:32,230
你知道時間不是這么算的吧
You know that's not how time works, huh?

142
00:06:33,050 --> 00:06:35,230
我知道  但我昨晚我到家時索菲亞很傷心
I know, but Sofia was so depressed when I got home last night,

143
00:06:35,230 --> 00:06:36,100
我不忍心告訴她
I didn't have the heart to tell her

144
00:06:36,100 --> 00:06:37,100
她沒被錄用
she didn't get the internship, 

145
00:06:37,100 --> 00:06:38,670
所以我得在她第一天
so, I gotta get Josh out of here

146
00:06:38,670 --> 00:06:41,740
上這不存在的班之前  把喬什支走
before she gets here for her fake first day.

147
00:06:43,210 --> 00:06:45,070
在我沒想出來怎么辦之前  你能先配合我嗎
Can you just play along until I figure out what to do?

148
00:06:45,080 --> 00:06:46,370
求你了  讓我做什么都行
Please? I'll do anything.

149
00:06:46,920 --> 00:06:48,070
什么都行嗎
Anything?

150
00:06:49,120 --> 00:06:50,490
你能寫個保證嗎
Can I get that in writing?

151
00:06:50,520 --> 00:06:53,540
不  不對  不能留下筆跡
No, no, no. Scratch that. No paper trail.

152
00:06:56,630 --> 00:06:57,670
早上好
Good morning.

153
00:06:57,670 --> 00:07:00,470
喬什  我打包好你的早餐了
Oh, hey Josh. Listen, I packed your breakfast to go

154
00:07:00,470 --> 00:07:02,650
這樣你開會就不會遲到了  再見
so you're not late for your meeting, goodbye.

155
00:07:02,650 --> 00:07:04,420
加比  來得及  還有一個小時才開會呢
Gabi, I'm fine. The meeting's in an hour.

156
00:07:04,420 --> 00:07:07,050
真的嗎
Oh, oh, ho-ho, really?

157
00:07:08,100 --> 00:07:09,500
鐘肯定壞掉了
Well, that clock must be broken

158
00:07:09,500 --> 00:07:10,940
因為我手表顯示的是九點
because my watch says it's nine o' clock.

159
00:07:10,940 --> 00:07:13,930
難道說我準時來上班了嗎
Oh, so I'm on time for work?

160
00:07:15,080 --> 00:07:16,670
該死  我的表壞了
Son of a bitch, my watch is broken.

161
00:07:17,460 --> 00:07:18,280
叫艾略特拿去修
Have Elliot fix this.

162
00:07:18,280 --> 00:07:20,280
-好的  再見  -我要遲到了
- Okay, all right, good bye. - I'm gonna be late.

163
00:07:23,650 --> 00:07:25,110
你好
Hi!

164
00:07:25,290 --> 00:07:27,870
我來這上班了
I'm here, at my job!

165
00:07:28,850 --> 00:07:30,820
照你吩咐  我買了咖啡
And I brought coffee like you asked me to.

166
00:07:31,150 --> 00:07:32,580
喬什在哪
Okay, so where's Josh?

167
00:07:32,630 --> 00:07:34,050
他剛走
Ah, you just missed him.

168
00:07:34,070 --> 00:07:34,790
不過  別擔心
But, don't worry,

169
00:07:34,790 --> 00:07:36,880
他給我留了一份清單要你做
he left me a list of things for you to get started on.

170
00:07:36,880 --> 00:07:39,600
首先要做的是...
The first of which is to...

171
00:07:40,030 --> 00:07:43,090
給他辦公室里的所有東西拍照
take pictures of everything in his office.

172
00:07:44,720 --> 00:07:45,880
為什么
Why?

173
00:07:46,870 --> 00:07:48,270
為什么呢
Why indeed.

174
00:07:49,640 --> 00:07:52,280
以防著火之后他要把屋里的一切
In case there's a fire and he has to recreate everything

175
00:07:52,280 --> 00:07:54,180
恢復成原來的樣子
in a second location, duh.

176
00:07:55,930 --> 00:07:58,660
有錢人真怪
Oh, rich people are weird.

177
00:07:59,920 --> 00:08:01,170
尤蘭達
Hey, Yolanda.

178
00:08:01,170 --> 00:08:03,150
上班妹子
Hey, working girl.

179
00:08:06,260 --> 00:08:07,970
不好  她來了
Oh no, she's here!

180
00:08:07,980 --> 00:08:09,590
她來了
She's here!

181
00:08:11,350 --> 00:08:13,180
天吶  這一整天我和她要做什么
Oh God, what am I gonna do with her all day?

182
00:08:13,550 --> 00:08:17,810
向她介紹這快速發展的美妙修表業
Introduce her to the exciting fast-paced world of watch repair.

183
00:08:18,750 --> 00:08:20,280
喬什讓你拿去修
Josh wants you to get that fixed.

184
00:08:25,220 --> 00:08:27,650
你好  媽媽  很高興見到你
Hello, mother, it's lovely to see you.

185
00:08:27,670 --> 00:08:30,790
你那肥臉還能看得見人  真是不錯
It's lovely you can see at all with those fat cheeks.

186
00:08:34,020 --> 00:08:35,400
難以置信
This is incredible.

187
00:08:35,770 --> 00:08:37,480
我應該把這些話都記下來
I feel like I should be taking notes.

188
00:08:39,560 --> 00:08:40,650
媽媽
Mother,

189
00:08:41,120 --> 00:08:42,610
我想給你看點東西
I want to show you something.

190
00:08:42,950 --> 00:08:44,410
天吶
Oh, my God!

191
00:08:44,700 --> 00:08:46,930
你找到戴得上的戒指了
You found a ring that fits you.

192
00:08:48,040 --> 00:08:49,290
我想跟你談的就是這事
That's why I wanted to talk to you,

193
00:08:49,290 --> 00:08:51,850
一個完美男人向我求婚了
a wonderful man has asked me to marry him.

194
00:08:54,410 --> 00:08:57,140
真奢華
Whoa, fancy.

195
00:08:58,960 --> 00:09:01,470
更奢華
Whoa, fancier.

196
00:09:02,930 --> 00:09:05,120
喬什喜歡貴的東西
Yeah, well, Josh has expensive tastes.

197
00:09:05,150 --> 00:09:06,430
喬什嗎
Josh?

198
00:09:09,390 --> 00:09:12,110
帕克夫人  艾略特沒跟我說你要來
Mrs. Park. Elliot didn't tell me you were stopping by.

199
00:09:12,660 --> 00:09:16,150
他剛跟我說他訂婚了
He just told me about the engagement!

200
00:09:17,130 --> 00:09:18,510
是不是很讓人興奮
Isn't it exciting?

201
00:09:19,230 --> 00:09:20,170
世上的男人們  對不起
Sorry men of the world,

202
00:09:20,170 --> 00:09:22,350
艾略特·帕克已經名花有主了
Elliot Park is of the market.

203
00:09:24,920 --> 00:09:26,020
我開會要遲到了
Hey, I'm late for a meeting.

204
00:09:26,020 --> 00:09:27,340
我忘了拿我辦公室里的包
I just forgot a bag in my office.

205
00:09:27,340 --> 00:09:29,230
我去拿  我去拿
I'll get it! I'll get it! I'll get it!

206
00:09:31,430 --> 00:09:33,520
帕克夫人  很高興見到你
Mrs. Park, always good to see you.

207
00:09:33,720 --> 00:09:35,120
我也是
You, too...

208
00:09:37,110 --> 00:09:38,870
女婿
Son-in-law.

209
00:09:39,540 --> 00:09:42,550
你怎么做到的   胖小姐拉貝爾
How did you score that, Miss Fatty Labelle?

210
00:09:39,540 --> 00:09:42,550
{\an8}圖片分享網上的紅人

211
00:09:46,040 --> 00:09:47,630
索菲亞  我剛想起來
Sofia, uh, I just remembered,

212
00:09:47,630 --> 00:09:49,680
喬什要你把那盆植物移到門后去
Josh wants you to move that plant behind the door!

213
00:09:49,680 --> 00:09:51,520
-什么  -別問我了
- What? - Stop questioning me!

214
00:09:59,250 --> 00:10:02,040
-現在做什么  -繼續干活
- Now what? - Okay, uh, now back to business.

215
00:10:02,040 --> 00:10:06,040
喬什要你...
Uh, now Josh wants you to, uh...

216
00:10:06,040 --> 00:10:09,460
在剩下的時間里
Uh...ah, oh, work on these files

217
00:10:09,570 --> 00:10:12,820
回家處理這些文件
ah, for the rest of the day, from home.

218
00:10:12,820 --> 00:10:15,520
為什么我不能在這里弄呢
Oh, well why can't I just work on them here?

219
00:10:17,900 --> 00:10:19,140
索菲亞  我哪知道
Sofia, I don't know. 

220
00:10:19,140 --> 00:10:21,260
喬什是個天才
I mean, uh, Josh is a genius, you know. 

221
00:10:21,260 --> 00:10:23,010
你會問愛因斯坦
Would you ask Albert Einstein 

222
00:10:23,010 --> 00:10:25,590
為什么他在家工作嗎
why he would work on his files from home?

223
00:10:25,590 --> 00:10:27,760
不會  因為他死了
No, because he's dead.

224
00:10:31,690 --> 00:10:32,530
喬什
Josh,

225
00:10:32,530 --> 00:10:34,770
出了點狀況
a situation has presented itself.

226
00:10:35,420 --> 00:10:38,770
我媽媽好像以為你是我未婚夫
It seems that my mother thinks you're my fiance.

227
00:10:40,510 --> 00:10:41,730
不好笑嗎
Isn't that funny?

228
00:10:42,560 --> 00:10:43,260
不
No.

229
00:10:43,260 --> 00:10:44,990
好笑的地方在于
But here's the funny part,

230
00:10:45,160 --> 00:10:48,510
由于覺得你喜歡我  她也喜歡我了
she likes me because she thinks you like me.

231
00:10:48,510 --> 00:10:49,990
你知道誰真的喜歡你嗎
You know who really likes you? 

232
00:10:50,160 --> 00:10:52,970
埃蘭  你真正的未婚夫
Alan, your actual fiance.

233
00:10:53,450 --> 00:10:56,830
我也愛他  但不保證媽媽也喜歡他
And I love him too, but there's no guarantee that mother will.

234
00:10:56,830 --> 00:10:58,870
她終于對我友好起來了
She's finally being nice to me.

235
00:10:58,980 --> 00:11:01,600
感覺真的超爽
It feels good, it feels real good.

236
00:11:02,500 --> 00:11:04,830
你就不能假裝一晚我未婚夫
Can't you just pretend to be my fiance for one night

237
00:11:04,830 --> 00:11:06,610
直到她明天走嗎
until she leaves tomorrow?

238
00:11:06,620 --> 00:11:07,750
不能
No.

239
00:11:08,230 --> 00:11:09,620
你不懂
You don't understand.

240
00:11:09,680 --> 00:11:12,130
她第一次夸獎了我
She gave me my first compliment ever.

241
00:11:12,790 --> 00:11:15,420
說我肥得剛剛好
She said my weight gain is plateauing nicely.

242
00:11:16,510 --> 00:11:17,980
求你了  求你了
Please, oh please, oh please, oh please,

243
00:11:17,980 --> 00:11:20,320
求你了  求你了
oh please, oh please, oh please, oh please, oh please.

244
00:11:20,320 --> 00:11:21,480
-求你了  -好吧
- please. - All right!

245
00:11:21,480 --> 00:11:22,750
好棒
Yeah!

246
00:11:25,400 --> 00:11:26,650
還有  今晚
FYI, tonight,

247
00:11:26,650 --> 00:11:28,980
你可不能那么冷血哦
You're going to need to be a little bit less of a cold bitch. 

248
00:11:28,980 --> 00:11:30,010
謝謝
Thanks.

249
00:11:36,160 --> 00:11:40,040
天啊  加比  我發現一件大事
Oh my god, Gabi, I discovered something huge.

250
00:11:40,670 --> 00:11:43,050
是發現你不想替喬什工作了嗎
That you don't want to work for Josh anymore?

251
00:11:44,360 --> 00:11:46,090
我在看你給我的文件
I was looking through the files you gave me

252
00:11:46,090 --> 00:11:47,890
發現他的新應用
and I found a patent application

253
00:11:47,900 --> 00:11:49,940
有個專利申請書沒簽字
for his new app that he never signed,

254
00:11:49,940 --> 00:11:53,240
但因為我發現了  他可以補救回來  省幾百萬
But because I found it he can fix it and save millions.

255
00:11:54,210 --> 00:11:58,130
我讓你看有沒有拼寫錯誤  不是幫他省錢
Yeah, see I told you to look for typos, not save him millions.

256
00:11:59,050 --> 00:12:01,500
我知道  是不是好棒
I know, isn't it great?

257
00:12:02,320 --> 00:12:04,550
我明天一早就去告訴他這事
I'm gonna tell him all about it first thing in the morning.

258
00:12:04,550 --> 00:12:05,850
不  不行
No, no you're not.

259
00:12:06,300 --> 00:12:07,620
我不行嗎
Ah, I'm not?

260
00:12:09,630 --> 00:12:10,950
索菲亞
Sofia...

261
00:12:13,990 --> 00:12:15,450
這真的很難說出口
this is really hard for me to say,

262
00:12:15,450 --> 00:12:16,750
但我跟你說的
but there may have been something

263
00:12:16,750 --> 00:12:18,780
喬什的那個工作
about the job at Josh's that I told you

264
00:12:18,780 --> 00:12:20,970
可能不完全是真話
that wasn't 100 percent true.

265
00:12:22,110 --> 00:12:23,660
-什么  -你沒被錄用
- What? - That you have it.

266
00:12:24,320 --> 00:12:25,550
什么
What?

267
00:12:26,010 --> 00:12:27,570
其實喬什沒錄用你
Josh didn't actually hire you.

268
00:12:27,570 --> 00:12:30,820
我騙你說錄用了  是因為魯本跟你分手
I lied and I said that he did because Reuben broke up with you

269
00:12:30,820 --> 00:12:32,370
你特別傷心
and you were really sad.

270
00:12:33,470 --> 00:12:34,610
什么
What?

271
00:12:35,130 --> 00:12:36,840
我知道  真對不起  好嗎
I know, I'm really sorry, okay?

272
00:12:36,840 --> 00:12:38,550
你辭職以后  我慌了
When you quit your job I freaked out

273
00:12:38,550 --> 00:12:40,910
-然后...  -你猜怎么著  沒關系
- and-- - Well, you know what, it doesn't even matter.

274
00:12:41,980 --> 00:12:44,150
-太好了  -不  別碰我
- Yeah. - No, get off me!

275
00:12:45,020 --> 00:12:47,960
因為我還是要告訴喬什  我說了以后
Because I'm gonna tell Josh what I found and when I do

276
00:12:47,960 --> 00:12:49,630
他會錄用我的
he's gonna give me a job. 

277
00:12:51,700 --> 00:12:53,960
那他會不會也開除我
Will he or will he not and also fire me?

278
00:12:54,770 --> 00:12:56,500
加比  他為什么要開除你
Gabi, why would he fire you?

279
00:12:56,570 --> 00:12:59,120
因為我覺得盜竊機密文件
Ah, because I think stealing confidential files

280
00:12:59,120 --> 00:13:01,890
交給自己室友不是好事
and giving them to your roommate is frowned upon.

281
00:13:02,740 --> 00:13:04,580
好吧
Okay, well, hmm.

282
00:13:04,680 --> 00:13:08,360
負責任的做法是去找喬什  好嗎
The responsible thing to do is to just go to Josh, okay,

283
00:13:08,360 --> 00:13:10,470
把事情原原本本地告訴他
and we're just gonna tell him everything that happened.

284
00:13:12,420 --> 00:13:13,970
或者...
Or...

285
00:13:15,770 --> 00:13:19,000
或者按你現在想出來的蠢辦法做
Or we could do whatever stupid plan you're thinking of now.

286
00:13:20,120 --> 00:13:22,290
-太好了  -不  別碰我
- Yeah. - No, get off of me!

287
00:13:26,660 --> 00:13:27,910
喬什
Josh,

288
00:13:27,940 --> 00:13:31,900
我希望你們收下這個做訂婚禮物
I want you to have this as an engagement present.

289
00:13:35,280 --> 00:13:36,610
我們會珍藏的
We'll treasure it.

290
00:13:37,970 --> 00:13:39,690
喬什  跟我說說
So Josh, tell me,

291
00:13:39,940 --> 00:13:44,450
我怎么有福  找到你這么好的女婿
how did I get to be so lucky to have you as a son-in-law?

292
00:13:44,680 --> 00:13:45,990
對  喬什
Yes, Josh,

293
00:13:46,100 --> 00:13:48,450
告訴媽媽你愛我哪一點
tell mother what it is you love about me.

294
00:13:54,060 --> 00:13:55,210
你懂的
You know,

295
00:13:56,130 --> 00:13:57,810
就是那些東西
it's the usual stuff, it's...

296
00:13:59,560 --> 00:14:01,030
他的打扮
his style,

297
00:14:01,700 --> 00:14:03,000
性格
personality--

298
00:14:03,170 --> 00:14:04,690
還有我的翹臀嗎
My cute tushy?

299
00:14:07,670 --> 00:14:08,860
沒錯
Sure.

300
00:14:10,670 --> 00:14:12,370
但最重要的是
But most importantly,

301
00:14:12,810 --> 00:14:14,210
我愛他媽媽
I love his mom.

302
00:14:16,900 --> 00:14:20,580
如果你是直男  我再年輕五歲...
If you were straight and I was five years younger...

303
00:14:22,640 --> 00:14:25,210
艾略特  你撿到寶了
Elliot, you found a winner.

304
00:14:25,390 --> 00:14:27,340
我真為你驕傲
I'm proud of you.

305
00:14:28,230 --> 00:14:29,620
真的嗎  媽媽
Really, mother?

306
00:14:30,870 --> 00:14:32,280
艾略特  你去開門
Elliot, you go.

307
00:14:33,030 --> 00:14:34,350
你別走
You stay.

308
00:14:38,220 --> 00:14:39,370
埃蘭
Alan.

309
00:14:39,970 --> 00:14:42,250
你怎么來了  我說過我媽媽病了
What are you doing here? I told you my mother was sick.

310
00:14:42,250 --> 00:14:43,770
所以我才帶了雞湯來
That's why I brought chicken soup.

311
00:14:43,770 --> 00:14:46,170
謝謝  我會給她的  再見
Thanks, I'll be sure she gets it. Bye-ee.

312
00:14:46,520 --> 00:14:47,550
艾略特
Elliot,

313
00:14:47,550 --> 00:14:49,620
你為什么不想讓我見我的岳母
Why don't you want me to meet my future mother-in-law?

314
00:14:50,590 --> 00:14:52,720
出了點狀況
A situation has presented itself.

315
00:14:52,920 --> 00:14:54,270
什么狀況
What situation?

316
00:14:54,280 --> 00:14:57,740
我媽媽認為喬什是我未婚夫
A situation where my mom thinks Josh is my fiance.

317
00:15:00,400 --> 00:15:01,660
不好笑嗎
Isn't that funny?

318
00:15:01,890 --> 00:15:03,710
我懂了
Oh, I get it.

319
00:15:03,860 --> 00:15:06,770
你說喬什是你未婚夫  因為覺得我丟你臉
You told her Josh is your fiance because you're ashamed of me.

320
00:15:07,010 --> 00:15:08,080
沒有
No.

321
00:15:08,080 --> 00:15:10,390
只是我人生中第一次
It's just that for the first time in my life

322
00:15:10,390 --> 00:15:12,190
我媽說她為我驕傲
my mom said she was proud of me.

323
00:15:12,190 --> 00:15:14,160
如果你和我在一起她就不驕傲嗎
And she wouldn't be proud if you were with me?

324
00:15:14,390 --> 00:15:15,930
你不明白
You don't understand

325
00:15:15,930 --> 00:15:17,970
因為你媽媽不是怪物
because your mother's not a monster.

326
00:15:18,460 --> 00:15:21,790
就算我媽是波卡拉頓嘴最毒的女人
Even if my mother was the meanest woman in Boca,

327
00:15:22,920 --> 00:15:25,180
我也會大方地把你介紹給她
I would never be ashamed to introduce you.

328
00:15:25,340 --> 00:15:26,520
我沒有覺得丟臉
I'm not ashamed.

329
00:15:26,520 --> 00:15:28,000
那現在就介紹我啊
Then introduce me right now.

330
00:15:28,150 --> 00:15:29,430
現在嗎
Right now, now?

331
00:15:30,070 --> 00:15:33,160
行了  艾略特  你做了選擇  我也是
That's it, Elliot. You've made your choice and I've made mine.

332
00:15:33,160 --> 00:15:34,550
再見
Goodbye.

333
00:15:35,850 --> 00:15:37,440
鍋要還給我
I'll need that pot back.

334
00:15:40,270 --> 00:15:41,730
謝謝你幫忙  尤蘭達
Thank you for your help, Yolanda.

335
00:15:41,730 --> 00:15:43,900
也謝謝你的威士忌
Thank you for the scotch.

336
00:15:54,720 --> 00:15:55,580
喬什
Hey Josh,

337
00:15:55,580 --> 00:15:56,460
希望你不介意
ah, I hope you don't mind,

338
00:15:56,460 --> 00:15:58,660
我請索菲亞來陽臺吃午飯
I invited Sofia to have lunch on the terrace

339
00:15:58,700 --> 00:16:00,120
我覺得在戶外吃頓飯
I thought a little dining al fresco

340
00:16:00,120 --> 00:16:02,920
可能會讓她開心一點
might help her feel a little less depressed-o.

341
00:16:05,300 --> 00:16:06,680
看來挺有效
Well, looks like it's working.

342
00:16:06,830 --> 00:16:07,640
希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind,

343
00:16:07,640 --> 00:16:10,630
-我來打掃下你的文件柜  -好
- I'm just gonna dust your file cabinet. - Okay.

344
00:16:10,640 --> 00:16:12,520
別問了  這是我工作
Why the third degree? It's my job!

345
00:16:13,660 --> 00:16:16,090
我把文件都拿出來
Um, I'm just gonna get the files out.

346
00:16:21,160 --> 00:16:21,990
尤蘭達
Yolanda.

347
00:16:22,000 --> 00:16:25,070
不好  文件掉了  我來撿
Oh no, your files! I'll get them.

348
00:16:26,760 --> 00:16:28,360
哎呀呀
I mean, alas!

349
00:16:28,730 --> 00:16:31,760
你看我發現了什么  喬什
What's this I just found right now, Josh?

350
00:16:32,720 --> 00:16:34,420
稍等  是我律師的電話
Hold that thought, it's my attorney.

351
00:16:34,530 --> 00:16:35,850
拉里  什么事
Hey Larry, what's up?

352
00:16:37,530 --> 00:16:39,150
我沒簽哪個申請書
What patent didn't I sign?

353
00:16:39,450 --> 00:16:40,730
這個  這個
This one. This one.

354
00:16:40,730 --> 00:16:43,150
謝天謝地你發現了  你真厲害
Oh, thank god you caught this, you're the man.

355
00:16:43,150 --> 00:16:44,970
厲害的是我  是我
No, I'm the man. I'm the man!

356
00:16:44,970 --> 00:16:47,770
如果你不是已經替我干活了  我會雇你的
You know what? If you didn't work for me, I'd hire you.

357
00:16:47,780 --> 00:16:48,620
下次要記住
So here's what I want to do next time.

358
00:16:48,620 --> 00:16:50,580
我們嚴格按流程來  避免...
Let's really stick to the process and avoid this...

359
00:16:52,940 --> 00:16:55,080
計劃真棒  加比
Great plan, Gabi.

360
00:16:58,720 --> 00:17:00,150
現在她不開心了
Now she's depressed-o.

361
00:17:06,230 --> 00:17:07,370
艾略特
Elliot...

362
00:17:08,020 --> 00:17:09,250
對不起
I'm sorry.

363
00:17:09,710 --> 00:17:12,010
我一晚上沒睡著  在想著埃蘭的烤布丁
I was up all night thinking about Alan's kugel

364
00:17:12,010 --> 00:17:13,680
還有我這輩子也沒機會吃了
and how I'm never gonna have it again.

365
00:17:16,380 --> 00:17:17,700
你要跟他聊聊
You just have to talk to him.

366
00:17:18,070 --> 00:17:20,200
不行  我太慚愧了
I can't, I'm too ashamed.

367
00:17:20,570 --> 00:17:22,170
我知道
Yeah, I know.

368
00:17:22,620 --> 00:17:23,900
所以...
Which is why...

369
00:17:24,360 --> 00:17:25,640
我喊他來了
I called him.

370
00:17:26,060 --> 00:17:29,170
終于開門了  我在外面像個呆子站了十分鐘
Finally, I've been standing out here like a schmuck for 10 minutes.

371
00:17:30,770 --> 00:17:31,700
你好
Hi.

372
00:17:31,700 --> 00:17:32,900
天啊
Oh my god.

373
00:17:33,650 --> 00:17:36,520
艾略特  我不該就那樣走掉
Elliot, I was wrong to walk away like that.

374
00:17:36,530 --> 00:17:38,450
你知道我就喜歡抓馬的情節
You know I have a flair for the dramatic.

375
00:17:39,770 --> 00:17:41,410
但在喬什打給我
But after Josh called and explained

376
00:17:41,410 --> 00:17:43,900
說了你媽媽多壞以后
how terrible your mother really is,

377
00:17:44,020 --> 00:17:46,120
我意識到你需要些東西
I realized you need something.

378
00:17:46,390 --> 00:17:47,950
-什么  -這個
- What? - This.

379
00:17:50,550 --> 00:17:52,280
我配不上你
I don't deserve you.

380
00:17:52,280 --> 00:17:53,910
沒錯
You don't.

381
00:17:55,100 --> 00:17:56,870
但我又能找誰  我都四十二了
But where am I going? I'm 42.

382
00:18:02,970 --> 00:18:04,920
媽媽  我以為你已經去機場了
Mother, I thought you were on your way to the airport.

383
00:18:04,920 --> 00:18:09,110
不跟女婿道別  我怎么會走
I couldn't leave without saying goodbye to my son-in-law.

384
00:18:10,460 --> 00:18:13,160
喬什呢  我找不到他
Where's Josh, I don't see him.

385
00:18:14,200 --> 00:18:15,860
他把你甩了  是不是
He dumped you, didn't he?

386
00:18:16,920 --> 00:18:19,150
我就知道你配不上他
I knew you weren't good enough for him.

387
00:18:23,100 --> 00:18:24,290
這是誰
Who's this?

388
00:18:24,290 --> 00:18:25,940
我在樓下看到你了
I saw you downstairs.

389
00:18:25,940 --> 00:18:27,680
你是門童嗎
Are you the doorman?

390
00:18:28,850 --> 00:18:31,230
我不給三十歲以上的人小費
I don't tip people over 30.

391
00:18:33,340 --> 00:18:35,620
我誰都不是  正準備走
I'm nobody, I was just leaving.

392
00:18:38,320 --> 00:18:39,510
站住
Stop!

393
00:18:40,790 --> 00:18:42,520
你才沒有誰都不是
You're not nobody.

394
00:18:43,770 --> 00:18:45,910
媽媽  這是埃蘭
Mother, this is Alan.

395
00:18:46,340 --> 00:18:47,920
我要嫁的人
The man I'm going to marry.

396
00:18:48,600 --> 00:18:50,890
你要嫁給個門童嗎
You're marrying a doorman?

397
00:18:52,520 --> 00:18:55,400
他不是門童  是我愛的人
He's not the doorman, he's the man I love.

398
00:18:56,070 --> 00:18:57,870
很高興見到您  帕克夫人
It's nice to meet you, Mrs. Park.

399
00:19:00,590 --> 00:19:01,770
他嗎
Him?

400
00:19:02,050 --> 00:19:03,960
不是我家喬什嗎
And not my Josh?

401
00:19:05,400 --> 00:19:07,020
但喬什可有十分
But Josh is a 10.

402
00:19:08,520 --> 00:19:09,940
你就四分
You're a four.

403
00:19:11,770 --> 00:19:13,070
最多了
At best.

404
00:19:14,350 --> 00:19:17,280
但您嘗了我的烤布丁以后  我會沖到五分的
But after you taste my kugel, I'll shoot up to a five.

405
00:19:18,720 --> 00:19:20,340
烤布丁是什么
What the hell's a kugel?

406
00:19:21,730 --> 00:19:23,780
說英語  四分男
Speak english, four.

407
00:19:25,020 --> 00:19:26,930
-夠了  -艾略特  沒事
- That's enough. - No Elliot, it's fine.

408
00:19:26,930 --> 00:19:28,730
才不是沒事
No, it's not fine.

409
00:19:28,740 --> 00:19:30,360
我告訴你
Let me tell you something.

410
00:19:30,440 --> 00:19:32,260
埃蘭在我這里就是十分
Alan is a 10 in my book.

411
00:19:32,490 --> 00:19:34,260
你評分標準是什么
What book are you reading?

412
00:19:35,740 --> 00:19:38,580
標準是  "我聽夠你的廢話了
A book called, "I've had enough of your crap,

413
00:19:38,580 --> 00:19:41,460
埃蘭是個好人  和他在一起我很幸運
"Alan is an amazing man and I'm lucky to have him,

414
00:19:41,460 --> 00:19:43,620
你愛接受不接受"
"So deal with it."

415
00:19:45,410 --> 00:19:46,960
這是標準嗎
That's the title?

416
00:19:49,190 --> 00:19:52,070
語文果然不是你的強項
Writing was never your strong suit.

417
00:19:53,240 --> 00:19:55,220
支持孩子也不是你的強項
And being supportive isn't yours.

418
00:19:56,520 --> 00:19:57,840
我聽夠了
I heard enough.

419
00:19:58,060 --> 00:19:59,200
我走了
I'm leaving.

420
00:19:59,210 --> 00:20:01,830
很好  走遠遠的
Good. Go!

421
00:20:03,210 --> 00:20:05,390
我猜還是沒能讓她喜歡上我
I guess I'm not gonna win her over after all.

422
00:20:05,490 --> 00:20:07,160
我還是回醫院吧
I better get back to the hospital,

423
00:20:07,160 --> 00:20:08,810
還有手術在等我
I'm needed in surgery.

424
00:20:14,580 --> 00:20:16,100
你是醫生嗎
You're a doctor?

425
00:20:17,240 --> 00:20:19,590
其實是個神經外科醫生
A neurosurgeon, actually.

426
00:20:21,480 --> 00:20:24,920
歡迎來我們家
Welcome to the family.

427
00:20:26,410 --> 00:20:27,420
我說了吧
Told ya.

428
00:20:27,420 --> 00:20:29,140
媽媽們愛我
Moms love me.

429
00:20:29,440 --> 00:20:30,860
我也是
So do Elliot's.

430
00:20:37,310 --> 00:20:39,150
看我給你買了什么
Look what I gotcha.

431
00:20:40,370 --> 00:20:41,560
怎么了
What?

432
00:20:41,580 --> 00:20:43,460
看我給你買了什么
Look what I gotcha.

433
00:20:44,620 --> 00:20:46,340
等等  你為什么會覺得愧疚
Wait, why do you feel guilty?

434
00:20:46,340 --> 00:20:48,040
事情都是我搞砸的
I'm the one that messed everything up.

435
00:20:48,620 --> 00:20:50,660
這個嘛...
Eh. Okay, um...

436
00:20:50,990 --> 00:20:53,480
這真的很難說出口  但是...
Wow, this is really hard for me to say, but, um...

437
00:20:53,560 --> 00:20:55,540
我跟你說的辭職那事
I may have told you something about quitting my job

438
00:20:55,540 --> 00:20:57,370
可能不完全是真話
That wasn't 100 percent true.

439
00:20:57,370 --> 00:20:58,710
-什么  -我不是辭職
- What? - That I quit my job.

440
00:20:58,710 --> 00:20:59,880
什么
What?

441
00:21:00,640 --> 00:21:02,460
-是被開除了  -什么
- I was fired. - What?

442
00:21:02,700 --> 00:21:04,160
在那男人被升職以后
When they promoted that guy over me,

443
00:21:04,160 --> 00:21:06,360
我可能對老板說了些
I may have said a couple of things to my boss

444
00:21:06,360 --> 00:21:08,490
不太適合工作場合的話
that were inappropriate for the workplace.

445
00:21:09,060 --> 00:21:10,370
或者任何場合
Or any place.

446
00:21:12,250 --> 00:21:14,530
等等  索菲亞  你是被開除不是辭職
Wait, Sofia, you were fired instead of quit?

447
00:21:14,530 --> 00:21:16,090
你知道這意味著什么嗎
Do you understand what this means?

448
00:21:16,390 --> 00:21:17,850
你看不起我了嗎
Now you think less of me?

449
00:21:18,100 --> 00:21:19,210
不
No.

450
00:21:19,210 --> 00:21:21,520
你現在能領失業金了
Now you can collect unemployment.

451
00:21:22,330 --> 00:21:24,690
-天啊  沒錯  -太棒了
- Oh my god, yes! - Yes!

