[MAN SINGING " MY WAY" IN RUSSIAN]
[CONTINUES SINGING "MY WAY"
IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Misha!
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
[ALARM BLEEPING
AND BOTH SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
[BOTH SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
LARA:
Listen carefully...
...my son.
By now, Kal-El...
...you are entering the
atmosphere of the planet Earth.
I pray you have made a safe journay.
Your new home's yellow sun
givas you graat physical powers.
But it cannot console your splrit.
Placed aboard this vessel
ls an energy module...
...all that remalns
of a onca-powerful civlllzatlon:
Krypton, your mother planat.
lt is my Iast gift to you.
Onca removed, the ship wlll
grow cold and silent...
...and you will be finally alone.
The power in the module
can be used but onca.
Usa it wisely, my son.
C ark, you out here?
CIark Kent!
Hi, Mr. Hornsby. Over here.
-There you are.
-How are you, s r?
-I'm fine. How are you?
-Nice to see you.
-It's been a ong time.
-A Iong time.
I was tidying up for you
to show t.
Did I mention there was
an offer to buy, sight unseen?
I don't want to seII
to a big deveIoper.
The buyer has to want a farm,
not a shopping center.
Now darn it, CIark,
why are you so stubborn?
Today, nobody wants a farm.
You bI nk your eye and they'II
aI be gone. That's progress.
Oh, my gosh, ook at this.
Oh, what a joker
oId Jonathan Kent was.
You know, I asked him
what happened to the baby's cr b.
And he said:
"Oh, ittIe C ark must've had
a bad dream and kicked it.''
-I swear, Dad Iiked a good joke.
-Yeah.
Maybe you'd I ke
to keep these for your grandchiIdren.
Why, thank you very much, CIark.
Here, batter up.
-Oh, no--
-Come on. We'lI hit a few.
Watch out now, these wiII
come n pretty fast.
You never couId hit a curve baII!
My decision's finaI about the pIace.
I'm hoIding out for a farmer.
You are?
You're just as obstinate
as your father was.
I'm sorry, that's
just the way it is.
Be carefuI when you get back
to Metropo s.
It's a ong way from
where you were born.
Yes. sir.
I never forget that, sir.
-Bye.
-Bye, CIark.
[WHISTLES MOZART TUNE]
CONVICT: What is that God-awfuI no se
you're making?
Mozart, my Iow-forehead frend.
Even this wretched pit can't diminish
true genius.
Life itseIf started in a murky p t
Iike this.
A true genius Iike myse f
Iearns to seize the moment.
You're the first to know...
...that I now have pIans
to re-create Iife itse f.
Luthor, start break ng a sweat
or we'lI throw you to the woIves.
Get them duds dirty.
-Move it, meathead.
-Let's see you sweat.
What's that car doing here?!
Stop that vehicIe!
-Hey, stop!
-HoId it there, son.
Where the heII is this and how
do I get to Cedar City?
Ha, ha. You on the wrong s de
of the state.
-No chance.
-Oh, no.
You got a fine, fine super-f ne
sound system here, son.
I guess you dudes never seen
these Sensurround 100s?
Yeah, I seen one once in a magazine.
WeII, heck. Come on, get in.
-ReaIIy?
-Come on.
-You want to hear it, come on!
-A I right.
Hop in, Bubba.
Let's give it a Iisten.
This is great!
Doors....
-What's going on?
-Windows....
GUARD 1: Whoa! What's happening?
-The top.
Seats!
Lordy! Lordy!
And away!
Y'aII come back and see us!
Launch.
[GUARDS SCREAMING]
AII right!
Did I do okay or what, Unc e Lex?
Lenny, you're the Dutch eIm
disease of my famiIy tree.
But you did fine.
You gonna skip the country, UncIe Lex?
You pathetic product of the pubIic
schooIs, I've thought of nothing e se...
...since I've been ncarcerated
except one thing:
-Destroy Superman!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Sorry.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
CIark!
[GRUNTING]
HeIp!
HeIp! HeIp!
Somebody get heIp!
[ALL SHOUTING]
Superman!
[CROWD MURMURING]
He's okay. He needs a doctor.
Superman!
GentIemen, one moment. I want peopIe
to know that our subway...
... s the safest, most re iabIe
pubIic transit. Thank you.
Thanks.
WH TE:
You're late, Kent.
-Sorry, won't happen aga n.
-Ha!
Where is everybody?
DAVID:
Boring.
Tedious.
-Hey, what's going on?
-Abom nabIe!
Regardez, volla David WarfieId.
David WarfieId who owns those
sIeazy tabIoids?
Au contraire. Who owns those
sIeazy tab oids and The Dally Planet.
Tedious.
You onIy read the pictures?
The fact is, Mr. White,
that I onIy read the Iedger.
A Iedger the previous owners
paid so IittIe attent on to...
...I bought the paper from them.
The Daily Planet hasn't made
money n three years.
The name of the game
is making money.
Ladies and gentIemen,
my daughter, Lacy Warfie d.
-Thanks, Daddy.
-It's nice to meet you.
Mr. White, Lacy w I be heIping you.
HeIp ng me? HeIping me what?
Here are some mock copies
of our new Iayout.
It's super. We can change the suit.
Excuse me, Mr. WarfieId.
The worId isn't on the brink.
Isn't that headIine irresponsib e?
Maybe, but it' seII
a Iot of newspapers.
Mr. White, don't do anything rash.
You won't turn this grand
oId Iady into one of your bimbos--
May I point out that Daddy
hoIds aII of your contracts...
...which you must honor.
-Excusez-moi, your spoiIed-ness...
-Why is Lois speaking French?
...I'm fIying to Paris for
the emergency Min sters' Conference--
Not so fast. AII trips are canceIed.
You mean my trip to Paris is canceIed?
Mr. White, I want to see your books.
Everyone get back to work.
This isn't fair.
I'II speak to Miss WarfieId.
-Me too.
-Excuse me, M ss WarfieId.
I speak for us aII when I say
we'lI cooperate.
Thank you.
But a reporter's first aIIeg ance
is to the truth.
This city depends on us
and we can't Iet them down.
Thank you.
Is he for reaI?
100 percent, and I Iike him that way.
-Oh, you have a thing for him.
-For CIark?! No!
LACY:
He's kind of cute.
Look, M ss WarfieId...
...CIark is the o dest
Iiving Boy Scout, okay?
He's trustworthy, he's heIpfuI...
...he's IoyaI, he's obed ent, he--
I don't know how to say it.
I just don't th nk he'd be attracted
to somebody ike you.
Don't be siIIy. A men I ke me.
I'm very, very rch!
Why aren't there air traveI expenses
for you, Mr. Kent?
I get airsick,
mostIy when it's bumpy.
Lois, get in here!
Lois, exp ain this co umn of f gures.
-The president s coming on Iive.
CLARK: Right now?
-It won't be good.
-You aIways overreact.
-It won't be that terrib e.
-Hopefu y very terribIe.
C rcuIation wiII doubIe
with a crisis.
PRESIDENT:
Becausa tha summlt has fallad...
...we have no choice but
to strlve to ba second to none...
...ln the nuclear arms raca.
Therefore, l am announcing
the following measures--
I know you're aII upset
by the crisis.
The best thing we can do
is to try to think positiveIy.
Now, s there anything we can do?
Doesn't anyone have a suggestion?
AII right, I'II make a suggestion.
Why don't we write to our congressman?
-That'II do a Iot of good.
-Somebody has to be an opt m st.
Jeremy?
What can we do about the crisis?
STUDENT 1:
He doesn't know what's go ng on.
I know who I'd write to
who'd do some good.
STUDENT 2: Who? Santa CIaus?
-No, Superman!
TOUR GUIDE:
Superman, n our new exh bit...
...donated a strand
of his hair to the museum...
...so we can have fun seeing
how strong he reaIIy is.
Here you see a 1000-pound Ioad...
...easiIy suspended
by h s s ngIe hair.
The museum w be cIosing soon,
so we shouId hurry.
LEX: Know what I can do with
a strand of his hair?
LENNY:
You couId make a fIying toupee.
LEX: That hair is
Superman's genetic materiaI.
The buiIding bIocks of h s body.
With my genius and enough nuc ear
power to mutate the genes...
...I can create a being
more powerfuI than him.
With totaI aIIegiance to me.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
You better stand back.
Keep your eye out.
[ALARM RINGING]
-Miss Warfie d, you want to see me?
-Hi, CIark. Come in.
I've come up with a briII ant idea.
Oh, reaIIy?
Daddy th nks it's br Iiant.
You'II wrte a series
caI ed "MetropoIis After Hours."
Who, me? I....
It's wonderfuI.
It's great, isn't it?
-I don't think I'm rght for this.
-You're perfect for it.
You're young, you're singIe,
you're successfuI.
I'm usuaI y in bed by 10:30.
That's just it, you don't
fIaunt it.
You're no sIave to fashion.
AIthough...
-...have you thought of contacts?
-They make my eyes itch.
Don't worry. I thought
we'd do this together.
-Oh?
-I know aII the right pIaces.
I beIong to the rght cIubs.
We' start tonight at the Metro CIub.
-Oh, tonight.
-Yeah, it's a date.
A date! Ah!
-A date?
-WeI , it's just business, actuaIIy.
I've got a Ietter here for Superman,
care of me.
-What?
-Superman gets ma here?
It's probabIy a photo request.
I'I handIe it.
I think it's more than just
a fan Ietter. Read it.
"Dear Superman, my teacher spoke about
the president's speech on the arms race.
We're a very unhappy about it.
And I sa d we shouId get Superman
to rid the worId of nuc ear arms...
...because on y he couId do it.
Once you've destroyed aII the nuc ear
m ssiIes, they'II see I'm right.
Superman can make sure we don't
bIow ourseIves up.
I know you'II come through.
Your friend, Jeremy.''
Poor kid. Oh, weII,
I better get back to work.
-No, there's an angIe here.
-An angIe! He's just a k d!
Daddy oves wh pping up campaigns.
And the pubIic Ioves it!
LOIS: Lacy!
-We'lI make the kid a ceIebrity.
The word s gonna be
wondering what Superman's repIy is.
WeIcome to MetropoIis, Jeremy.
I'm Mr. Warfie d and this is
my daughter, Lacy.
-Hi, Jeremy.
-Come a ong and meet the press.
DAVID: How was your trip?
JEREMY: The car had a fIat.
DAVID:
Sorry to hear that. Turn around.
Let everybody get a picture of you.
-That's it, everyone.
MAN 1 : Jeremy!
What a boy! Now come aIong...
...and te the American pub ic
what you toId me.
I just sa d I w sh Superman
wouId've said yes.
DAVID: Did you get that?
GROUP: No.
WeII, say it again. LoudIy.
I said I wish Superman
wouId've said yes!
Miss Lane!
Miss Lane, take a Iook at this.
Hot off the press.
Oh, my God!
This t me he's gone too far.
Look, CIark.
Can't wait to see
the chiefs reaction.
I'm through taking it Iy ng down.
I'II be downtown.
JIMMY:
Chief Iook different to you?
He Iooks Iike my father used to Iook
when he asked the bank for a Ioan.
I'II make sure he's a rght.
There's nothing we can do.
It's Superman's decision now.
I'm sure he'II do the right thing.
LARA:
May the elders watch over you...
...my son.
Thelr wlsdom is all that's left
of a once powerful...
...and enllghtened planet.
You must llsten to them, Kal-El.
Listen.
I know I'm forbidden to interfere.
And yet the Earth s threatened
by the same fate as Krypton's .
The Earth s too primitive.
You can fIee to new worIds...
...where war is ong forgotten.
SECOND ELDER: If you teach the Earth
to put its fate in any one man...
...even yourseIf...
...you're teaching them
to be betrayed.
Betrayed, betrayed...
...betrayed, betrayed!
[MAN SPEAK NG RUSSIAN ON TV]
TRANSLATOR [ON TV]:
Becausa tha summlt has fallad...
...we hava no cholca but to strive...
...to be second to none
ln the nuclaar arms raca.
To that end...
...thls adminlstratlon has pursued
and will continue to pursue....
[DOORBELL RINGS]
...the most vigorous policy.
Therefore--
Just a minute.
-Lois?
-There you are. What happened?
-What do you mean?
-Nothing, just:
''Meet me in the Iobby at 6:00
forthe awards dinner.
Dress nice
and don't be ate.''
-You were taIking about some other Lois?
-I'm sorry, I forgot.
Go get your penguin suit on
and we'lI go.
I'd rather not, if you don't mind.
I've got Iots of th nk ng to do.
But you go ahead. Okay?
C ark? Something's wrong, isn't it?
-Is there anything I can do?
-Yes, as a matter of fact.
-What?
-CouId we go get some fresh a r?
Fresh air?
Fresh a r. Fresh air, sure.
Sure, CIark. Sure.
Who needs rubber chicken anyway?
Let's go.
Let's get some fresh a r.
Breathe. Do you feeI better?
C ark?
C ark? CIark, things aren't
that bad! Stop!
Oh, CIark!
C ark! CIark!
Superman!
You okay?
Great.
Hey, ook at that.
-There you go. Bye-bye!
-Ah!
[CHUCKLING]
-How'd you ike going soIo?
-I Ioved t.
Not as much as being wth you.
I needed to be with you too.
You make me Iaugh.
You're the onIy one I can ta k to.
See, sometimes I don't know
what I'm supposed to do.
I'm aIways here for you,
you know that.
And you' do the right thing,
no matter what. You aIways have.
Thank you.
-You know something?
-What?
-You don't even know my name.
-KaI-EI.
You remember, don't you?
I remember everything.
"Never set one of them above the rest.
Love aII humanity instead."
That's not fa r.
-Lois! It's time to go. We'II be Iate.
-Huh?
Why am I out here
freezing my butt off?
Oh, you wanted some fresh air.
That's okay.
I don't want to catch a coId.
I fee kind of weird,
Iike I'm jet-Iagged or something.
CLARK: Jeepers!
LOIS: Am I going crazy?
-How about you? Are you st I down?
-Nope. Things are cIear.
Good. Too much thinking
wears down your batteries.
-CIark, you gotta go with your gut.
-Hm.
Come on.
JIMMY:
Here you go, Jeremy.
Mr. Warf eId wants shots with ocaI
coIor, but I can't think of anything.
-Hi, Jeremy.
-Superman!
Jimmy.
What a scoop!
[CROWD MURMURING]
-How'd you Iike to waIk with me?
-Sure!
Jimmy, come on.
[CROWD CHEERING]
LACY:
You can't ! You' get towed.
-Do you know how much tickets cost?
-It's onIy money.
WiII you wait for me
in the gaIIery?
Sure, okay.
-Good Iuck, Superman.
-Thanks.
I saved you a seat.
Yeah!
AII right, Superman!
Madam Secretary, I'd Iike to
address the deIegates.
We , in that case,
you wiII need a sponsor.
I beIieve that w II do. PIease.
Thank you.
-What's he gonna say?
-Something wonderfuI.
SUPERMAN:
Madam Secretary...
...honorabIe deIegates,
Iadies and gentIemen.
For many years now
I've I ved among you as...
...a visitor.
I've seen the beauty of your cuItures.
I've feIt joy n your magnificent
accompI shments.
I've seen the foIIy of your wars.
As of today I'm not a v sitor
anymore...
...because the Earth is my home too.
We can't Iive in fear.
And I can't stand...
... dIy by and watch us
stumbIe into the madness...
...of possibIe nucIear destruction.
I've come to a decision.
I'II do what our governments couIdn't.
Effective immed ateIy, I'lI
rd our pIanet of aII nucIear weapons.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
AII right, Superman!
Way to go, Superman!
MissiIe test AIpha, aII systems go.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
--three, two, one.
LEX:
Oh!
Oh. N ce to see you guys!
Why don't you just reIax.
I'II get on with the introductions:
Dix e and Trixie.
From the Iand of the free, the home of
the cost overrun, Harry HowIer:
NucIear strategist from
Amerca's top think tank.
A great ittIe warmonger
in his own rght.
A hearty blenvenue
to Jean P erre Dubois:
NucIear warhead deaIer to the worId.
His motto s:
"If you didn't buy it from Jean Pierre,
it wasn't on the bIack market."
GeneraI Romoff.
PeopIe think of you
as the " Mad Russian."
I Iike to think of you
as just madIy eccentric.
PIease be seated.
Look guys. know you're aII choked
up, kind of overcome with joy...
...that Superman has ended
the arms race.
But if we work together,
we can make the worId safe...
-...for war profits.
-Get to the point.
I, Lex Luthor, the greatest
cr minaI m nd of the modern era...
...know how to destroy Superman.
Beho d, my unscrupuIous friends....
Shut those b inds.
-The sun is hurting my eyes!
-ExactIy.
You know what the sun is? Nothing
more than a huge nucIear bomb...
...with so much radiation, it'd
incinerate the average man Iike that!
Yes, but Superman is no average man.
Aha, right!
What is your pIan?
Boys, oId Lex here
has kind of a secret recipe...
...a genetic stew in this dish,
if you wiII.
If you'lI heIp me put this
on one of your missiIes...
...I promise, Superman wiII have
the biggest surprise of h s Iife.
I'lI introduce him to his first
nightmare, a "NucIear Man."
He' p erce h s skin, make
him mortaI. He'II become sick.
We' dance on his grave.
Why shouId we deaI with
a scoundre Iike you?
Remember my motto: ''T he more fear
you make, the more Ioot you take."
And the more m ssiIes you seII.
Yes, but what's n it for you?
A tiny comm ssion.
LEX:
Someth ng appropriate.
A number...
...with a Iot of zeros beh nd it.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Lenny.
The new genet c materiaI.
LEX:
And now, Leonard...
...your Unc e Lex...
...with protopIasm grown
from Superman's hair ceIIs...
...wiII dupIicate creation itseIf.
Now the fabric.
UncIe Lex, this ain't gonna cover him.
The computer inside w I...
...Ieave enough materiaI to maintain
the high moraI standards...
...that I've aIways subscribed to.
-Know what this means, UncIe Lex?
-What?
We're gonna be parents.
-What's your name?
-York, sir.
At ease.
[TRUCK BEEPING]
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Launch controI. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
There's a weather probIem.
We gotta hoId.
Ho d?
-What's your name, son?
-Goram.
"Goram, s r."
-Goram, s r.
-You know your code book?
Of course, s r.
27-0-6, inc ement overrde.
Fire on my command. Fire.
Yes, sir. Stand by to aunch.
Ten, nine--
[CONTROL PANEL BEEPING]
M ssed us.
TEACHER:
Reach out.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
Come on.
Down.
Reach out.
And stretch.
Down.
-Up.
CLARK: Ugh!
-Are you okay?
-I think I better s t this out.
Are you sure? This wou d be great
for your series on MetropoIis.
Let's try it again. Come on.
Two, three, four.
-One, two, three.
-Ugh.
-I don't think so.
-What, are you okay?
28, 29...
-...33.
-Heh, heh, heh.
-Done. Great.
LACY: Okay, you try it now.
-Let's set t a IittIe h gher for you.
-Okay.
LACY:
Just push down.
-Are you okay? Just step down.
MAN: Need some he p?
He doesn't know his own strength.
C ark, this is PauI.
-He's a trainer.
-Nice to meet you.
Hey, I got just the thing for you.
Over here, CIarky.
C arky?
CLARK:
It's reaI nice of him to heIp me out.
LACY: He's reaIIy good.
-Here, try this one.
C ark! Are you okay? Sorry.
No pain, no gain.
Jeez, what a jerk.
Never reaI zed it before.
I guess a ot of peopIe I know
are jerks.
You must think I am too.
That's why you avoid me.
I don't think that at aII.
Just been reaIIy busy.
LACY:
But wait!
Lois is doing that interv ew
with Superman about his peace m ssion.
I was thinking the four of us can get
together at my hoteI, have high tea.
It's very chic.
PAUL: Can you hand me those weights?
-Excuse me.
Wait, Lacy.
Come eary. The view s romantic
from my baIcony. See you.
CLARK: Oh, sure. Here.
-Not those! The other one!
No pain, no gain?
[WHIRRING]
What was that?
Unc e Lex.
You're spooking me out.
[WHIRRING]
There.
Madam, thank you very much.
[BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH]
I'm incredibIe.
UncIe Lex, he's Iike--
He's beaut fuI. He's perfect.
We come home, NucIear Man.
Your father's happy to see you.
The power of the sun gives him
internaIIy generated heat.
I'm a....
You are....
I'm.... What? I'm a genius?
I'm incredibIe. I'm....
You are nothing. I am the father now.
-You have my voice.
-No, you have my vo ce.
Just remember, I made you.
Yeah, you're just an experiment,
freako.
What is that?
-Oh, no.
-I'm an exper ment. I'm a freako.
I was just k dding about freako!
If anyone's a freako here,
t's gotta be me!
Oh, wow. Oh!
Oh, wow, I'm break dancing, hey!
Th s rocks. Hey!
-I made you. I can destroy you.
-Destroy.
Destroy Superman now.
You sweet thing.
But not quite yet, no.
Come here. We'lI discuss
when the proper t me is.
LENNY:
UncIe Lex.
Oh, no!
He's , Iike.... He's , Iike, coId.
Of course he is.
That's h s vuInerabiIity.
The onIy way he'lI be stopped.
What?
Lenny, my oud-mouthed nephew,
he gets his energy from the sun.
Without t, he's Iike you at night:
UseIess.
Nobody's perfect.
[HUMMING]
I never had a doub e date before.
It's fun. How do I Iook?
IIIega . Like the Iast six dresses
you tred on.
Listen, Lacy? I don't want to
burst your bubbIe...
-...but C ark won't not ce your dress.
-Yes, he wiII.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
-There's CIark.
-Fix that. There you go. You Iook great.
-Maybe it's just Superman.
-No.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
No, Superman makes a d fferent
kind of entrance.
-Hi, Lacy.
-Hi, Clark.
Can you break a 20?
Driver had no change.
Yeah, sure. Let me get my purse.
CLARK: Hi, Lois.
-Hi, CIark.
-CIark.
CLARK: What?
You won't beIieve
these quest ons...
...Mr. WarfieId gave me
to ask Superman.
"Are you part of a pIot
to weaken our nationaI defense?"
-Oh, my goodness.
-I think his gray matter is--
-How wiII I ask h m this?
-WeI , poIiteIy I guess.
Let's see, I have 18 doIIars and...
C ark, she reaIIy Iikes you,
so notice the dress.
...my American Express card.
-Dress.
-Oh, hey, neat dress.
Thanks. Be right back.
What's that?
Now, there's a d fferent
kind of entrance.
-Hi, Lois.
-He Io, Superman.
SUPERMAN:
How are you?
I'm fine.
Oh. Superman, this is Lacy WarfieId.
She's the boss's daughter.
How do you do?
That's an attractive outfit.
-We shou d start our interview.
-Excuse me.
Two's company.
Oh, right, yeah.
Yeah, I' go get CIark.
C ark s probab y he ping the cab driver
change a fIat tire, or someth ng.
That guy.
-Something smeI s wonderfuI.
-Thank you.
I'm cooking us some scaIIops
and some duck...
... n th s wonderfuI mushroom sauce
with champagne.
In case we got hungry afterwards.
I mean, Iater.
You shouIdn't have gone
through aII that troubIe.
Shou d we get on with the nterview?
Yes, Iet's get on
with the interview.
Um....
Have you had any troubIe
confiscating the miss Ies?
There aIways was the possibiIity
that warped individuaIs...
...wouId take advantage of
the worId's goodwiI , but....
Is there something wrong?
[LOIS SNIFFING]
Oh! My d nner! My dinner!
I'II be right back.
Be rght back.
Hi.
-I missed you, CIark.
-Oh. WeII....
Lois and Superman are boring.
Let's do something wi d.
They're expecting us.
It's not poI te.
Yeah, you're right.
How can one man be so square
and so de icious?
Let's go chitchat. If I
have to face Superman, so do you.
Lacy?
Oh, CIark.
Uh-- Uh-- Stop.
I don't beIieve it! I never had duck
turn out so perfect y. It's amaz ng!
-I'm out here, Lois.
-Oh.
-Isn't it beautifuI?
-Yes, it is beautifuI.
The whoIe worId is beautifuI.
I feeI moments Iike this
shouId be shared with someone you--
Someone you care a Iot about.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
-Isn't that the doorbeII?
-Yes. Heh, heh.
Lacy.
-Where's C ark?
-He was getting in the eIevator--
-Never mind, it's a Iong story.
-It aIways is with CIark.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
LACY:
Great, t's h m.
-CIark?
CLARK: Hi.
Those beIIboys ought to
Iook where they're going.
Superman?
-I'm so gIad you're back.
-Is dinner ready? Can we eat?
-Yeah, Iet's go sit down.
-Oh, great.
[CRASHING AND CLANGING]
-Sorry!
-My goodness! That's okay.
Just Ieave it there.
It's on your pants.
Let me just get a rag.
Be rght back.
Where's CIark?
[LOUD RING]
LEX [SINGING]: Hallo, Dolly
Hello, DoIIy
lt's so nice to have me back
Whera l belong
Don't be concerned, Blue Boy.
Only you can hear me.
lt's my own private fraquency.
You mlght call lt "Lex TV."
Look to your laft,
tall, dark and handsome.
l'll blow 20 stories off that building,
glve or take a floor or two.
Peaca.
Men.
LACY: I hope CIark's okay. I'lI ook.
-Okay.
I'm sorry, but an emergency's come up.
My apoIogies to Miss WarfieId.
LOIS:
Oh, but....
Superman! Take me with you!
I can cover the story!
-You seen C ark?
-Huh?
Guess who?
It's your oId friend Lex.
[CHUCKLES]
I suspect f you'd actuaIIy pIanted
a bomb, you'd be miIes away by now.
This is my nephew Lenny.
He worships me.
The dude of steeI.
Boy, are you gonna get it.
Si Iy me, thinking that
I cou d fooI a super guy.
You're right. No bomb.
It's just that you're so invo ved
in th s word peace bit...
...you don't have time
for soc aI caIIs.
I confess, I trcked you.
You Iook great.
Never mind the smaII taIk.
What are you up to?
You know you're a workaho ic?
You're pIaying a good guy
24 hours a day.
Why don't you stop and
sme the roses, huh?
Get yourseIf a hobby? A pet?
A kitten, a puppy?
I know you hate ch Idren and animaIs.
What are you doing back in MetropoIis?
I want to be f rst to introduce
you to the new kid on the bIock.
LEX:
Look c oseIy at the ce I structure.
You see anything famiIiar?
You've aIready broke
aII the Iaws of man.
Now you've broken the Iaws
of nature too.
I assume you hid a dev ce of some kind
in a m ssiIe I hurIed into the sun.
Mr. MuscIe, I'm gonna reaIIy miss
these Iitt e chats we had together.
OnIy you can keep up with me.
-Lenny!
-What?
I wanna propose a toast.
To a nice guy, who's about
to finish Iast.
[ROARS]
Destroy Superman.
LEX:
Later. Heh, heh, heh.
He's a ittIe bit anxious.
Can you bIame him?
Not one of your great thinkers.
But I, in a modesty, am.
The touching thing about this pIan
is, you heIped me devise it.
Prison has twisted
your mind nto a deIusionaI state.
No, no, no. L sten.
When I escaped prison,
I had one thing on my mind:
The end of Superman.
There I was, the first time in my I fe...
...that I didn't have a Iong-range,
truIy dev ous, cr mina scheme.
And then I came up w th it.
Wth this guy...
...and you gone, I'II make
a fortune rearming the worId.
You'd rsk nucIear warfor
your own financia gain.
Nobody wants war. I just want
to keep the threat aIive.
[SIZZLING NOISE]
LEX:
Nifty, huh?
[SIZZLING]
Good night, sweet prince.
Parting is...
... nevitab e.
Destroy Superman.
First, I have fun.
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
[CROWD MURMURING]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING]
HeIp me!
Superman!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[SPEAKING ITAL AN]
[IN ITALIAN]
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[NUCLEAR MAN ROARING]
[NUCLEAR MAN ROARS]
[MOANS]
I said I'd get you to run one of our
papers yourseIf, and I meant it.
CongratuIations, Miss PubIisher.
Thank you, Daddy, that's very nice.
Step nto your office.
-Where'd this come from?
-Somebody brought it in.
We bought it, cheap.
Okay, this time you've both
gone too far.
You can print your stupid rag
without Lois Lane.
And you certain y have
no rght to this.
LACY: Lois, I'm sorry!
-Let her go, darIing.
I mean, she's useIess.
And whi e you're at it,
fire CIark Kent.
He hasn't been around
or teIephoned.
I know, I'm worried about him.
Oh, kitten...
...didn't we have a ta k about
persona invoIvement with the heIp?
-Now that you're the pubIisher--
-Daddy.
-Yes, darIing.
-Stuff it!
Lois. Lois, I'm sorry.
I promise, I had
nothing to do with that.
[SIGHS]
Have you heard from C ark?
No.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Just a minute.
Oh, Lois.
-What are you do ng here?
-I knew it.
I just got a reaI y bad fIu.
What do you mean you knew it?
You haven't been to work
or caIIed the office.
You haven't even caIIed me back.
How couId you not caI me back?
Whatever it is,
you've got your reasons.
But I knew you were here, you know?
Somehow...
...something pu ed me here.
I aIways know when Superman's
n troubIe.
Heh, heh, heh. Superman?
Someth ng's happened to him?
Everybody's saying that
he's dead but...
... t can't be true. I just know it.
I feeI t in my heart.
I think he just needs heIp.
Wherever he is,
I'm sure he'lI manage.
WeII, if he can't manage...
...and f he reaIIy is in troubIe...
...then there's a few things
I'd Iike to teII him.
I'd teII him...
...that wiII aIways cherish
the time we spent together.
And that I never expected
anything in return.
And no matter...
...how few m nutes I saw him for,
it aIways made me happy.
And I wouId teII him
that I Iove him...
...and that I'II aIways Iove h m.
And that...
...whatever...
...happens to the worId...
...I know that...
...he's doing his best to make sure
it's good for a I of us.
Wherever he is, Lois...
...I know that he wou d
want to thank you.
L sten, I'm pretty tired, you know?
So I think I'II just rest here
for a whiIe. Okay?
I'II be fine.
It's okay. PIease?
-I hope you feeI better, CIark.
-Thanks.
If you do see him, or hear from him...
...he might need this.
HARRY: Oh, Lex. We're very pIeased
at aII the nuc ear arms...
...you heIped us se I...
...and we've decided
to increase your commission.
Guys, rea y, that's great.
ROMOFF:
It is the Ieast we couId do.
LEX: I had another idea.
GentIemen...
...I've decided to assume controI
of the company.
My first officiaI act
is to say, ''Y ou're fired!"
[LAUGHS]
You're mad.
Oh, reaIIy?
If you want a reference for work...
...forget it!
That's a good bit.
You know with my brains, and your--
FrankIy, your...
...brawn, the possib Iities
are abso uteIy staggering.
I couId be president,
emperor, king.
-See how scared those guys were?
-And what do you fear?
What? Now? With Superman dead,
and you're on my team?
It's Iike I'm the coach, and you're the
best power forward ever. What's to fear?
LARA: All that remains of
Krypton's energy is yours.
Aftar it ls gone...
...you wlll belong solely
to your naw home.
lf our dying planet can
save your life, my son...
...we hava not dled in vain.
[ROARS]
[CROWD MURMURING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
-Where is the woman?
-You'II neverfind her.
If you wiI not te I me,
I w I hurt peop e.
[ROARING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Stop! Don't do t, the peop e!
[SIRENS WA LING]
[FIREMEN SHOUTING]
[SCREAMS]
Whoa!
ALL:
-What's happening?
-Easy, easy, easy.
AII rght, stop! Stop! That's enough!
That's enough!
You win.
I'II take you to her.
[ROARS]
-Where s she?
-Far away from here and safe.
She's not in there!
[GROANING]
[GROANS]
[ROARS]
[SCREAMING]
[SUPERMAN GRUNTING]
LACY: We must tone down
the headI nes.
Tone down our headI nes?
That's aII the common man reads!
-We can do w th Iess sensationaIism.
-Less sensat onaI papers go broke.
I taught you that the
business of newspapers is bus ness.
No, Daddy...
...our business is journaIism.
We can't be rresponsibIe or we'II
ead everyone into d saster.
Don't be overdramatic,
young Iady.
What kind of disaster cou d
we bring about?
[ROARS]
Lacy!
[GASPING]
[GROANS]
[ALARM SOUNDING]
What's going on? Hey!
[APPLAUSE]
Are you sure you know what
you're do ng?
-WeII....
LOIS: Uh-- Ahem.
Here comes Mr. W arfield .
You'd better have
a good expIanation, Wh te...
...or e se you'II be ta king
to your Iawyers from jaiI.
You know, I'm not a tycoon.
I'm just an oId reporter.
But I've read enough n my own
newspaper over the years...
...about hostiIe takeovers
of big companies.
You, Mr. Warf eId,
must've been asIeep at the wheeI.
Because I convinced the city's bankers
that our DaiIy Planet...
...shouId be treated Iike a naturaI
resource, protected from predators.
They Ient me the money.
I bought up aII the outstanding shares.
And you, Mr. WarfieId,
are now a minority shareho der.
-Everyone, back to work.
JIMMY: Way to te I him, chief!
LOIS:
Yay!
I'm sorry.
You win some and you Iose some.
Now, th s is what I caII a newspaper.
CompI ments of Tha Dally Planet.
-Have a nice day. We did it!
-We're back! Ha, ha, ha.
[CROWD MURMURING]
-Hi, am I Iate?
-No. He's not here yet.
It must've been some effort for you
to drag yourseIf out of bed.
I'm fee ng a Iot better.
Had a visit from a pretty good nurse.
Must have been good.
Miss Lane said you were reaIIy iII.
Sometimes aI you need is Ioving
attention from the right person.
GIad you're back.
And remember, I am covering
Superman's press conference.
-You tape reactions from the crowd.
-Reactions, okay.
Oh, dear. Guess I need
a tape recorder, huh?
-Be right back.
-Same Mr. Kent. He'l never change.
I hope not.
CROWD:
Ooh.
[CROWD CHEERING AND APPLAUDING]
-How you doing, Superman?
-Lois. Good to see you again.
Good to see you too.
Morning, gentIemen.
Excuse me.
Thank you. We survived the threat
of war and found a fragiIe peace.
I thought I couId g ve you
freedom from war...
...but I was wrong.
It's not m ne to g ve.
We're st a young pIanet.
There are gaIaxies out there...
...other civiIizations for us
to meet, to earn from.
Whata brilliantf.uture .
There wiII be peace when the peopIe of
the worId want it so badIy...
...that their governments wiII have
no choice but to give it to them.
I w sh you couId see the Earth
the way I do.
When you reaIIy Iook at it,
it's just one worId.
Do you think he'lI f nd us?
Never. We'lI Iay Iow for a whiIe,
a coupIe of years.
I'II come up with a new pIan.
Good thing I bought my drums.
[HORN HONKING]
LENNY:
Whoa!
UncIe Lex,
you won't beI eve this...
-...but it's Superman.
-Superman.
LENNY:
Heh, heh. Oh, wow. Oh, wow.
-Hey, this rocks.
SUPERMAN: Morning, Father.
He's been under a bad nfIuence.
Can you heIp h m?
-Every boy can be heIped.
-You're right.
-Good Iuck, son.
-Come with me.
You wouIdn't happen
to have a drum set, wou d you?
Hey, Mozart's back!
[PRISONERS WHISTLING MOZART TUNE]
BUBBA: Duane, Mozart's back!
DUANE: I see h m, Bubba!
[PR SONERS CONTINUE
WHISTLING MOZART TUNE]
-Shut up!
PRISONERS: Ha, ha, ha.
-Take him away.
-Thank you. Come on, Luthor.
-Just one thing, how d d you beat him?
-High schooI physics.
I had t me to figure out...
...that if t was born from the sun,
that was its energy.
-WiII the worId be vaporzed?
-No, Luthor.
It's as it aIways was, on the brink,
with good fight ng eviI. See you in 20.