1
00:00:01,860 --> 00:00:03,470
My name is Leonar Da Vinci.

2
00:00:03,830 --> 00:00:05,930
You're the eccentric that Verrocchio employs.

3
00:00:06,260 --> 00:00:09,400
I'm an artist and an anatomist and an engineer of some note.

4
00:00:09,660 --> 00:00:13,000
Search for the Book of Leaves. Fate has chosen you.

5
00:00:13,160 --> 00:00:14,800
Where do I start my search?

6
00:00:14,930 --> 00:00:16,130
The hanged man.

7
00:00:16,160 --> 00:00:18,300
The Jew that was hanged. I want to unearth his body.

8
00:00:18,600 --> 00:00:22,860
My mistress insisted that you be the one to capture her beauty.

9
00:00:24,430 --> 00:00:26,300
I sense the Vatican's hand behind this.

10
00:00:26,460 --> 00:00:28,400
You need weapons of your own, Your Magnificence.

11
00:00:28,600 --> 00:00:31,700
This will greatly increase your firepower.

12
00:00:32,000 --> 00:00:34,400
The Medicis have employed him to design siege weapons.

13
00:00:34,630 --> 00:00:36,530
- You know this how?  - I have an agent

14
00:00:36,730 --> 00:00:37,830
within Lorenzo's ranks.

15
00:00:39,000 --> 00:00:49,000


16
00:00:50,000 --> 00:01:05,000


17
00:01:35,000 --> 00:01:39,500


18
00:01:50,260 --> 00:01:52,560
He told you time is a river?

19
00:01:53,600 --> 00:01:57,060
He told me the river was circular.

20
00:01:57,300 --> 00:02:00,130
That one man's death paves the way for the birth of another.

21
00:02:00,360 --> 00:02:03,760
Indeed, and men like ourselves,

22
00:02:04,030 --> 00:02:07,430
we can change the river's course.

23
00:02:07,600 --> 00:02:10,130
I'm like you, then?

24
00:02:12,360 --> 00:02:14,960
I find that hard to believe.

25
00:02:15,200 --> 00:02:17,430
You don't know who I am, do you?

26
00:02:21,100 --> 00:02:24,600
My brother and I... Your bandits tried to take my honor.

27
00:02:24,800 --> 00:02:26,660
- Where?  - Down the path, to the left.

28
00:02:26,900 --> 00:02:28,930
- Hurry!  - This way.

29
00:02:29,100 --> 00:02:33,300
In you go. Go on, in.

30
00:02:33,430 --> 00:02:35,160
Alright.

31
00:02:35,300 --> 00:02:37,060
You should be safe in there.

32
00:02:40,960 --> 00:02:42,330
Come on.

33
00:02:45,860 --> 00:02:48,360
I'm sorry the fools locked the gate.

34
00:02:48,500 --> 00:02:50,630
The fools are worth worrying about.

35
00:02:50,760 --> 00:02:52,060
A locked gate...

36
00:02:54,560 --> 00:02:56,900
not so much.

37
00:02:57,060 --> 00:02:59,600
There is no yesterday, you see.

38
00:02:59,730 --> 00:03:01,530
No tomorrow.

39
00:03:01,830 --> 00:03:06,360
Time is all one single continuum.

40
00:03:07,860 --> 00:03:10,300
We have met, haven't we?

41
00:03:10,560 --> 00:03:13,930
Of course. We're brothers.

42
00:03:14,830 --> 00:03:16,600
Who are you?

43
00:03:16,900 --> 00:03:19,200
Start with your heel, roll to your toe, you have a lot to learn.

44
00:03:19,460 --> 00:03:22,460
- I already have a maestro.  - I am no suggesting you advent Da Vinci's counsel,

45
00:03:22,560 --> 00:03:25,360
but enhance it.

46
00:03:25,530 --> 00:03:26,900
There.

47
00:03:29,260 --> 00:03:30,830
What is it?

48
00:03:31,030 --> 00:03:32,930
They don't like their graves being violated,

49
00:03:33,130 --> 00:03:36,460
so they cover them in sand and letters to alert them of mischief.

50
00:03:36,660 --> 00:03:38,660
What does it say?

51
00:03:38,800 --> 00:03:41,230
Funnily enough...

52
00:03:41,430 --> 00:03:43,600
'Taken.'

53
00:03:43,930 --> 00:03:47,430
I'm a son of earth and starry heaven.

54
00:03:48,130 --> 00:03:49,760
I'm thirsty.

55
00:03:51,760 --> 00:03:53,830
Please...

56
00:03:54,030 --> 00:03:57,100
give me something to drink from the fountain of memory.

57
00:04:03,960 --> 00:04:06,700
See, as I have seen...

58
00:04:06,860 --> 00:04:09,600
into infinity...

59
00:04:09,730 --> 00:04:11,400
and you will be a god.

60
00:04:13,530 --> 00:04:15,860
But know this.

61
00:04:16,030 --> 00:04:18,860
You will... suffer.

62
00:04:19,100 --> 00:04:22,230
One corpse.

63
00:04:22,360 --> 00:04:25,460
Freshly plucked.

64
00:04:25,600 --> 00:04:28,200
Was it a nightmare, Maestro?

65
00:04:28,400 --> 00:04:30,100
No, it was something else entirely.

66
00:04:33,400 --> 00:04:35,730
Take notes, would you?

67
00:04:35,900 --> 00:04:40,700
I perceive the expected marks from strangulation.

68
00:04:40,860 --> 00:04:42,660
Crushed larynx.

69
00:04:42,830 --> 00:04:44,160
Nico.

70
00:04:44,330 --> 00:04:47,900
Diminished musculature. Likely from malnutrition.

71
00:04:48,060 --> 00:04:49,700
Circumcised member.

72
00:04:49,930 --> 00:04:51,360
I've never seen one of those before.

73
00:04:53,630 --> 00:04:54,960
What is that?

74
00:04:57,460 --> 00:05:01,530
A missing fingernail, on the right digitus primus.

75
00:05:09,300 --> 00:05:12,060
Leo, what are you doing?

76
00:05:12,260 --> 00:05:16,430
The Turk said to start my quest with a hanged man.

77
00:05:16,660 --> 00:05:20,500
Specifically, the seat of the soul.

78
00:05:21,430 --> 00:05:23,260
It's a euphemism for the stomach.

79
00:05:39,500 --> 00:05:41,400
The missing fingernail.

80
00:05:42,530 --> 00:05:44,930
Odd that he would ingest it.

81
00:05:56,660 --> 00:05:59,500
One man's death

82
00:05:59,700 --> 00:06:03,060
opens the doorway for another.

83
00:06:13,430 --> 00:06:15,200
Did your husband give you that?

84
00:06:20,130 --> 00:06:22,400
It's a family heirloom.

85
00:06:22,530 --> 00:06:24,160
From Ceylon.

86
00:06:24,360 --> 00:06:26,730
It's a stone called Serendibite.

87
00:06:33,500 --> 00:06:35,300
What's troubling you?

88
00:06:35,330 --> 00:06:40,200
Count Riario is coming to pay us a visit.

89
00:06:40,330 --> 00:06:41,860
For what purpose?

90
00:06:42,130 --> 00:06:44,360
Oh, nothing pleasant, I'm sure.

91
00:06:46,300 --> 00:06:49,400
But I'll be expected to wine and dine him,

92
00:06:49,630 --> 00:06:51,900
whilst hosting the rest of Florence's elite.

93
00:06:53,800 --> 00:06:55,960
Will you come?

94
00:06:56,160 --> 00:06:59,060
You can keep Riario entertained.

95
00:06:59,100 --> 00:07:01,000
Will Clarice be there?

96
00:07:01,160 --> 00:07:02,260
Of course.

97
00:07:04,900 --> 00:07:08,300
We can steal glances throughout the evening.

98
00:07:10,800 --> 00:07:13,800
I'll even invite that scoundrel, if you like.

99
00:07:15,960 --> 00:07:18,360
Da Vinci.

100
00:07:18,600 --> 00:07:21,430
The one who's supposed to be painting your portrait.

101
00:07:22,760 --> 00:07:26,030
And building me a weapon.

102
00:07:42,060 --> 00:07:44,030
You're late, son.

103
00:07:44,160 --> 00:07:46,560
Contract... signed.

104
00:07:48,530 --> 00:07:50,930
And now binding.

105
00:07:51,200 --> 00:07:53,430
- Did you not even read it? - We'd agreed the terms.

106
00:07:53,660 --> 00:07:56,430
But not the administration of those terms.

107
00:07:56,560 --> 00:07:58,630
I told you to stay away.

108
00:07:58,830 --> 00:08:00,900
I let you know there would be consequences.

109
00:08:01,100 --> 00:08:03,230
What do you think you've done?

110
00:08:03,400 --> 00:08:05,000
Painting Lucrezia Donati,

111
00:08:05,260 --> 00:08:09,860
fraudulently leading the Medicis to believe you can deliver preposterous weapons of war.

112
00:08:10,230 --> 00:08:14,900
You've overreached, and now I've made it so you'll soon be gone.

113
00:08:15,130 --> 00:08:19,400
There isn't a contract you can devise that can contain me.

114
00:08:19,630 --> 00:08:23,360
You're the bastard son of a servant girl I spilled my seed into.

115
00:08:23,500 --> 00:08:25,860
Your heritage contains you.

116
00:09:12,430 --> 00:09:14,900
No!

117
00:09:15,160 --> 00:09:17,160
- What's wrong?  - What's changed?

118
00:09:18,700 --> 00:09:22,660
Something's shifted in you since last we met.

119
00:09:22,930 --> 00:09:27,560
Perhaps it's just you and me here in Lorenzo's home.

120
00:09:27,700 --> 00:09:28,830
Feeling guilty?

121
00:09:29,100 --> 00:09:32,530
It's not as if I don't have affection for him.

122
00:09:32,730 --> 00:09:35,260
Or perhaps...

123
00:09:35,500 --> 00:09:38,900
I'm guilty about feeling guilty.

124
00:09:40,900 --> 00:09:43,200
It's not as if I don't have affection for you as well.

125
00:09:43,360 --> 00:09:45,830
Which guilt do you prefer, then?

126
00:09:46,130 --> 00:09:49,100
I have known Lorenzo since I was a girl. I've known you a week.

127
00:09:49,360 --> 00:09:51,830
- That's not an answer.  - Well...

128
00:09:56,660 --> 00:09:58,630
The Jew they executed...

129
00:10:01,600 --> 00:10:03,400
What was his offence?

130
00:10:05,000 --> 00:10:07,900
He said he had to run from cut-throats...

131
00:10:08,130 --> 00:10:10,900
and he took refuge in a bookstore.

132
00:10:11,130 --> 00:10:14,160
The authorities suspect he stole something,

133
00:10:14,300 --> 00:10:16,160
but nothing was missing,

134
00:10:16,400 --> 00:10:18,460
and the bag he carried was empty.

135
00:10:19,500 --> 00:10:22,300
So, they hanged a man...

136
00:10:22,500 --> 00:10:24,760
for stealing something that wasn't missing.

137
00:10:27,130 --> 00:10:30,830
The scene of the crime requires further investigation.

138
00:10:33,260 --> 00:10:34,560
Does it?

139
00:10:40,260 --> 00:10:42,460
Prepare the horses!

140
00:10:42,660 --> 00:10:44,260
I want to be off at once.

141
00:10:48,000 --> 00:10:49,630
You've finished today's siting already?

142
00:10:49,800 --> 00:10:52,700
Yes. Signor Da Vinci had somewhere to be.

143
00:10:52,900 --> 00:10:56,830
Ah, yes. He's testing his gun for us.

144
00:10:57,000 --> 00:11:00,330
Today he gives Florence its sting...

145
00:11:01,860 --> 00:11:03,730
while I show him mine.

146
00:11:05,260 --> 00:11:08,230
It's quite considerate he left us a moment to be alone.

147
00:11:14,330 --> 00:11:16,860
Lorenzo, anybody could walk in.

148
00:11:17,000 --> 00:11:18,700
I just needed a bit of you.

149
00:11:18,830 --> 00:11:20,800
And you will have it...

150
00:11:20,960 --> 00:11:22,630
for it is yours alone.

151
00:11:27,830 --> 00:11:30,960
- Good luck today.  - We're off!

152
00:11:35,530 --> 00:11:37,260
Good luck.

153
00:11:37,430 --> 00:11:39,260
That bit of you...

154
00:11:41,600 --> 00:11:43,400
It's not his alone.

155
00:11:43,600 --> 00:11:46,630
No... it's not.

156
00:11:46,860 --> 00:11:50,630
But it will always be his first.

157
00:12:12,500 --> 00:12:15,130
Do you have any saltpeter?

158
00:12:15,300 --> 00:12:17,600
What do you need potassium nitrate for?

159
00:12:17,800 --> 00:12:21,060
Gunpowder. The maestro's designing a weapon.

160
00:12:21,230 --> 00:12:23,060
He calls it the pipe-organ musket.

161
00:12:29,060 --> 00:12:30,900
The recoil will kill him.

162
00:12:31,130 --> 00:12:32,700
Don't worry. He's worked it out.

163
00:12:32,930 --> 00:12:37,360
By God... he's corrupted you already.

164
00:12:37,600 --> 00:12:41,860
Over there, third shelf, between the vermillion and the ultramarine.

165
00:12:43,030 --> 00:12:45,430
And tell him I expect to be paid in coin,

166
00:12:45,460 --> 00:12:48,430
not idle boasts, like last time.

167
00:12:51,160 --> 00:12:53,360
Come on.

168
00:12:53,600 --> 00:12:55,730
- God!  - Careful, Giuliano.

169
00:12:56,000 --> 00:12:59,230
Fucking hell! What are we doing here, in the middle of nowhere?

170
00:12:59,500 --> 00:13:01,930
- Where is he?  - Perhaps he's simply late.

171
00:13:02,300 --> 00:13:07,000
Or perhaps he realized what he proposed was more than a flying party trick.

172
00:13:07,260 --> 00:13:10,030
I wouldn't be surprised if he had no intention of coming here.

173
00:13:10,330 --> 00:13:13,630
I'm telling you, brother. The man's a lunatic and a coward.

174
00:13:13,800 --> 00:13:14,900
God! Shit!

175
00:13:14,930 --> 00:13:17,360
Keep control of yourself they're only cut-outs.

176
00:13:17,630 --> 00:13:21,160
Quickly! Soldiers advancing on Florence!

177
00:13:28,600 --> 00:13:31,000
How... how dare you?

178
00:13:31,300 --> 00:13:35,130
You are pointing a weapon at the house of Medici! Men, take him!

179
00:13:35,300 --> 00:13:38,200
- Hold.  - It passed its first test.

180
00:13:38,500 --> 00:13:42,900
- It's done nothing.  - No, it's done a great deal.

181
00:13:43,030 --> 00:13:44,500
Intimidation.

182
00:13:44,700 --> 00:13:48,060
Now, if you will proceed to the gallery...

183
00:13:48,300 --> 00:13:52,260
we will proceed to testing its less ephemeral utility.

184
00:13:52,560 --> 00:13:54,230
You've picked quite a day for it Da Vinci.

185
00:13:54,460 --> 00:13:55,860
Yes. You like it?

186
00:13:56,030 --> 00:13:58,300
I think it adds to the verisimilitude.

187
00:13:58,530 --> 00:14:01,500
I question the company the maestro keeps.

188
00:14:01,730 --> 00:14:03,860
That man's a known reprobate.

189
00:14:03,900 --> 00:14:06,400
Are these soldiers meant to be Swiss?

190
00:14:06,630 --> 00:14:09,000
- And you would be...?  - Commander Quattrone,

191
00:14:09,230 --> 00:14:11,360
leader of the Florentine militia.

192
00:14:11,730 --> 00:14:16,860
His Magnificence thought it wise to bring a military strategist along.

193
00:14:17,100 --> 00:14:19,430
In order to better evaluate your work.

194
00:14:19,700 --> 00:14:23,800
- I wish I'd brought a boat.  - Well, Commander has a keen eye.

195
00:14:24,100 --> 00:14:30,200
What you see here is a representation of Rome's private mercenary regiment.

196
00:14:30,360 --> 00:14:32,460
It's a bit of theatrics,

197
00:14:32,730 --> 00:14:35,630
but often presentation is more than half the performance.

198
00:14:35,930 --> 00:14:37,900
Well, get on with it, Da Vinci.

199
00:14:38,060 --> 00:14:41,060
While you delay, we drown.

200
00:14:41,100 --> 00:14:43,900
- Where was I? Yes.  - Come on.

201
00:14:44,060 --> 00:14:47,760
Quickly! Soldiers advancing on Florence!

202
00:14:48,000 --> 00:14:50,300
- Yes, yes, yes.  - The man is mad.

203
00:15:24,460 --> 00:15:28,700
The house of Medici has invested hundreds of florins in this project.

204
00:15:28,900 --> 00:15:31,600
According to your contract, the failure of this contraption

205
00:15:31,760 --> 00:15:33,800
constitutes fraud.

206
00:15:33,960 --> 00:15:36,300
Men, take him away.

207
00:15:38,160 --> 00:15:40,300
On your feet, maestro.

208
00:15:41,800 --> 00:15:43,830
Hold.

209
00:15:44,000 --> 00:15:46,900
You have one week, artista.

210
00:15:47,030 --> 00:15:48,500
Lorenzo, no.

211
00:15:48,700 --> 00:15:51,330
The materials alone will cost another 200 florins.

212
00:15:51,500 --> 00:15:53,630
One week.

213
00:15:53,800 --> 00:15:57,930
That sounds... quite reasonable.

214
00:16:02,330 --> 00:16:04,300
I'll have two, if the price is right.

215
00:16:12,960 --> 00:16:14,700
I'm gonna have words with you, boy.

216
00:16:15,030 --> 00:16:18,360
We found footprints in the graveyard where the Jew's body was stolen.

217
00:16:18,700 --> 00:16:24,500
A donkey's, a man's and a child's.

218
00:16:24,660 --> 00:16:27,760
Long-toed poulaines...

219
00:16:27,900 --> 00:16:29,800
such as you are wearing.

220
00:16:41,500 --> 00:16:43,230
Do you know who I am?

221
00:16:45,630 --> 00:16:49,060
I am Lord Girolamo Riario.

222
00:16:49,230 --> 00:16:52,860
Count and Captain General of the Holy Roman Church.

223
00:16:53,730 --> 00:16:56,660
Nephew of His Holiness...

224
00:16:56,830 --> 00:16:58,760
Pope Sixtus IV.

225
00:17:00,500 --> 00:17:04,160
Signor Morgante has informed us of your grave-robbing exploits.

226
00:17:04,430 --> 00:17:08,560
- I don't know what you mean.  - Don't insult us, boy.

227
00:17:08,800 --> 00:17:10,960
We're well aware of who your master is.

228
00:17:11,130 --> 00:17:15,000
Erm... Your Excellency, there was the matter of payment.

229
00:17:16,500 --> 00:17:18,160
Hmm.

230
00:17:18,330 --> 00:17:19,600
Yes, of course.

231
00:17:20,760 --> 00:17:22,600
Captain Grunwald.

232
00:17:33,130 --> 00:17:34,930
Jesus!

233
00:17:38,130 --> 00:17:41,630
Now that we've established my propensity for directness,

234
00:17:41,660 --> 00:17:45,100
I trust our conversation will proceed smoothly.

235
00:17:45,360 --> 00:17:50,400
Now, we're interested in why Da Vinci required the Jew's body,

236
00:17:50,560 --> 00:17:54,430
and, lest you be tempted to feign further ignorance,

237
00:17:54,600 --> 00:17:57,730
I wanted to demonstrate a remarkable device

238
00:17:57,900 --> 00:18:01,160
I recently acquired from the Orient.

239
00:18:01,460 --> 00:18:04,930
It's called... the Widow's Tear.

240
00:18:14,600 --> 00:18:16,230
No!

241
00:18:16,560 --> 00:18:21,000
The source of the discomfort you're feeling is an exquisitely tooled diamond needle

242
00:18:21,200 --> 00:18:25,800
the titular Widow's Tear.

243
00:18:25,960 --> 00:18:28,730
And as I turn the handle, the diamond...

244
00:18:30,460 --> 00:18:34,000
slowly incises a circle of skin,

245
00:18:34,200 --> 00:18:38,200
from the back of the hand, one layer of epidermis at a time.

246
00:18:41,860 --> 00:18:47,230
Now, I want you to weigh your next answer very, very carefully.

247
00:18:47,430 --> 00:18:50,730
Why did Da Vinci unearth the Jew's body?

248
00:18:57,860 --> 00:19:00,400
Very well. Another turn.

249
00:19:11,400 --> 00:19:14,460
Stop! Stop, stop.

250
00:19:16,260 --> 00:19:20,330
Shhh, shhh. It's alright, Nico.

251
00:19:20,530 --> 00:19:24,730
Just a few simple words, and we can end all this unpleasantness.

252
00:19:27,230 --> 00:19:30,760
He was searching...

253
00:19:30,900 --> 00:19:33,660
The Jew swallowed something.

254
00:19:33,830 --> 00:19:36,000
What, child?

255
00:19:40,000 --> 00:19:41,530
A key.

256
00:19:44,400 --> 00:19:48,200
Leave nothing unturned. Just find the key.

257
00:19:52,500 --> 00:19:54,460
Rip it apart!

258
00:19:54,630 --> 00:19:55,900
Stop!

259
00:19:58,030 --> 00:19:59,800
You won't find it.

260
00:20:20,000 --> 00:20:22,130
That's what you're looking for.

261
00:20:29,900 --> 00:20:33,730
- Open it.  - I can't. It's locked.

262
00:20:33,860 --> 00:20:35,430
Hack it apart.

263
00:20:44,200 --> 00:20:45,830
Wait a moment!

264
00:20:51,460 --> 00:20:54,830
Let's get out of here! Hurry!

265
00:20:55,060 --> 00:20:56,660
Let's get out of here!

266
00:20:56,800 --> 00:20:59,260
You, boy...! You...!

267
00:21:02,060 --> 00:21:04,560
You have defied instruments of the Lord's will!

268
00:21:04,800 --> 00:21:07,230
Leonardo!

269
00:21:07,400 --> 00:21:09,500
Go! Go!

270
00:21:09,700 --> 00:21:13,160
Leonardo! Are you alright?

271
00:21:16,060 --> 00:21:18,800
Oh, merciful heaven! What happened here?

272
00:21:19,030 --> 00:21:21,330
These men are agents of the papacy.

273
00:21:21,660 --> 00:21:24,600
What, it wasn't enough to tangle with the Medicis? Now you're...?

274
00:21:24,860 --> 00:21:27,230
Leo, you're talking about the Pope.

275
00:21:27,400 --> 00:21:29,960
Not to worry. They could only have our entrails when I already suck it out...

276
00:21:30,130 --> 00:21:33,100
Nico, who did this to you?

277
00:21:33,260 --> 00:21:35,560
Count Riario.

278
00:21:35,730 --> 00:21:37,600
The papal nephew and attack dog?

279
00:21:37,800 --> 00:21:39,960
He snatched me from the market.

280
00:21:40,130 --> 00:21:42,300
I told him... I'm sorry.

281
00:21:42,500 --> 00:21:44,800
I told him you took the key from the Jew's body.

282
00:21:45,060 --> 00:21:48,330
Well, you may have told them that, but you showed them something else.

283
00:21:48,360 --> 00:21:52,560
Hey, you've done something exceptional, Nico.

284
00:21:52,760 --> 00:21:55,300
You've saved your own life, into the bargain.

285
00:22:02,430 --> 00:22:04,500
Halt!

286
00:22:04,660 --> 00:22:07,260
Be still.

287
00:22:07,430 --> 00:22:10,030
Our visitor was expected.

288
00:22:10,330 --> 00:22:13,900
You know I can't be seen with you. There are too many prying eyes.

289
00:22:14,130 --> 00:22:15,830
If I had been stopped on the road...

290
00:22:18,960 --> 00:22:21,600
You needn't lecture me on the necessity of discretion.

291
00:22:21,830 --> 00:22:26,860
I wouldn't jeopardize such a valuable asset as yourself without ample reason.

292
00:22:30,330 --> 00:22:33,460
Now, take these.

293
00:22:33,630 --> 00:22:37,930
A list of secure locales hidden throughout Florence.

294
00:22:38,900 --> 00:22:40,930
I need more information.

295
00:22:41,130 --> 00:22:45,030
Details of Lorenzo and Da Vinci's activities.

296
00:22:45,200 --> 00:22:47,600
If you have something pertinent to convey,

297
00:22:47,630 --> 00:22:50,730
inscribe the Greek letter alpha

298
00:22:50,900 --> 00:22:54,200
above whichever locale is convenient.

299
00:22:54,360 --> 00:22:56,830
If we have something to convey to you,

300
00:22:57,000 --> 00:23:00,930
we will inscribe the letter omega.

301
00:23:03,800 --> 00:23:05,800
Are you clear on all this?

302
00:23:06,000 --> 00:23:08,360
That's the official papal seal.

303
00:23:08,500 --> 00:23:10,700
Mark your messages with it.

304
00:23:10,830 --> 00:23:12,800
And one final thing.

305
00:23:14,960 --> 00:23:16,660
What is it?

306
00:23:16,830 --> 00:23:18,760
Instructions will be forthcoming.

307
00:23:18,930 --> 00:23:22,200
In the meantime, keep it hidden.

308
00:23:23,060 --> 00:23:25,030
Now, Da Vinci...

309
00:23:25,200 --> 00:23:29,730
Has your celebrated artist made any mention of a key?

310
00:23:29,960 --> 00:23:33,560
- What about the Jew?  - He asked about his capture.

311
00:23:33,800 --> 00:23:36,000
He wanted to return to the scene of the crime.

312
00:23:36,230 --> 00:23:37,560
That's how he put it.

313
00:23:37,800 --> 00:23:41,000
He was preoccupied with why a Jew would hide in a bookshop.

314
00:23:41,160 --> 00:23:43,560
Why would Da Vinci concern himself with a bookshop?

315
00:23:43,830 --> 00:23:47,600
I don't know. Perhaps Da Vinci is more clever than you.

316
00:23:47,830 --> 00:23:51,660
But then that would be heresy, wouldn't it?

317
00:23:51,800 --> 00:23:53,760
Keep an eye on that bookshop.

318
00:23:54,000 --> 00:23:58,060
If we're lucky, Da Vinci will complete our investigations for us.

319
00:23:58,200 --> 00:24:01,330
And you, Miss Donati,

320
00:24:01,560 --> 00:24:05,800
do continue ensnaring Lorenzo and Da Vinci with that...

321
00:24:05,930 --> 00:24:07,800
pretty little cunt of yours.

322
00:24:09,430 --> 00:24:11,600
- You're a bastard.  - Yes.

323
00:24:11,760 --> 00:24:14,330
And the architect of my pedigree

324
00:24:14,460 --> 00:24:17,760
is the Holy Father himself.

325
00:24:17,800 --> 00:24:21,460
Now, go, lest the prying eyes of Florence see us together

326
00:24:21,630 --> 00:24:25,230
and question your already compromised character.

327
00:24:30,200 --> 00:24:34,130
She grows more impertinent with every encounter.

328
00:24:35,500 --> 00:24:37,700
Hmm.

329
00:24:38,030 --> 00:24:42,060
Even a mouse occasionally bears its teeth when it's about to be crushed.

330
00:24:44,260 --> 00:24:47,500
Scudos, the papal currency.

331
00:24:49,860 --> 00:24:52,430
Let's review the events again, Da Vinci.

332
00:24:52,630 --> 00:24:56,100
They took the boy and ransacked your workshop.

333
00:24:56,260 --> 00:24:57,560
What were they looking for?

334
00:24:57,700 --> 00:24:59,500
My weapon designs, I present.

335
00:24:59,730 --> 00:25:04,100
Well, let Rome have them. By this time next week, they'll have decimated themselves.

336
00:25:08,160 --> 00:25:11,160
By this time next week, they could decimate US!

337
00:25:11,200 --> 00:25:14,160
- Lorenzo...  - Open your eyes, brother!

338
00:25:14,360 --> 00:25:17,330
We no longer enjoy Milan's protection.

339
00:25:17,560 --> 00:25:19,630
I want your men to surround this building.

340
00:25:19,860 --> 00:25:22,300
No-one to come in or out, save Da Vinci and the boy.

341
00:25:22,530 --> 00:25:25,500
You will accompany Da Vinci wherever he goes.

342
00:25:25,700 --> 00:25:28,300
Oh, I hardly think that's necessary!

343
00:25:31,200 --> 00:25:32,430
Go.

344
00:25:34,930 --> 00:25:38,060
You have three days for a successful fire of your gun.

345
00:25:38,300 --> 00:25:40,660
If it fails, there will be no second chances.

346
00:25:40,900 --> 00:25:44,530
There will be no trial. You will hang.

347
00:25:47,460 --> 00:25:51,030
Whatever you need to accomplish this you will possess.

348
00:25:51,200 --> 00:25:54,260
Money, materials, men.

349
00:25:54,500 --> 00:25:57,100
Make your vision real, Da Vinci...

350
00:25:58,930 --> 00:26:01,330
for your very life.

351
00:26:06,860 --> 00:26:10,500
When the black hood pulls the lever...

352
00:26:10,730 --> 00:26:13,630
be sure to clench.

353
00:26:16,800 --> 00:26:20,430
Those guards are going to make it difficult to sneak off to the tavern.

354
00:26:20,660 --> 00:26:24,160
- Did you hear what he said?  - Yes.

355
00:26:24,360 --> 00:26:26,330
I need to think.

356
00:26:26,530 --> 00:26:29,030
And if I need to think, I need to drink.

357
00:26:33,230 --> 00:26:35,430
This place is wonderful.

358
00:26:35,660 --> 00:26:38,360
So much better than the convent.

359
00:26:38,560 --> 00:26:42,430
A million thanks to you, Leonardo.

360
00:26:43,130 --> 00:26:44,830
What are you doing?

361
00:26:45,060 --> 00:26:49,560
I'm trying to envisage what kind of lock the notches on this key correspond to.

362
00:27:12,330 --> 00:27:15,160
Nico, do you have that coin the Turk gave you?

363
00:27:24,530 --> 00:27:26,060
I thought so.

364
00:27:27,700 --> 00:27:29,660
Two keys.

365
00:27:40,260 --> 00:27:42,530
Whatever lock this corresponds with, I'd wager

366
00:27:42,800 --> 00:27:47,260
the key represents only half of the mechanism needed to open it.

367
00:27:47,430 --> 00:27:50,260
Leo, honestly, who cares?

368
00:27:50,460 --> 00:27:52,630
Just give the damn thing to Riario.

369
00:27:52,640 --> 00:27:52,780
You have a musket to complete.

370
00:27:52,800 --> 00:27:54,230
Inspiration can't be forced.

371
00:27:54,430 --> 00:27:55,600
Oh, well, tell that to the hangman...

372
00:27:55,760 --> 00:27:57,200
Hangman: Inspiration cannot be forced

373
00:27:57,400 --> 00:28:01,100
Look, the fact that Riario would jeopardize a formal visit

374
00:28:01,230 --> 00:28:02,800
to acquire this is telling.

375
00:28:03,030 --> 00:28:06,560
Obviously, it's linked to the Book of Leaves. The Turk confirmed it.

376
00:28:06,800 --> 00:28:08,860
Of course, the Turk. Your mystery man.

377
00:28:09,030 --> 00:28:13,660
Yes! And since we have a mystery here...

378
00:28:13,830 --> 00:28:15,300
I intend to see it through.

379
00:28:15,530 --> 00:28:18,430
What mystery? The Jew stole a key.

380
00:28:18,630 --> 00:28:21,630
He swallowed it to prevent his pursuers from getting it.

381
00:28:21,830 --> 00:28:23,530
Why would he break into a bookshop?

382
00:28:23,800 --> 00:28:27,230
That's where the key was in the first place. That's why he broke in.

383
00:28:27,560 --> 00:28:29,130
No, the narrative doesn't hold up.

384
00:28:29,330 --> 00:28:30,460
The bookshop reported nothing missing.

385
00:28:30,660 --> 00:28:33,800
- Oh, for fuck's sake!  - And his bag was empty.

386
00:28:34,030 --> 00:28:39,600
And why the fingernail? And why was the Jew being pursued...

387
00:28:39,760 --> 00:28:41,260
before the bookshop?

388
00:28:49,760 --> 00:28:54,830
According to the Count, the Jew crossed the piazza to Duomo...

389
00:28:55,030 --> 00:28:58,800
and then entered Via Dei Librai... here.

390
00:29:00,430 --> 00:29:03,900
Perhaps someone witnessed the event.

391
00:29:04,060 --> 00:29:07,360
Please, signor, can you offer any charity?

392
00:29:07,530 --> 00:29:09,460
Tell me, good man.

393
00:29:09,660 --> 00:29:11,500
Were you here the night the Jew was caught?

394
00:29:11,660 --> 00:29:14,860
Indeed I was, for this is my home, and I have no other.

395
00:29:15,160 --> 00:29:17,200
Now he's lacking visual, can't you see this man's blind?

396
00:29:17,360 --> 00:29:18,560
Shhh.

397
00:29:21,000 --> 00:29:23,500
A florin, signor?

398
00:29:23,730 --> 00:29:25,500
You could identify that by its sound?

399
00:29:25,830 --> 00:29:29,460
I am well versed in the respective tones of our realm's coinage.

400
00:29:29,730 --> 00:29:33,230
If you would, my friend, could you describe what you heard that night?

401
00:29:33,400 --> 00:29:36,500
With pleasure. It was a cold night.

402
00:29:36,800 --> 00:29:40,000
When I first heard the shouts, I thought I was dreaming.

403
00:29:40,230 --> 00:29:42,400
They were coming from the Duomo.

404
00:29:42,660 --> 00:29:46,100
Then I heard the Jew's footsteps and his breath.

405
00:29:46,330 --> 00:29:49,500
He was terrified. I could tell that.

406
00:29:49,630 --> 00:29:52,300
Then he fell.

407
00:29:52,630 --> 00:29:55,930
Dropped something. Pages fluttering like bird's wings.

408
00:29:56,230 --> 00:29:58,900
Then I heard the Jew say, 'Wo, wo?'

409
00:29:59,030 --> 00:30:00,900
Wo, wo?

410
00:30:00,930 --> 00:30:03,900
And I heard more shouts, his pursuers calling after him.

411
00:30:04,230 --> 00:30:09,660
I did not understand a word they said, except for 'halt'.

412
00:30:09,830 --> 00:30:11,960
Halt.

413
00:30:12,200 --> 00:30:14,260
You still think this shed light on your mystery?

414
00:30:14,560 --> 00:30:18,630
The men chasing the Jew spoke a foreign tongue, yet they used the word 'halt'.

415
00:30:18,660 --> 00:30:20,400
Only two languages use that word, German and English.

416
00:30:20,600 --> 00:30:22,460
- So...?  - So, the Swiss mercenaries

417
00:30:22,660 --> 00:30:24,830
employed by Rome speak German,

418
00:30:25,060 --> 00:30:27,630
and they must have assumed the Jew understood it,

419
00:30:27,860 --> 00:30:30,360
which makes sense, since most Jews speak Yiddish, a form of German.

420
00:30:30,700 --> 00:30:34,900
The word 'wo' in Yiddish means 'where'.

421
00:30:35,100 --> 00:30:38,930
The Jew wasn't fearful. He was searching for something.

422
00:30:39,130 --> 00:30:42,400
See, I believe he had two items in his possession.

423
00:30:42,630 --> 00:30:45,830
The first was small enough for him to swallow, the key.

424
00:30:46,000 --> 00:30:47,800
The second was larger,

425
00:30:48,000 --> 00:30:49,630
forcing him to find a hiding-place for it.

426
00:30:49,660 --> 00:30:53,400
- The fluttering pages is a book.  - Precisely.

427
00:30:53,600 --> 00:30:57,100
And where would one best hide a book?

428
00:31:03,130 --> 00:31:07,430
Would you mind skulking around, making the proprietor apprehensive?

429
00:31:07,460 --> 00:31:09,100
Why me?

430
00:31:09,260 --> 00:31:11,360
Well, because you reek of dishonesty.

431
00:31:11,530 --> 00:31:13,900
As usual.

432
00:31:14,060 --> 00:31:16,200
Signor Vesticci, how goes it?

433
00:31:16,360 --> 00:31:19,430
Tell me, how many rows of shelves do you have?

434
00:31:19,560 --> 00:31:20,900
Ten. What of it?

435
00:31:21,130 --> 00:31:24,630
You there, did you just stuff something into your robes just now?

436
00:31:24,860 --> 00:31:28,360
I beg your pardon? You offend me. I was simply hefting the weight of this tome.

437
00:31:28,560 --> 00:31:31,230
The fingernail was a clue to the second item's location.

438
00:31:31,400 --> 00:31:33,630
Ten shelves. Ten fingers.

439
00:31:33,800 --> 00:31:36,100
Now, we're facing the west.

440
00:31:36,400 --> 00:31:40,600
It would be more obvious, when counting, to face the opposite direction,

441
00:31:40,760 --> 00:31:43,430
the east and the rising sun.

442
00:31:45,630 --> 00:31:50,000
Additionally, Hebrew is the sacred language of the Jews,

443
00:31:50,000 --> 00:31:51,560
which is read from right to left.

444
00:31:51,800 --> 00:31:55,600
So, if we count from the right...

445
00:31:58,130 --> 00:32:00,530
we get row number five.

446
00:32:00,700 --> 00:32:02,430
Blood.

447
00:32:02,460 --> 00:32:04,860
Now, we know he bit off his fingernail.

448
00:32:07,660 --> 00:32:09,930
Look, Nico. There.

449
00:32:10,130 --> 00:32:12,560
Dust. None's disturbed these books in ages.

450
00:32:12,700 --> 00:32:14,760
But here...

451
00:32:18,600 --> 00:32:20,700
There's no dust at all on this book.

452
00:32:21,900 --> 00:32:24,000
Written in Hebrew, no less.

453
00:32:27,430 --> 00:32:29,830
I think we've found item number two.

454
00:32:32,230 --> 00:32:34,960
I take it all back. If you had tits, I'd marry you.

455
00:32:35,230 --> 00:32:39,000
So, you long for the soul of a man but the breasts of a woman?

456
00:32:39,230 --> 00:32:41,760
You have a treacherous road ahead, my friend.

457
00:32:50,200 --> 00:32:53,100
Artista, you will come with us.

458
00:32:53,430 --> 00:32:59,430
If you resist... Well, just ask your little friend about Riario's hospitality.

459
00:32:59,730 --> 00:33:04,030
Well, unfortunately, we will have to decline the Count's invitation.

460
00:33:09,800 --> 00:33:11,100
What is that?

461
00:33:11,330 --> 00:33:15,030
Well, you're acquainted with my infernal devices.

462
00:33:15,230 --> 00:33:17,760
The exploding chest, in my workshop.

463
00:33:17,960 --> 00:33:21,900
Well, this works on the same principle.

464
00:33:22,130 --> 00:33:25,830
It is a grenado. It's packed with gunpowder.

465
00:33:26,060 --> 00:33:28,160
Activated by a push-button on its base.

466
00:33:28,200 --> 00:33:31,500
And if I remove my thumb...

467
00:33:33,360 --> 00:33:34,730
the device will explode.

468
00:33:35,030 --> 00:33:37,430
He's lying. It's a snuff-box.

469
00:33:37,700 --> 00:33:41,000
Don't test my resolve. I do not care for you to die,

470
00:33:41,160 --> 00:33:42,730
on this day or any other.

471
00:33:43,030 --> 00:33:47,700
You think the greatest mind in all of Europe needs to bluff? Then try us.

472
00:33:47,900 --> 00:33:50,030
There's a vendor nearby that sells those things.

473
00:33:50,230 --> 00:33:52,030
This is Da Vinci you're staring down. This is a grenado.

474
00:33:52,330 --> 00:33:54,460
- It's a snuff-box.  - It's a fucking grenado.

475
00:33:58,700 --> 00:34:01,200
- Fuck me.  - Split up.

476
00:34:06,800 --> 00:34:08,760
After him!

477
00:34:09,030 --> 00:34:11,900
Halt! You won't get away from us!

478
00:34:25,760 --> 00:34:27,700
Halt!

479
00:34:31,430 --> 00:34:33,800
Halt!

480
00:34:33,960 --> 00:34:35,460
Stay where you are!

481
00:34:35,660 --> 00:34:37,730
- Got him!  - Shit!

482
00:34:41,600 --> 00:34:43,200
Shit.

483
00:34:46,760 --> 00:34:48,560
Stop!

484
00:35:11,130 --> 00:35:15,830
Oh, please, give Riario my regrets!

485
00:35:29,460 --> 00:35:32,660
Count Riario, if you'd be so kind.

486
00:35:34,500 --> 00:35:36,830
Signor di Medici.

487
00:35:36,960 --> 00:35:38,760
Lady Orsini.

488
00:35:39,000 --> 00:35:42,330
Thank you most humbly for the hospitality

489
00:35:42,600 --> 00:35:45,260
you've extended to our modest delegation.

490
00:35:45,430 --> 00:35:47,300
We are only too happy

491
00:35:47,560 --> 00:35:50,560
to receive Rome's favored son.

492
00:35:52,660 --> 00:35:54,900
Lord Girolamo.

493
00:36:02,530 --> 00:36:04,760
We are ecstatic.

494
00:36:06,060 --> 00:36:09,030
Shall you and I retire to my study for a few moments?

495
00:36:15,000 --> 00:36:17,300
Drop the niceties, Riario.

496
00:36:17,630 --> 00:36:22,130
Your men broke into my artist's studio. I want to know why.

497
00:36:22,330 --> 00:36:25,800
Word of Da Vinci has reached the Holy Father's ears.

498
00:36:26,100 --> 00:36:30,760
He's tasked me with finding artisans to adorn the great chapel he's building.

499
00:36:30,900 --> 00:36:33,200
I thought...

500
00:36:33,330 --> 00:36:34,930
Do you know what?

501
00:36:35,100 --> 00:36:37,730
An exploratory meeting might be in order.

502
00:36:37,760 --> 00:36:40,900
And was the death of your men part of that exploration?

503
00:36:41,200 --> 00:36:44,360
Only retroactively, but it taught me a few things about your man

504
00:36:44,600 --> 00:36:46,760
and made me anxious to make his acquaintance.

505
00:36:47,000 --> 00:36:49,300
Da Vinci is a mere dilettante.

506
00:36:49,530 --> 00:36:51,030
An amusement. Nothing more.

507
00:36:51,300 --> 00:36:53,960
And yet I'm told you've advanced him a stipend

508
00:36:54,130 --> 00:36:56,630
of 50 florins.

509
00:36:59,730 --> 00:37:02,900
Quite a handsome allowance for a mere dilettante.

510
00:37:03,060 --> 00:37:08,200
Rome hears every whisper, Lorenzo.

511
00:37:08,400 --> 00:37:13,860
Even outlandish ones concerning artisans capable of constructing war machines.

512
00:37:14,160 --> 00:37:17,700
The manufacture of armaments could be construed as a provocative move.

513
00:37:17,930 --> 00:37:20,500
As could the assassination of Duke Sforza.

514
00:37:21,730 --> 00:37:25,230
Or the refusal to pay one's debts.

515
00:37:25,430 --> 00:37:28,630
Usury. It's such an unseemly business.

516
00:37:28,930 --> 00:37:32,630
I hear the Holy Father is now borrowing money from the Pazzi family.

517
00:37:32,660 --> 00:37:34,960
Is he planning on bilking them as well?

518
00:37:36,700 --> 00:37:38,930
Since we're on the subject of provocations,

519
00:37:39,130 --> 00:37:42,660
I believe it's time I stated the purpose of my visit.

520
00:37:42,960 --> 00:37:47,830
His Holiness wishes to inform you of his choice for the Archbishop of Pisa.

521
00:37:48,100 --> 00:37:50,060
Pisa falls under Florence's jurisdiction.

522
00:37:50,230 --> 00:37:54,030
Nevertheless, the selection has been made.

523
00:37:54,200 --> 00:37:59,230
His Holiness has appointed Francesco Salviati.

524
00:38:01,060 --> 00:38:03,460
- Your cousin.  - Hmm.

525
00:38:05,700 --> 00:38:07,460
Well...

526
00:38:07,630 --> 00:38:10,600
It appears congratulations are in order.

527
00:38:10,860 --> 00:38:12,660
Please, inform the Holy Father

528
00:38:12,930 --> 00:38:16,660
that you and Salviati should assemble the largest army you can find...

529
00:38:16,900 --> 00:38:21,460
because the only way you're setting foot in Pisa is if I am dead and buried.

530
00:38:21,600 --> 00:38:23,000
I see.

531
00:38:23,200 --> 00:38:25,600
So, that's your proposed condition?

532
00:38:25,830 --> 00:38:28,130
Rome fired the first salvo, not I.

533
00:38:28,260 --> 00:38:31,060
And we intend to fire the last.

534
00:38:37,460 --> 00:38:40,560
Good night, Magnifico.

535
00:38:44,700 --> 00:38:47,300
How in Christ's name

536
00:38:47,460 --> 00:38:49,530
did he know all that?

537
00:38:49,700 --> 00:38:51,360
Troubling.

538
00:39:12,360 --> 00:39:14,930
You look very fetching in your night shirt.

539
00:39:15,200 --> 00:39:18,630
What are you doing, skulking around? I could have hurt you.

540
00:39:18,760 --> 00:39:20,930
With a drafting compass?

541
00:39:22,560 --> 00:39:24,160
Why are you here, Leonardo?

542
00:39:24,530 --> 00:39:28,860
I can't go to my quarters. The Vatican's thugs are looking for me.

543
00:39:29,100 --> 00:39:32,900
Lorenzo's men have been in and out of here all day, looking for you.

544
00:39:33,130 --> 00:39:36,460
Lorenzo gave me a deadline on my musket.

545
00:39:36,730 --> 00:39:38,500
Frankly, I'm not sure I can make it.

546
00:39:38,700 --> 00:39:40,200
I'm not surprised.

547
00:39:40,500 --> 00:39:44,200
You have three layers of cannons on top of one another. Yes?

548
00:39:44,360 --> 00:39:45,860
Mm-hm.

549
00:39:46,200 --> 00:39:48,960
Well, there's going to be some powder contamination between the tiers.

550
00:39:49,260 --> 00:39:53,560
Look, I promised Lorenzo a musket that could be fired and loaded simultaneously.

551
00:39:53,860 --> 00:39:57,760
This is a dangerous game you're playing with Lorenzo. Are you sure you have overreached?

552
00:39:58,030 --> 00:40:01,830
Christ, Andrea! The whole point of progress is overreaching.

553
00:40:02,060 --> 00:40:04,500
Why doesn't anyone understand that?

554
00:40:10,660 --> 00:40:12,130
Drink.

555
00:40:13,960 --> 00:40:17,460
Now, do you want to tell me what this is all really about?

556
00:40:23,060 --> 00:40:27,130
Have you heard of the Book of Leaves?

557
00:40:28,660 --> 00:40:31,230
It's a myth. No more real than a unicorn.

558
00:40:31,460 --> 00:40:33,330
I have reason to believe it exists. 

559
00:40:33,560 --> 00:40:36,700
A book of wonders, containing the secret history of the world? Please!

560
00:40:37,660 --> 00:40:40,560
- The Jew that was hanged.  - Hm?

561
00:40:40,730 --> 00:40:42,300
This was his.

562
00:40:42,330 --> 00:40:46,160
Your Hebrew's better than mine. Perhaps you can tell me what it concerns.

563
00:40:53,560 --> 00:40:58,360
It's... it's a treatise on the origins of the universe.

564
00:40:59,800 --> 00:41:02,560
Astronomy.

565
00:41:02,730 --> 00:41:06,960
It keeps referring to the Vault of Heaven, how it can be opened.

566
00:41:07,100 --> 00:41:09,000
Or perhaps... Ah-ha.

567
00:41:09,200 --> 00:41:11,930
So, the Vault of Heaven could refer to the night sky.

568
00:41:12,200 --> 00:41:15,330
So, perhaps the Book can be found by looking for a constellation.

569
00:41:15,530 --> 00:41:18,230
Leo, give up on this fool's errand

570
00:41:18,360 --> 00:41:20,130
and focus on your commission.

571
00:41:20,300 --> 00:41:22,730
Stop borrowing trouble based on a fable.

572
00:41:26,300 --> 00:41:27,960
This fable...

573
00:41:30,560 --> 00:41:32,960
is bound up in the fate of my mother.

574
00:41:38,100 --> 00:41:43,300
I can draw anything I've seen, Andrea. Anything.

575
00:41:43,530 --> 00:41:46,330
But I can't draw her face.

576
00:41:46,530 --> 00:41:48,100
I've tried. I can't.

577
00:41:48,460 --> 00:41:52,560
I can't. I just can't remember it.

578
00:41:52,760 --> 00:41:55,030
If there's any knowledge to be had of her

579
00:41:55,060 --> 00:41:57,960
bound up in this quest...

580
00:41:58,130 --> 00:42:00,100
I need to see it through.

581
00:42:02,030 --> 00:42:05,600
Then your need will most likely end up getting you killed.

582
00:42:26,360 --> 00:42:29,460
He told me the linens were from Naples.

583
00:42:29,660 --> 00:42:32,000
Isn't that right, dear?

584
00:42:32,160 --> 00:42:34,300
Me, a textile merchant.

585
00:42:34,600 --> 00:42:38,760
I suggested he start getting his wine from the Orient, while he's at it.

586
00:42:39,000 --> 00:42:41,900
Shouldn't you be working on Lorenzo's musket?

587
00:42:41,930 --> 00:42:45,400
Well, unlike you father. I'm capable of doing two things at the same time.

588
00:42:45,600 --> 00:42:48,560
Drinking and digging your own grave.

589
00:42:58,000 --> 00:42:59,600
Yours.

590
00:43:01,500 --> 00:43:05,030
The question you asked of me earlier.

591
00:43:05,160 --> 00:43:07,400
Which gift do I prefer.

592
00:43:11,700 --> 00:43:13,430
You seem very uncomfortable.

593
00:43:13,460 --> 00:43:15,960
I don't often attend affairs such as this.

594
00:43:16,230 --> 00:43:21,460
Well, I do. It's a confection of pretence and masks.

595
00:43:21,660 --> 00:43:24,860
Smile. Lorenzo's watching us.

596
00:43:32,260 --> 00:43:36,860
Your pardons and indulgences. Your pardons and indulgences.

597
00:43:36,900 --> 00:43:40,500
Welcome, all of you...

598
00:43:40,660 --> 00:43:42,760
to a feast of Florence,

599
00:43:42,800 --> 00:43:46,230
so full of life and vibrancy.

600
00:43:47,860 --> 00:43:50,030
So like Eden.

601
00:43:52,000 --> 00:43:55,260
Full of fresh fruits.

602
00:43:58,230 --> 00:44:00,900
Full of bird and game.

603
00:44:13,500 --> 00:44:16,460
Full of nature's grace.

604
00:44:39,700 --> 00:44:41,930
So like Eden...

605
00:44:42,130 --> 00:44:46,660
but, of course, Eden had guests.

606
00:44:49,330 --> 00:44:51,460
As do we.

607
00:44:51,830 --> 00:44:55,960
Of course, our guest is somewhat more pleasant than the serpent.

608
00:44:57,400 --> 00:45:01,360
Please let us welcome Count Girolamo Riario,

609
00:45:01,600 --> 00:45:03,400
emissary from Rome,

610
00:45:03,600 --> 00:45:07,030
to our Eden, to our Florence.

611
00:45:12,860 --> 00:45:15,930
Dinner is served.

612
00:45:29,500 --> 00:45:30,900
What do you see?

613
00:45:33,000 --> 00:45:37,000
I know who you are, you know who I am. We both know what's transpired.

614
00:45:37,000 --> 00:45:39,230
Now, tell me: what do you see?

615
00:45:39,430 --> 00:45:43,260
I believe I saw someone call you a snake in front of all those people.

616
00:45:45,200 --> 00:45:48,830
And I see a key that you will be giving to me...

617
00:45:49,030 --> 00:45:51,230
along with what you took from that bookstore.

618
00:45:51,430 --> 00:45:55,100
Well, both the key and the book the Jew hid are quite useless,

619
00:45:55,300 --> 00:45:59,360
unless one has the intellect required to find the Vault of Heaven.

620
00:45:59,430 --> 00:46:01,100
Then I'll have you as well. 

621
00:46:01,100 --> 00:46:03,130
Why would I possibly surrender myself to Rome?

622
00:46:03,260 --> 00:46:05,900
Perhaps you value your life?

623
00:46:08,160 --> 00:46:10,200
Not enough to betray Florence.

624
00:46:10,360 --> 00:46:12,600
Then...

625
00:46:12,830 --> 00:46:15,760
perhaps you value the life of another a little more.

626
00:46:18,360 --> 00:46:23,660
I know desire when I see it, and I am very well versed in the myriad ways

627
00:46:23,830 --> 00:46:26,160
of exploiting it.

628
00:46:26,400 --> 00:46:31,160
You know, this doesn't have to be contentious, Da Vinci.

629
00:46:31,400 --> 00:46:35,500
Join us, and the whole of the Vatican's Secret Archives

630
00:46:35,630 --> 00:46:37,160
can be at your disposal.

631
00:46:37,200 --> 00:46:39,700
You're offering me forbidden fruit now.

632
00:46:41,530 --> 00:46:44,100
That's what serpents do, isn't it?

633
00:46:48,100 --> 00:46:50,060
Meet me tomorrow at sunrise.

634
00:46:50,200 --> 00:46:55,500
And then the key, all of its secrets... can be yours.

635
00:46:55,660 --> 00:46:57,460
And your services?

636
00:46:57,830 --> 00:47:01,130
Surely, if I'm to find the Book of Leaves, I'll need those, as well?

637
00:47:43,730 --> 00:47:47,160
- What is he doing?  - He's playing with a bottle.

638
00:47:47,330 --> 00:47:48,860
Of course he is.

639
00:47:49,030 --> 00:47:51,400
I'll admit he eluded us once,

640
00:47:51,600 --> 00:47:54,100
but this time we're ready for him.

641
00:47:57,800 --> 00:48:00,600
There. It makes sense.

642
00:48:00,760 --> 00:48:03,830
He was already working with the Roman scum.

643
00:48:34,230 --> 00:48:36,330
Do we need any more proof?

644
00:48:36,460 --> 00:48:38,430
He is complicit with them.

645
00:48:39,830 --> 00:48:42,030
Consider this a retainer.

646
00:48:42,200 --> 00:48:44,300
For your services to Rome.

647
00:48:46,330 --> 00:48:48,230
Why do you hesitate, Da Vinci?

648
00:48:48,400 --> 00:48:50,330
This is the next step.

649
00:48:50,500 --> 00:48:53,100
Sorry. I don't follow you.

650
00:48:53,930 --> 00:48:55,960
Why did you exhume the Jew?

651
00:48:56,160 --> 00:48:59,600
Why do you endeavor to find the Vault?

652
00:48:59,800 --> 00:49:02,200
I don't endeavor.

653
00:49:02,400 --> 00:49:04,630
I've found it.

654
00:49:04,830 --> 00:49:09,360
The Vault of Heaven, which, presumably, contains the Book of Leaves.

655
00:49:09,600 --> 00:49:13,260
I've had it put on wheels, so I might move it for safekeeping.

656
00:49:13,430 --> 00:49:18,160
Apparently, it requires two keys to open.

657
00:49:18,330 --> 00:49:22,960
The Jew. The Vault. The Book.

658
00:49:23,200 --> 00:49:26,660
You've done all this, because you want to know,

659
00:49:26,860 --> 00:49:28,800
what's next.

660
00:49:29,030 --> 00:49:30,900
Between the base animal clawing for money,

661
00:49:31,230 --> 00:49:34,600
and the enlightened man's reach for God,

662
00:49:34,760 --> 00:49:37,160
lies knowledge.

663
00:49:37,430 --> 00:49:41,160
You just want to know what's next. I do too.

664
00:49:41,330 --> 00:49:43,830
Oh, that's not what you want.

665
00:49:44,000 --> 00:49:46,330
You want to suppress knowledge.

666
00:49:46,460 --> 00:49:49,800
No. I want to administer it.

667
00:49:50,000 --> 00:49:53,460
Someone has to. Why not an agent of God?

668
00:49:53,660 --> 00:49:58,530
Well, if God exists, surely, He intended His knowledge to be shared by all?

669
00:49:58,700 --> 00:50:02,860
The truth is, progress frightens you and your ilk.

670
00:50:03,060 --> 00:50:07,300
Not at all. We embrace it.

671
00:50:07,330 --> 00:50:10,830
Really?! Really?

672
00:50:11,000 --> 00:50:14,530
Are we at an impasse, then?

673
00:50:14,700 --> 00:50:17,560
That would be unfortunate.

674
00:50:17,730 --> 00:50:20,930
This is your last chance for an amicable partnership.

675
00:50:21,960 --> 00:50:23,860
I decline your offer.

676
00:50:25,430 --> 00:50:30,230
I pledge allegiance to Lorenzo the Magnificent,

677
00:50:30,360 --> 00:50:32,200
his foolish brother,

678
00:50:32,360 --> 00:50:35,130
and the whole of Florence!

679
00:50:35,230 --> 00:50:37,530
You want to tame Florence,

680
00:50:37,660 --> 00:50:40,160
but I prefer it wild,

681
00:50:40,400 --> 00:50:42,830
for all its quirks and criminals.

682
00:50:43,100 --> 00:50:46,060
So, why don't you scurry on back to Rome,

683
00:50:46,230 --> 00:50:51,130
and tell your Pope that neither Florence nor Da Vinci,

684
00:50:51,300 --> 00:50:53,000
will be contained?

685
00:50:59,560 --> 00:51:02,300
You hurt my friend!

686
00:51:03,060 --> 00:51:06,430
Go! Run, you fools!

687
00:51:40,130 --> 00:51:42,160
I'm sorry.

688
00:51:47,430 --> 00:51:49,300
I did warn you.

689
00:52:08,600 --> 00:52:12,630
Why aren't we meeting at the palace?

690
00:52:12,860 --> 00:52:16,400
I come here to retreat from public life.

691
00:52:16,660 --> 00:52:20,930
And the words I would have with you aren't meant to be public.

692
00:52:21,160 --> 00:52:24,530
I believe there may be a spy in my court.

693
00:52:24,760 --> 00:52:27,260
Riario knew the details of our arrangement,

694
00:52:27,530 --> 00:52:31,130
the exact amount of the stipend I've advanced you.

695
00:52:33,760 --> 00:52:36,960
You suspect my allegiance?

696
00:52:39,430 --> 00:52:41,260
No.

697
00:52:41,500 --> 00:52:44,930
No, the fact that you just killed six of the papal guard,

698
00:52:45,230 --> 00:52:47,060
releases you from the circle of suspicion.

699
00:52:47,200 --> 00:52:48,660
Hmm.

700
00:52:48,930 --> 00:52:52,730
No, you wanted me to witness your meeting with Riario today, didn't you?

701
00:52:52,860 --> 00:52:55,100
What makes you say that?

702
00:52:55,330 --> 00:52:59,730
Well, you managed to evade my officers, even though I insisted they watch over you,

703
00:52:59,930 --> 00:53:02,360
and then today, conveniently, you slip up.

704
00:53:02,600 --> 00:53:04,860
You intended for us to track you to the quarry.

705
00:53:05,200 --> 00:53:09,730
I thought you'd appreciate seeing the gun work on real opponents, not wooden ones.

706
00:53:09,930 --> 00:53:11,930
How did you fix the gun's flaws?

707
00:53:11,960 --> 00:53:14,130
The cannons needed more separation,

708
00:53:14,330 --> 00:53:16,860
so the rotating drum I fashioned did just that.

709
00:53:17,100 --> 00:53:19,730
And can your musket now be produced on a large scale?

710
00:53:19,960 --> 00:53:24,160
Well, given the resources, absolutely.

711
00:53:24,260 --> 00:53:26,500
Then you will have them.

712
00:53:26,660 --> 00:53:28,930
You have done well, Da Vinci.

713
00:53:29,100 --> 00:53:32,060
We struck Riario quite a blow today.

714
00:53:33,860 --> 00:53:36,630
But it won't be long before he retaliates.

715
00:53:36,860 --> 00:53:38,860
Lorenzo, we don't have much...

716
00:53:41,100 --> 00:53:43,930
- I thought we were alone.  - It's all right, Lucrezia.

717
00:53:44,100 --> 00:53:46,130
It's only Da Vinci.

718
00:53:46,300 --> 00:53:49,060
And I trust we can rely on his discretion.

719
00:53:50,460 --> 00:53:53,030
Absolutely.

720
00:53:53,230 --> 00:53:55,200
Good man.

721
00:53:55,360 --> 00:53:57,930
Get to work, Maestro.

722
00:53:58,060 --> 00:54:01,130
Florence is counting on you.

723
00:54:26,760 --> 00:54:28,500
Why do you laugh?

724
00:54:28,660 --> 00:54:30,600
One day, Lupo,

725
00:54:30,800 --> 00:54:35,400
all that you see here will fall under Rome's rule.

726
00:54:35,560 --> 00:54:38,460
And if that day happens a bit further down the road,

727
00:54:38,660 --> 00:54:42,400
because of Da Vinci's intervention...

728
00:54:42,530 --> 00:54:44,330
so be it.

729
00:54:44,500 --> 00:54:46,030
But he has the key.

730
00:54:47,900 --> 00:54:51,030
That makes him one step closer to obtaining the Book of Leaves.

731
00:54:51,200 --> 00:54:54,800
Let him keep it for now. At least we know where it is.

732
00:54:55,000 --> 00:55:00,400
And besides... the key is useless without its counterpart.

733
00:55:00,600 --> 00:55:03,100
And what if Da Vinci obtains that?

734
00:55:04,700 --> 00:55:07,300
He won't.

735
00:55:07,430 --> 00:55:08,800
How do you know?

736
00:55:10,730 --> 00:55:12,760
Because I have it! 

737
00:55:18,060 --> 00:55:21,100
And now you know, dear Lupo...

738
00:55:21,260 --> 00:55:25,600
why I find the whole affair so amusing.

739
00:55:37,930 --> 00:55:40,000
Why the long face, Leo?

740
00:55:40,330 --> 00:55:42,030
The Maestro's never satisfied.

741
00:55:42,330 --> 00:55:46,700
The possibility of perfection, another puzzle looming over the horizon.

742
00:55:46,900 --> 00:55:48,900
How many letters are in the Hebrew alphabet?

743
00:55:49,060 --> 00:55:51,330
27.

744
00:55:51,560 --> 00:55:54,060
There are 27 illustrations in this book.

745
00:55:54,260 --> 00:55:55,500
So...?

746
00:55:57,400 --> 00:55:59,700
Have you gone mad?

747
00:55:59,860 --> 00:56:01,660
Help me move this table back.

748
00:56:03,360 --> 00:56:08,530
Hebrew, as we've already established, is written from right to left.

749
00:56:10,400 --> 00:56:16,300
If the first illustration corresponds with the first page of the alphabet...

750
00:56:16,460 --> 00:56:17,660
Aleph.

751
00:56:17,930 --> 00:56:20,760
And the second page corresponds with the second...

752
00:56:20,960 --> 00:56:23,160
- Beth.  - And the third page

753
00:56:23,330 --> 00:56:25,130
follows the same pattern...

754
00:56:25,300 --> 00:56:26,530
Gimel.

755
00:56:26,760 --> 00:56:29,460
Do you see how the gold lines up from one page to the next?

756
00:56:29,760 --> 00:56:31,600
Have you heard of steganography?

757
00:56:31,860 --> 00:56:33,860
It's cryptography developed by the Greeks.

758
00:56:34,100 --> 00:56:36,100
It means 'concealed writing'.

759
00:56:36,300 --> 00:56:39,630
It's basically hiding a coded message in plain sight.

760
00:56:39,860 --> 00:56:44,160
- Leaves in a forest.  - Make a grid of three rows,

761
00:56:44,300 --> 00:56:46,100
each of them nine across...

762
00:56:46,130 --> 00:56:49,360
- What is it?  - Patience, Nico.

763
00:56:49,500 --> 00:56:51,660
As with most puzzles...

764
00:56:51,830 --> 00:56:55,230
it needs to be viewed from a different perspective.

765
00:57:01,660 --> 00:57:04,430
The Vault of Heaven isn't a metaphor.

766
00:57:04,600 --> 00:57:06,660
It's an actual vault,

767
00:57:06,900 --> 00:57:09,660
containing the Book of Leaves.

768
00:57:09,830 --> 00:57:12,260
And that, gentlemen,

769
00:57:12,530 --> 00:57:16,300
is a map, detailing the vault's location.

770
00:57:16,500 --> 00:57:18,830
The land this describes doesn't exist.

771
00:57:19,160 --> 00:57:23,100
Well, then, we'll just have to discover it, won't we?

772
00:57:42,000 --> 00:57:52,000


773
00:57:53,000 --> 00:58:08,000

